<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1529 | AM LottiePlayer &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Uploaded Lottie File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1529</link><description>The AM LottiePlayer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via uploaded lottie files in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3874 | WordPress Simple PayPal Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 5.1.3 - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3874</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3 due to lack of randomization of a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access customer shopping carts and edit product links, add or delete products, and discover coupon codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3889 | WordPress Simple PayPal Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 5.1.3 - Insecure Direct Object Reference via &amp;#x27;quantity&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3889</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3 via the 'process_payment_data' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the quantity of a product to a negative number, which subtracts the product cost from the total order cost. The attack will only work with Manual Checkout mode, as PayPal and Stripe will not process payments for a negative quantity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3890 | WordPress Simple PayPal Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 5.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3890</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp_cart_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4162 | PCMan FTP Server ASCII Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4162</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PCMan FTP Server up to 2.0.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component ASCII Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27007 | WordPress SureTriggers &amp;lt;= 1.0.82 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27007</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Brainstorm Force SureTriggers allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SureTriggers: from n/a through 1.0.82.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4161 | PCMan FTP Server VERBOSE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4161</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PCMan FTP Server up to 2.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the component VERBOSE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4160 | PCMan FTP Server LS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4160</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PCMan FTP Server up to 2.0.7. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component LS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4159 | PCMan FTP Server GLOB Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4159</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PCMan FTP Server up to 2.0.7. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component GLOB Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4158 | PCMan FTP Server PROMPT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4158</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PCMan FTP Server up to 2.0.7. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component PROMPT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4157 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System booking-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4157</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/booking-details.php. The manipulation of the argument Status leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4156 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System change-image.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4156</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/change-image.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47154 | LibJS in Ladybird through b8fa355 mishandles the freeing of the vector that arguments_list references, leading to a use-after-free, and allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47154</link><description>LibJS in Ladybird through b8fa355 mishandles the freeing of the vector that arguments_list references, leading to a use-after-free, and allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .js file. NOTE: the GitHub README says "Ladybird is in a pre-alpha state, and only suitable for use by developers."</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4155 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System edit-boat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4155</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-boat.php. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47153 | Certain build processes for libuv and Node.js for 32-bit systems, such as for the nodejs binary package through nodejs_20.19.0+dfsg-1_i386.d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47153</link><description>Certain build processes for libuv and Node.js for 32-bit systems, such as for the nodejs binary package through nodejs_20.19.0+dfsg-1_i386.deb for Debian GNU/Linux, have an inconsistent off_t size (e.g., building on i386 Debian always uses _FILE_OFFSET_BITS=64 for the libuv dynamic library, but uses the _FILE_OFFSET_BITS global system default of 32 for nodejs), leading to out-of-bounds access. NOTE: this is not a problem in the Node.js software itself. In particular, the Node.js website's download page does not offer prebuilt Node.js for Linux on i386.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4154 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System enrollment-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4154</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/enrollment-details.php. The manipulation of the argument Status leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3521 | Team Members – Best WordPress Team Plugin with Team Slider, Team Showcase &amp;amp; Team Builder &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3521</link><description>The Team Members – Best WordPress Team Plugin with Team Slider, Team Showcase &amp; Team Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Link icons in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4100 | Nautic Pages &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4100</link><description>The Nautic Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'np_marinetraffic_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4153 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4153</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument adminname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13381 | Calculated Fields Form &amp;lt; 5.2.62 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13381</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form WordPress plugin before 5.2.62 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3502 | WP Maps &amp;lt; 4.7.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3502</link><description>The WP Maps  WordPress plugin before 4.7.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its Map settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3503 | WP Maps &amp;lt; 4.7.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3503</link><description>The WP Maps  WordPress plugin before 4.7.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its Map settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3504 | WP Maps &amp;lt; 4.7.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3504</link><description>The WP Maps  WordPress plugin before 4.7.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its Map settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4152 | PHPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4152</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Birth Certificate System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4151 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System pass-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4151</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/pass-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4150 | Netgear EX6200 sub_54340 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4150</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sub_54340. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13845 | Gravity Forms WebHooks &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Webhook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13845</link><description>The Gravity Forms WebHooks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 via the 'process_feed' method of the GF_Webhooks class This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3952 | Projectopia &amp;amp;#8211; WordPress Project Management &amp;lt;= 5.1.16 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Option Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3952</link><description>The Projectopia – WordPress Project Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'pto_remove_logo' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary option values on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to delete an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4099 | List Children &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4099</link><description>The List Children plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'list_children' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4149 | Netgear EX6200 sub_54014 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4149</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sub_54014. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1304 | NewsBlogger &amp;lt;= 0.2.5.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1304</link><description>The NewsBlogger theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability check on the newsblogger_install_and_activate_plugin() function in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.5.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1305 | NewsBlogger &amp;lt;= 0.2.5.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1305</link><description>The NewsBlogger theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.5.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the newsblogger_install_and_activate_plugin() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files and achieve remote code execution via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2168 | Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons, Woocommerce Builder, EDD Builder, Elementor Store Builder, Product Grid, Product Table, Woocommerce Slider &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited User Meta Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2168</link><description>The Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons, Woocommerce Builder, EDD Builder, Elementor Store Builder, Product Grid, Product Table, Woocommerce Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the dismiss() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to set arbitrary user meta values to `1` which can be leveraged to lock and administrator out of their site via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4148 | Netgear EX6200 sub_503FC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4148</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_503FC. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2816 | Page View Count 2.8.0 - 2.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2816</link><description>The Page View Count plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the yellow_message_dontshow() function in versions 2.8.0 to 2.8.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to one on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4147 | Netgear EX6200 sub_47F7C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4147</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_47F7C. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4146 | Netgear EX6200 sub_41940 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4146</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94. Affected is the function sub_41940. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4144 | PKCE bypass via downgrade attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4144</link><description>PKCE was implemented in the OAuth implementation in workers-oauth-provider that is part of  MCP framework https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-mcp . However, it was found that an attacker could cause the check to be skipped.


Fixed in:

 

 https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-oauth-provider/pull/27 https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-oauth-provider/pull/27 


Impact: 

PKCE is a defense-in-depth mechanism against certain kinds of attacks and was an optional extension in OAuth 2.0 which became required in the OAuth 2.1 draft. (Note that the MCP specification requires OAuth 2.1.). This bug completely bypasses PKCE protection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4143 | Missing validation of redirect_uri on authorize endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4143</link><description>The OAuth implementation in workers-oauth-provider that is part of  MCP framework https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-mcp , did not correctly validate that redirect_uri was on the allowed list of redirect URIs for the given client registration.

Fixed in:  https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-oauth-provider/pull/26 https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-oauth-provider/pull/26 

Impact:

 

Under certain circumstances (see below), if a victim had previously authorized with a server built on workers-oath-provider, and an attacker could later trick the victim into visiting a malicious web site, then attacker could potentially steal the victim's credentials to the same OAuth server and subsequently impersonate them.

In order for the attack to be possible, the OAuth server's authorized callback must be designed to auto-approve authorizations that appear to come from an OAuth client that the victim has authorized previously. The authorization flow is not implemented by workers-oauth-provider; it is up to the application built on top to decide whether to implement such automatic re-authorization. However, many applications do implement such logic.

Note: It is a basic, well-known requirement that OAuth servers should verify that the redirect URI is among the allowed list for the client, both during the authorization flow and subsequently when exchanging the authorization code for an access token. workers-oauth-provider implemented only the latter check, not the former. Unfortunately, the former is the much more important check. Readers who are familiar with OAuth may recognize that failing to check redirect URIs against the allowed list is a well-known, basic mistake, covered extensively in the RFC and elsewhere. The author of this library would like everyone to know that he was, in fact, well-aware of this requirement, thought about it a lot while designing the library, and then, somehow, forgot to actually make sure the check was in the code. That is, it's not that he didn't know what he was doing, it's that he knew what he was doing but flubbed it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4145 | Netgear EX6200 sub_3D0BC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4145</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94. This issue affects the function sub_3D0BC. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4142 | Netgear EX6200 sub_3C8EC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4142</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sub_3C8EC. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4141 | Netgear EX6200 sub_3C03C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4141</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Netgear EX6200 1.0.3.94. This affects the function sub_3C03C. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4140 | Netgear EX6120 sub_30394 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4140</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Netgear EX6120 1.0.3.94. Affected by this issue is the function sub_30394. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30146 | HCL Domino Leap is affected by improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30146</link><description>Improper access control of endpoint in HCL Domino Leap
allows certain admin users to import applications from the
server's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42450 | HCL Domino Volt is affected by Cross-site scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42450</link><description>Improper sanitization of SVG files in HCL Domino Volt allows client-side script injection in deployed applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37517 | HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap are affected by missing &amp;quot;no cache&amp;quot; headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37517</link><description>Missing "no cache" headers in HCL Leap permits sensitive data to be cached.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37535 | HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap are affected by a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37535</link><description>Insufficient URI protocol whitelist in HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap
allow script injection through query parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45721 | HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap are affected by a disclosure of private personal information vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45721</link><description>Insufficient default configuration in HCL Leap
allows anonymous access to directory information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30115 | HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap are affected by a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30115</link><description>Insufficient sanitization policy in HCL Leap
allows client-side script injection in the deployed application through the
HTML widget.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30145 | HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap are affected by a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30145</link><description>Multiple vectors in HCL Domino Volt and Domino Leap allow client-side
script injection in the authoring environment and deployed applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42449 | HCL Domino Volt is affected by an unrestricted upload of a dangerous file type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42449</link><description>Unsafe default file type filter policy in HCL Domino Volt allows upload of .html file and execution of unsafe JavaScript in deployed applications</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27562 | HCL Domino Volt is affected by an unrestricted upload of a dangerous file type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27562</link><description>Unsafe default file type filter policy in HCL Domino Volt allows upload of .html file and execution of unsafe JavaScript in deployed applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24132 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in AirPlay audio SDK 2.7.1, AirPlay video SDK 3.6.0.126, CarPlay ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24132</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in AirPlay audio SDK 2.7.1, AirPlay video SDK 3.6.0.126, CarPlay Communication Plug-in R18.1. An attacker on the local network may cause an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30422 | A buffer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in AirPlay audio SDK 2.7.1, AirPlay video SDK 3.6.0.126,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30422</link><description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in AirPlay audio SDK 2.7.1, AirPlay video SDK 3.6.0.126, CarPlay Communication Plug-in R18.1. An attacker on the local network may cause an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4139 | Netgear EX6120 fwAcosCgiInbound buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4139</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Netgear EX6120 1.0.0.68. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fwAcosCgiInbound. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13943 | Tesla Model S Iris Modem QCMAP_ConnectionManager Improper Input Validation Sandbox Escape Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13943</link><description>Tesla Model S Iris Modem QCMAP_ConnectionManager Improper Input Validation Sandbox Escape Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escape the sandbox on affected affected Tesla Model S vehicles. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the QCMAP_ConnectionManager component. An attacker can abuse the service to assign LAN addresses to the WWAN. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to access network services that were only intended to be exposed to the internal LAN. Was ZDI-CAN-23199.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6029 | Tesla Model S Iris Modem Race Condition Firewall Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6029</link><description>Tesla Model S Iris Modem Race Condition Firewall Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass the firewall on the Iris modem in affected Tesla Model S vehicles. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.
 
The specific flaw exists within the firewall service. The issue results from a failure to obtain the xtables lock. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass firewall rules. Was ZDI-CAN-23197.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6030 | Tesla Model S oFono Unnecessary Privileges Sandbox Escape Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6030</link><description>Tesla Model S oFono Unnecessary Privileges Sandbox Escape Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escape the sandbox on affected Tesla Model S vehicles. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code within the sandbox on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.
 
The specific flaw exists within the oFono process. The process allows an attacker to modify interfaces. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass the iptables network sandbox. Was ZDI-CAN-23200.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6031 | Tesla Model S oFono AT Command Heap-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6031</link><description>Tesla Model S oFono AT Command Heap-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Tesla Model S vehicles. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.
 
The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-23198.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6032 | Tesla Model S Iris Modem ql_atfwd Command Injection Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6032</link><description>Tesla Model S Iris Modem ql_atfwd Command Injection Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Tesla Model S vehicles. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.
 
The specific flaw exists within the ql_atfwd process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code on the target modem in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23201.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2082 | Tesla Model 3 VCSEC Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2082</link><description>Tesla Model 3 VCSEC Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Tesla Model 3 vehicles. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the VCSEC module. By manipulating the certificate response sent from the Tire Pressure Monitoring System (TPMS), an attacker can trigger an integer overflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the VCSEC module and send arbitrary messages to the vehicle CAN bus. Was ZDI-CAN-23800.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27611 | base-x homograph attack allows Unicode lookalike characters to bypass validation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27611</link><description>base-x is a base encoder and decoder of any given alphabet using bitcoin style leading zero compression. Versions 4.0.0, 5.0.0, and all prior to 3.0.11, are vulnerable to attackers potentially deceiving users into sending funds to an unintended address. This issue has been patched in versions 3.0.11, 4.0.1, and 5.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4136 | Weitong Mall Sale Endpoint improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4136</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Weitong Mall 1.0.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component Sale Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2170 | A Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the SMA1000 Appliance Work Place interface, which in specific cond...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2170</link><description>A Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the SMA1000 Appliance Work Place interface, which in specific conditions could potentially enable a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause the appliance to make requests to an unintended location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9876 | Application is vulnerable to Privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9876</link><description>: Modification of Assumed-Immutable Data (MAID) vulnerability in ABB ANC, ABB ANC-L, ABB ANC-mini.This issue affects ANC: through 1.1.4; ANC-L: through 1.1.4; ANC-mini: through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9877 | Sensitive information submitted using GET method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9877</link><description>: Use of GET Request Method With Sensitive Query Strings vulnerability in ABB ANC, ABB ANC-L, ABB ANC-mini.This issue affects ANC: through 1.1.4; ANC-L: through 1.1.4; ANC-mini: through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24887 | OpenCTI bypass of protected attribute update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24887</link><description>OpenCTI is an open-source cyber threat intelligence platform. In versions starting from 6.4.8 to before 6.4.10, the allow/deny lists can be bypassed, allowing a user to change attributes that are intended to be unmodifiable by the user. It is possible to toggle the `external` flag on/off and change the own token value for a user. It is also possible to edit attributes that are not in the allow list, such as `otp_qr` and `otp_activated`. If external users exist in the OpenCTI setup and the information about these users identities is sensitive, the above vulnerabilities can be used to enumerate existing user accounts as a standard low privileged user. This issue has been patched in version 6.4.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32777 | Volcano Scheduler Denial of Service via Unbounded Response from Elastic Service/extender Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32777</link><description>Volcano is a Kubernetes-native batch scheduling system. Prior to versions 1.11.2, 1.10.2, 1.9.1, 1.11.0-network-topology-preview.3, and 1.12.0-alpha.2, attacker compromise of either the Elastic service or the extender plugin can cause denial of service of the scheduler. This is a privilege escalation, because Volcano users may run their Elastic service and extender plugins in separate pods or nodes from the scheduler. In the Kubernetes security model, node isolation is a security boundary, and as such an attacker is able to cross that boundary in Volcano's case if they have compromised either the vulnerable services or the pod/node in which they are deployed. The scheduler will become unavailable to other users and workloads in the cluster. The scheduler will either crash with an unrecoverable OOM panic or freeze while consuming excessive amounts of memory. This issue has been patched in versions 1.11.2, 1.10.2, 1.9.1, 1.11.0-network-topology-preview.3, and 1.12.0-alpha.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46331 | OpenFGA Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46331</link><description>OpenFGA is a high-performance and flexible authorization/permission engine built for developers and inspired by Google Zanzibar. OpenFGA v1.8.10 to v1.3.6 (Helm chart &lt;= openfga-0.2.28, docker &lt;= v.1.8.10) are vulnerable to authorization bypass when certain Check and ListObject calls are executed. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46554 | XWiki missing authorization when accessing the wiki level attachments list and metadata via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46554</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 1.8.1 to before 14.10.22, from 15.0-rc-1 to before 15.10.12, from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.4.3, and from 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.7.0, anyone can access the metadata of any attachment in the wiki using the wiki attachment REST endpoint. There is no filtering for the results depending on current user rights, meaning an unauthenticated user could exploit this even in a private wiki. This issue has been patched in versions 14.10.22, 15.10.12, 16.4.3, and 16.7.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46557 | Any user with view access to the XWiki space can change the authenticator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46557</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 15.3-rc-1 to before 15.10.14, from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.4.6, and from 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.10.0-rc-1, a user who can access pages located in the XWiki space (by default, anyone) can access the page XWiki.Authentication.Administration and (unless an authenticator is set in xwiki.cfg) switch to another installed authenticator. Note that, by default, there is only one authenticator available (Standard XWiki Authenticator). So, if no authenticator extension was installed, it's not really possible to do anything for an attacker. Also, in most cases, if an SSO authenticator is installed and utilized (like OIDC or LDAP for example), the worst an attacker can do is break authentication by switching back to the standard authenticator (that's because it's impossible to login to a user which does not have a stored password, and that's usually what SSO authenticator produce). This issue has been patched in versions 15.10.14, 16.4.6, and 16.10.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46558 | org.xwiki.contrib.markdown:syntax-markdown-commonmark12 vulnerable to XSS via Markdown content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46558</link><description>XWiki Contrib's Syntax Markdown allows importing Markdown content into wiki pages and creating wiki content in Markdown. In versions starting from 8.2 to before 8.9, the Markdown syntax is vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) through HTML. In particular, using Markdown syntax, it's possible for any user to embed Javascript code that will then be executed on the browser of any other user visiting either the document or the comment that contains it. In the instance that this code is executed by a user with admins or programming rights, this issue compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This issue has been patched in version 8.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47784 | Unverified Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47784</link><description>Unverified Password Change for ANC software that allows an authenticated attacker to bypass the old Password check in the password change form via a web HMI
This issue affects ANC software version 1.1.4 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46619 | A security issue has been discovered in Couchbase Server before 7.6.4 and fixed in v.7.6.4 and v.7.2.7 for Windows that could allow unauthor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46619</link><description>A security issue has been discovered in Couchbase Server before 7.6.4 and fixed in v.7.6.4 and v.7.2.7 for Windows that could allow unauthorized access to sensitive files. Depending on the level of privileges, this vulnerability may grant access to files such as /etc/passwd or /etc/shadow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44194 | SourceCodester Simple Barangay Management System v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /barangay_management/admin/?page=view_household.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44194</link><description>SourceCodester Simple Barangay Management System v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /barangay_management/admin/?page=view_household.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4135 | Netgear WG302v2 ui_get_input_value command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4135</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WG302v2 up to 5.2.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function ui_get_input_value. The manipulation of the argument host leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24091 | An app could impersonate system notifications. Sensitive notifications now require restricted entitlements. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24091</link><description>An app could impersonate system notifications. Sensitive notifications now require restricted entitlements. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, iPadOS 17.7.3. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39413 | WordPress Simple Sitemap – Create a Responsive HTML Sitemap plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39413</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in David Gwyer Simple Sitemap – Create a Responsive HTML Sitemap.This issue affects Simple Sitemap – Create a Responsive HTML Sitemap: from n/a through 3.5.14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44192 | SourceCodester Simple Barangay Management System v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /barangay_management/admin/?page=view_clearance.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44192</link><description>SourceCodester Simple Barangay Management System v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /barangay_management/admin/?page=view_clearance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44193 | SourceCodester Simple Barangay Management System v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /barangay_management/admin/?page=view_complaint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44193</link><description>SourceCodester Simple Barangay Management System v1.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /barangay_management/admin/?page=view_complaint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21416 | Azure Virtual Desktop Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21416</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30389 | Azure Bot Framework SDK Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30389</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30390 | Azure ML Compute Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30390</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30391 | Microsoft Dynamics Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30391</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30392 | Azure AI bot Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30392</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33074 | Azure Functions Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33074</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3599 | Symantec Endpoint Protection Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3599</link><description>Symantec Endpoint Protection Windows Agent, running an ERASER Engine prior to 119.1.7.8, may be susceptible to an Elevation of Privilege vulnerability, which may allow an attacker to delete resources that are normally protected from an application or user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3859 | Websites directing users to long URLs that caused eliding to occur in the location view could leverage the truncating behavior to potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3859</link><description>Websites directing users to long URLs that caused eliding to occur in the location view could leverage the truncating behavior to potentially trick users into thinking they were on a different webpage This vulnerability affects Focus &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27134 | Privilege escalation in Joplin server via user patch endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27134</link><description>Joplin is a free, open source note taking and to-do application, which can handle a large number of notes organised into notebooks. Prior to version 3.3.3, a privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Joplin server, allowing non-admin users to exploit the API endpoint `PATCH /api/users/:id` to set the `is_admin` field to 1. The vulnerability allows malicious low-privileged users to perform administrative actions without proper authorization. This issue has been patched in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27409 | Joplin Server Vulnerable to Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27409</link><description>Joplin is a free, open source note taking and to-do application, which can handle a large number of notes organised into notebooks. Prior to version 3.3.3, path traversal is possible in Joplin Server if static file path starts with `css/pluginAssets` or `js/pluginAssets`. The `findLocalFile` function in the `default route` calls `localFileFromUrl` to check for special `pluginAssets` paths. If the function returns a path, the result is returned directly, without checking for path traversal. The vulnerability allows attackers to read files outside the intended directories. This issue has been patched in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32376 | Discourse DM limits aren’t always properly enforced</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32376</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to versions 3.4.3 on the stable branch and 3.5.0.beta3 on the beta branch, the users limit for a DM can be bypassed, thus giving the ability to potentially create a DM with every user from a site in it. This issue has been patched in stable version 3.4.3 and beta version 3.5.0.beta3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32970 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-wysiwyg-api Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32970</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 13.5-rc-1 to before 15.10.13, from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.4.4, and from 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.8.0, an open redirect vulnerability in the HTML conversion request filter allows attackers to construct URLs on an XWiki instance that redirects to any URL. This issue has been patched in versions 15.10.13, 16.4.4, and 16.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32971 | XWiki Solr script service doesn&amp;#x27;t take dropped programming right into account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32971</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 4.5.1 to before 15.10.13, from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.4.4, and from 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.8.0-rc-1, the Solr script service doesn't take dropped programming rights into account. The Solr script service that is accessible in XWiki's scripting API normally requires programming rights to be called. Due to using the wrong API for checking rights, it doesn't take the fact into account that programming rights might have been dropped by calling `$xcontext.dropPermissions()`. If some code relies on this for the safety of executing Velocity code with the wrong author context, this could allow a user with script rights to either cause a high load by indexing documents or to temporarily remove documents from the search index. This issue has been patched in versions 15.10.13, 16.4.4, and 16.8.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32972 | The lesscss script service allows cache clearing without programming right</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32972</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 6.1-milestone-1 to before 15.10.12, from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.4.3, and from 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.8.0-rc-1, the script API of the LESS compiler in XWiki is incorrectly checking for rights when calling the cache cleaning API, making it possible to clean the cache without having programming right. The only impact of this is a slowdown in XWiki execution as the caches are re-filled. As this vulnerability requires script right to exploit, and script right already allows unlimited execution of scripts, the additional impact due to this vulnerability is low. This issue has been patched in versions 15.10.12, 16.4.3, and 16.8.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32973 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-component-wiki provides no warning when granting XWiki.ComponentClass programming right</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32973</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 15.9-rc-1 to before 15.10.12, from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.4.3, and from 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.8.0-rc-1, when a user with programming rights edits a document in XWiki that was last edited by a user without programming rights and contains an XWiki.ComponentClass, there is no warning that this will grant programming rights to this object. An attacker who created such a malicious object could use this to gain programming rights on the wiki. For this, the attacker needs to have edit rights on at least one page to place this object and then get an admin user to edit that document. This issue has been patched in versions 15.10.12, 16.4.3, and 16.8.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32974 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-security-requiredrights-default required rights analysis doesn&amp;#x27;t consider TextAreas with default content type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32974</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 15.9-rc-1 to before 15.10.8 and from 16.0.0-rc-1 to before 16.2.0, the required rights analysis doesn't consider TextAreas with default content type. When editing a page, XWiki warns since version 15.9 when there is content on the page like a script macro that would gain more rights due to the editing. This analysis doesn't consider certain kinds of properties, allowing a user to put malicious scripts in there that will be executed after a user with script, admin, or programming rights edited the page. Such a malicious script could impact the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This issue has been patched in versions 15.10.8 and 16.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46342 | Kyverno vulnerable to bypass of policy rules that use namespace selectors in match statements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46342</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for cloud native platform engineering teams. Prior to versions 1.13.5 and 1.14.0, it may happen that policy rules using namespace selector(s) in their match statements are mistakenly not applied during admission review request processing due to a missing error propagation in function `GetNamespaceSelectorsFromNamespaceLister` in `pkg/utils/engine/labels.go`. As a consequence, security-critical mutations and validations are bypassed, potentially allowing attackers with K8s API access to perform malicious operations. This issue has been patched in versions 1.13.5 and 1.14.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4122 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 sub_435E04 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_435E04. The manipulation of the argument host leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4120 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 sub_4238E8 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4120</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function sub_4238E8. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4121 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 cmd_wireless command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4121</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cmd_wireless. The manipulation of the argument host leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45021 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the admin/edit-directory.php file of the PHPGurukul Directory Management System v2.0. Attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45021</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the admin/edit-directory.php file of the PHPGurukul Directory Management System v2.0. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability via the email parameter in a POST request to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45009 | A HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the normal-search.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45009</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the normal-search.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the searchdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45010 | A HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the normal-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45010</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the normal-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the fromdate and todate POST request parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45011 | A HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the foreigner-search.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45011</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the foreigner-search.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the searchdata POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4118 | Weitong Mall Product History historyList access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4118</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Weitong Mall 1.0.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /historyList of the component Product History Handler. The manipulation of the argument isDelete with the input 1 leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4119 | Weitong Mall Product Statistics queryTotal access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4119</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Weitong Mall 1.0.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /queryTotal of the component Product Statistics Handler. The manipulation of the argument isDelete with the input 1 leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45015 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45015</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code via the fromdate and todate parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45017 | A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in edit-ticket.php of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45017</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in edit-ticket.php of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the tprice POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45018 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45018</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL code via the todate parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45019 | A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in /add-foreigners-ticket.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45019</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in /add-foreigners-ticket.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the cprice POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45020 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the normal-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45020</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the normal-bwdates-reports-details.php file of PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System v2.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL code via the todate parameter in a POST request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4117 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 sub_41A914 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4117</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. This affects the function sub_41A914. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3394 | Vulnerability in user management of Automation Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3394</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in ABB Automation Builder.This issue affects Automation Builder: through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3395 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource, Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in ABB Automation Builder.Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3395</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource, Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in ABB Automation Builder.This issue affects Automation Builder: through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45007 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the profile.php file of PHPGurukul Timetable Generator System v1.0. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45007</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the profile.php file of PHPGurukul Timetable Generator System v1.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the adminname POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4115 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 default_version_is_new buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4115</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. Affected by this vulnerability is the function default_version_is_new. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4116 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 get_cur_lang_ver buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4116</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. Affected by this issue is the function get_cur_lang_ver. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4114 | Netgear JWNR2000v2 check_language_file buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4114</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Netgear JWNR2000v2 1.0.0.11. Affected is the function check_language_file. The manipulation of the argument host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24350 | A vulnerability in the “Certificates and Keys” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24350</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Certificates and Keys” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to write arbitrary certificates in arbitrary file system paths via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24351 | A vulnerability in the “Remote Logging” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24351</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Remote Logging” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands in the context of user “root” via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27532 | A vulnerability in the “Backup &amp; Restore” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27532</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Backup &amp; Restore” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) attacker to access secret information via multiple crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24346 | A vulnerability in the “Proxy” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) attacker to ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24346</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Proxy” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) attacker to manipulate the “/etc/environment” file via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24347 | A vulnerability in the “Network Interfaces” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24347</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Network Interfaces” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to manipulate the network configuration file via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24348 | A vulnerability in the “Network Interfaces” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24348</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Network Interfaces” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to manipulate the wireless network configuration file via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24349 | A vulnerability in the “Network Interfaces” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24349</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Network Interfaces” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) attacker to delete the configuration of physical network interfaces via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24344 | A vulnerability in the error notification messages of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to inject arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24344</link><description>A vulnerability in the error notification messages of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary HTML tags and, possibly, execute arbitrary client-side code in the context of another user's browser via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24345 | A vulnerability in the “Hosts” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24345</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Hosts” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to manipulate the “hosts” file in an unintended manner via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24343 | A vulnerability in the “Manages app data” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24343</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Manages app data” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to write arbitrary files in arbitrary file system paths via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24342 | A vulnerability in the login functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to guess valid userna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24342</link><description>A vulnerability in the login functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to guess valid usernames via multiple crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24341 | A vulnerability in the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to induce a Denial-of-Service (Do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24341</link><description>A vulnerability in the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to induce a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition on the device via multiple crafted HTTP requests. In the worst case, a full power cycle is needed to regain control of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24339 | A vulnerability in the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to conduct various attacks against users of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24339</link><description>A vulnerability in the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to conduct various attacks against users of the vulnerable system, including web cache poisoning or Man-in-the-Middle (MitM), via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24340 | A vulnerability in the users configuration file of ctrlX OS may allow a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to recover the plaint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24340</link><description>A vulnerability in the users configuration file of ctrlX OS may allow a remote authenticated (low-privileged) attacker to recover the plaintext passwords of other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4112 | PHPGurukul Student Record System add-course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4112</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add-course.php. The manipulation of the argument course-short leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4113 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System edit-pass-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4113</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit-pass-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 11:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24338 | A vulnerability in the “Manages app data” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24338</link><description>A vulnerability in the “Manages app data” functionality of the web application of ctrlX OS allows a remote authenticated (lowprivileged) attacker to execute arbitrary client-side code in the context of another user's browser via multiple crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4110 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System edit-teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4110</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4111 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System visitor-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4111</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/visitor-details.php. The manipulation of the argument Status leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4108 | PHPGurukul Student Record System add-subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4108</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add-subject.php. The manipulation of the argument sub1 leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4109 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4109</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2890 | tagDiv Opt-In Builder &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via subscriptionCouponId Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2890</link><description>The tagDiv Opt-In Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘subscriptionCouponId’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4124 | ISPSoft File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4124</link><description>Delta Electronics ISPSoft version 3.20 is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code when parsing ISP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4125 | ISPSoft File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4125</link><description>Delta Electronics ISPSoft version 3.20 is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code when parsing ISP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 08:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22884 | ISPSoft File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22884</link><description>Delta Electronics ISPSoft version 3.20 is vulnerable to a Stack-Based buffer overflow vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code when parsing DVP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 07:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22882 | ISPSoft File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22882</link><description>Delta Electronics ISPSoft version 3.20 is vulnerable to a Stack-Based buffer overflow vulnerability that could allow an attacker to leverage debugging logic to execute arbitrary code when parsing CBDGL file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 07:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22883 | ISPSoft File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22883</link><description>Delta Electronics ISPSoft version 3.20 is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code when parsing DVP file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3471 | SureForms &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Contributor+ Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3471</link><description>The SureForms  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not have proper authorisation check when updating its settings via the REST API, which could allow Contributor and above roles to perform such action</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3953 | WP Statistics – The Most Popular Privacy-Friendly Analytics Plugin &amp;lt;= 14.13.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3953</link><description>The WP Statistics – The Most Popular Privacy-Friendly Analytics Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'optionUpdater' function in all versions up to, and including, 14.13.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 05:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30202 | Data exposure via ZeroMQ on multi-node vLLM deployment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30202</link><description>vLLM is a high-throughput and memory-efficient inference and serving engine for LLMs. Versions starting from 0.5.2 and prior to 0.8.5 are vulnerable to denial of service and data exposure via ZeroMQ on multi-node vLLM deployment. In a multi-node vLLM deployment, vLLM uses ZeroMQ for some multi-node communication purposes. The primary vLLM host opens an XPUB ZeroMQ socket and binds it to ALL interfaces. While the socket is always opened for a multi-node deployment, it is only used when doing tensor parallelism across multiple hosts. Any client with network access to this host can connect to this XPUB socket unless its port is blocked by a firewall. Once connected, these arbitrary clients will receive all of the same data broadcasted to all of the secondary vLLM hosts. This data is internal vLLM state information that is not useful to an attacker. By potentially connecting to this socket many times and not reading data published to them, an attacker can also cause a denial of service by slowing down or potentially blocking the publisher. This issue has been patched in version 0.8.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32444 | vLLM Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Mooncake Integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32444</link><description>vLLM is a high-throughput and memory-efficient inference and serving engine for LLMs. Versions starting from 0.6.5 and prior to 0.8.5, having vLLM integration with mooncake, are vulnerable to remote code execution due to using pickle based serialization over unsecured ZeroMQ sockets. The vulnerable sockets were set to listen on all network interfaces, increasing the likelihood that an attacker is able to reach the vulnerable ZeroMQ sockets to carry out an attack. vLLM instances that do not make use of the mooncake integration are not vulnerable. This issue has been patched in version 0.8.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46560 | vLLM phi4mm: Quadratic Time Complexity in Input Token Processing​ leads to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46560</link><description>vLLM is a high-throughput and memory-efficient inference and serving engine for LLMs. Versions starting from 0.8.0 and prior to 0.8.5 are affected by a critical performance vulnerability in the input preprocessing logic of the multimodal tokenizer. The code dynamically replaces placeholder tokens (e.g., &lt;|audio_|&gt;, &lt;|image_|&gt;) with repeated tokens based on precomputed lengths. Due to ​​inefficient list concatenation operations​​, the algorithm exhibits ​​quadratic time complexity (O(n²))​​, allowing malicious actors to trigger resource exhaustion via specially crafted inputs. This issue has been patched in version 0.8.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 01:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29906 | Finit bundled getty can bypass /bin/login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29906</link><description>Finit is a fast init for Linux systems. Versions starting from 3.0-rc1 and prior to version 4.11 bundle an implementation of getty for the `tty` configuration directive that can bypass `/bin/login`, i.e., a user can log in as any user without authentication. This issue has been patched in version 4.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 22:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46552 | KHC-INVITATION-AUTOMATION Sensitive User Information Leakage in Invitation Automation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46552</link><description>KHC-INVITATION-AUTOMATION is a GitHub automation script that automatically invites followers of a bot account to join your organization. In some commits on version 1.2, a vulnerability was identified where user data, including email addresses and Discord usernames, were exposed in API responses without proper access controls. This allowed unauthorized users to access sensitive user information by directly calling specific endpoints. This issue has been patched in a later commit on version 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 22:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3501 | Org.keycloak.protocol.services: keycloak hostname verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3501</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. By setting a verification policy to 'ALL', the trust store certificate verification is skipped, which is unintended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3910 | Org.keycloak.authentication: two factor authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3910</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. The org.keycloak.authorization package may be vulnerable to circumventing required actions, allowing users to circumvent requirements such as setting up two-factor authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46344 | Auth0 NextJS SDK v4 Missing Session Invalidation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46344</link><description>The Auth0 Next.js SDK is a library for implementing user authentication in Next.js applications. Versions starting from 4.0.1 and prior to 4.5.1, do not invoke `.setExpirationTime` when generating a JWE token for the session. As a result, the JWE does not contain an internal expiration claim. While the session cookie may expire or be cleared, the JWE remains valid. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46348 | YesWiki Vulnerable to Unauthenticated Site Backup Creation and Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46348</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, the request to commence a site backup can be performed and downloaded without authentication. The archives are created with a predictable filename, so a malicious user could create and download an archive without being authenticated. This could result in a malicious attacker making numerous requests to create archives and fill up the file system, or by downloading the archive which contains sensitive site information. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46549 | Yeswiki Vulnerable to Unauthenticated Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46549</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, an attacker can use a reflected cross-site scripting attack to steal cookies from an authenticated user by having them click on a malicious link. Stolen cookies allow the attacker to take over the user’s session. This vulnerability may also allow attackers to deface the website or embed malicious content. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46550 | Yeswiki Vulnerable to Unauthenticated Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46550</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, the `/?BazaR` endpoint and `idformulaire` parameter are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An attacker can use a reflected cross-site scripting attack to steal cookies from an authenticated user by having them click on a malicious link. Stolen cookies allow the attacker to take over the user’s session. This vulnerability may also allow attackers to deface the website or embed malicious content. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57698 | An issue in modernwms v.1.0 allows an attacker view the MD5 hash of the administrator password and other attributes without authentication, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57698</link><description>An issue in modernwms v.1.0 allows an attacker view the MD5 hash of the administrator password and other attributes without authentication, even after initial configuration and password change. This happens due to excessive exposure of information and the lack of adequate access control on the /user/list?culture=en-us endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4078 | Wangshen SecGate 3600 g=log_export_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4078</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Wangshen SecGate 3600 2400. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ?g=log_export_file. The manipulation of the argument file_name leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0520 | ShowDoc Unauthenticated File Upload Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0520</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in ShowDoc caused by improper validation of file extension allows execution of arbitrary PHP, leading to remote code execution.This issue affects ShowDoc: before 2.8.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 19:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4080 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System view-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4080</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-request.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4079 | PCMan FTP Server RENAME Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4079</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PCMan FTP Server up to 2.0.7. Affected is an unknown function of the component RENAME Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4076 | LB-LINK BL-AC3600 Password lighttpd.cgi easy_uci_set_option_string_0 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4076</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in LB-LINK BL-AC3600 up to 1.0.22. This affects the function easy_uci_set_option_string_0 of the file /cgi-bin/lighttpd.cgi of the component Password Handler. The manipulation of the argument routepwd leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4077 | code-projects School Billing System searchrec stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4077</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects School Billing System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function searchrec. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4074 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System pass-bwdates-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4074</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/pass-bwdates-report.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4075 | VMSMan login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4075</link><description>A vulnerability was found in VMSMan up to 20250416. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Email with the input "&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3911 | Exposure in Docker Desktop logs of environment variables configured for running containers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3911</link><description>Recording of environment variables, configured for running containers, in Docker Desktop application logs could lead to unintentional disclosure of sensitive information such as api keys, passwords, etc.

A malicious actor with read access to these logs could obtain sensitive credentials information and further use it to gain unauthorized access to other systems. Starting with version 4.41.0, Docker Desktop no longer logs environment variables set by the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46347 | YesWiki Remote Code Execution via Arbitrary PHP File Write and Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46347</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, YesWiki vulnerable to remote code execution. An arbitrary file write can be used to write a file with a PHP extension, which then can be browsed to in order to execute arbitrary code on the server, resulting in a full compromise of the server. This could potentially be performed unwittingly by a user. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46349 | YesWiki Vulnerable to Unauthenticated Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46349</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, YesWiki is vulnerable to reflected XSS in the file upload form. This vulnerability allows any malicious unauthenticated user to create a link that can be clicked on by the victim to perform arbitrary actions. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46350 | Yeswiki Vulnerable to Authenticated Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46350</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, an attacker can use a reflected cross-site scripting attack to steal cookies from an authenticated user by having them click on a malicious link. Stolen cookies allow the attacker to take over the user’s session. This vulnerability may also allow attackers to deface the website or embed malicious content. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4095 | Registry Access Management (RAM) policies not applied when sign-in enforcement is configured via a configuration profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4095</link><description>Registry Access Management (RAM) is a security feature allowing administrators to restrict access for their developers to only allowed registries. When a MacOS configuration profile is used to enforce organization sign-in, the RAM policies are not being applied, which would allow Docker Desktop users to pull down unapproved, and potentially malicious images from any registry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4073 | PHPGurukul Student Record System change-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4073</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Student Record System 3.20. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /change-password.php. The manipulation of the argument currentpassword leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45956 | A SQL injection vulnerability in manage_damage.php in Sourcecodester Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows an authenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45956</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in manage_damage.php in Sourcecodester Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "id" parameter</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4072 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System edit-nurse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4072</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit-nurse.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0716 | AngularJS improper sanitization in SVG &amp;#x27;&amp;lt;image&amp;gt;&amp;#x27; element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0716</link><description>Improper sanitization of the value of the 'href' and 'xlink:href' attributes in '' SVG elements in AngularJS allows attackers to bypass common image source restrictions. This can lead to a form of  Content Spoofing https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/Content_Spoofing  and also negatively affect the application's performance and behavior by using too large or slow-to-load images.

This issue affects all versions of AngularJS.

Note:
The AngularJS project is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://docs.angularjs.org/misc/version-support-status .</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23180 | Ribbon Communications - CWE-250: Execution with Unnecessary Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23180</link><description>CWE-250: Execution with Unnecessary Privileges</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23181 | Ribbon Communications - CWE-250: Execution with Unnecessary Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23181</link><description>CWE-250: Execution with Unnecessary Privileges</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23178 | Ribbon Communications - CWE-923: Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23178</link><description>CWE-923: Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23179 | Ribbon Communications - CWE-798: Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23179</link><description>CWE-798: Use of Hard-coded Credentials</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23177 | Ribbon Communications - CWE-427: Uncontrolled Search Path Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23177</link><description>CWE-427: Uncontrolled Search Path Element</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4070 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4070</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/changeimage.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4071 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System test-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4071</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /test-details.php. The manipulation of the argument Status leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25403 | Slims (Senayan Library Management Systems) 9 Bulian V9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin/modules/master_file/coll_type.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25403</link><description>Slims (Senayan Library Management Systems) 9 Bulian V9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin/modules/master_file/coll_type.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40619 | Improper access control vulnerability in Bookgy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40619</link><description>Bookgy does not provide for proper authorisation control in multiple areas of the application. This deficiency could allow a malicious actor, without authentication, to reach private areas and/or areas intended for other roles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1551 | IBM Operational Decision Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1551</link><description>IBM Operational Decision Manager 8.11.0.1, 8.11.1.0, 8.12.0.1, and 9.0.0.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25962 | An issue in Coresmartcontracts Uniswap v.3.0 and fixed in v.4.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the _modifyPosition func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25962</link><description>An issue in Coresmartcontracts Uniswap v.3.0 and fixed in v.4.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the _modifyPosition function</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40615 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bookgy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40615</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bookgy. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the "TEXTO" parameter in /api/api_ajustes.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40616 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bookgy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40616</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bookgy. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the "IDRESERVA" parameter in /bkg_imprimir_comprobante.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40617 | SQL injection vulnerability in Bookgy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40617</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Bookgy. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases by sending an HTTP request through the "IDTIPO", "IDPISTA" and "IDSOCIO" parameters in /bkg_seleccionar_hora_ajax.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40618 | SQL injection vulnerability in Bookgy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40618</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Bookgy. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases by sending an HTTP request through the "IDRESERVA"  parameter in /bkg_imprimir_comprobante.php</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32354 | In Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 through 10.1, a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the GraphQL endpoint (/service/e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32354</link><description>In Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 through 10.1, a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the GraphQL endpoint (/service/extension/graphql) of Zimbra webmail due to a lack of CSRF token validation. This allows attackers to perform unauthorized GraphQL operations, such as modifying contacts, changing account settings, and accessing sensitive user data when an authenticated user visits a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46346 | YesWiki Vulnerable to Stored XSS in Comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46346</link><description>YesWiki is a wiki system written in PHP. Prior to version 4.5.4, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the application’s comments feature. This issue allows a malicious actor to inject JavaScript payloads that are stored and later executed in the browser of any user viewing the affected comment. The XSS occurs because the application fails to properly sanitize or encode user input submitted to the comments. Notably, the application sanitizes or does not allow execution of `</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4068 | code-projects Simple Movie Ticket Booking System changeprize stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4068</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Movie Ticket Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function changeprize. The manipulation of the argument prize leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4069 | code-projects Product Management System add_item stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4069</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Product Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function add_item. The manipulation of the argument st.productname leads to stack-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4067 | ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System viewpackage.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4067</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/viewpackage.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4065 | ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System addadvertisement.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4065</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/addadvertisement.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4066 | ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System addpackage.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4066</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/addpackage.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4064 | ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System viewenquiry.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ScriptAndTools Online-Travling-System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/viewenquiry.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3301 | DPA Countermeasures Unavailable for Certain Cryptographic Operations on Series 2 Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3301</link><description>DPA countermeasures are unavailable for ECDH key agreement and EdDSA signing operations on Curve25519 and Curve448 on all Series 2 modules and SoCs due to a lack of hardware and software support. A successful DPA attack may result in exposure of confidential information. The best practice is to use the impacted crypto curves and operations with ephemeral keys to reduce the number of DPA traces that can be collected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4062 | code-projects Theater Seat Booking System cancel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4062</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Theater Seat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cancel. The manipulation of the argument cancelcustomername leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4063 | code-projects Student Information Management System cancel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4063</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Information Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cancel. The manipulation of the argument first_name/last_name leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2817 | Mozilla Firefox's update mechanism allowed a medium-integrity user process to interfere with the SYSTEM-level updater by manipulating the fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2817</link><description>Mozilla Firefox's update mechanism allowed a medium-integrity user process to interfere with the SYSTEM-level updater by manipulating the file-locking behavior. By injecting code into the user-privileged process, an attacker could bypass intended access controls, allowing SYSTEM-level file operations on paths controlled by a non-privileged user and enabling privilege escalation. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23, Thunderbird &lt; 138, and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4082 | Modification of specific WebGL shader attributes could trigger an out-of-bounds read, which, when chained with other vulnerabilities, could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4082</link><description>Modification of specific WebGL shader attributes could trigger an out-of-bounds read, which, when chained with other vulnerabilities, could be used to escalate privileges.
*This bug only affects Firefox for macOS. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23, Thunderbird &lt; 138, and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4083 | A process isolation vulnerability in Firefox stemmed from improper handling of javascript: URIs, which could allow content to execute in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4083</link><description>A process isolation vulnerability in Firefox stemmed from improper handling of javascript: URIs, which could allow content to execute in the top-level document's process instead of the intended frame, potentially enabling a sandbox escape. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23, Thunderbird &lt; 138, and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4084 | Due to insufficient escaping of the special characters in the "copy as cURL" feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4084</link><description>Due to insufficient escaping of the special characters in the "copy as cURL" feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command, potentially leading to local code execution on the user's system.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Windows. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23, and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4085 | An attacker with control over a content process could potentially leverage the privileged UITour actor to leak sensitive information or esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4085</link><description>An attacker with control over a content process could potentially leverage the privileged UITour actor to leak sensitive information or escalate privileges. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4086 | A specially crafted filename containing a large number of encoded newline characters could obscure the file's extension when displayed in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4086</link><description>A specially crafted filename containing a large number of encoded newline characters could obscure the file's extension when displayed in the download dialog.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4087 | A vulnerability was identified in Firefox where XPath parsing could trigger undefined behavior due to missing null checks during attribute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4087</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Firefox where XPath parsing could trigger undefined behavior due to missing null checks during attribute access. This could lead to out-of-bounds read access and potentially, memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10, Thunderbird &lt; 138, and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4088 | A security vulnerability in Firefox allowed malicious sites to use redirects to send credentialed requests to arbitrary endpoints on any sit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4088</link><description>A security vulnerability in Firefox allowed malicious sites to use redirects to send credentialed requests to arbitrary endpoints on any site that had invoked the Storage Access API. This enabled potential Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks across origins. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4089 | Due to insufficient escaping of special characters in the "copy as cURL" feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command, po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4089</link><description>Due to insufficient escaping of special characters in the "copy as cURL" feature, an attacker could trick a user into using this command, potentially leading to local code execution on the user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4090 | A vulnerability existed in Firefox for Android where potentially sensitive library locations were logged via Logcat. This vulnerability affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4090</link><description>A vulnerability existed in Firefox for Android where potentially sensitive library locations were logged via Logcat. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4091 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 137, Thunderbird 137, Firefox ESR 128.9, and Thunderbird 128.9. Some of these bugs showed evidence of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4091</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 137, Thunderbird 137, Firefox ESR 128.9, and Thunderbird 128.9. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10, Thunderbird &lt; 138, and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4092 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 137 and Thunderbird 137. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4092</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 137 and Thunderbird 137. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4093 | Memory safety bug present in Firefox ESR 128.9, and Thunderbird 128.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4093</link><description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox ESR 128.9, and Thunderbird 128.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10 and Thunderbird ESR &lt; 128.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4035 | Libsoup: cookie domain validation bypass via uppercase characters in libsoup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4035</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. When handling cookies, libsoup clients mistakenly allow cookies to be set for public suffix domains if the domain contains at least two components and includes an uppercase character. This bypasses public suffix protections and could allow a malicious website to set cookies for domains it does not own, potentially leading to integrity issues such as session fixation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4061 | code-projects Clothing Store Management System add_item stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4061</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Clothing Store Management System up to 1.0. Affected is the function add_item. The manipulation of the argument st.productname leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4060 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4060</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /category.php. The manipulation of the argument catname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3891 | Mod_auth_openidc: dos via empty post in mod_auth_openidc with oidcpreservepost enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3891</link><description>A flaw was found in the mod_auth_openidc module for Apache httpd. This flaw allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trigger a denial of service by sending an empty POST request when the OIDCPreservePost directive is enabled. The server crashes consistently, affecting availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 12:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4059 | code-projects Prison Management System Prison_Mgmt_Sys addrecord stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4059</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Prison Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function addrecord of the component Prison_Mgmt_Sys. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to stack-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 12:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58099 | vmxnet3: Fix packet corruption in vmxnet3_xdp_xmit_frame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58099</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vmxnet3: Fix packet corruption in vmxnet3_xdp_xmit_frame

Andrew and Nikolay reported connectivity issues with Cilium's service
load-balancing in case of vmxnet3.

If a BPF program for native XDP adds an encapsulation header such as
IPIP and transmits the packet out the same interface, then in case
of vmxnet3 a corrupted packet is being sent and subsequently dropped
on the path.

vmxnet3_xdp_xmit_frame() which is called e.g. via vmxnet3_run_xdp()
through vmxnet3_xdp_xmit_back() calculates an incorrect DMA address:

  page = virt_to_page(xdpf-&gt;data);
  tbi-&gt;dma_addr = page_pool_get_dma_addr(page) +
                  VMXNET3_XDP_HEADROOM;
  dma_sync_single_for_device(&amp;amp;adapter-&gt;pdev-&gt;dev,
                             tbi-&gt;dma_addr, buf_size,
                             DMA_TO_DEVICE);

The above assumes a fixed offset (VMXNET3_XDP_HEADROOM), but the XDP
BPF program could have moved xdp-&gt;data. While the passed buf_size is
correct (xdpf-&gt;len), the dma_addr needs to have a dynamic offset which
can be calculated as xdpf-&gt;data - (void *)xdpf, that is, xdp-&gt;data -
xdp-&gt;data_hard_start.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1194 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in huggingface/transformers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1194</link><description>A Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability was identified in the huggingface/transformers library, specifically in the file `tokenization_gpt_neox_japanese.py` of the GPT-NeoX-Japanese model. The vulnerability occurs in the SubWordJapaneseTokenizer class, where regular expressions process specially crafted inputs. The issue stems from a regex exhibiting exponential complexity under certain conditions, leading to excessive backtracking. This can result in high CPU usage and potential application downtime, effectively creating a Denial of Service (DoS) scenario. The affected version is v4.48.1 (latest).</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3929 | Stored XSS vulnerability in MDaemon Email Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3929</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in MDaemon Email Server version 25.0.1 and below. An attacker can send a specially crafted HTML e-mail message with JavaScript in an img tag. This could allow a remote attacker to load arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of a webmail user's browser window, and access user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4058 | Projectworlds Online Examination System Bloodgroop_process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4058</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Projectworlds Online Examination System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Bloodgroop_process.php. The manipulation of the argument Pat_BloodGroup1 leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30194 | Denial of service via crafted DoH exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30194</link><description>When DNSdist is configured to provide DoH via the nghttp2 provider, an attacker can cause a denial of service by crafting a DoH exchange that triggers an illegal memory access (double-free) and crash of DNSdist, causing a denial of service.

The remedy is: upgrade to the patched 1.9.9 version.

A workaround is to temporarily switch to the h2o provider until DNSdist has been upgraded to a fixed version.

We would like to thank Charles Howes for bringing this issue to our attention.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3452 | SecuPress Free &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3452</link><description>The SecuPress Free — WordPress Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'secupress_reinstall_plugins_admin_ajax_cb' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2893 | Gutenverse &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via countdown Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2893</link><description>The Gutenverse – Ultimate Block Addons and Page Builder for Site Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's countdown Block in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12273 | Calculated Fields Form &amp;lt; 5.2.62 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12273</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form WordPress plugin before 5.2.62 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 06:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46329 | Snowflake Connector for C/C++ inserts client-side encryption key in DEBUG logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46329</link><description>libsnowflakeclient is the Snowflake Connector for C/C++. Versions starting from 0.5.0 to before 2.2.0, are vulnerable to local logging of sensitive information. When the logging level was set to DEBUG, the Connector would log locally the client-side encryption master key of the target stage during the execution of GET/PUT commands. This key by itself does not grant access to any sensitive data without additional access authorizations, and is not logged server-side by Snowflake. This issue has been patched in version 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46330 | Snowflake Connector for C/C++ retries malformed requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46330</link><description>libsnowflakeclient is the Snowflake Connector for C/C++. Versions starting from 0.5.0 to before 2.2.0, incorrectly treat malformed requests that caused the HTTP response status code 400, as able to be retried. This could hang the application until SF_CON_MAX_RETRY requests were sent. This issue has been patched in version 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46338 | Audiobookshelf Vulnerable to Cross-Site-Scripting Reflected via POST Request in /api/upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46338</link><description>Audiobookshelf is a self-hosted audiobook and podcast server. Prior to version 2.21.0, an improper input handling vulnerability in the `/api/upload` endpoint allows an attacker to perform a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack by submitting malicious payloads in the `libraryId` field. The unsanitized input is reflected in the server’s error message, enabling arbitrary JavaScript execution in a victim's browser. This issue has been patched in version 2.21.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46343 | n8n Vulnerable to Stored XSS through Attachments View Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46343</link><description>n8n is a workflow automation platform. Prior to version 1.90.0, n8n is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting (XSS) through the attachments view endpoint. n8n workflows can store and serve binary files, which are accessible to authenticated users. However, there is no restriction on the MIME type of uploaded files, and the MIME type could be controlled via a GET parameter. This allows the server to respond with any MIME type, potentially enabling malicious content to be interpreted and executed by the browser. An authenticated attacker with member-level permissions could exploit this by uploading a crafted HTML file containing malicious JavaScript. When another user visits the binary data endpoint with the MIME type set to text/html, the script executes in the context of the user’s session. This script could send a request to change the user’s email address in their account settings, effectively enabling account takeover. This issue has been patched in version 1.90.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 04:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24179 | A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, visionOS 2.3, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24179</link><description>A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, visionOS 2.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.3, tvOS 18.3. An attacker on the local network may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24206 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24206</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may be able to bypass authentication policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24251 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24251</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, watchOS 11.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may cause an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24252 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24252</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may be able to corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24270 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24270</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24271 | An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24271</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An unauthenticated user on the same network as a signed-in Mac could send it AirPlay commands without pairing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30445 | A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30445</link><description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may cause an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31197 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31197</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, macOS Ventura 13.7.5, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may cause an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31202 | A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, macOS Sequoia 15.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31202</link><description>A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31203 | An integer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31203</link><description>An integer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4, tvOS 18.4, iPadOS 17.7.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, watchOS 11.4, visionOS 2.4. An attacker on the local network may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>