<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 11:43:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-1104 | Temporary denial of service during a brute force attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1104</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can bypass the brute force prevention mechanism and disturb the webservice for all users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 11:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0220 | B&amp;amp;R products use insufficient communication encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0220</link><description>B&amp;R Automation Studio Upgrade Service and B&amp;R Technology Guarding use insufficient cryptography for communication to the upgrade and the licensing servers. A network-based attacker could exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the products or sniff sensitive data.



Missing Encryption of Sensitive Data, Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information, Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection'), Inadequate Encryption Strength vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation B&amp;R Automation Studio (Upgrade Service modules), B&amp;R Industrial Automation Technology Guarding.This issue affects B&amp;R Automation Studio: &lt;4.6; Technology Guarding: &lt;1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 10:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22393 | Apache Answer: Pixel Flood Attack by uploading the large pixel file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22393</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Pixel Flood Attack by uploading large pixel files will cause server out of memory. A logged-in user can cause such an attack by uploading an image when posting content.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23349 | Apache Answer: XSS vulnerability when submitting summary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

XSS attack when user enters summary. A logged-in user, when modifying their own submitted question, can input malicious code in the summary to create such an attack.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29179 | A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, Fortiproxy version 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29179</link><description>A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, Fortiproxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.10 allows attacker to denial of service via  specially crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29180 | A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 through 6.2.14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29180</link><description>A null pointer dereference in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 through 6.2.14, 6.0.0 through 6.0.16, FortiProxy 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, 2.0.0 through 2.0.12, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7 allows attacker to denial of service via specially crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29181 | A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29181</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.12, 6.2.0 through 6.2.14, 6.0.0 through 6.0.16, FortiProxy 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, 2.0.0 through 2.0.12, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7, FortiPAM 1.0.0 through 1.0.3 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26578 | Apache Answer: Repeated submission at registration created duplicate users with the same name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26578</link><description>Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Repeated submission during registration resulted in the registration of the same user. When users register, if they rapidly submit multiple registrations using scripts, it can result in the creation of multiple user accounts simultaneously with the same name.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0903 | The User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0903</link><description>The User Feedback – Create Interactive Feedback Form, User Surveys, and Polls in Seconds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page_submitted' 'link' value in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in the feedback submission page that will execute when a user clicks the link, while also pressing the command key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1053 | The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1053</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'email' action in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to email the attendees list to themselves.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26489 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Social block links' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26489</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Social block links' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Profile Name text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26490 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Simple module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26490</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Simple module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Title text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26491 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Media Gallery with description' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26491</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Addon JD Flusity 'Media Gallery with description' module of flusity-CMS v2.33 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Gallery name text field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25801 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Add Media function of SKINsoft S-Museum v7.02.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25801</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Add Media function of SKINsoft S-Museum v7.02.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26481 | Kirby CMS v4.1.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the URL parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26481</link><description>Kirby CMS v4.1.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the URL parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26482 | An HTML injection vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26482</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26483 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Profile Image module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26483</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Profile Image module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26484 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26484</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Content Layout module of Kirby CMS v4.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Link field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 05:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23136 | A maliciously crafted STP file when ASMKERN228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to dereference an untrusted pointer. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23136</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when ASMKERN228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to dereference an untrusted pointer. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23137 | A maliciously crafted STP or SLDPRT file when ODXSW_DLL.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to uninitialized variable. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23137</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP or SLDPRT file when ODXSW_DLL.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to uninitialized variable. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27283 | A vulnerability was discovered in Veritas eDiscovery Platform before 10.2.5. The application administrator can upload potentially malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27283</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in Veritas eDiscovery Platform before 10.2.5. The application administrator can upload potentially malicious files to arbitrary locations on the server on which the application is installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23135 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when ASMkern228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23135</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when ASMkern228A.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23134 | A maliciously crafted IGS file when tbb.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23134</link><description>A maliciously crafted IGS file when tbb.dll parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used in user-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23132 | A maliciously crafted STP file in atf_dwg_consumer.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23132</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file in atf_dwg_consumer.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23133 | A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23133</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23131 | A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMKERN228A.dll or ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23131</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file in ASMKERN228A.dll or ASMDATAX228A.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 04:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23130 | A maliciously crafted SLDASM, or SLDPRT files in ODXSW_DLL.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23130</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDASM, or SLDPRT files in ODXSW_DLL.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23129 | A maliciously crafted MODEL 3DM, STP or SLDASM files in opennurbs.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23129</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL 3DM, STP or SLDASM files in opennurbs.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23128 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file in libodxdll.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by wr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23128</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file in libodxdll.dll when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD could lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23127 | A maliciously crafted MODEL, SLDPRT or SLDASM file when parsed VCRUNTIME140.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Heap-based O...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23127</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL, SLDPRT or SLDASM file when parsed VCRUNTIME140.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23125 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23125</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23126 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23126</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23124 | A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23124</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23122 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23122</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23123 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23123</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23121 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23121</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25251 | code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 is suffers from Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25251</link><description>code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 is suffers from Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4895 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25423 | An issue in MAXON CINEMA 4D R2024.2.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted c4d_base.xdl64 file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25423</link><description>An issue in MAXON CINEMA 4D R2024.2.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted c4d_base.xdl64 file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23120 | A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23120</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMIMPORT228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6477 | Improper Privilege Management in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0410 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link><description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0861 | Improper Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1451 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1525 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1525</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0446 | A maliciously crafted STP, CATPART or MODEL file when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0446</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP, CATPART or MODEL file when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3509 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26148 | Querybook&amp;#x27;s Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability allows Privilege Elevation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26148</link><description>Querybook is a user interface for querying big data. Prior to version 3.31.1, there is a vulnerability in Querybook's rich text editor that enables users to input arbitrary URLs without undergoing necessary validation. This particular security flaw allows the use of `javascript:` protocol which can potentially trigger arbitrary client-side execution. The most extreme exploit of this flaw could occur when an admin user unknowingly clicks on a cross-site scripting URL, thereby unintentionally compromising admin role access to the attacker. A patch to rectify this issue has been introduced in Querybook version `3.31.1`. The fix is backward compatible and automatically fixes existing DataDocs. There are no known workarounds for this issue, except for manually checking each URL prior to clicking on them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26147 | Helm&amp;#x27;s Missing YAML Content Leads To Panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26147</link><description>Helm is a package manager for Charts for Kubernetes. Versions prior to 3.14.2 contain an uninitialized variable vulnerability when Helm parses index and plugin yaml files missing expected content. When either an `index.yaml` file or a plugins `plugin.yaml` file were missing all metadata a panic would occur in Helm. In the Helm SDK, this is found when using the `LoadIndexFile` or `DownloadIndexFile` functions in the `repo` package or the `LoadDir` function in the `plugin` package. For the Helm client this impacts functions around adding a repository and all Helm functions if a malicious plugin is added as Helm inspects all known plugins on each invocation. This issue has been resolved in Helm v3.14.2. If a malicious plugin has been added which is causing all Helm client commands to panic, the malicious plugin can be manually removed from the filesystem. If using Helm SDK versions prior to 3.14.2, calls to affected functions can use `recover` to catch the panic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52155 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/sauvegarde/run.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52155</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/sauvegarde/run.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the sauvegardes variable through the /admin/sauvegarde/run.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52153 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in /pmb/opac_css/includes/sessions.inc.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote unauthenticated attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52153</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in /pmb/opac_css/includes/sessions.inc.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows remote unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands via the PmbOpac-LOGIN cookie value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52154 | File Upload vulnerability in pmb/camera_upload.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted PHT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52154</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in pmb/camera_upload.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted PHTML files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51828 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/convert/export.class.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier versions allows remote unauthenticated attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51828</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in /admin/convert/export.class.php in PMB 7.4.7 and earlier versions allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the query parameter in get_next_notice function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37177 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PMB Services PMB v.7.4.7 and before allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37177</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PMB Services PMB v.7.4.7 and before allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via the query parameter in the /admin/convert/export_z3950.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38844 | SQL injection vulnerability in PMB v.7.4.7 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the thesaurus parameter in exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38844</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PMB v.7.4.7 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the thesaurus parameter in export_skos.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25124 | Fiber has Insecure CORS Configuration, Allowing Wildcard Origin with Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25124</link><description>Fiber is a web framework written in go. Prior to version 2.52.1, the CORS middleware allows for insecure configurations that could potentially expose the application to multiple CORS-related vulnerabilities. Specifically, it allows setting the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header to a wildcard (`*`) while also having the Access-Control-Allow-Credentials set to true, which goes against recommended security best practices. The impact of this misconfiguration is high as it can lead to unauthorized access to sensitive user data and expose the system to various types of attacks listed in the PortSwigger article linked in the references. Version 2.52.1 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, users may manually validate the CORS configurations in their implementation to ensure that they do not allow a wildcard origin when credentials are enabled. The browser fetch api, as well as browsers and utilities that enforce CORS policies, are not affected by this.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24333 | A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC21 with firmware version US_AC21V1.0re_V16.03.08.15_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24333</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC21 with firmware version US_AC21V1.0re_V16.03.08.15_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to /goform/openSchedWifi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24334 | A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC23 with firmware version US_AC23V1.0re_V16.03.07.45_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24334</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC23 with firmware version US_AC23V1.0re_V16.03.07.45_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via schedStartTime parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24332 | A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC6 with firmware version US_AC6V5.0re_V03.03.02.01_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24332</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC6 with firmware version US_AC6V5.0re_V03.03.02.01_cn_TDC01 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to /goform/PowerSaveSet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23654 | discourse-ai admin-initiated SSRF when interacting with AI services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23654</link><description>discourse-ai is the AI plugin for the open-source discussion platform Discourse. Prior to commit 94ba0dadc2cf38e8f81c3936974c167219878edd, interactions with different AI services are vulnerable to admin-initiated SSRF attacks. Versions of the plugin that include commit 94ba0dadc2cf38e8f81c3936974c167219878edd contain a patch. As a workaround, one may disable the discourse-ai plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24331 | Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 816 with firmware version DIR-816_A2_v1.10CNB04 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24331</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 816 with firmware version DIR-816_A2_v1.10CNB04 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the urlAdd parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24330 | Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 882 with firmware version DIR882A1_FW130B06 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24330</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in D-Link Dir 882 with firmware version DIR882A1_FW130B06 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to /HNAP1/.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25461 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Terrasoft, Creatio Terrasoft CRM v.7.18.4.1532 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25461</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Terrasoft, Creatio Terrasoft CRM v.7.18.4.1532 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the terrasoft.axd component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6533 | Silicon Labs PC Controller Denial of Service Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6533</link><description>Malformed Device Reset Locally Command Class packets can be sent to the controller, causing the controller to assume the end device has left the network. After this, frames sent by the end device will not be acknowledged by the controller. This vulnerability exists in PC Controller v5.54.0, and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6640 | Silicon Labs PC Controller v5.54.0 and Earlier Denial of Service Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6640</link><description>Malformed S2 Nonce Get Command Class packets can be sent to crash PC Controller v5.54.0 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25249 | An issue in He3 App for macOS version 2.0.17, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectAr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25249</link><description>An issue in He3 App for macOS version 2.0.17, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26310 | Archer Platform 6.8 before 6.14 P2 (6.14.0.2) contains an improper access control vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26310</link><description>Archer Platform 6.8 before 6.14 P2 (6.14.0.2) contains an improper access control vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user could potentially exploit this to gain access to API information that should only be accessible with extra privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26311 | Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF1 (6.14.0.2.1) contains a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26311</link><description>Archer Platform 6.x before 6.14 P2 HF1 (6.14.0.2.1) contains a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this by tricking a victim application user into supplying malicious JavaScript code to the vulnerable web application. This code is then reflected to the victim and gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24476 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Wireshark team Wireshark before v.4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the pan/a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24476</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Wireshark team Wireshark before v.4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the pan/addr_resolv.c, and ws_manuf_lookup_str(), size components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 19:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24479 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Wireshark team Wireshark before v.4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the wsuti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24479</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Wireshark team Wireshark before v.4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the wsutil/to_str.c, and format_fractional_part_nsecs components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25381 | There is a Stored XSS Vulnerability in Emlog Pro 2.2.8 Article Publishing, due to non-filtering of quoted content.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25381</link><description>There is a Stored XSS Vulnerability in Emlog Pro 2.2.8 Article Publishing, due to non-filtering of quoted content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50975 | The TD Bank TD Advanced Dashboard client through 3.0.3 for macOS allows arbitrary code execution because of the lack of electron::fuses::IsR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50975</link><description>The TD Bank TD Advanced Dashboard client through 3.0.3 for macOS allows arbitrary code execution because of the lack of electron::fuses::IsRunAsNodeEnabled (i.e., ELECTRON_RUN_AS_NODE can be used in production). This makes it easier for a compromised process to access banking information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1707 | GARO WALLBOX GLB+ T2EV7 Software Update index.jsp#settings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1707</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GARO WALLBOX GLB+ T2EV7 0.5. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.jsp#settings of the component Software Update Handler. The manipulation of the argument Reference leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254397 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22473 | Uninitialized TRNG used for ECDSA after EM2/EM3 sleep for VSE devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22473</link><description>TRNG is used before initialization by ECDSA signing driver when exiting EM2/EM3 on Virtual Secure Vault (VSE) devices. This defect may allow Signature Spoofing by Key Recreation.This issue affects Gecko SDK through v4.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1706 | ZKTeco ZKBio Access IVS Department Name Search Bar cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1706</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ZKTeco ZKBio Access IVS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Department Name Search Bar. The manipulation with the input &lt;marquee&gt;hi leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254396. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25897 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCatalog.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25897</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCatalog.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25898 | A XSS vulnerability was found in the ChurchCRM v.5.5.0 functionality, edit your event, where malicious JS or HTML code can be inserted in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25898</link><description>A XSS vulnerability was found in the ChurchCRM v.5.5.0 functionality, edit your event, where malicious JS or HTML code can be inserted in the Event Sermon field in EventEditor.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 18:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25892 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 ConfirmReport.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the familyId GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25892</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 ConfirmReport.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the familyId GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25893 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCertificates.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25893</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRCertificates.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25894 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 /EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EventCount POST parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25894</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 /EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EventCount POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25896 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EID POST parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25896</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 EventEditor.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the EID POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25891 | ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRBidSheets.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25891</link><description>ChurchCRM 5.5.0 FRBidSheets.php is vulnerable to Blind SQL Injection (Time-based) via the CurrentFundraiser GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25895 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChurchCRM 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25895</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChurchCRM 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the type parameter of /EventAttendance.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1212 | LoadMaster Pre-Authenticated OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1212</link><description>Unauthenticated remote attackers can access the system through the LoadMaster management interface, enabling arbitrary system command execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1704 | ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB crud delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB 5.2.2. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function save/delete of the file /adminapi/system/crud. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254392. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1705 | Shopwind Installation DefaultController.php actionCreate code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shopwind up to 4.6. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function actionCreate of the file /public/install/controllers/DefaultController.php of the component Installation. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254393 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26145 | Uninvited user is able to join and mark the attendance of the the private event</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26145</link><description>Discourse Calendar adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic on Discourse. Uninvited users are able to gain access to private events by crafting a request to update their attendance. This problem is resolved in commit dfc4fa15f340189f177a1d1ab2cc94ffed3c1190. As a workaround, one may use post visibility to limit access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1703 | ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB openfile absolute path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1703</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZhongBangKeJi CRMEB 5.2.2. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function openfile of the file /adminapi/system/file/openfile. The manipulation leads to absolute path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254391. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26138 | License information is public, exposing instance id and license holder details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26138</link><description>The XWiki licensor application, which manages and enforce application licenses for paid extensions, includes the document `Licenses.Code.LicenseJSON` that provides information for admins regarding active licenses. This document is public and thus exposes this information publicly. The information includes the instance's id as well as first and last name and email of the license owner. This is a leak of information that isn't supposed to be public. The instance id allows associating data on the active installs data with the concrete XWiki instance. Active installs assures that "there's no way to find who's having a given UUID" (referring to the instance id). Further, the information who the license owner is and information about the obtained licenses can be used for targeted phishing attacks. Also, while user information is normally public, email addresses might only be displayed obfuscated,  depending on the configuration. This has been fixed in Application Licensing 1.24.2. There are no known workarounds besides upgrading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26133 | EventStoreDB Projections Subsystem has potential password leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26133</link><description>EventStoreDB (ESDB) is an operational database built to store events. A vulnerability has been identified in the projections subsystem in versions 20 prior to 20.10.6, 21 prior to 21.10.11, 22 prior to 22.10.5, and 23 prior to 23.10.1. Only database instances that use custom projections are affected by this vulnerability. User passwords may become accessible to those who have access to the chunk files on disk, and users who have read access to system streams. Only users in the `$admins` group can access system streams by default. ESDB 23.10.1, 22.10.5, 21.10.11, and 20.10.6 contain a patch for this issue. Users should upgrade EventStoreDB, reset the passwords for current and previous members of `$admins` and `$ops` groups, and, if a password was reused in any other system, reset it in those systems to a unique password to follow best practices. If an upgrade cannot be done immediately, reset the passwords for current and previous members of `$admins` and `$ops` groups. Avoid creating custom projections until the patch has been applied.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1702 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1702</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254390 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26130 | cryptography NULL pointer deference with pkcs12.serialize_key_and_certificates when called with a non-matching certificate and private key and an hmac_hash override</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26130</link><description>cryptography is a package designed to expose cryptographic primitives and recipes to Python developers. Starting in version 38.0.0 and prior to version 42.0.4, if `pkcs12.serialize_key_and_certificates` is called with both a certificate whose public key did not match the provided private key and an `encryption_algorithm` with `hmac_hash` set (via `PrivateFormat.PKCS12.encryption_builder().hmac_hash(...)`, then a NULL pointer dereference would occur, crashing the Python process. This has been resolved in version 42.0.4, the first version in which a `ValueError` is properly raised.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25117 | php-svg-lib lacks path validation on font through SVG inline styles </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25117</link><description>php-svg-lib is a scalable vector graphics (SVG) file parsing/rendering library. Prior to version 0.5.2, php-svg-lib fails to validate that font-family doesn't contain a PHAR url, which might leads to RCE on PHP &lt; 8.0, and doesn't validate if external references are allowed. This might leads to bypass of restrictions or RCE on projects that are using it, if they do not strictly revalidate the fontName that is passed by php-svg-lib. The `Style::fromAttributes(`), or the `Style::parseCssStyle()` should check the content of the `font-family` and prevents it to use a PHAR url, to avoid passing an invalid and dangerous `fontName` value to other libraries. The same check as done in the `Style::fromStyleSheets` might be reused. Libraries using this library as a dependency might be vulnerable to some bypass of restrictions, or even remote code execution, if they do not double check the value of the `fontName` that is passed by php-svg-lib. Version 0.5.2 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20325 | A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20325</link><description>A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modify data in a repository that belongs to an internal service on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient access control implementations on cluster configuration CLI requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a cluster configuration CLI request to specific directories on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and modify data that is handled by an internal service on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23346 | pymatgen arbitrary code execution when parsing a maliciously crafted JonesFaithfulTransformation transformation_string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23346</link><description>Pymatgen (Python Materials Genomics) is an open-source Python library for materials analysis. A critical security vulnerability exists in the `JonesFaithfulTransformation.from_transformation_str()` method within the `pymatgen` library prior to version 2024.2.20. This method insecurely utilizes `eval()` for processing input, enabling execution of arbitrary code when parsing untrusted input. Version 2024.2.20 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24478 | An issue in Wireshark team Wireshark before v.4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the packet-bgp.c, dissect_bgp_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24478</link><description>An issue in Wireshark team Wireshark before v.4.2.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the packet-bgp.c, dissect_bgp_open(tvbuff_t*tvb, proto_tree*tree, packet_info*pinfo), optlen components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25288 | SLIMS (Senayan Library Management Systems) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via pop-scope-vocabolary.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25288</link><description>SLIMS (Senayan Library Management Systems) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via pop-scope-vocabolary.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46241 | Potential account take over due to unverified emails from Microsoft Identity Platform </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46241</link><description>`discourse-microsoft-auth` is a plugin that enables authentication via Microsoft. On sites with the `discourse-microsoft-auth` plugin enabled, an attack can potentially take control of a victim's Discourse account. Sites that have configured their application's account type to any options other than `Accounts in this organizational directory only (O365 only - Single tenant)` are vulnerable. This vulnerability has been patched in commit c40665f44509724b64938c85def9fb2e79f62ec8 of `discourse-microsoft-auth`. A `microsoft_auth:revoke` rake task has also been added which will deactivate and log out all users that have connected their accounts to Microsoft. User API keys as well as API keys created by those users will also be revoked. The rake task will also remove the connection records to Microsoft for those users. This will allow affected users to re-verify their account emails as well as reconnect their Discourse account to Microsoft for authentication. As a workaround, disable the `discourse-microsoft-auth` plugin by setting the `microsoft_auth_enabled` site setting to `false`. Run the `microsoft_auth:log_out_users` rake task to log out all users with associated Microsoft accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49100 | Trusted Firmware-A (TF-A) before 2.10 has a potential read out-of-bounds in the SDEI service. The input parameter passed in register x1 is n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49100</link><description>Trusted Firmware-A (TF-A) before 2.10 has a potential read out-of-bounds in the SDEI service. The input parameter passed in register x1 is not validated well enough in the function sdei_interrupt_bind. The parameter is passed to a call to plat_ic_get_interrupt_type. It can be any arbitrary value passing checks in the function plat_ic_is_sgi. A compromised Normal World (Linux kernel) can enable a root-privileged attacker to issue arbitrary SMC calls. Using this primitive, he can control the content of registers x0 through x6, which are used to send parameters to TF-A. Out-of-bounds addresses can be read in the context of TF-A (EL3). Because the read value is never returned to non-secure memory or in registers, no leak is possible. An attacker can still crash TF-A, however.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22220 | An issue was discovered in Terminalfour 7.4 through 7.4.0004 QP3 and 8 through 8.3.19, and Formbank through 2.1.10-FINAL. Unauthenticated St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22220</link><description>An issue was discovered in Terminalfour 7.4 through 7.4.0004 QP3 and 8 through 8.3.19, and Formbank through 2.1.10-FINAL. Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting can occur, with resultant Admin Session Hijacking. The attack vectors are Form Builder and Form Preview.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45169 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A URL Redirection to an Untrusted Site (Open Redirect) can occur under ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45169</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A URL Redirection to an Untrusted Site (Open Redirect) can occur under the /api/v1/notification/createnotification endpoint, allowing an authenticated user to send an arbitrary push notification to any other user of the system. This push notification can include an (invisible) clickable link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45177 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. An Observable Response Discrepancy can occur under the /api/v1/vdeskint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45177</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. An Observable Response Discrepancy can occur under the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/user/isenableuser endpoint, the /api/v1/sharedsearch?search={NAME]+{SURNAME] endpoint, and the /login endpoint. The web application provides different responses to incoming requests in a way that reveals internal state information to an unauthorized actor outside of the intended control sphere.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45179 | An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A basic XSS vulnerability exists under the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/tod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45179</link><description>An issue was discovered in LIVEBOX Collaboration vDesk through v031. A basic XSS vulnerability exists under the /api/v1/vdeskintegration/todo/createorupdate endpoint via the title parameter and /dashboard/reminders. A remote user (authenticated to the product) can store arbitrary HTML code in the reminder section title in order to corrupt the web page (for example, by creating phishing sections to exfiltrate victims' credentials).</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1474 | WS_FTP Server Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in Administrative Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1474</link><description>In WS_FTP Server versions before 8.8.5, reflected cross-site scripting issues have been identified on various user supplied inputs on the WS_FTP Server administrative interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1709 | Authentication bypass using an alternate path or channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1709</link><description>ConnectWise ScreenConnect 23.9.7 and prior are affected by an Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel

 vulnerability, which may allow an attacker direct access to confidential information or 

critical systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1700 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1700</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument username with the input &lt;script&gt;alert("xss")&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254388. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1701 | keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System edit.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1701</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254389 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1708 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory (“path traversal”)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1708</link><description>ConnectWise ScreenConnect 23.9.7 and prior are affected by path-traversal vulnerability, which may allow an attacker 

the ability to execute remote code or directly impact confidential data or critical systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26582 | net: tls: fix use-after-free with partial reads and async decrypt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26582</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: tls: fix use-after-free with partial reads and async decrypt

tls_decrypt_sg doesn't take a reference on the pages from clear_skb,
so the put_page() in tls_decrypt_done releases them, and we trigger
a use-after-free in process_rx_list when we try to read from the
partially-read skb.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26583 | tls: fix race between async notify and socket close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26583</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: fix race between async notify and socket close

The submitting thread (one which called recvmsg/sendmsg)
may exit as soon as the async crypto handler calls complete()
so any code past that point risks touching already freed data.

Try to avoid the locking and extra flags altogether.
Have the main thread hold an extra reference, this way
we can depend solely on the atomic ref counter for
synchronization.

Don't futz with reiniting the completion, either, we are now
tightly controlling when completion fires.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26584 | net: tls: handle backlogging of crypto requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26584</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: tls: handle backlogging of crypto requests

Since we're setting the CRYPTO_TFM_REQ_MAY_BACKLOG flag on our
requests to the crypto API, crypto_aead_{encrypt,decrypt} can return
 -EBUSY instead of -EINPROGRESS in valid situations. For example, when
the cryptd queue for AESNI is full (easy to trigger with an
artificially low cryptd.cryptd_max_cpu_qlen), requests will be enqueued
to the backlog but still processed. In that case, the async callback
will also be called twice: first with err == -EINPROGRESS, which it
seems we can just ignore, then with err == 0.

Compared to Sabrina's original patch this version uses the new
tls_*crypt_async_wait() helpers and converts the EBUSY to
EINPROGRESS to avoid having to modify all the error handling
paths. The handling is identical.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26585 | tls: fix race between tx work scheduling and socket close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26585</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: fix race between tx work scheduling and socket close

Similarly to previous commit, the submitting thread (recvmsg/sendmsg)
may exit as soon as the async crypto handler calls complete().
Reorder scheduling the work before calling complete().
This seems more logical in the first place, as it's
the inverse order of what the submitting thread will do.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33843 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33843</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  256544.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50955 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50955</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow an authenticated privileged user to obtain the absolute path of the web server installation which could aid in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275777.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22778 | HackMD CodiMD &lt;2.5.2 is vulnerable to Denial of Service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22778</link><description>HackMD CodiMD &lt;2.5.2 is vulnerable to Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47795 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Document and Media widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.18 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47795</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Document and Media widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.18 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 update 18 through 92 allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a document's “Title” text field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 14:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7235 | The OpenVPN GUI installer before version 2.6.9 did not set the proper access control restrictions to the installation directory of OpenVPN b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7235</link><description>The OpenVPN GUI installer before version 2.6.9 did not set the proper access control restrictions to the installation directory of OpenVPN binaries when using a non-standard installation path, which allows an attacker to replace binaries to run arbitrary executables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 10:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24798 | WordPress Debug Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24798</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SoniNow Team Debug.This issue affects Debug: from n/a through 1.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52442 | ksmbd: validate session id and tree id in compound request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52442</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: validate session id and tree id in compound request

`smb2_get_msg()` in smb2_get_ksmbd_tcon() and smb2_check_user_session()
will always return the first request smb2 header in a compound request.
if `SMB2_TREE_CONNECT_HE` is the first command in compound request, will
return 0, i.e. The tree id check is skipped.
This patch use ksmbd_req_buf_next() to get current command in compound.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24802 | WordPress JTRT Responsive Tables Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24802</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in John Tendik JTRT Responsive Tables.This issue affects JTRT Responsive Tables: from n/a through 4.1.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52440 | ksmbd: fix slub overflow in ksmbd_decode_ntlmssp_auth_blob()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52440</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix slub overflow in ksmbd_decode_ntlmssp_auth_blob()

If authblob-&gt;SessionKey.Length is bigger than session key
size(CIFS_KEY_SIZE), slub overflow can happen in key exchange codes.
cifs_arc4_crypt copy to session key array from SessionKey from client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52441 | ksmbd: fix out of bounds in init_smb2_rsp_hdr()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52441</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix out of bounds in init_smb2_rsp_hdr()

If client send smb2 negotiate request and then send smb1 negotiate
request, init_smb2_rsp_hdr is called for smb1 negotiate request since
need_neg is set to false. This patch ignore smb1 packets after -&gt;need_neg
is set to false.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24837 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FG PrestaShop, FG Drupal and FG Joomla WordPress plugins </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24837</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Frédéric GILLES FG PrestaShop to WooCommerce, Frédéric GILLES FG Drupal to WordPress, Frédéric GILLES FG Joomla to WordPress.This issue affects FG PrestaShop to WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.44.3; FG Drupal to WordPress: from n/a through 3.67.0; FG Joomla to WordPress: from n/a through 4.15.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24843 | WordPress PowerPack Pro for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt; 2.10.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24843</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PowerPack Addons for Elementor PowerPack Pro for Elementor.This issue affects PowerPack Pro for Elementor: from n/a before 2.10.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24849 | WordPress Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24849</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mark Stockton Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin.This issue affects Quicksand Post Filter jQuery Plugin: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24872 | WordPress Themify Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24872</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Themify Themify Builder.This issue affects Themify Builder: from n/a through 7.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24876 | WordPress Admin Menu Editor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24876</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Janis Elsts Admin Menu Editor.This issue affects Admin Menu Editor: from n/a through 1.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0593 | The Simple Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data| due to insufficient authorization checking on the fe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0593</link><description>The Simple Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data| due to insufficient authorization checking on the fetch_quick_job() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to fetch arbitrary posts, which can be password protected or private and contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1081 | The 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bookmark feature...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1081</link><description>The 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bookmark feature in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25904 | WordPress TinyMCE Professional Formats and Styles Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25904</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in David Stockl TinyMCE and TinyMCE Advanced Professsional Formats and Styles.This issue affects TinyMCE and TinyMCE Advanced Professsional Formats and Styles: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25905 | WordPress Multi Step Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25905</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mondula GmbH Multi Step Form.This issue affects Multi Step Form: from n/a through 1.7.18.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42823 | The issue was resolved by sanitizing logging This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42823</link><description>The issue was resolved by sanitizing logging This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42835 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker may be able to access user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42835</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An attacker may be able to access user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42839 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42839</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42848 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42848</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42853 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42853</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42858 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42858</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42873 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42873</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42878 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42878</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42946 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42946</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42834 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42834</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42836 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42836</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2. An attacker may be able to access connected network volumes mounted in the home directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42838 | An access issue was addressed with improvements to the sandbox. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42838</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improvements to the sandbox. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.2. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code out of its sandbox or with certain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42840 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42840</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42843 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42843</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, Safari 17.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42855 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42855</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An attacker with physical access may be able to silently persist an Apple ID on an erased device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42859 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42859</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42860 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42860</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42877 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42877</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42889 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42889</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42928 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to gain elevated pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42928</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to gain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42939 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user's private browsing activity may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42939</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user's private browsing activity may be unexpectedly saved in the App Privacy Report.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42942 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42942</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, tvOS 17.1, iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.1. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42945 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may gain unauthorized acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42945</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.1. An app may gain unauthorized access to Bluetooth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42951 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user may be unable to delete br...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42951</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. A user may be unable to delete browsing history items.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42952 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42952</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1, macOS Ventura 13.6.3, macOS Sonoma 14.1, macOS Monterey 12.7.1. An app with root privileges may be able to access private information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42953 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42953</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22235 | VMware Aria Operations contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with administrative access to the local system...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22235</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with administrative access to the local system can escalate privileges to 'root'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 05:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1501 | The Database Reset plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.22. This is due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1501</link><description>The Database Reset plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.22. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the install_wpr() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install the WP Reset Plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1562 | The WooCommerce Google Sheet Connector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1562</link><description>The WooCommerce Google Sheet Connector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the execute_post_data function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25151 | The Calendar module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25151</link><description>The Calendar module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions does not escape user supplied data in the default notification email template, which allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the title of a calendar event or the user's name. This may lead to a content spoofing or cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks depending on the capability of the receiver's mail client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25151 | The Calendar module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25151</link><description>The Calendar module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions does not escape user supplied data in the default notification email template, which allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the title of a calendar event or the user's name. This may lead to a content spoofing or cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks depending on the capability of the receiver's mail client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1669 | Out of bounds memory access in Blink in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1669</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in Blink in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1670 | Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1670</link><description>Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1671 | Inappropriate implementation in Site Isolation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1671</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Site Isolation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security policy via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1672 | Inappropriate implementation in Content Security Policy in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1672</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Content Security Policy in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass content security policy via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1673 | Use after free in Accessibility in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1673</link><description>Use after free in Accessibility in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI gestures. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1674 | Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass navigation restrictio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1674</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass navigation restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1675 | Insufficient policy enforcement in Download in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass filesystem restricti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1675</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in Download in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to bypass filesystem restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1676 | Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to spoof security UI via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1676</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 122.0.6261.57 allowed a remote attacker to spoof security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40191 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the instance settings for Accounts in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.44 through 7.4.3.97, and Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40191</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the instance settings for Accounts in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.44 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 update 44 through 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the “Blocked Email Domains” text field</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1108 | The Plugin Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_ini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1108</link><description>The Plugin Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_init() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the settings of the plugin, which can also cause a denial of service due to a misconfiguration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42498 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Language Override edit screen in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.97, and Life...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42498</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Language Override edit screen in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 5, and 7.4 update 4 through 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the _com_liferay_portal_language_override_web_internal_portlet_PLOPortlet_key parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26269 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Frontend JS module's portlet.js in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.37, and Liferay DXP 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26269</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Frontend JS module's portlet.js in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.37, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 38, 7.3 before update 11, 7.2 before fix pack 20, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the anchor (hash) part of a URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26266 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.13, and older unsupported versions, and Lif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26266</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.13, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 10, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allow remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the first/middle/last name text field of the user who creates an entry in the (1) Announcement widget, or (2) Alerts widget.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42496 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the add assignees to a role page in Liferay Portal 7.3.3 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42496</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the add assignees to a role page in Liferay Portal 7.3.3 through 7.4.3.97, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, 7.4 GA through update 92, and 7.3 before update 34 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the _com_liferay_roles_admin_web_portlet_RolesAdminPortlet_tabs2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1631 | agent-js: Insecure Key Generation in `Ed25519KeyIdentity.generate`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1631</link><description>Impact: The library offers a function to generate an ed25519 key pair via Ed25519KeyIdentity.generate with an optional param to provide a 32 byte seed value, which will then be used as the secret key. When no seed value is provided, it is expected that the library generates the secret key using secure randomness. However, a recent change broke this guarantee and uses an insecure seed for key pair generation. Since the private key of this identity (535yc-uxytb-gfk7h-tny7p-vjkoe-i4krp-3qmcl-uqfgr-cpgej-yqtjq-rqe) is compromised, one could lose funds associated with the principal on ledgers or lose access to a canister where this principal is the controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25603 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Dynamic Data Mapping module's DDMForm in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and ol...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25603</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Dynamic Data Mapping module's DDMForm in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the instanceId parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25152 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Message Board widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25152</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Message Board widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the filename of an attachment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25601 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Expando module's geolocation custom fields in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and old...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25601</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Expando module's geolocation custom fields in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the name text field of a geolocation custom field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25602 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Users Admin module's edit user page in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25602</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Users Admin module's edit user page in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into an organization’s “Name” text field</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25147 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HtmlUtil.escapeJsLink in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25147</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HtmlUtil.escapeJsLink in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via crafted javascript: style links.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50923 | In QUIC in RFC 9000, the Latency Spin Bit specification (section 17.4) does not strictly constrain the bit value when the feature is disable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50923</link><description>In QUIC in RFC 9000, the Latency Spin Bit specification (section 17.4) does not strictly constrain the bit value when the feature is disabled, which might allow remote attackers to construct a covert channel with data represented as changes to the bit value. NOTE: The "Sheridan, S., Keane, A. (2015). In Proceedings of the 14th European Conference on Cyber Warfare and Security (ECCWS), University of Hertfordshire, Hatfield, UK." paper says "Modern Internet communication protocols provide an almost infinite number of ways in which data can be hidden or embed whithin seemingly normal network traffic."</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23758 | An issue discovered in Unisys Stealth 5.3.062.0 allows attackers to view sensitive information via the Enterprise ManagementInstaller_msi.lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23758</link><description>An issue discovered in Unisys Stealth 5.3.062.0 allows attackers to view sensitive information via the Enterprise ManagementInstaller_msi.log file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 22:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47422 | An access control issue in /usr/sbin/httpd in Tenda TX9 V1 V22.03.02.54, Tenda AX3 V3 V16.03.12.11, Tenda AX9 V1 V22.03.01.46, and Tenda AX1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47422</link><description>An access control issue in /usr/sbin/httpd in Tenda TX9 V1 V22.03.02.54, Tenda AX3 V3 V16.03.12.11, Tenda AX9 V1 V22.03.01.46, and Tenda AX12 V1 V22.03.01.46 allows attackers to bypass authentication on any endpoint via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 22:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6936 |  Heap-buffer over-read with WOLFSSL_CALLBACKS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6936</link><description>In wolfSSL prior to 5.6.6, if callback functions are enabled (via the WOLFSSL_CALLBACKS flag), then a malicious TLS client or network attacker can trigger a buffer over-read on the heap of 5 bytes (WOLFSSL_CALLBACKS is only intended for debugging).</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26140 | com.yetanalytics/lrs has Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in Statement Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26140</link><description>com.yetanalytics/lrs is the Yet Analytics Core LRS Library. Prior to version 1.2.17 of the LRS library and version 0.7.5 of SQL LRS, a maliciously crafted xAPI statement could be used to perform script or other tag injection in the LRS Statement Browser. The problem is patched in version 1.2.17 of the LRS library and version 0.7.5 of SQL LRS. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23830 | MantisBT Host Header Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23830</link><description>MantisBT is an open source issue tracker. Prior to version 2.26.1, an unauthenticated attacker who knows a user's email address and username can hijack the user's account by poisoning the link in the password reset notification message. A patch is available in version 2.26.1. As a workaround, define `$g_path` as appropriate in `config_inc.php`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26136 | kedi ElectronCord&amp;#x27;s Discord Token is public</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26136</link><description>kedi ElectronCord is a bot management tool for Discord. Commit aaaeaf4e6c99893827b2eea4dd02f755e1e24041 exposes an account access token in the `config.json` file. Malicious actors could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information or perform malicious actions on behalf of the repository owner. As of time of publication, it is unknown whether the owner of the repository has rotated the token or taken other mitigation steps aside from informing users of the situation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-29050 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the terms of use page in Liferay Portal before 7.3.6, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29050</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the terms of use page in Liferay Portal before 7.3.6, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 1, 7.2 before fix pack 11 allows remote attackers to accept the site's terms of use via social engineering and enticing the user to visit a malicious page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-29038 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.5, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before fix pack 1, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29038</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.5, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before fix pack 1, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions does not obfuscate password reminder answers on the page, which allows attackers to use man-in-the-middle or shoulder surfing attacks to steal user's password reminder answers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25428 | SQL Injection vulnerability in MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to run arbitrary system commands via the status parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25428</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to run arbitrary system commands via the status parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46967 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the sanitize function in Enhancesoft osTicket 1.18.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46967</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the sanitize function in Enhancesoft osTicket 1.18.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted support ticket.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49034 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ProjeQtOr 11.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to thec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49034</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ProjeQtOr 11.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to thecheckvalidHtmlText function in the ack.php and security.php files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 20:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25141 | Apache Airflow Mongo Provider: Certificate validation isn&amp;#x27;t respected even if SSL is enabled for apache-airflow-providers-mongo </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25141</link><description>When ssl was enabled for Mongo Hook, default settings included "allow_insecure" which caused that certificates were not validated. This was unexpected and undocumented.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 20:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26135 | MeshCentral cross-site websocket hijacking (CSWSH) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26135</link><description>MeshCentral is a full computer management web site. Versions prior to 1.1.21 a cross-site websocket hijacking (CSWSH) vulnerability within the control.ashx endpoint. This component is the primary mechanism used within MeshCentral to perform administrative actions on the server. The vulnerability is exploitable when an attacker is able to convince a victim end-user to click on a malicious link to a page hosting an attacker-controlled site. The attacker can then originate a cross-site websocket connection using client-side JavaScript code to connect to `control.ashx` as the victim user within MeshCentral. Version 1.1.21 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6565 | The InfiniteWP Client plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.3 via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6565</link><description>The InfiniteWP Client plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.3 via the multi-call backup option. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from a temporary SQL file via repeated GET requests during the limited time window of the backup process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6806 | The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Job Settings user profile fields in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6806</link><description>The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Job Settings user profile fields in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6923 | The Matomo Analytics – Ethical Stats. Powerful Insights. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the idsite...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6923</link><description>The Matomo Analytics – Ethical Stats. Powerful Insights. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the idsite parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0379 | The Custom Twitter Feeds – A Tweets Widget or X Feed Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0379</link><description>The Custom Twitter Feeds – A Tweets Widget or X Feed Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ctf_auto_save_tokens function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the site's twitter API token and secret via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0438 | The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wrapper link parameter in the Age G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0438</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wrapper link parameter in the Age Gate in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0442 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via element URL parameters in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0442</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via element URL parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0506 | The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the $...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0506</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the $instance[alt] parameter in the get_image_alt function in all versions up to, and including, 3.18.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0512 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0512</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the add_to_wishlist function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add items to user wishlists via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0513 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0513</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the remove_from_wishlist function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to remove items from user wishlists via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0514 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0514</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the add_to_compare function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add items to user compare lists via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0515 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0515</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the remove_from_compare function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to remove items from user compare lists via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0516 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post metadata update due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0516</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post metadata update due to a missing capability check on the wpr_update_form_action_meta function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update certain metadata.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0590 | The Microsoft Clarity plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.3. This is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0590</link><description>The Microsoft Clarity plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.3. This is due to missing nonce validation on the edit_clarity_project_id() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the project id and add malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0602 | The YARPP – Yet Another Related Posts Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0602</link><description>The YARPP – Yet Another Related Posts Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 5.30.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0604 | The Best WordPress Gallery Plugin – FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0604</link><description>The Best WordPress Gallery Plugin – FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0616 | The Passster – Password Protect Pages and Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0616</link><description>The Passster – Password Protect Pages and Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.2 via API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain post titles, slugs, IDs, content and other metadata including passwords of password-protected posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0620 | The PPWP – Password Protect Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0620</link><description>The PPWP – Password Protect Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.9 via API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain post titles, IDs, slugs as well as other information including for password-protected posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0621 | The Simple Share Buttons Adder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0621</link><description>The Simple Share Buttons Adder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0656 | The Password Protected – Ultimate Plugin to Password Protect Your WordPress Content with Ease plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0656</link><description>The Password Protected – Ultimate Plugin to Password Protect Your WordPress Content with Ease plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Google Captcha Site Key in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0658 | The Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the user's name when accessing the insert-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0658</link><description>The Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the user's name when accessing the insert-php-code-snippet-manage page in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0702 | The Oliver POS – A WooCommerce Point of Sale (POS) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability check...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0702</link><description>The Oliver POS – A WooCommerce Point of Sale (POS) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several functions hooked via AJAX in the includes/class-pos-bridge-install.php file in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform several unauthorized actions like deactivating the plugin, disconnecting the subscription, syncing the status and more.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0792 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0792</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on RSS feed content. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0821 | The Cost of Goods Sold (COGS): Cost &amp; Profit Calculator for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0821</link><description>The Cost of Goods Sold (COGS): Cost &amp; Profit Calculator for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'section' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0838 | The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the side image URL parameter in the Age...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0838</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the side image URL parameter in the Age Gate in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0978 | The My Private Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.14 via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0978</link><description>The My Private Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.14 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's site privacy feature and view restricted page and post content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0983 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0983</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the enableOptimization function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to enable image optimization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0984 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0984</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the disableOptimization function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to disable the image optimization setting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1043 | The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1043</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'amppb_remove_saved_layout_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.93.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to delete arbitrary posts on the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1044 | The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1044</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'submit_review' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.38.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to submit reviews with arbitrary email addresses regardless of whether reviews are globally enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1054 | The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's &#13;
'wcj_product_barcode' short...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1054</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's &#13;
'wcj_product_barcode' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'color'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1058 | The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the onclick parameter in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1058</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the onclick parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.58.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. 1.58.3 offers a partial fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1070 | The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the features attribute in all versions u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1070</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the features attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.58.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1089 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1089</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the optimizeAllOn function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify image optimization settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1090 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1090</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the stopOptimizeAll function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify image optimization settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1091 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1091</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the reinitialize function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to remove all plugin data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1128 | The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1128</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This is due to insufficient sanitization of HTML input in the Q&amp;A functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Student access and above, to inject arbitrary HTML onto a site, though it does not allow Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1133 | The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of restricted Q&amp;A content due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1133</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of restricted Q&amp;A content due to a missing capability check when interacting with questions in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to interact with questions in courses in which they are not enrolled including private courses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1171 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1171</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery Widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1172 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1172</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1206 | The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'recipes' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1206</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'recipes' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1217 | The Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress – Kali Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin deactivation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1217</link><description>The Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress – Kali Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin deactivation due to a missing capability check on the await_plugin_deactivation function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.41. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to deactivate any active plugins.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1218 | The Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress – Kali Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modificat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1218</link><description>The Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress – Kali Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data via API due to an inconsistent capability check on several REST endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.41. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to obtain access to or modify forms or entries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1235 | The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom class field in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1235</link><description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom class field in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1236 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1236</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Filterable Controls label icon parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1242 | The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button onclick attribute in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1242</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button onclick attribute in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1276 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1276</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Content Ticker arrow attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1277 | The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom fields in all versions up to, and including, 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1277</link><description>The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom fields in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1282 | The Email Encoder – Protect Email Addresses and Phone Numbers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1282</link><description>The Email Encoder – Protect Email Addresses and Phone Numbers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1288 | The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1288</link><description>The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'saswp_reviews_form_render' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.26. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to modify the plugin's stored reCaptcha site and secret keys, potentially breaking the reCaptcha functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1294 | The Sunshine Photo Cart: Free Client Galleries for Photographers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1294</link><description>The Sunshine Photo Cart: Free Client Galleries for Photographers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.24 via the 'invoice'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including customer email and physical addresses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1317 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1317</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘search_key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1318 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1318</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'feedzy_wizard_step_process' and 'import_status' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor access and above, who are normally restricted to only being able to create posts rather than pages, to draft and publish posts with arbitrary content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1322 | The Directorist – WordPress Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1322</link><description>The Directorist – WordPress Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'setup_wizard' function in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to recreate default pages and enable or disable monetization and change map provider.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1334 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1334</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the enableOptimization function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable image optimization via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1335 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1335</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the disableOptimization function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable the image optimization setting via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1336 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1336</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the optimizeAllOn function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify image optimization settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1337 | The SKT Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'saveS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1337</link><description>The SKT Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'saveSktbuilderPageData' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to inject arbitrary content into pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1338 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1338</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the stopOptimizeAll function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify image optimization settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1339 | The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1339</link><description>The ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the reinitialize function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to remove all plugin data via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1340 | The Login Lockdown – Protect Login Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1340</link><description>The Login Lockdown – Protect Login Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the generate_export_file function in all versions up to, and including, 2.08. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and higher, to export this plugin's settings that include whitelisted IP addresses as well as a global unlock key. With the global unlock key an attacker can add their IP address to the whitelist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1349 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for Wor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1349</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1389 | The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1389</link><description>The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pms_stripe_connect_handle_authorization_return function in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the Stripe payment keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1390 | The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1390</link><description>The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the creating_pricing_table_page function in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to create pricing tables.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1408 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1408</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's edit-profile-text-box shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'type'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1411 | The PowerPack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the settings of the Twitter Buttons...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1411</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the settings of the Twitter Buttons Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1425 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for Wor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1425</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Google Calendar Widget Link in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1445 | The Page scroll to id plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1445</link><description>The Page scroll to id plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1447 | The Sydney Toolbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aThemes Slider button element in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1447</link><description>The Sydney Toolbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aThemes Slider button element in all versions up to, and including, 1.25 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied link. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1448 | The Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1448</link><description>The Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.56 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1472 | The WP Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.6 via the REST API. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1472</link><description>The WP Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.6 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's maintenance mode obtain post and page content via REST API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1475 | The Coming Soon Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1475</link><description>The Coming Soon Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain post and page content thus bypassing the protection provided by the plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1492 | The WPify Woo Czech plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the maybe_send_to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1492</link><description>The WPify Woo Czech plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the maybe_send_to_packeta function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain shipping details for orders as long as the order number is known.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1496 | The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the fifu_input_url parameter in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1496</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the fifu_input_url parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1519 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1519</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This requires a member listing page to be active and using the Gerbera theme.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1570 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1570</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's login-password shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1586 | The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom schema in all ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1586</link><description>The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom schema in all versions up to, and including, 1.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. By default the required authentication level is admin, but administrators have the ability to assign role based access to users as low as subscriber.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6247 | The PKCS#7 parser in OpenVPN 3 Core Library versions through 3.8.3 did not properly validate the parsed data, which would result in the appl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6247</link><description>The PKCS#7 parser in OpenVPN 3 Core Library versions through 3.8.3 did not properly validate the parsed data, which would result in the application crashing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0407 | Certain HP Enterprise LaserJet, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0407</link><description>Certain HP Enterprise LaserJet, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers are potentially vulnerable to information disclosure, when connections made by the device back to services enabled by some solutions may have been trusted without the appropriate CA certificate in the device's certificate store.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52436 | f2fs: explicitly null-terminate the xattr list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52436</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: explicitly null-terminate the xattr list

When setting an xattr, explicitly null-terminate the xattr list.  This
eliminates the fragile assumption that the unused xattr space is always
zeroed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52437 | Revert &amp;quot;md/raid5: Wait for MD_SB_CHANGE_PENDING in raid5d&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52437</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "md/raid5: Wait for MD_SB_CHANGE_PENDING in raid5d"

This reverts commit 5e2cf333b7bd5d3e62595a44d598a254c697cd74.

That commit introduced the following race and can cause system hung.

 md_write_start:             raid5d:
 // mddev-&gt;in_sync == 1
 set "MD_SB_CHANGE_PENDING"
                            // running before md_write_start wakeup it
                             waiting "MD_SB_CHANGE_PENDING" cleared
                             &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; hung
 wakeup mddev-&gt;thread
 ...
 waiting "MD_SB_CHANGE_PENDING" cleared
 &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; hung, raid5d should clear this flag
 but get hung by same flag.

The issue reverted commit fixing is fixed by last patch in a new way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52438 | binder: fix use-after-free in shinker&amp;#x27;s callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52438</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

binder: fix use-after-free in shinker's callback

The mmap read lock is used during the shrinker's callback, which means
that using alloc-&gt;vma pointer isn't safe as it can race with munmap().
As of commit dd2283f2605e ("mm: mmap: zap pages with read mmap_sem in
munmap") the mmap lock is downgraded after the vma has been isolated.

I was able to reproduce this issue by manually adding some delays and
triggering page reclaiming through the shrinker's debug sysfs. The
following KASAN report confirms the UAF:

  ==================================================================
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in zap_page_range_single+0x470/0x4b8
  Read of size 8 at addr ffff356ed50e50f0 by task bash/478

  CPU: 1 PID: 478 Comm: bash Not tainted 6.6.0-rc5-00055-g1c8b86a3799f-dirty #70
  Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
  Call trace:
   zap_page_range_single+0x470/0x4b8
   binder_alloc_free_page+0x608/0xadc
   __list_lru_walk_one+0x130/0x3b0
   list_lru_walk_node+0xc4/0x22c
   binder_shrink_scan+0x108/0x1dc
   shrinker_debugfs_scan_write+0x2b4/0x500
   full_proxy_write+0xd4/0x140
   vfs_write+0x1ac/0x758
   ksys_write+0xf0/0x1dc
   __arm64_sys_write+0x6c/0x9c

  Allocated by task 492:
   kmem_cache_alloc+0x130/0x368
   vm_area_alloc+0x2c/0x190
   mmap_region+0x258/0x18bc
   do_mmap+0x694/0xa60
   vm_mmap_pgoff+0x170/0x29c
   ksys_mmap_pgoff+0x290/0x3a0
   __arm64_sys_mmap+0xcc/0x144

  Freed by task 491:
   kmem_cache_free+0x17c/0x3c8
   vm_area_free_rcu_cb+0x74/0x98
   rcu_core+0xa38/0x26d4
   rcu_core_si+0x10/0x1c
   __do_softirq+0x2fc/0xd24

  Last potentially related work creation:
   __call_rcu_common.constprop.0+0x6c/0xba0
   call_rcu+0x10/0x1c
   vm_area_free+0x18/0x24
   remove_vma+0xe4/0x118
   do_vmi_align_munmap.isra.0+0x718/0xb5c
   do_vmi_munmap+0xdc/0x1fc
   __vm_munmap+0x10c/0x278
   __arm64_sys_munmap+0x58/0x7c

Fix this issue by performing instead a vma_lookup() which will fail to
find the vma that was isolated before the mmap lock downgrade. Note that
this option has better performance than upgrading to a mmap write lock
which would increase contention. Plus, mmap_write_trylock() has been
recently removed anyway.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52439 | uio: Fix use-after-free in uio_open</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52439</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

uio: Fix use-after-free in uio_open

core-1				core-2
-------------------------------------------------------
uio_unregister_device		uio_open
				idev = idr_find()
device_unregister(&amp;idev-&gt;dev)
put_device(&amp;idev-&gt;dev)
uio_device_release
				get_device(&amp;idev-&gt;dev)
kfree(idev)
uio_free_minor(minor)
				uio_release
				put_device(&amp;idev-&gt;dev)
				kfree(idev)
-------------------------------------------------------

In the core-1 uio_unregister_device(), the device_unregister will kfree
idev when the idev-&gt;dev kobject ref is 1. But after core-1
device_unregister, put_device and before doing kfree, the core-2 may
get_device. Then:
1. After core-1 kfree idev, the core-2 will do use-after-free for idev.
2. When core-2 do uio_release and put_device, the idev will be double
   freed.

To address this issue, we can get idev atomic &amp; inc idev reference with
minor_lock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26132 | Element Android can be asked to share internal files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26132</link><description>Element Android is an Android Matrix Client. A third-party malicious application installed on the same phone can force Element Android, version 0.91.0 through 1.6.12, to share files stored under the `files` directory in the application's private data directory to an arbitrary room. The impact of the attack is reduced by the fact that the databases stored in this folder are encrypted. However, it contains some other potentially sensitive information, such as the FCM token. Forks of Element Android which have set `android:exported="false"` in the `AndroidManifest.xml` file for the `IncomingShareActivity` activity are not impacted. This issue is fixed in Element Android 1.6.12. There is no known workaround to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37495 | HCL Domino is susceptible to a weak cryptography vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37495</link><description>Internet passwords stored in Person documents in the Domino® Directory created using the "Add Person" action on the People &amp; Groups tab in the Domino® Administrator are secured using a cryptographically weak hash algorithm.  This could enable attackers with access to the hashed value to determine a user's password, e.g. using a brute force attack.  This issue does not impact Person documents created through  user registration https://help.hcltechsw.com/domino/10.0.1/admin/conf_userregistration_c.html .</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52435 | net: prevent mss overflow in skb_segment()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52435</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: prevent mss overflow in skb_segment()

Once again syzbot is able to crash the kernel in skb_segment() [1]

GSO_BY_FRAGS is a forbidden value, but unfortunately the following
computation in skb_segment() can reach it quite easily :

	mss = mss * partial_segs;

65535 = 3 * 5 * 17 * 257, so many initial values of mss can lead to
a bad final result.

Make sure to limit segmentation so that the new mss value is smaller
than GSO_BY_FRAGS.

[1]

general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc000000000e: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN
KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000070-0x0000000000000077]
CPU: 1 PID: 5079 Comm: syz-executor993 Not tainted 6.7.0-rc4-syzkaller-00141-g1ae4cd3cbdd0 #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 11/10/2023
RIP: 0010:skb_segment+0x181d/0x3f30 net/core/skbuff.c:4551
Code: 83 e3 02 e9 fb ed ff ff e8 90 68 1c f9 48 8b 84 24 f8 00 00 00 48 8d 78 70 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 48 89 fa 48 c1 ea 03 &lt;0f&gt; b6 04 02 84 c0 74 08 3c 03 0f 8e 8a 21 00 00 48 8b 84 24 f8 00
RSP: 0018:ffffc900043473d0 EFLAGS: 00010202
RAX: dffffc0000000000 RBX: 0000000000010046 RCX: ffffffff886b1597
RDX: 000000000000000e RSI: ffffffff886b2520 RDI: 0000000000000070
RBP: ffffc90004347578 R08: 0000000000000005 R09: 000000000000ffff
R10: 000000000000ffff R11: 0000000000000002 R12: ffff888063202ac0
R13: 0000000000010000 R14: 000000000000ffff R15: 0000000000000046
FS: 0000555556e7e380(0000) GS:ffff8880b9900000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS: 0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 0000000020010000 CR3: 0000000027ee2000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
&lt;TASK&gt;
udp6_ufo_fragment+0xa0e/0xd00 net/ipv6/udp_offload.c:109
ipv6_gso_segment+0x534/0x17e0 net/ipv6/ip6_offload.c:120
skb_mac_gso_segment+0x290/0x610 net/core/gso.c:53
__skb_gso_segment+0x339/0x710 net/core/gso.c:124
skb_gso_segment include/net/gso.h:83 [inline]
validate_xmit_skb+0x36c/0xeb0 net/core/dev.c:3626
__dev_queue_xmit+0x6f3/0x3d60 net/core/dev.c:4338
dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3134 [inline]
packet_xmit+0x257/0x380 net/packet/af_packet.c:276
packet_snd net/packet/af_packet.c:3087 [inline]
packet_sendmsg+0x24c6/0x5220 net/packet/af_packet.c:3119
sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
__sock_sendmsg+0xd5/0x180 net/socket.c:745
__sys_sendto+0x255/0x340 net/socket.c:2190
__do_sys_sendto net/socket.c:2202 [inline]
__se_sys_sendto net/socket.c:2198 [inline]
__x64_sys_sendto+0xe0/0x1b0 net/socket.c:2198
do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
do_syscall_64+0x40/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b
RIP: 0033:0x7f8692032aa9
Code: 28 00 00 00 75 05 48 83 c4 28 c3 e8 d1 19 00 00 90 48 89 f8 48 89 f7 48 89 d6 48 89 ca 4d 89 c2 4d 89 c8 4c 8b 4c 24 08 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 c7 c1 b8 ff ff ff f7 d8 64 89 01 48
RSP: 002b:00007fff8d685418 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 000000000000002c
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 0000000000000003 RCX: 00007f8692032aa9
RDX: 0000000000010048 RSI: 00000000200000c0 RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 00000000000f4240 R08: 0000000020000540 R09: 0000000000000014
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00007fff8d685480
R13: 0000000000000001 R14: 00007fff8d685480 R15: 0000000000000003
&lt;/TASK&gt;
Modules linked in:
---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
RIP: 0010:skb_segment+0x181d/0x3f30 net/core/skbuff.c:4551
Code: 83 e3 02 e9 fb ed ff ff e8 90 68 1c f9 48 8b 84 24 f8 00 00 00 48 8d 78 70 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 48 89 fa 48 c1 ea 03 &lt;0f&gt; b6 04 02 84 c0 74 08 3c 03 0f 8e 8a 21 00 00 48 8b 84 24 f8 00
RSP: 0018:ffffc900043473d0 EFLAGS: 00010202
RAX: dffffc0000000000 RBX: 0000000000010046 RCX: ffffffff886b1597
RDX: 000000000000000e RSI: ffffffff886b2520 RDI: 0000000000000070
RBP: ffffc90004347578 R0
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6881 | fs: fuse: buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zephyr FS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6881</link><description>Possible buffer overflow in is_mount_point</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26131 | Element Android Intent Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26131</link><description>Element Android is an Android Matrix Client. Element Android version 1.4.3 through 1.6.10 is vulnerable to intent redirection, allowing a third-party malicious application to start any internal activity by passing some extra parameters. Possible impact includes making Element Android display an arbitrary web page, executing arbitrary JavaScript; bypassing PIN code protection; and account takeover by spawning a login screen to send credentials to an arbitrary home server. This issue is fixed in Element Android 1.6.12. There is no known workaround to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52434 | smb: client: fix potential OOBs in smb2_parse_contexts()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52434</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb: client: fix potential OOBs in smb2_parse_contexts()

Validate offsets and lengths before dereferencing create contexts in
smb2_parse_contexts().

This fixes following oops when accessing invalid create contexts from
server:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffff8881178d8cc3
  #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
  PGD 4a01067 P4D 4a01067 PUD 0
  Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
  CPU: 3 PID: 1736 Comm: mount.cifs Not tainted 6.7.0-rc4 #1
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS
  rel-1.16.2-3-gd478f380-rebuilt.opensuse.org 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:smb2_parse_contexts+0xa0/0x3a0 [cifs]
  Code: f8 10 75 13 48 b8 93 ad 25 50 9c b4 11 e7 49 39 06 0f 84 d2 00
  00 00 8b 45 00 85 c0 74 61 41 29 c5 48 01 c5 41 83 fd 0f 76 55 &lt;0f&gt; b7
  7d 04 0f b7 45 06 4c 8d 74 3d 00 66 83 f8 04 75 bc ba 04 00
  RSP: 0018:ffffc900007939e0 EFLAGS: 00010216
  RAX: ffffc90000793c78 RBX: ffff8880180cc000 RCX: ffffc90000793c90
  RDX: ffffc90000793cc0 RSI: ffff8880178d8cc0 RDI: ffff8880180cc000
  RBP: ffff8881178d8cbf R08: ffffc90000793c22 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: ffff8880180cc000 R11: 0000000000000024 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: 0000000000000020 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffffc90000793c22
  FS: 00007f873753cbc0(0000) GS:ffff88806bc00000(0000)
  knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: ffff8881178d8cc3 CR3: 00000000181ca000 CR4: 0000000000750ef0
  PKRU: 55555554
  Call Trace:
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   ? __die+0x23/0x70
   ? page_fault_oops+0x181/0x480
   ? search_module_extables+0x19/0x60
   ? srso_alias_return_thunk+0x5/0xfbef5
   ? exc_page_fault+0x1b6/0x1c0
   ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x26/0x30
   ? smb2_parse_contexts+0xa0/0x3a0 [cifs]
   SMB2_open+0x38d/0x5f0 [cifs]
   ? smb2_is_path_accessible+0x138/0x260 [cifs]
   smb2_is_path_accessible+0x138/0x260 [cifs]
   cifs_is_path_remote+0x8d/0x230 [cifs]
   cifs_mount+0x7e/0x350 [cifs]
   cifs_smb3_do_mount+0x128/0x780 [cifs]
   smb3_get_tree+0xd9/0x290 [cifs]
   vfs_get_tree+0x2c/0x100
   ? capable+0x37/0x70
   path_mount+0x2d7/0xb80
   ? srso_alias_return_thunk+0x5/0xfbef5
   ? _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0x44/0x60
   __x64_sys_mount+0x11a/0x150
   do_syscall_64+0x47/0xf0
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6f/0x77
  RIP: 0033:0x7f8737657b1e</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24474 | QEMU before 8.2.0 has an integer underflow, and resultant buffer overflow, via a TI command when an expected non-DMA transfer length is less...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24474</link><description>QEMU before 8.2.0 has an integer underflow, and resultant buffer overflow, via a TI command when an expected non-DMA transfer length is less than the length of the available FIFO data. This occurs in esp_do_nodma in hw/scsi/esp.c because of an underflow of async_len.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25631 | Unencrypted traffic between pods when using Wireguard and an external kvstore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25631</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. For Cilium users who have enabled an external kvstore and Wireguard transparent encryption, traffic between pods in the affected cluster is not encrypted. This issue affects Cilium v1.14 before v1.14.7 and has been patched in Cilium v1.14.7. There is no workaround to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21678 | This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.&#13;
&#13;
This Stored XSS vulnerability, wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21678</link><description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.&#13;
&#13;
This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
Data Center&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||&#13;
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|&#13;
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|&#13;
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|&#13;
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
Server&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
&#13;
 &#13;
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||&#13;
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |&#13;
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|&#13;
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|&#13;
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|&#13;
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|&#13;
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|&#13;
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|&#13;
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21682 | This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21682</link><description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25630 | Cilium has unencrypted ingress/health traffic when using Wireguard transparent encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25630</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. For Cilium users who are using CRDs to store Cilium state (the default configuration) and Wireguard transparent encryption, traffic to/from the Ingress and health endpoints is not encrypted. This issue affects Cilium v1.14 before v1.14.7 and has been patched in Cilium v1.14.7. There is no workaround to this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22245 | Arbitrary Authentication Relay Vulnerability in Deprecated EAP Browser Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22245</link><description>Arbitrary Authentication Relay and Session Hijack vulnerabilities in the deprecated VMware Enhanced Authentication Plug-in (EAP) could allow a malicious actor that could trick a target domain user with EAP installed in their web browser into requesting and relaying service tickets for arbitrary Active Directory Service Principal Names (SPNs).</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22250 | Session Hijack Vulnerability in Deprecated EAP Browser Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22250</link><description>Session Hijack vulnerability in Deprecated VMware Enhanced Authentication Plug-in could allow a malicious actor with unprivileged local access to a windows operating system can hijack a privileged EAP session when initiated by a privileged domain user on the same system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24763 | JumpServer Open Redirect Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24763</link><description>JumpServer is an open source bastion host and an operation and maintenance security audit system. Prior to version 3.10.0, attackers can exploit this vulnerability to construct malicious links, leading users to click on them, thereby facilitating phishing attacks or cross-site scripting attacks. Version 3.10.0 contains a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51447 | Decidim vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) in the dynamic file uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51447</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.27.0 and prior to versions 0.27.5 and 0.28.0, the dynamic file upload feature is subject to potential cross-site scripting attacks in case the attacker manages to modify the file names of the records being uploaded to the server. This appears in sections where the user controls the file upload dialogs themselves and has the technical knowledge to change the file names through the dynamic upload endpoint. Therefore I believe it would require the attacker to control the whole session of the particular user but in any case, this needs to be fixed. Successful exploit of this vulnerability would require the user to have successfully uploaded a file blob to the server with a malicious file name and then have the possibility to direct the other user to the edit page of the record where the attachment is attached. The users are able to craft the direct upload requests themselves controlling the file name that gets stored to the database. The attacker is able to change the filename e.g. to `&lt;svg onload=alert('XSS')&gt;` if they know how to craft these requests themselves. And then enter the returned blob ID to the form inputs manually by modifying the edit page source. Versions 0.27.5 and 0.28.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable dynamic uploads for the instance, e.g. from proposals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48220 | Decidim&amp;#x27;s devise_invitable gem vulnerable to circumvention of invitation token expiry period</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48220</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.4.rc3 and prior to version 2.0.9 of the `devise_invitable` gem, the invites feature allows users to accept the invitation for an unlimited amount of time through the password reset functionality. This issue creates vulnerable dependencies starting in version 0.0.1.alpha3 and prior to versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 of the `decidim,` `decidim-admin`, and `decidim-system` gems. When using the password reset functionality, the `devise_invitable` gem always accepts the pending invitation if the user has been invited. The only check done is if the user has been invited but the code does not ensure that the pending invitation is still valid as defined by the `invite_for` expiry period. Decidim sets this configuration to `2.weeks` so this configuration should be respected. The bug is in the `devise_invitable` gem and should be fixed there and the dependency should be upgraded in Decidim once the fix becomes available. `devise_invitable` to version `2.0.9` and above fix this issue. Versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 of the `decidim,` `decidim-admin`, and `decidim-system` gems contain this fix. As a workaround, invitations can be cancelled directly from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0794 | Certain LaserJet Pro, HP Enterprise LaserJet, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Buffer Overflow, Potential Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0794</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP Enterprise LaserJet, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers are potentially vulnerable to Remote Code Execution due to buffer overflow when rendering fonts embedded in a PDF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25260 | elfutils v0.189 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the handle_verdef() function at readelf.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25260</link><description>elfutils v0.189 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the handle_verdef() function at readelf.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22054 | A malformed discovery packet sent by a malicious actor with preexisting access to the network could interrupt the functionality of device ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22054</link><description>A malformed discovery packet sent by a malicious actor with preexisting access to the network could interrupt the functionality of device management and discovery.

 

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Access Points

UniFi Switches

UniFi LTE Backup

UniFi Express (Only Mesh Mode, Router mode is not affected)

  

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Access Points to Version 6.6.65 or later.

Update UniFi Switches to Version 6.6.61 or later.

Update UniFi LTE Backup to Version 6.6.57 or later.

Update UniFi Express to Version 3.2.5 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47635 | Decidim vulnerable to possible CSRF attack at questionnaire templates preview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47635</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.23.0 and prior to versions 0.27.5 and 0.28.0, the CSRF authenticity token check is disabled for the questionnaire templates preview. The issue does not imply a serious security thread as you need to have access also to the session cookie in order to see this resource. This URL does not allow modifying the resource but it may allow attackers to gain access to information which was not meant to be public. The issue is fixed in version 0.27.5 and 0.28.0. As a workaround, disable the templates functionality or remove all available templates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47634 | Decidim has race condition in Endorsements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47634</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.10.0 and prior to versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0, a race condition in the endorsement of resources (for instance, a proposal) allows a user to make more than once endorsement. To exploit this vulnerability, the request to set an endorsement must be sent several times in parallel. Versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable the Endorsement feature in the components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25262 | texlive-bin commit c515e was discovered to contain heap buffer overflow via the function ttfLoadHDMX:ttfdump. This vulnerability allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25262</link><description>texlive-bin commit c515e was discovered to contain heap buffer overflow via the function ttfLoadHDMX:ttfdump. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted TTF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21722 | [20240201] - Core - Insufficient session expiration in MFA management views</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21722</link><description>The MFA management features did not properly terminate existing user sessions when a user's MFA methods have been modified.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21723 | [20240202] - Core - Open redirect in installation application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21723</link><description>Inadequate parsing of URLs could result into an open redirect.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21724 | [20240203] - Core - XSS in media selection fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21724</link><description>Inadequate input validation for media selection fields lead to XSS vulnerabilities in various extensions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21725 | [20240204] - Core - XSS in mail address outputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21725</link><description>Inadequate escaping of mail addresses lead to XSS vulnerabilities in various components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21726 | [20240205] - Core - Inadequate content filtering within the filter code </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21726</link><description>Inadequate content filtering leads to XSS vulnerabilities in various components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1470 | Elevation of Privilege attack on NetIQ Client login extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1470</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in NetIQ (OpenText) Client Login Extension on Windows allows Privilege Escalation, Code Injection.This issue 

only 

affects NetIQ Client Login Extension: 4.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21795 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the .egi parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21795</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the .egi parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .egi file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21812 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21812</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .famos file can lead to an out-of-bounds write which in turn can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22097 | A double-free vulnerability exists in the BrainVision Header Parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig Master Branch (ab0ee111) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22097</link><description>A double-free vulnerability exists in the BrainVision Header Parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig Master Branch (ab0ee111) and 2.5.0. A specially crafted .vdhr file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23305 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the BrainVisionMarker Parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23305</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the BrainVisionMarker Parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .vmrk file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23310 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23310</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .famos file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23313 | An integer underflow vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23313</link><description>An integer underflow vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .famos file can lead to an out-of-bounds write which in turn can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23606 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23606</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the sopen_FAMOS_read functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .famos file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23809 | A double-free vulnerability exists in the BrainVision ASCII Header Parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Br...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23809</link><description>A double-free vulnerability exists in the BrainVision ASCII Header Parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 2.5.0 and Master Branch (ab0ee111). A specially crafted .vdhr file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25366 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in mz-automation.de libiec61859 v.1.4.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mmsServe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25366</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in mz-automation.de libiec61859 v.1.4.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mmsServer_handleGetNameListRequest function to the mms_getnamelist_service component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25274 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /sysFile/upload of Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25274</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /sysFile/upload of Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22369 | Apache Camel: Camel-SQL: Unsafe Deserialization from JDBCAggregationRepository</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22369</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel SQL ComponentThis issue affects Apache Camel: from 3.0.0 before 3.21.4, from 3.22.0 before 3.22.1, from 4.0.0 before 4.0.4, from 4.1.0 before 4.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.4.0, which fixes the issue. If users are on the 4.0.x LTS releases stream, then they are suggested to upgrade to 4.0.4. If users are on 3.x, they are suggested to move to 3.21.4 or 3.22.1</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23114 | Apache Camel: Camel-CassandraQL: Unsafe Deserialization from CassandraAggregationRepository</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23114</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel CassandraQL Component AggregationRepository which is vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. Under specific conditions it is possible to deserialize malicious payload.This issue affects Apache Camel: from 3.0.0 before 3.21.4, from 3.22.0 before 3.22.1, from 4.0.0 before 4.0.4, from 4.1.0 before 4.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.4.0, which fixes the issue. If users are on the 4.0.x LTS releases stream, then they are suggested to upgrade to 4.0.4. If users are on 3.x, they are suggested to move to 3.21.4 or 3.22.1</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:10:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38562 | A double-free vulnerability exists in the IP header loopback parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-TCP-IP v3.06.01. A specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38562</link><description>A double-free vulnerability exists in the IP header loopback parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-TCP-IP v3.06.01. A specially crafted set of network packets can lead to memory corruption, potentially resulting in code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39540 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the ICMP and ICMPv6 parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-TCP-IP v3.06.01. A specially cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39540</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the ICMP and ICMPv6 parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-TCP-IP v3.06.01. A specially crafted network packet can lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns a denial of service within the parsing an IPv4 ICMP packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39541 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the ICMP and ICMPv6 parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-TCP-IP v3.06.01. A specially cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39541</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the ICMP and ICMPv6 parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-TCP-IP v3.06.01. A specially crafted network packet can lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability concerns a denial of service within the parsing an IPv6 ICMPv6 packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45318 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP git commit 80d4004. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45318</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP git commit 80d4004. A specially crafted network packet can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22824 | An issue in Timo v.2.0.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the filetype restrictions in the UploadController.java compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22824</link><description>An issue in Timo v.2.0.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the filetype restrictions in the UploadController.java component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1156 | Incorrect directory permissions for the shared NI RabbitMQ service may allow a local authenticated user to read RabbitMQ configuration infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1156</link><description>Incorrect directory permissions for the shared NI RabbitMQ service may allow a local authenticated user to read RabbitMQ configuration information and potentially enable escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1155 | Incorrect permissions for shared NI SystemLink Elixir based services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1155</link><description>Incorrect permissions in the installation directories for shared SystemLink Elixir based services may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50306 | IBM Common Licensing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50306</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0 could allow a local user to enumerate usernames due to an observable response discrepancy.  IBM X-Force ID:  273337.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26270 | The Account Settings page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.76 through 7.4.3.99, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 5, and 7.4 update 76 through 92 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26270</link><description>The Account Settings page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.76 through 7.4.3.99, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 5, and 7.4 update 76 through 92 embeds the user’s hashed password in the page’s HTML source, which allows man-in-the-middle attackers to steal a user's hashed password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25196 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the nav2_controll...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25196</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the nav2_controller process. This vulnerability is triggerd via sending a crafted .yaml file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25197 | Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the isCu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25197</link><description>Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions were discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the isCurrent() function at /src/layered_costmap.cpp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25198 | Inappropriate pointer order of laser_scan_filter_.reset() and tf_listener_.reset() (amcl_node.cpp) in Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25198</link><description>Inappropriate pointer order of laser_scan_filter_.reset() and tf_listener_.reset() (amcl_node.cpp) in Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions leads to a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25199 | Inappropriate pointer order of map_sub_ and map_free(map_) (amcl_node.cpp) in Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25199</link><description>Inappropriate pointer order of map_sub_ and map_free(map_) (amcl_node.cpp) in Open Robotics Robotic Operating Sytstem 2 (ROS2) and Nav2 humble versions leads to a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42791 | A relative path traversal in Fortinet FortiManager version 7.4.0 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.3 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.8 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.12 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42791</link><description>A relative path traversal in Fortinet FortiManager version 7.4.0 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.3 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.8 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.12 and 6.2.0 through 6.2.11 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1546 | When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1546</link><description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1547 | Through a series of API calls and redirects, an attacker-controlled alert dialog could have been displayed on another website (with the vict...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1547</link><description>Through a series of API calls and redirects, an attacker-controlled alert dialog could have been displayed on another website (with the victim website's URL shown). This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1548 | A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1548</link><description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1549 | If a website set a large custom cursor, portions of the cursor could have overlapped with the permission dialog, potentially resulting in us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1549</link><description>If a website set a large custom cursor, portions of the cursor could have overlapped with the permission dialog, potentially resulting in user confusion and unexpected granted permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1550 | A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-pos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1550</link><description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1551 | Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type respon...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1551</link><description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1552 | Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1552</link><description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1553 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122, Firefox ESR 115.7, and Thunderbird 115.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1553</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122, Firefox ESR 115.7, and Thunderbird 115.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1554 | The `fetch()` API and navigation incorrectly shared the same cache, as the cache key did not include the optional headers `fetch()` may cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1554</link><description>The `fetch()` API and navigation incorrectly shared the same cache, as the cache key did not include the optional headers `fetch()` may contain.  Under the correct circumstances, an attacker may have been able to poison the local browser cache by priming it with a `fetch()` response controlled by the additional headers. Upon navigation to the same URL, the user would see the cached response instead of the expected response. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1555 | When opening a website using the `firefox://` protocol handler, SameSite cookies were not properly respected. This vulnerability affects Fir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1555</link><description>When opening a website using the `firefox://` protocol handler, SameSite cookies were not properly respected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1556 | The incorrect object was checked for NULL in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *No...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1556</link><description>The incorrect object was checked for NULL in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1557 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1557</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26268 | User enumeration vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26268</link><description>User enumeration vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before update 8, 7.2 before fix pack 20, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to determine if an account exist in the application by comparing the request's response time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26267 | In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.25, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 26, 7.3 before update 5, 7.2 bef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26267</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.25, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 26, 7.3 before update 5, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions the default value of the portal property `http.header.version.verbosity` is set to `full`, which allows remote attackers to easily identify the version of the application that is running and the vulnerabilities that affect that version via 'Liferay-Portal` response header.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52433 | netfilter: nft_set_rbtree: skip sync GC for new elements in this transaction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52433</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_set_rbtree: skip sync GC for new elements in this transaction

New elements in this transaction might expired before such transaction
ends. Skip sync GC for such elements otherwise commit path might walk
over an already released object. Once transaction is finished, async GC
will collect such expired element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26265 | The Image Uploader module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 16, 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26265</link><description>The Image Uploader module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 16, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions relies on a request parameter to limit the size of files that can be uploaded, which allows remote authenticated users to upload arbitrarily large files to the system's temp folder by modifying the `maxFileSize` parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26581 | netfilter: nft_set_rbtree: skip end interval element from gc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26581</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_set_rbtree: skip end interval element from gc

rbtree lazy gc on insert might collect an end interval element that has
been just added in this transactions, skip end interval elements that
are not yet active.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25610 | In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25610</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions, the default configuration does not sanitize blog entries of JavaScript, which allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML (XSS) via a crafted payload injected into a blog entry’s content text field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1661 | Totolink X6000R shadow hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1661</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254179. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7245 | The nodejs framework in OpenVPN Connect 3.0 through 3.4.3 (Windows)/3.4.7 (macOS) was not properly configured, which allows a local user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7245</link><description>The nodejs framework in OpenVPN Connect 3.0 through 3.4.3 (Windows)/3.4.7 (macOS) was not properly configured, which allows a local user to execute arbitrary code within the nodejs process context via the ELECTRON_RUN_AS_NODE environment variable</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24793 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24793</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafted DICOM file can cause premature freeing of memory that is used later. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker would need to induce the vulnerable application to process a malicious DICOM image.The Use-After-Free happens in the `parse_meta_element_create()` parsing the elements in the File Meta Information header.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24794 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24794</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the DICOM Element Parsing as implemented in Imaging Data Commons libdicom 1.0.5. A specially crafted DICOM file can cause premature freeing of memory that is used later. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker would need to induce the vulnerable application to process a malicious DICOM image.The Use-After-Free happens in the `parse_meta_sequence_end()` parsing the Sequence Value Represenations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50270 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Session do not expire after password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50270</link><description>Session Fixation Apache DolphinScheduler before version 3.2.0, which session is still valid after the password change.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51770 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51770</link><description>Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49109 | Remote Code Execution in Apache Dolphinscheduler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49109</link><description>Exposure of Remote Code Execution in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49250 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Insecure TLS TrustManager used in HttpUtil</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49250</link><description>Because the HttpUtils class did not verify certificates, an attacker that could perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack on outgoing https connections could impersonate the server.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25609 | HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25609</link><description>HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.12, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 9, 7.3 service pack 3, 7.2 fix pack 15 through 18, and older unsupported versions can be circumvented by using two forward slashes, which allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the (1) 'redirect` parameter (2) `FORWARD_URL` parameter, and (3) others parameters that rely on HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect. This vulnerability is the result of an incomplete fix in CVE-2022-28977.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25608 | HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.18, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 19, 7.3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25608</link><description>HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.18, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 19, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions can be circumvented by using the 'REPLACEMENT CHARACTER' (U+FFFD), which allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the (1) 'redirect` parameter (2) `FORWARD_URL` parameter, (3) `noSuchEntryRedirect` parameter, and (4) others parameters that rely on HtmlUtil.escapeRedirect.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25607 | The default password hashing algorithm (PBKDF2-HMAC-SHA1) in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Life...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25607</link><description>The default password hashing algorithm (PBKDF2-HMAC-SHA1) in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 16, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions defaults to a low work factor, which allows attackers to quickly crack password hashes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1608 | OPPO Usercenter Credit sdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1608</link><description>In OPPO Usercenter Credit SDK, there's a possible escalation of privilege due to loose permission check, This could lead to application internal information leak w/o user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25606 | XXE vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.7, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 4, 7.3 before u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25606</link><description>XXE vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.7, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 4, 7.3 before update 12, 7.2 before fix pack 20, and older unsupported versions allows attackers with permission to deploy widgets/portlets/extensions to obtain sensitive information or consume system resources via the Java2WsddTask._format method.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25605 | The Journal module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25605</link><description>The Journal module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions grants guest users view permission to web content templates by default, which allows remote attackers to view any template via the UI or API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25604 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25604</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.4, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4.13, 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions does not properly check user permissions, which allows remote authenticated users with the VIEW user permission to edit their own permission via the User and Organizations section of the Control Panel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25150 | Information disclosure vulnerability in the Control Panel in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25150</link><description>Information disclosure vulnerability in the Control Panel in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.2, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to obtain a user's full name from the page's title by enumerating user screen names.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25973 | Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25973</link><description>The Frentix GmbH OpenOlat LMS is affected by multiple stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. An attacker with rights to create or edit groups can create a course with a name that contains an XSS payload. Furthermore, attackers with the permissions to create or rename a catalog (sub-category) can enter unfiltered input in the name field. In addition, attackers who are allowed to create curriculums can also enter unfiltered input in the name field. This allows an attacker to execute stored JavaScript code with the permissions of the victim in the context of the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25974 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) within the Media Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25974</link><description>The Frentix GmbH OpenOlat LMS is affected by stored a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. It is possible to upload files within the Media Center of OpenOlat version 18.1.5 (or lower) as an authenticated user without any other rights. Although the filetypes are limited, an SVG image containing an XSS payload can be uploaded. After a successful upload the file can be shared with groups of users (including admins) who can be attacked with the JavaScript payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 08:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22234 | CVE-2024-22234: Broken Access Control in Spring Security With Direct Use of isFullyAuthenticated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22234</link><description>In Spring Security, versions 6.1.x prior to 6.1.7 and versions 6.2.x prior to 6.2.2, an application is vulnerable to broken access control when it directly uses the AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated(Authentication) method.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable if:

  *  The application uses AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated(Authentication) directly and a null authentication parameter is passed to it resulting in an erroneous true return value.


An application is not vulnerable if any of the following is true:

  *  The application does not use AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated(Authentication) directly.
  *  The application does not pass null to AuthenticationTrustResolver.isFullyAuthenticated
  *  The application only uses isFullyAuthenticated via  Method Security https://docs.spring.io/spring-security/reference/servlet/authorization/method-security.html  or  HTTP Request Security https://docs.spring.io/spring-security/reference/servlet/authorization/authorize-http-requests.html</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25149 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25149</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions does not properly restrict membership of a child site when the "Limit membership to members of the parent site" option is enabled, which allows remote authenticated users to add users who are not a member of the parent site to a child site. The added user may obtain permission to perform unauthorized actions in the child site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44308 | Open redirect vulnerability in adaptive media administration page in Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44308</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in adaptive media administration page in Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_adaptive_media_web_portlet_AMPortlet_redirect parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5190 | Open redirect vulnerability in the Countries Management’s edit region page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.45 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5190</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability in the Countries Management’s edit region page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.45 through 7.4.3.101, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3 before patch 6, and 7.4 update 45 through 92 allows remote attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external URLs via the _com_liferay_address_web_internal_portlet_CountriesManagementAdminPortlet_redirect parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45320 | Liferay Portal before 7.4.3.16 and Liferay DXP before 7.2 fix pack 19, 7.3 before update 6, and 7.4 before update 16 allow remote authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45320</link><description>Liferay Portal before 7.4.3.16 and Liferay DXP before 7.2 fix pack 19, 7.3 before update 6, and 7.4 before update 16 allow remote authenticated users to become the owner of a wiki page by editing the wiki page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 04:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1559 | The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'll_reciprocal' parameter in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1559</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'll_reciprocal' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 03:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1510 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_tooltip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1510</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_tooltip shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes and user supplied tags. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6764 | A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6764</link><description>A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an attacker to achieve unauthorized remote code execution by sending a sequence of specially crafted payloads containing an invalid pointer; however, such an attack would require detailed knowledge of an affected device’s memory layout and configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6399 | A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6399</link><description>A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1 could allow an authenticated IPSec VPN user to cause DoS conditions against the “deviceid” daemon by sending a crafted hostname to an affected device if it has the “Device Insight” feature enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6398 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6398</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, 

USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1,

NWA50AX firmware versions through 6.29(ABYW.3), WAC500 firmware versions through 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware versions through 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware versions through 6.65(ACGG.1) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via FTP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21890 | The Node.js Permission Model does not clarify in the documentation that wildcards should be only used as the last character of a file path. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21890</link><description>The Node.js Permission Model does not clarify in the documentation that wildcards should be only used as the last character of a file path. For example:
```
 --allow-fs-read=/home/node/.ssh/*.pub
```

will ignore `pub` and give access to everything after `.ssh/`.

This misleading documentation affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21891 | Node.js depends on multiple built-in utility functions to normalize paths provided to node:fs functions, which can be overwitten with user-d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21891</link><description>Node.js depends on multiple built-in utility functions to normalize paths provided to node:fs functions, which can be overwitten with user-defined implementations leading to filesystem permission model bypass through path traversal attack.
This vulnerability affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.
Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21892 | On Linux, Node.js ignores certain environment variables if those may have been set by an unprivileged user while the process is running with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21892</link><description>On Linux, Node.js ignores certain environment variables if those may have been set by an unprivileged user while the process is running with elevated privileges with the only exception of CAP_NET_BIND_SERVICE.
Due to a bug in the implementation of this exception, Node.js incorrectly applies this exception even when certain other capabilities have been set.
This allows unprivileged users to inject code that inherits the process's elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21896 | The permission model protects itself against path traversal attacks by calling path.resolve() on any paths given by the user. If the path is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21896</link><description>The permission model protects itself against path traversal attacks by calling path.resolve() on any paths given by the user. If the path is to be treated as a Buffer, the implementation uses Buffer.from() to obtain a Buffer from the result of path.resolve(). By monkey-patching Buffer internals, namely, Buffer.prototype.utf8Write, the application can modify the result of path.resolve(), which leads to a path traversal vulnerability.
This vulnerability affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.
Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22019 | A vulnerability in Node.js HTTP servers allows an attacker to send a specially crafted HTTP request with chunked encoding, leading to resour...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22019</link><description>A vulnerability in Node.js HTTP servers allows an attacker to send a specially crafted HTTP request with chunked encoding, leading to resource exhaustion and denial of service (DoS). The server reads an unbounded number of bytes from a single connection, exploiting the lack of limitations on chunk extension bytes. The issue can cause CPU and network bandwidth exhaustion, bypassing standard safeguards like timeouts and body size limits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6397 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6397</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow a LAN-based attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by downloading a crafted RAR compressed file onto a LAN-side host if the firewall has the “Anti-Malware” feature enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0715 | EL Injection Vulnerability in Hitachi Global Link Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0715</link><description>Expression Language Injection vulnerability in Hitachi Global Link Manager on Windows allows Code Injection.This issue affects Hitachi Global Link Manager: before 8.8.7-03.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1647 | pyhtml2pdf 0.0.6 - Local File Read via Server Side XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1647</link><description>Pyhtml2pdf version 0.0.6 allows an external attacker to remotely obtain

arbitrary local files. This is possible because the application does not

validate the HTML content entered by the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1648 | electron-pdf 20.0.0 - Local File Read via Server Side XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1648</link><description>electron-pdf version 20.0.0 allows an external attacker to remotely obtain

arbitrary local files. This is possible because the application does not

validate the HTML content entered by the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>