<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:52:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6716 | Libtiff: libtiff: out-of-memory issue in tiffreadencodedstrip() may lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6716</link><description>A flaw was found in libtiff. This flaw allows an attacker to create a crafted tiff file, forcing libtiff to allocate memory indefinitely. This issue can result in a denial of service of the system consuming libtiff due to memory starvation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38495 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager User Enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38495</link><description>A specific authentication strategy allows a malicious attacker to learn ids of all PAM users defined in its database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38496 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38496</link><description>The vulnerability allows a malicious low-privileged PAM user to access information about other PAM users and their group memberships.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38493 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Reflected Cross Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38493</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the PAM UI web interface. A remote attacker able to convince a PAM user to click on a specially crafted link to the PAM UI web interface could potentially execute arbitrary client-side code in the context of PAM UI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38494 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Remote Command Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38494</link><description>This vulnerability allows a high-privileged authenticated PAM user to achieve remote command execution on the affected PAM system by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38491 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38491</link><description>The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38492 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Remote Command Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38492</link><description>This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote command execution on the affected PAM system by uploading a specially crafted PAM upgrade file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36458 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36458</link><description>The vulnerability allows a malicious low-privileged PAM user to perform server upgrade related actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36457 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Authentication Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36457</link><description>The vulnerability allows an attacker to bypass the authentication requirements for a specific PAM endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36455 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Remote Command Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36455</link><description>An improper input validation allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote command execution on the affected PAM system by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36456 | Symantec Privileged Access Manager Remote Command Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36456</link><description>This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote command execution on the affected PAM system by uploading a specially crafted PAM upgrade file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6689 | Local privilege escalation vulnerability in baramundi Management Agent via MSI Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6689</link><description>Local Privilege Escalation in MSI-Installer in baramundi Management Agent v23.1.172.0 on Windows allows a local unprivileged user to escalate privileges to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5402 | Mint Workbench I Unquoted Service Path Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5402</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in ABB Mint Workbench.



A local attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain elevated privileges by inserting an executable file in the path of the affected service.


This issue affects Mint Workbench I versions: from 5866 before 5868.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6746 | NaiboWang EasySpider HTTP GET Request server.js path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6746</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in NaiboWang EasySpider 0.6.2 on Windows. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file \EasySpider\resources\app\server.js of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation with the input /../../../../../../../../../Windows/win.ini leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271477 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The code maintainer explains, that this is not a big issue "because the default is that the software runs locally without going through the Internet".</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6745 | code-projects Simple Ticket Booking Login adminauthenticate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6745</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Simple Ticket Booking 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file adminauthenticate.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271476.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6398 | An information disclosure vulnerability in SWG in versions 12.x prior to 12.2.10 and 11.x prior to 11.2.24 allows information stored in a cu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6398</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in SWG in versions 12.x prior to 12.2.10 and 11.x prior to 11.2.24 allows information stored in a customizable block page to be disclosed to third-party websites due to Same Origin Policy Bypass of browsers in certain scenarios. The risk is low, because other recommended default security policies such as URL categorization and GTI are in place in most policies to block access to uncategorized/high risk websites. Any information disclosed depends on how the customers have customized the block pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 09:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41007 | tcp: avoid too many retransmit packets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41007</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: avoid too many retransmit packets

If a TCP socket is using TCP_USER_TIMEOUT, and the other peer
retracted its window to zero, tcp_retransmit_timer() can
retransmit a packet every two jiffies (2 ms for HZ=1000),
for about 4 minutes after TCP_USER_TIMEOUT has 'expired'.

The fix is to make sure tcp_rtx_probe0_timed_out() takes
icsk-&gt;icsk_user_timeout into account.

Before blamed commit, the socket would not timeout after
icsk-&gt;icsk_user_timeout, but would use standard exponential
backoff for the retransmits.

Also worth noting that before commit e89688e3e978 ("net: tcp:
fix unexcepted socket die when snd_wnd is 0"), the issue
would last 2 minutes instead of 4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32945 | LaTeX post content manipulation via renderer state leak across contexts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32945</link><description>Mattermost Mobile Apps versions &lt;=2.16.0 fail to protect against abuse of a globally shared MathJax state which allows an attacker to change the contents of a LateX post, by creating another post with specific  macro definitions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39767 | Spoofed push notifications from malicious server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39767</link><description>Mattermost Mobile Apps versions &lt;=2.16.0 fail to validate that the push notifications received for a server actually came from this serve that which allows a malicious server to send push notifications with another server’s diagnostic ID or server URL and have them show up in mobile apps as that server’s push notifications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6741 | Openfind Mail2000 - HttpOnly flag bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6741</link><description>Openfind's Mail2000 has a vulnerability that allows the HttpOnly flag to be bypassed. Unauthenticated remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability using specific JavaScript code to obtain the session cookie with the HttpOnly flag enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6740 | Openfind Mail2000 - Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6740</link><description>Openfind's Mail2000 does not properly validate email atachments, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject JavaScript code within the attachment and perform Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41916 | Apache Linkis DataSource: DatasourceManager module has a  JDBC parameter judgment logic vulnerability that allows for arbitrary file reading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41916</link><description>In Apache Linkis =1.4.0, due to the lack of effective filtering
of parameters, an attacker configuring malicious Mysql JDBC parameters in the DataSource Manager Module will trigger arbitrary file reading. Therefore, the parameters in the Mysql JDBC URL should be blacklisted. This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out. Versions of Apache Linkis = 1.4.0 will be affected. 
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46801 | Apache Linkis DataSource: DataSource Remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46801</link><description>In Apache Linkis &lt;= 1.5.0, data source management module, when adding Mysql data source, exists remote code execution vulnerability for java version &lt; 1.8.0_241. The deserialization vulnerability exploited through jrmp can inject malicious files into the server and execute them. 

This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out.  We recommend that users upgrade the java version to &gt;= 1.8.0_241. Or users upgrade Linkis to version 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49566 | Apache Linkis DataSource: JDBC Datasource Module with DB2 has JNDI Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49566</link><description>In Apache Linkis &lt;=1.5.0, due to the lack of effective filtering
of parameters, an attacker configuring malicious 

db2

 parameters in the DataSource Manager Module will result in jndi injection. Therefore, the parameters in the DB2 URL should be blacklisted. 

This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out.

 Versions of Apache Linkis 

&lt;=1.5.0

 will be affected.
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23794 | Agents are able to lock the ticket without the &amp;quot;Owner&amp;quot; permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23794</link><description>An incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability in the inline editing functionality of OTRS can lead to privilege escalation. This flaw allows an agent with read-only permissions to gain full access to a ticket. This issue arises in very rare instances when an admin has previously enabled the setting 'RequiredLock' of 'AgentFrontend::Ticket::InlineEditing::Property###Watch' in the system configuration.This issue affects OTRS: 

  *  8.0.X
  *  2023.X
  *  from 2024.X through 2024.4.x</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6540 | Information exlosure in external interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6540</link><description>Improper filtering of fields when using the export function in the ticket overview of the external interface could allow an authorized user to download a list of tickets containing information about tickets of other customers. The problem only occurs if the TicketSearchLegacyEngine has been disabled by the administrator.
This issue affects OTRS: 8.0.X, 2023.X, from 2024.X through 2024.4.x</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6744 | The SMTP Listener of Secure Email Gateway from Cellopoint does not properly validate user input, leading to a Buffer Overflow vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6744</link><description>The SMTP Listener of Secure Email Gateway from Cellopoint does not properly validate user input, leading to a Buffer Overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6743 | AguardNet Space Management System - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6743</link><description>AguardNet's Space Management System does not properly validate user input, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5630 | Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress &amp;lt; 4.3000000024 - Author+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5630</link><description>The Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress plugin before 4.3000000024 does not prevent authors from uploading arbitrary files to the site, which may allow them to upload PHP shells on affected sites.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6072 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.5 - Reflected XSS via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;REQUEST_URI&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6072</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.5 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6073 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.5 - Reflected XSS in Discount Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6073</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6074 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.5 - Reflected XSS in Customer Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6074</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6075 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.5 - Coupon Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6075</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.5 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6076 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.5 - Reflected XSS in Category Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6076</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6289 | WPS Hide Login &amp;lt; 1.9.16.4 - Hidden Login Page Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6289</link><description>The WPS Hide Login WordPress plugin before 1.9.16.4 does not prevent redirects to the login page via the auth_redirect WordPress function, allowing an unauthenticated visitor to access the hidden login page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6742 | AguardNet Space Management System - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6742</link><description>AguardNet Technology's Space Management System does not properly filter user input, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to inject JavaScript and perform Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21513 | Versions of the package langchain-experimental from 0.0.15 and before 0.0.21 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution when retrieving valu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21513</link><description>Versions of the package langchain-experimental from 0.0.15 and before 0.0.21 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution when retrieving values from the database, the code will attempt to call 'eval' on all values. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability and execute arbitrary python code if they can control the input prompt and the server is configured with VectorSQLDatabaseChain.&#13;&#13;**Notes:**&#13;&#13;Impact on the Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the vulnerable component:&#13;&#13;Confidentiality: Code execution happens within the impacted component, in this case langchain-experimental, so all resources are necessarily accessible.&#13;&#13;Integrity: There is nothing protected by the impacted component inherently. Although anything returned from the component counts as 'information' for which the trustworthiness can be compromised.&#13;&#13;Availability: The loss of availability isn't caused by the attack itself, but it happens as a result during the attacker's post-exploitation steps.&#13;&#13;&#13;Impact on the Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the subsequent system:&#13;&#13;As a legitimate low-privileged user of the package (PR:L) the attacker does not have more access to data owned by the package as a result of this vulnerability than they did with normal usage (e.g. can query the DB). The unintended action that one can perform by breaking out of the app environment and exfiltrating files, making remote connections etc. happens during the post exploitation phase in the subsequent system - in this case, the OS.&#13;&#13;AT:P: An attacker needs to be able to influence the input prompt, whilst the server is configured with the VectorSQLDatabaseChain plugin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6739 | Openfind MailGates and MailAudit - Sensitive Cookie Without &amp;#x27;HttpOnly&amp;#x27; Flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6739</link><description>The session cookie in MailGates and MailAudit from Openfind does not have the HttpOnly flag enabled, allowing remote attackers to potentially steal the session cookie via XSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 03:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6738 | WisdomGarden Tronclass - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6738</link><description>The tumbnail API of Tronclass from WisdomGarden lacks proper access control, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to obtain certain specific files by modifying the URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 03:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6737 | 2100 TECHNOLOGY Electronic Official Document Management System - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6737</link><description>The access control in the Electronic Official Document Management System from 2100 TECHNOLOGY  is not properly implemented, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to access the account settings functionality and create an administrator account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39729 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39729</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information from source code that could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  295968.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39735 | IBM Datacap Navigator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39735</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  296002.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39740 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39740</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 displays version information in HTTP requests that could allow an attacker to gather information for future attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  296009.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39741 | IBM Datacap Navigator directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39741</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  296010.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39728 | IBM Datacap Navigator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39728</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  295967.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39731 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39731</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  295970.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39736 | IBM Datacap Navigator HTTP HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39736</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers. This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking. IBM X-Force ID: 296003.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39737 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39737</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  296004.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39739 | IBM Datacap Navigator server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39739</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.  IBM X-Force ID:  296008.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 01:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6736 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System view_employee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file view_employee.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271457 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 01:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6345 | Remote Code Execution in pypa/setuptools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6345</link><description>A vulnerability in the package_index module of pypa/setuptools versions up to 69.1.1 allows for remote code execution via its download functions. These functions, which are used to download packages from URLs provided by users or retrieved from package index servers, are susceptible to code injection. If these functions are exposed to user-controlled inputs, such as package URLs, they can execute arbitrary commands on the system. The issue is fixed in version 70.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6735 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System setgeneral.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file setgeneral.php. The manipulation of the argument sitename/email/mobile/sms/currency leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271456.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 01:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6734 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System templateadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6734</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file templateadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title/msg leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271455.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6733 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System templateedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file templateedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/title/msg leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6732 | SourceCodester Student Study Center Desk Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6732</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Student Study Center Desk Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /sscdms/classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 22:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6731 | SourceCodester Student Study Center Desk Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6731</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Student Study Center Desk Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Master.php?f=save_student. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271449 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 22:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39733 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39733</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  295972.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39732 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39732</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 temporarily stores data from different environments that could be obtained by a malicious user.  IBM X-Force ID:  295791.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 12:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39734 | IBM Datacap Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39734</link><description>IBM Datacap Navigator 9.1.5, 9.1.6, 9.1.7, 9.1.8, and 9.1.9 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.  IBM X-Force ID:  296001.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 12:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52885 | SUNRPC: Fix UAF in svc_tcp_listen_data_ready()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52885</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

SUNRPC: Fix UAF in svc_tcp_listen_data_ready()

After the listener svc_sock is freed, and before invoking svc_tcp_accept()
for the established child sock, there is a window that the newsock
retaining a freed listener svc_sock in sk_user_data which cloning from
parent. In the race window, if data is received on the newsock, we will
observe use-after-free report in svc_tcp_listen_data_ready().

Reproduce by two tasks:

1. while :; do rpc.nfsd 0 ; rpc.nfsd; done
2. while :; do echo "" | ncat -4 127.0.0.1 2049 ; done

KASAN report:

  ==================================================================
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in svc_tcp_listen_data_ready+0x1cf/0x1f0 [sunrpc]
  Read of size 8 at addr ffff888139d96228 by task nc/102553
  CPU: 7 PID: 102553 Comm: nc Not tainted 6.3.0+ #18
  Hardware name: VMware, Inc. VMware Virtual Platform/440BX Desktop Reference Platform, BIOS 6.00 11/12/2020
  Call Trace:
   
   dump_stack_lvl+0x33/0x50
   print_address_description.constprop.0+0x27/0x310
   print_report+0x3e/0x70
   kasan_report+0xae/0xe0
   svc_tcp_listen_data_ready+0x1cf/0x1f0 [sunrpc]
   tcp_data_queue+0x9f4/0x20e0
   tcp_rcv_established+0x666/0x1f60
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x51c/0x850
   tcp_v4_rcv+0x23fc/0x2e80
   ip_protocol_deliver_rcu+0x62/0x300
   ip_local_deliver_finish+0x267/0x350
   ip_local_deliver+0x18b/0x2d0
   ip_rcv+0x2fb/0x370
   __netif_receive_skb_one_core+0x166/0x1b0
   process_backlog+0x24c/0x5e0
   __napi_poll+0xa2/0x500
   net_rx_action+0x854/0xc90
   __do_softirq+0x1bb/0x5de
   do_softirq+0xcb/0x100
   
   
   ...
   

  Allocated by task 102371:
   kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
   kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
   __kasan_kmalloc+0x7b/0x90
   svc_setup_socket+0x52/0x4f0 [sunrpc]
   svc_addsock+0x20d/0x400 [sunrpc]
   __write_ports_addfd+0x209/0x390 [nfsd]
   write_ports+0x239/0x2c0 [nfsd]
   nfsctl_transaction_write+0xac/0x110 [nfsd]
   vfs_write+0x1c3/0xae0
   ksys_write+0xed/0x1c0
   do_syscall_64+0x38/0x90
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x72/0xdc

  Freed by task 102551:
   kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
   kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
   kasan_save_free_info+0x2a/0x50
   __kasan_slab_free+0x106/0x190
   __kmem_cache_free+0x133/0x270
   svc_xprt_free+0x1e2/0x350 [sunrpc]
   svc_xprt_destroy_all+0x25a/0x440 [sunrpc]
   nfsd_put+0x125/0x240 [nfsd]
   nfsd_svc+0x2cb/0x3c0 [nfsd]
   write_threads+0x1ac/0x2a0 [nfsd]
   nfsctl_transaction_write+0xac/0x110 [nfsd]
   vfs_write+0x1c3/0xae0
   ksys_write+0xed/0x1c0
   do_syscall_64+0x38/0x90
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x72/0xdc

Fix the UAF by simply doing nothing in svc_tcp_listen_data_ready()
if state != TCP_LISTEN, that will avoid dereferencing svsk for all
child socket.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 07:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6730 | Nanjing Xingyuantu Technology SparkShop uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nanjing Xingyuantu Technology SparkShop up to 1.1.6. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/Common/uploadFile. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271403.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 02:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6729 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System add_act.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6729</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /control/add_act.php. The manipulation of the argument aname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271402 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 01:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6728 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System typeedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6728</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file typeedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271401 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 01:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6465 | WP Links Page &amp;lt;= 4.9.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Image Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6465</link><description>The WP Links Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wplf_ajax_update_screenshots' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to regenerate the link's thumbnail image.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 11:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2870 | Swift Framework &amp;lt; 2024.04.30 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2870</link><description>The socialdriver-framework WordPress plugin before 2024.04.30 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3026 | WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons &amp;lt; 9.7.8 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3026</link><description>The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons WordPress plugin before 9.7.8 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as editor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3632 | Smart Image Gallery &amp;lt; 1.0.19 - Update/Delete Google API Key via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3632</link><description>The Smart Image Gallery WordPress plugin before 1.0.19 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3710 | Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid &amp;lt; 3.6.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3710</link><description>The Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid WordPress plugin before 3.6.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3751 | Seriously Simple Podcasting &amp;lt; 3.3.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3751</link><description>The Seriously Simple Podcasting WordPress plugin before 3.3.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3753 | Hostel &amp;lt; 1.1.5.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3753</link><description>The Hostel WordPress plugin before 1.1.5.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3919 | OpenPGP Form Encryption for WordPress &amp;lt; 1.5.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3919</link><description>The OpenPGP Form Encryption for WordPress plugin before 1.5.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3963 | RafflePress Lite &amp;lt; 1.12.14 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3963</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress  WordPress plugin before 1.12.14 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as editor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3964 | Product Enquiry for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 3.1.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3964</link><description>The Product Enquiry for WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 3.1.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4217 | Shortcodes Ultimate Pro &amp;lt; 7.1.5 - Contributor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4217</link><description>The shortcodes-ultimate-pro WordPress plugin before 7.1.5 does not properly escape some of its shortcodes' settings, making it possible for attackers with a Contributor account to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4269 | SVG Block &amp;lt; 1.1.20 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4269</link><description>The SVG Block WordPress plugin before 1.1.20 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which enables users with at least the author role to SVG with malicious JavaScript to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4272 | Support SVG &amp;lt; 1.1.0 - Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4272</link><description>The Support SVG  WordPress plugin before 1.1.0 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which enables users with at least the author role to SVG with malicious JavaScript to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4602 | Embed Peertube Playlist &amp;lt; 1.10 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4602</link><description>The Embed Peertube Playlist WordPress plugin before 1.10 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4752 | EventON &amp;lt; 2.2.15 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting via event subtitle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4752</link><description>The EventON WordPress plugin before 2.2.15 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4977 | Index WP MySQL For Speed &amp;lt; 1.4.18 - Admin+ Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4977</link><description>The Index WP MySQL For Speed WordPress plugin before 1.4.18 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5002 | User Submitted Posts  &amp;lt; 20240516 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5002</link><description>The User Submitted Posts  WordPress plugin before 20240516 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5028 | CM WordPress Search And Replace Plugin &amp;lt; 1.3.9 - Plugin Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5028</link><description>The CM WordPress Search And Replace Plugin WordPress plugin before 1.3.9 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5032 | SULly &amp;lt; 4.3.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5032</link><description>The SULly WordPress plugin before 4.3.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5033 | SULly &amp;lt; 4.3.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5033</link><description>The SULly WordPress plugin before 4.3.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5034 | SULly &amp;lt; 4.3.1 - Plugin Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5034</link><description>The SULly WordPress plugin before 4.3.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5074 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5074</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5075 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5075</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5076 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.6 - Bulk Delete via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5076</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.6 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5077 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.6 - Stored XSS in Blacklist via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5077</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5079 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.7 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS via Member Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5079</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.7 does not sanitise and escape some of the fields when members register, which allows unauthenticated users to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5080 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.6 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5080</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.6 does not validate files to be uploaded, which could allow admins to upload arbitrary files such as PHP on the server</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5151 | SULly &amp;lt; 4.3.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5151</link><description>The SULly WordPress plugin before 4.3.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5167 | CM Email Registration Blacklist and Whitelist &amp;lt; 1.4.9 - Add/Delete Emails via CSRF Add and delete any item from blacklist/whitelist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5167</link><description>The CM Email Registration Blacklist and Whitelist WordPress plugin before 1.4.9 does not have CSRF check when adding or deleting an item from the blacklist or whitelist, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin add or delete settings from the blacklist or whitelist menu via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5280 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - POST Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5280</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make non-logged in users execute an XSS payload via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5281 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - Reflected XSS via Affiliate Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5281</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5282 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - Reflected XSS via Registration Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5282</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5283 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - Reflected XSS via Lead Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5283</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5284 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5284</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5286 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - Reflected XSS via Banner Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5286</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5287 | WP Affiliate Platform &amp;lt; 6.5.1 - Profile Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5287</link><description>The wp-affiliate-platform WordPress plugin before 6.5.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in user change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5442 | NextGEN Gallery &amp;lt; 3.59.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5442</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and   WordPress plugin before 3.59.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5450 | Bug Library &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5450</link><description>The Bug Library WordPress plugin before 2.1.1 does not check the file type on user-submitted bug reports, allowing an unauthenticated user to upload PHP files</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5472 | WP QuickLaTeX &amp;lt; 3.8.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Background Color field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5472</link><description>The WP QuickLaTeX WordPress plugin before 3.8.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5575 | Ditty &amp;lt; 3.1.43 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5575</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.43 does not sanitise and escape some of its blocks' settings, which could allow high privilege users such as authors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5627 | WordPress Plugin Tournamatch &amp;lt; 4.6.1 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5627</link><description>The Tournamatch WordPress plugin before 4.6.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as subscriber to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5644 | WordPress Plugin Tournamatch &amp;lt; 4.6.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Ladders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5644</link><description>The Tournamatch WordPress plugin before 4.6.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5713 | if-so &amp;lt; 1.8.0.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5713</link><description>The If-So Dynamic Content Personalization WordPress plugin before 1.8.0.4 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5715 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.7 - Reflected XSS via Member Edit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5715</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5744 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.6.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5744</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.6.7 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6070 | if-so &amp;lt; 1.8.0.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6070</link><description>The If-So Dynamic Content Personalization WordPress plugin before 1.8.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6574 | Laposta &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6574</link><description>The Laposta plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.12. This is due to the plugin not preventing direct access to several test files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website. This plugin is no longer being maintained and has been closed for downloads.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39327 | Openjpeg: malicious files can cause the program to enter a large loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39327</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenJPEG. Maliciously constructed pictures can cause the program to enter a large loop and continuously print warning messages on the terminal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 03:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39329 | Openjpeg: resource exhaustion will occur in the opj_t1_decode_cblks function in the tcd.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39329</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenJPEG. A resource exhaustion can occur in the opj_t1_decode_cblks function in tcd.c through a crafted image file, causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 03:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>