<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:39:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-31970 | AdTran SRG 834-5 HDC17600021F1 devices (with SmartOS 11.1.1.1 and fixed in Version 12.1.3.1) have SSH enabled by default, accessible both ov...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31970</link><description>AdTran SRG 834-5 HDC17600021F1 devices (with SmartOS 11.1.1.1 and fixed in Version 12.1.3.1) have SSH enabled by default, accessible both over the LAN and the Internet. During a window of time when the device is being set up, it uses a default username and password combination of admin/admin with root-level privileges. An attacker can exploit this window to gain unauthorized root access by either modifying the existing admin account or creating a new account with equivalent privileges. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7069 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7069</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /employee_gatepass/classes/Master.php?f=delete_department. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272351.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22444 | A vulnerability within the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow a remote attacker to conduct a refl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22444</link><description>A vulnerability within the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow a remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in a victims browser in the context of the affected interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22443 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22443</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a server-side prototype pollution attack. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31971 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities on AdTran NetVanta 3120 18.01.01.00.E devices allow remote attackers to inject ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31971</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities on AdTran NetVanta 3120 18.01.01.00.E devices allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript, as demonstrated by /mainPassword.html, /processIdentity.html, /public.html, /dhcp.html, /private.html, /hostname.html, /connectivity.html, /NetworkMonitor.html, /trafficMonitoringConfig.html, and /wizardMain.html.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31977 | Adtran 834-5 11.1.0.101-202106231430, and fixed as of SmartOS Version 12.5.5.1, devices allow OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31977</link><description>Adtran 834-5 11.1.0.101-202106231430, and fixed as of SmartOS Version 12.5.5.1, devices allow OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters to the Ping or Traceroute utility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39345 | AdTran 834-5 HDC17600021F1 (SmartOS 11.1.1.1) devices enable the SSH service by default and have a hidden, undocumented, hard-coded support ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39345</link><description>AdTran 834-5 HDC17600021F1 (SmartOS 11.1.1.1) devices enable the SSH service by default and have a hidden, undocumented, hard-coded support account whose password is based on the devices MAC address. All of the devices internet interfaces share a similar MAC address that only varies in their final octet. This allows network-adjacent attackers to derive the support user's SSH password by decrementing the final octet of the connected gateway address or via the BSSID. An attacker can then execute arbitrary OS commands with root-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41914 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41914</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of EdgeConnect SD-WAN Orchestrator could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an administrative user of the interface. A successful exploit allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in a victim's browser in the context of the affected interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7068 | SourceCodester Insurance Management System update_sub_category cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7068</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Insurance Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Script/admin/core/update_sub_category. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272349 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45249 | Remote command execution due to use of default passwords. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45249</link><description>Remote command execution due to use of default passwords. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.0.1-61, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.1.1-71, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.2.1-69, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.3.1-53, Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) before build 5.4.4-132.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6096 | Unsafe Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6096</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Reporting versions prior to 18.1.24.709, a code execution attack is possible through object injection via an insecure type resolution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7067 | kirilkirkov Ecommerce-Laravel-Bootstrap Cart.php getCartProductsIds deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7067</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kirilkirkov Ecommerce-Laravel-Bootstrap up to 1f1097a3448ce8ec53e034ea0f70b8e2a0e64a87. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function getCartProductsIds of the file app/Cart.php. The manipulation of the argument laraCart leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is a02111a674ab49f65018b31da3011b1e396f59b1. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272348.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6327 | Progress Telerik Report Server Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6327</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q2 (10.1.24.709), a remote code execution attack is possible through an insecure deserialization vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3896 | Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 3.2.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Gallery Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3896</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the the Gallery title field in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5818 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.980 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Magazine Grid/Slider Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5818</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Magazine Grid/Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.980 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6896 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.0.96.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6896</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.96.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7066 | F-logic DataCube3 HTTP POST Request config_time_sync.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7066</link><description>A vulnerability was found in F-logic DataCube3 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/config_time_sync.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ntp_server leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272347.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7065 | Spina CMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7065</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Spina CMS up to 2.18.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/pages/. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272346 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3297 | Session establishment lock-up during replay of CASE Sigma1 messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3297</link><description>An issue in the Certificate Authenticated Session Establishment (CASE) protocol for establishing secure sessions between two devices, as implemented in the Matter protocol versions before Matter 1.1 allows an attacker to replay manipulated CASE Sigma1 messages to make the device unresponsive until the device is power-cycled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3454 | In-Fabric Matter Cluster Attribute Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3454</link><description>An implementation issue in the Connectivity Standards Alliance Matter 1.2 protocol as used in the connectedhomeip SDK allows a third party to disclose information about devices part of the same fabric (footprinting), even though the protocol is designed to prevent access to such information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48362 | Apache Drill: XXE Vulnerability in XML Format Reader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48362</link><description>XXE in the XML Format Plugin in Apache Drill version 1.19.0 and greater allows a user to read any file on a remote file system or execute commands via a malicious XML file.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.21.2, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39676 | Apache Pinot: Unauthorized endpoint exposed sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39676</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Pinot.

This issue affects Apache Pinot: from 0.1 before 1.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.0.0 and configure RBAC, which fixes the issue.

Details: 

When using a request to path “/appconfigs” to the controller, it can lead to the disclosure of sensitive information such as system information (e.g. arch, os version), environment information (e.g. maxHeapSize) and Pinot configurations (e.g. zookeeper path). This issue was addressed by the  Role-based Access Control https://docs.pinot.apache.org/operators/tutorials/authentication/basic-auth-access-control , so that /appConfigs` and all other APIs can be access controlled. Only authorized users have access to it. Note the user needs to add the admin role accordingly to the RBAC guide to control access to this endpoint, and in the future version of Pinot, a default admin role is planned to be added.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6874 | macidn punycode buffer overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6874</link><description>libcurl's URL API function
[curl_url_get()](https://curl.se/libcurl/c/curl_url_get.html) offers punycode
conversions, to and from IDN. Asking to convert a name that is exactly 256
bytes, libcurl ends up reading outside of a stack based buffer when built to
use the *macidn* IDN backend. The conversion function then fills up the
provided buffer exactly - but does not null terminate the string.

This flaw can lead to stack contents accidently getting returned as part of
the converted string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6197 | freeing stack buffer in utf8asn1str</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6197</link><description>libcurl's ASN1 parser has this utf8asn1str() function used for parsing an ASN.1 UTF-8 string. Itcan detect an invalid field and return error. Unfortunately, when doing so it also invokes `free()` on a 4 byte localstack buffer.  Most modern malloc implementations detect this error and immediately abort. Some however accept the input pointer and add that memory to its list of available chunks. This leads to the overwriting of nearby stack memory. The content of the overwrite is decided by the `free()` implementation; likely to be memory pointers and a set of flags.  The most likely outcome of exploting this flaw is a crash, although it cannot be ruled out that more serious results can be had in special circumstances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6930 | WP Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bookingform Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6930</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'type' attribute within the plugin's bookingform shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 10.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32471 | Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32471</link><description>Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read contents of stack memory and use this information for further exploits.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32466 | Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with hig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32466</link><description>Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to exposure of some UEFI code, leading to arbitrary code execution or escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6553 | WP Meteor Website Speed Optimization Addon &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6553</link><description>The WP Meteor Website Speed Optimization Addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3.This is due to the plugin utilizing wpdesk and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6571 | Optimize Images ALT Text (alt tag) &amp;amp; names for SEO using AI &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6571</link><description>The Optimize Images ALT Text (alt tag) &amp; names for SEO using AI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1. This is due the plugin utilizing cocur and not preventing direct access to the generate-default.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6629 | All-in-One Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 3.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6629</link><description>The All-in-One Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Video shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6094 | WP ULike &amp;lt; 4.7.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6094</link><description>The WP ULike  WordPress plugin before 4.7.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6836 | Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp;amp; One Click Upsells &amp;lt;= 3.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6836</link><description>The Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp; One Click Upsells plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update multiple settings, including templates, designs, checkouts, and other plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 05:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40767 | In OpenStack Nova before 27.4.1, 28 before 28.2.1, and 29 before 29.1.1, by supplying a raw format image that is actually a crafted QCOW2 im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40767</link><description>In OpenStack Nova before 27.4.1, 28 before 28.2.1, and 29 before 29.1.1, by supplying a raw format image that is actually a crafted QCOW2 image with a backing file path or VMDK flat image with a descriptor file path, an authenticated user may convince systems to return a copy of the referenced file's contents from the server, resulting in unauthorized access to potentially sensitive data. All Nova deployments are affected. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-47951 and CVE-2024-32498.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3246 | LiteSpeed Cache &amp;lt;= 6.2.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3246</link><description>The LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the token setting and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 03:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5861 | WP Easy Pay (Free) &amp;lt;= 4.2.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Service Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5861</link><description>The WP EasyPay – Square for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of datadue to a missing capability check on the wpep_square_disconnect() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disconnect square.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6750 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6750</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete post meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6751 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6751</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete post meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6752 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6752</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wp_name’ parameter in the 'wpw_auto_poster_map_wordpress_post_type' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6753 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6753</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘mapTypes’ parameter in the 'wpw_auto_poster_map_wordpress_post_type' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6754 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Meta Update via wpw_auto_poster_update_tweet_template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6754</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data to a missing capability check on the ‘wpw_auto_poster_update_tweet_template’ function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary post metadata.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6755 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6755</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the ‘wpw_auto_poster_quick_delete_multiple’ function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6756 | Social Auto Poster &amp;lt;= 5.3.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6756</link><description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'wpw_auto_poster_get_image_path' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. An attacker can use CVE-2024-6754 to exploit with subscriber-level access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7027 | WooCommerce - PDF Vouchers &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Authentication Bypass to Voucher Vendor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7027</link><description>The WooCommerce - PDF Vouchers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 4.9.3. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during a QR code login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing Voucher Vendor user on the site, if they have access to the user id.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38164 | GroupMe Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38164</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38176 | GroupMe Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38176</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41656 | Sentry vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41656</link><description>Sentry is an error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Starting in version 10.0.0 and prior to version 24.7.1, an unsanitized payload sent by an Integration platform integration allows storing arbitrary HTML tags on the Sentry side with the subsequent rendering them on the Issues page. Self-hosted Sentry users may be impacted in case of untrustworthy Integration platform integrations sending external issues from their side to Sentry. A patch has been released in Sentry 24.7.1. For Sentry SaaS customers, no action is needed. This has been patched on July 23, and even prior to the fix, the exploitation was not possible due to the strict Content Security Policy deployed on sentry.io site. For self-hosted users, the maintainers of Sentry strongly recommend upgrading Sentry to the latest version. If it is not possible, one could enable CSP on one's self-hosted installation with `CSP_REPORT_ONLY = False` (enforcing mode). This will mitigate the risk of cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0981 | Okta Browser Plugin versions 6.5.0 through 6.31.0 (Chrome/Edge/Firefox/Safari) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This issue occurs whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0981</link><description>Okta Browser Plugin versions 6.5.0 through 6.31.0 (Chrome/Edge/Firefox/Safari) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This issue occurs when the plugin prompts the user to save these credentials within Okta Personal. A fix was implemented to properly escape these fields, addressing the vulnerability. Importantly, if Okta Personal is not added to the plugin to enable multi-account view, the Workforce Identity Cloud plugin is not affected by this issue. The vulnerability is fixed in Okta Browser Plugin version 6.32.0 for Chrome/Edge/Safari/Firefox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41668 | cBioPortal Proxy Endpoint Vulnerabliity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41668</link><description>The cBioPortal for Cancer Genomics provides visualization, analysis, and download of large-scale cancer genomics data sets. When running a publicly exposed proxy endpoint without authentication, cBioPortal could allow someone to perform a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attack. Logged in users could do the same on private instances. A fix has been released in version 6.0.12. As a workaround, one might be able to disable `/proxy` endpoint entirely via, for example, nginx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11640 | Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11640</link><description>AdvaBuild uses a command queue to launch certain operations. An attacker who gains access to the
command queue can use it to launch an attack by running any executable on the AdvaBuild node. The
executables that can be run are not limited to AdvaBuild specific executables. 

Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ABB Advant MOD 300 AdvaBuild.This issue affects Advant MOD 300 AdvaBuild: from 3.0 through 3.7 SP2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11639 | Insufficient access control on Inter process communication,</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11639</link><description>An attacker could exploit the vulnerability by
injecting garbage data or specially crafted data. Depending on the data injected each process might be
affected differently. The process could crash or cause communication issues on the affected node, effectively causing a denial-of-service attack. The attacker could tamper with the data transmitted, causing
the product to store wrong information or act on wrong data or display wrong information.


This issue affects Advant MOD 300 AdvaBuild: from 3.0 through 3.7 SP2.




For an attack to be successful, the attacker must have local access to a node in the system and be able to
start a specially crafted application that disrupts the communication.
An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability would be able to manipulate the data in such
way as allowing reads and writes to the controllers or cause Windows processes in 800xA for MOD 300
and AdvaBuild to crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41661 | reNgine authenticated command injection in WAF detection tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41661</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. In versions 1.2.0 through 2.1.1, an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the WAF detection tool allows an authenticated attacker to remotely execute arbitrary commands as root user. The URL query parameter `url` is passed to `subprocess.check_output` without any sanitization, resulting in a command injection vulnerability. This API endpoint is accessible by authenticated users with any use role. Because the process runs as `root`, an attacker has root access. Commit edd3c85ee16f93804ad38dac5602549d2d30a93e contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41665 | Ampache Stored Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41665</link><description>Ampache, a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager, has a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in versions prior to 6.6.0. This vulnerability exists in the "Playlists - Democratic - Configure Democratic Playlist" feature. An attacker with Content Manager permissions can set the Name field to `&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;`. When any administrator or user accesses the Democratic functionality, they will be affected by this stored XSS vulnerability. The attacker can exploit this vulnerability to obtain the cookies of any user or administrator who accesses the `democratic.php` file. Version 6.6.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41664 | Blind SSRF via Canarytoken Webhook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41664</link><description>Canarytokens help track activity and actions on a network. Prior to `sha-8ea5315`, Canarytokens.org was vulnerable to a blind SSRF in the Webhook alert feature. When a Canarytoken is created, users choose to receive alerts either via email or via a webhook. If a webhook is supplied when a  Canarytoken is first created, the site will make a test request to the supplied URL to ensure it accepts alert notification HTTP requests. No safety checks were performed on the URL, leading to a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability. The SSRF is Blind because the content of the response is not displayed to the creating user; they are simply told whether an error occurred in making the test request. Using the Blind SSRF, it was possible to map out open ports for IPs inside the Canarytokens.org infrastructure. This issue is now patched on Canarytokens.org. Users of self-hosted Canarytokens installations can update by pulling the latest Docker image, or any Docker image after `sha-097d91a`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41178 | Apache Arrow Rust Object Store: AWS WebIdentityToken exposure in log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41178</link><description>Exposure of temporary credentials in logs in Apache Arrow Rust Object Store, version 0.10.1 and earlier on all platforms using AWS WebIdentityTokens. 

On certain error conditions, the logs may contain the OIDC token passed to  AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity https://docs.aws.amazon.com/STS/latest/APIReference/API_AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity.html . This allows someone with access to the logs to impersonate that identity, including performing their own calls to AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity, until the OIDC token expires. Typically OIDC tokens are valid for up to an hour, although this will vary depending on the issuer.

Users are recommended to use a different AWS authentication mechanism, disable logging or upgrade to version 0.10.2, which fixes this issue.

Details:

When using AWS WebIdentityTokens with the object_store crate, in the event of a failure and automatic retry, the underlying reqwest error, including the full URL with the credentials, potentially in the parameters, is written to the logs. 

Thanks to Paul Hatcherian for reporting this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41663 | Canarytoken &amp;quot;Cloned Website&amp;quot; Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41663</link><description>Canarytokens help track activity and actions on a network.  A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability was identified in the "Cloned Website" Canarytoken, whereby the Canarytoken's creator can attack themselves. The creator of a slow-redirect Canarytoken can insert Javascript into the destination URL of their slow redirect token. When the creator later browses the management page for their own Canarytoken, the Javascript executes. This is a self-XSS. An attacker could create a Canarytoken with this self-XSS, and send the management link to a victim. When they click on it, the Javascript would execute. However, no sensitive information (ex. session information) will be disclosed to the malicious actor. This issue is now patched on Canarytokens.org. Users of self-hosted Canarytokens installations can update by pulling the latest Docker image, or any Docker image after `sha-097d91a`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39702 | In lj_str_hash.c in OpenResty 1.19.3.1 through 1.25.3.1, the string hashing function (used during string interning) allows HashDoS (Hash Den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39702</link><description>In lj_str_hash.c in OpenResty 1.19.3.1 through 1.25.3.1, the string hashing function (used during string interning) allows HashDoS (Hash Denial of Service) attacks. An attacker could cause excessive resource usage during proxy operations via crafted requests, potentially leading to a denial of service with relatively few incoming requests. This vulnerability only exists in the OpenResty fork in the openresty/luajit2 GitHub repository. The LuaJIT/LuaJIT epository. is unaffected/</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6714 | An issue was discovered in provd before version 0.1.5 with a setuid binary, which allows a local attacker to escalate their privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6714</link><description>An issue was discovered in provd before version 0.1.5 with a setuid binary, which allows a local attacker to escalate their privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6783 | Vue client-side XSS via prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6783</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Vue, that allows an attacker to perform XSS via prototype pollution. The attacker could change the prototype chain of some properties such as `Object.prototype.staticClass` or `Object.prototype.staticStyle` to execute arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 15:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41655 | TF2 Item Format Regular Expression Denial of Service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41655</link><description>TF2 Item Format helps users format TF2 items to the community standards. Versions of `tf2-item-format` since at least `4.2.6`  and prior to `5.9.14` are vulnerable to a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) attack when parsing crafted user input. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to perform DoS attacks on any service that uses any `tf2-item-format` to parse user input. Version `5.9.14` contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 15:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1975 | SIG(0) can be used to exhaust CPU resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1975</link><description>If a server hosts a zone containing a "KEY" Resource Record, or a resolver DNSSEC-validates a "KEY" Resource Record from a DNSSEC-signed domain in cache, a client can exhaust resolver CPU resources by sending a stream of SIG(0) signed requests.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.49-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41319 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the cmd parameter in the webcmd functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41319</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the cmd parameter in the webcmd function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4076 | Assertion failure when serving both stale cache data and authoritative zone content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4076</link><description>Client queries that trigger serving stale data and that also require lookups in local authoritative zone data may result in an assertion failure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.13 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.33-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.13-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1737 | BIND&amp;#x27;s database will be slow if a very large number of RRs exist at the same name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1737</link><description>Resolver caches and authoritative zone databases that hold significant numbers of RRs for the same hostname (of any RTYPE) can suffer from degraded performance as content is being added or updated, and also when handling client queries for this name.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.4-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40060 | go-chart v2.1.1 was discovered to contain an infinite loop via the drawCanvas() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40060</link><description>go-chart v2.1.1 was discovered to contain an infinite loop via the drawCanvas() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0760 | A flood of DNS messages over TCP may make the server unstable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0760</link><description>A malicious client can send many DNS messages over TCP, potentially causing the server to become unstable while the attack is in progress. The server may recover after the attack ceases. Use of ACLs will not mitigate the attack. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.1 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4080 | Memory Corruption Due to Improper Length Checks in LabVIEW tdcore.dll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4080</link><description>A memory corruption issue due to an improper length check in LabVIEW tdcore.dll may disclose information or result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4081 | Memory Corruption Due to Improper Length Check in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4081</link><description>A memory corruption issue due to an improper length check in NI LabVIEW may disclose information or result in arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4079 | Out of Bounds Read Due to Missing Bounds Check in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4079</link><description>An out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check in LabVIEW may disclose information or result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5602 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in NI I/O Trace Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5602</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability due to a missing bounds check in the NI I/O Trace Tool may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted nitrace file.

The NI I/O Trace tool is installed as part of the NI System Configuration utilities included with many NI software products.  Refer to the NI Security Advisory for identifying the version of NI IO Trace.exe installed. The NI I/O Trace tool was also previously released as NI Spy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34128 | Stored XSS in `libs/granite/ui/components/coral/foundation/clientlibs/foundation/js/form/form.js` via loadingMask</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34128</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41836 | Adobe Indesign 2024 GIF File Parsing Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41836</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID18.5.2, ID19.3 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41839 | HTML Injection in Editor status bar for pages from AEM launches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41839</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could lead to a security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and affect the integrity of the page. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7014 | Improper multimedia file attachment validation in Telegram for Android app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7014</link><description>EvilVideo vulnerability allows sending malicious apps disguised as videos in Telegram for Android application affecting 
 versions 10.14.4 and older.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29070 | Apache StreamPark: session not invalidated after logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29070</link><description>On versions before 2.1.4, session is not invalidated after logout. When the user logged in successfully, the Backend service returns "Authorization" as the front-end authentication credential. "Authorization" can still initiate requests and access data even after logout.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 08:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41012 | filelock: Remove locks reliably when fcntl/close race is detected</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41012</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

filelock: Remove locks reliably when fcntl/close race is detected

When fcntl_setlk() races with close(), it removes the created lock with
do_lock_file_wait().
However, LSMs can allow the first do_lock_file_wait() that created the lock
while denying the second do_lock_file_wait() that tries to remove the lock.
Separately, posix_lock_file() could also fail to
remove a lock due to GFP_KERNEL allocation failure (when splitting a range
in the middle).

After the bug has been triggered, use-after-free reads will occur in
lock_get_status() when userspace reads /proc/locks. This can likely be used
to read arbitrary kernel memory, but can't corrupt kernel memory.

Fix it by calling locks_remove_posix() instead, which is designed to
reliably get rid of POSIX locks associated with the given file and
files_struct and is also used by filp_flush().</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 08:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4260 | CoBlocks &amp;lt; 3.1.12 - Contributor+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4260</link><description>The Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.1.12 does not prevent users from pinging arbitrary hosts via some of its shortcodes, which could allow high privilege users such as contributors to perform SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6231 | Request a Quote &amp;lt; 2.4.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6231</link><description>The Request a Quote WordPress plugin before 2.4.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6420 | Hide My WP Ghost &amp;lt; 5.2.02 - Hidden Login Page Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6420</link><description>The Hide My WP Ghost  WordPress plugin before 5.2.02 does not prevent redirects to the login page via the auth_redirect WordPress function, allowing an unauthenticated visitor to access the hidden login page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6828 | Redux Framework 4.4.12 -  4.4.17 - Unauthenticated JSON File Upload to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6828</link><description>The Redux Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated JSON file uploads due to missing authorization and capability checks on the Redux_Color_Scheme_Import function in versions 4.4.12 to 4.4.17. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload JSON files, which can be used to conduct stored cross-site scripting attacks and, in some rare cases, when the wp_filesystem fails to initialize - to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6885 | MaxiBlocks: 2200+ Patterns, 190 Pages, 14.2K Icons &amp;amp; 100 Styles &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6885</link><description>The MaxiBlocks: 2200+ Patterns, 190 Pages, 14.2K Icons &amp; 100 Styles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the maxi_remove_custom_image_size and maxi_add_custom_image_size functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1575 | The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel WBE660S firmware version 6.70(ACGG.3) and earlier versions could allow an authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1575</link><description>The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel WBE660S firmware version 6.70(ACGG.3) and earlier versions could allow an authenticated user to escalate privileges and download the configuration files on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 02:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6717 | Nomad Vulnerable to Allocation Directory Path Escape Through Archive Unpacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6717</link><description>HashiCorp Nomad and Nomad Enterprise 1.6.12 up to 1.7.9, and 1.8.1 archive unpacking during migration is vulnerable to path escaping of the allocation directory. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-6717, is fixed in Nomad 1.6.13, 1.7.10, and 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:02:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24507 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Act-On 2023 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the newUser parameter in the login....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24507</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Act-On 2023 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the newUser parameter in the login.jsp component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6805 | Missing Authorization Checks in NI VeriStand Gateway for File Transfer Resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6805</link><description>The NI VeriStand Gateway is missing authorization checks when an actor attempts to access File Transfer resources.  These missing checks may result in information disclosure or remote code execution.  This affects NI VeriStand 2024 Q2 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6806 | Missing Authorization Checks In NI VeriStand Gateway For Project Resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6806</link><description>The NI VeriStand Gateway is missing authorization checks when an actor attempts to access Project resources.  These missing checks may result in remote code execution.  This affects NI VeriStand 2024 Q2 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6913 | Execution with Unnecessary Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6913</link><description>Execution with unnecessary privileges in PerkinElmer ProcessPlus allows an attacker to spawn a remote shell on the windows system.This issue affects ProcessPlus: through 1.11.6507.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6912 | Hardcoded MSSQL Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6912</link><description>Use of hard-coded MSSQL credentials in PerkinElmer ProcessPlus on Windows allows an attacker to login remove on all prone installations.This issue affects ProcessPlus: through 1.11.6507.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6793 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in NI VeriStand DataLogging Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6793</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists in NI VeriStand  DataLogging Server that may result in remote code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to send a specially crafted message.  These vulnerabilities affect NI VeriStand 2024 Q2 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6794 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in NI VeriStand Waveform Streaming Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6794</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists in NI VeriStand Waveform Streaming  Server that may result in remote code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to send a specially crafted message. These vulnerabilities affect NI VeriStand 2024 Q2 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6911 | Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6911</link><description>Files on the Windows system are accessible without authentication to external parties due to a local file inclusion in PerkinElmer ProcessPlus.This issue affects ProcessPlus: through 1.11.6507.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6791 | Directory Path Traversal Vulnerability in NI VeriStand with vsmodel Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6791</link><description>A directory path traversal vulnerability exists when loading a vsmodel file in NI VeriStand that may result in remote code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .vsmodel file.  This vulnerability affects VeriStand 2024 Q2 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40502 | SQL injection vulnerability in Hospital Management System Project in ASP.Net MVC 1 allows aremote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40502</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Hospital Management System Project in ASP.Net MVC 1 allows aremote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the btn_login_b_Click function of the Loginpage.aspx</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34329 | Insecure permissions in Entrust Datacard XPS Card Printer Driver 8.4 and earlier allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34329</link><description>Insecure permissions in Entrust Datacard XPS Card Printer Driver 8.4 and earlier allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code as SYSTEM via a crafted DLL payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39250 | EfroTech Timetrax v8.3 was discovered to contain an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability via the q parameter in the search web interf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39250</link><description>EfroTech Timetrax v8.3 was discovered to contain an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability via the q parameter in the search web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6675 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data Vulnerability in NI VeriStand Project File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6675</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists in NI VeriStand that may result in remote code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted project file.  This vulnerability affects VeriStand 2024 Q2 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6638 | Integer Overflow Vulnerability Reading TDMS Files in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6638</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability due to improper input validation when reading TDMS files in LabVIEW may result in an infinite loop.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted TDMS file.  This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6121 | NI SystemLink Server Ships Out of Date Redis Version</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6121</link><description>An out-of-date version of Redis shipped with NI SystemLink Server is susceptible to multiple vulnerabilities, including CVE-2022-24834.  This affects NI SystemLink Server 2024 Q1 and prior versions.  It also affects NI FlexLogger 2023 Q2 and prior versions which installed this shared service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6122 | Incorrect Default Directory Permissions for NI SystemLink Redis Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6122</link><description>An incorrect permission in the installation directory for the shared NI SystemLink Server KeyValueDatabase service may result in information disclosure via local access.  This affects NI SystemLink Server 2024 Q1 and prior versions.  It also affects NI FlexLogger 2023 Q2 and prior versions which installed this shared service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38944 | An issue in Intelight X-1L Traffic controller Maxtime v.1.9.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /cgi-bin/generateFo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38944</link><description>An issue in Intelight X-1L Traffic controller Maxtime v.1.9.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /cgi-bin/generateForm.cgi?formID=142 component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40075 | Laravel v11.x was discovered to contain an XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40075</link><description>Laravel v11.x was discovered to contain an XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37380 | A misconfiguration on UniFi U6+ Access Point could cause an incorrect VLAN traffic forwarding to APs meshed to UniFi U6+ Access Point.


Aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37380</link><description>A misconfiguration on UniFi U6+ Access Point could cause an incorrect VLAN traffic forwarding to APs meshed to UniFi U6+ Access Point.


Affected Products:
UniFi U6+ Access Point (Version 6.6.65 and earlier) 

 
Mitigation:
Update your UniFi U6+ Access Point to Version 6.6.74 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41880 | In veilid-core in Veilid before 0.3.4, the protocol's ping function can be misused in a way that decreases the effectiveness of safety and p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41880</link><description>In veilid-core in Veilid before 0.3.4, the protocol's ping function can be misused in a way that decreases the effectiveness of safety and private routes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28698 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Marimer LLC CSLA .Net before 8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28698</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Marimer LLC CSLA .Net before 8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the MobileFormatter component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40051 | IP Guard v4.81.0307.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the file name parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40051</link><description>IP Guard v4.81.0307.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the file name parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 17:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-24102 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Punkbuster pbsv.d64 2.351, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24102</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Punkbuster pbsv.d64 2.351, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 17:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41130 | llama.cpp null pointer dereference in gguf_init_from_file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41130</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. Prior to b3427, llama.cpp contains a null pointer dereference in gguf_init_from_file. This vulnerability is fixed in b3427.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 17:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40634 | Argo CD Unauthenticated Denial of Service (DoS) Vulnerability via /api/webhook Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40634</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. This report details a security vulnerability in Argo CD, where an unauthenticated attacker can send a specially crafted large JSON payload to the /api/webhook endpoint, causing excessive memory allocation that leads to service disruption by triggering an Out Of Memory (OOM) kill. The issue poses a high risk to the availability of Argo CD deployments. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.11.6, 2.10.15, and 2.9.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39688 | fishaudio/Bert-VITS2 Limited File Write in webui_preprocess.py generate_config function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39688</link><description>Bert-VITS2 is the VITS2 Backbone with multilingual bert. User input supplied to the data_dir variable is concatenated with other folders and used to open a new file in the generate_config function, which leads to a limited file write. The issue allows for writing /config/config.json file in arbitrary directory on the server. If a given directory path doesn’t exist, the application will return an error, so this vulnerability could also be used to gain information about existing directories on the server. This affects fishaudio/Bert-VITS2 2.3 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39685 | fishaudio/Bert-VITS2 Command Injection in webui_preprocess.py resample function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39685</link><description>Bert-VITS2 is the VITS2 Backbone with multilingual bert. User input supplied to the data_dir variable is used directly in a command executed with subprocess.run(cmd, shell=True) in the resample function, which leads to arbitrary command execution. This affects fishaudio/Bert-VITS2 2.3 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39686 | fishaudio/Bert-VITS2 Command Injection in webui_preprocess.py bert_gen function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39686</link><description>Bert-VITS2 is the VITS2 Backbone with multilingual bert. User input supplied to the data_dir variable is used directly in a command executed with subprocess.run(cmd, shell=True) in the bert_gen function, which leads to arbitrary command execution. This affects fishaudio/Bert-VITS2 2.3 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41824 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 parameters of the "password" type could leak into the build log in some specific cases</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41824</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 parameters of the "password" type could leak into the build log in some specific cases</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41825 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 stored XSS was possible on the Code Inspection tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41825</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 stored XSS was possible on the Code Inspection tab</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41826 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 stored XSS was possible on Show Connection page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41826</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 stored XSS was possible on Show Connection page</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41827 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 access tokens could continue working after deletion or expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41827</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 access tokens could continue working after deletion or expiration</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41828 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 comparison of authorization tokens took non-constant time</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41828</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 comparison of authorization tokens took non-constant time</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41829 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 an OAuth code for JetBrains Space could be stolen via Space Application connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41829</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07 an OAuth code for JetBrains Space could be stolen via Space Application connection</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41131 | Out-of-bounds Write in SixLabors ImageSharp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41131</link><description>ImageSharp is a 2D graphics API. An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability has been found in the ImageSharp gif decoder, allowing attackers to cause a crash using a specially crafted gif. This can potentially lead to denial of service. All users are advised to upgrade to v3.1.5 or v2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41132 | SixLabors ImageSharp Allows Excessive Memory Allocation in Gif Decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41132</link><description>ImageSharp is a 2D graphics API. A vulnerability discovered in the ImageSharp library, where the processing of specially crafted files can lead to excessive memory usage in the Gif decoder. The vulnerability is triggered when ImageSharp attempts to process image files that are designed to exploit this flaw. All users are advised to upgrade to v3.1.5 or v2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21552 | All versions of `SuperAGI` are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution due to unsafe use of the ‘eval’ function. An attacker could induce the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21552</link><description>All versions of `SuperAGI` are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution due to unsafe use of the ‘eval’ function. An attacker could induce the LLM output to exploit this vulnerability and gain arbitrary code execution on the SuperAGI application server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26020 | An arbitrary script execution vulnerability exists in the MPV functionality of Ankitects Anki 24.04. A specially crafted flashcard can lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26020</link><description>An arbitrary script execution vulnerability exists in the MPV functionality of Ankitects Anki 24.04. A specially crafted flashcard can lead to a arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send malicious flashcard to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29073 | An vulnerability in the handling of Latex exists in Ankitects Anki 24.04. When Latex is sanitized to prevent unsafe commands, the verbatim p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29073</link><description>An vulnerability in the handling of Latex exists in Ankitects Anki 24.04. When Latex is sanitized to prevent unsafe commands, the verbatim package, which comes installed by default in many Latex distributions, has been overlooked. A specially crafted flashcard can lead to an arbitrary file read. An attacker can share a flashcard to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32152 | A blocklist bypass vulnerability exists in the LaTeX functionality of Ankitects Anki 24.04. A specially crafted malicious flashcard can lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32152</link><description>A blocklist bypass vulnerability exists in the LaTeX functionality of Ankitects Anki 24.04. A specially crafted malicious flashcard can lead to an arbitrary file creation at a fixed path. An attacker can share a malicious flashcard to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32484 | An reflected XSS vulnerability exists in the handling of invalid paths in the Flask server in Ankitects Anki 24.04. A specially crafted flas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32484</link><description>An reflected XSS vulnerability exists in the handling of invalid paths in the Flask server in Ankitects Anki 24.04. A specially crafted flashcard can lead to JavaScript code execution and result in an arbitrary file read. An attacker can share a malicious flashcard to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41129 | The ops library leaks secrets if `subprocess.CalledProcessError` happens with a `secret-*` CLI command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41129</link><description>The ops library is a Python framework for developing and testing Kubernetes and machine charms. The issue here is that ops passes the secret content as one of the args via CLI. This issue may affect any of the charms that are using: Juju (&gt;=3.0), Juju secrets and not correctly capturing and processing `subprocess.CalledProcessError`. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.15.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25638 | DNSJava DNSSEC Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25638</link><description>dnsjava is an implementation of DNS in Java. Records in DNS replies are not checked for their relevance to the query, allowing an attacker to respond with RRs from different zones. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39902 | Tuleap&amp;#x27;s recursive permissions to document manager folder are not properly applied</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39902</link><description>Tuleap is an open source suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Prior to Tuleap Community Edition 15.10.99.128 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.10-6 and 15.9-8, the checkbox "Apply same permissions to all sub-items of this folder" in the document manager permissions modal is not taken into account and always considered as unchecked. In situations where the permissions are being restricted some users might still keep, incorrectly, the possibility to edit or manage items. Only change made via the web UI are affected, changes directly made via the REST API are not impacted. This vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 15.10.99.128 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.10-6 and 15.9-8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37998 | A vulnerability has been identified in CPCI85 Central Processing/Communication (All versions &lt; V5.40), SICORE Base system (All versions &lt; V1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37998</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in CPCI85 Central Processing/Communication (All versions &lt; V5.40), SICORE Base system (All versions &lt; V1.4.0). The password of administrative accounts of the affected applications can be reset without requiring the knowledge of the current password, given the auto login is enabled. This could allow an unauthorized attacker to obtain administrative access of the affected applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39601 | A vulnerability has been identified in CPCI85 Central Processing/Communication (All versions &lt; V5.40), SICORE Base system (All versions &lt; V1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39601</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in CPCI85 Central Processing/Communication (All versions &lt; V5.40), SICORE Base system (All versions &lt; V1.4.0). Affected devices allow a remote authenticated user or an unauthenticated user with physical access to downgrade the firmware of the device. This could allow an attacker to downgrade the device to older versions with known vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41314 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the iface parameter in the vif_disable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41314</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the iface parameter in the vif_disable function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41315 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_do_e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41315</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_do_enr_pin_wps function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41316 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_canc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41316</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_cancel_wps function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41317 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_do_e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41317</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_do_enr_pbc_wps function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41318 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_wps_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41318</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the apcli_wps_gen_pincode function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41320 | TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the get_apcli_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41320</link><description>TOTOLINK A6000R V1.0.1-B20201211.2000 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ifname parameter in the get_apcli_conn_info function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38759 | WordPress Search &amp;amp; Replace plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38759</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WP MEDIA SAS Search &amp; Replace.This issue affects Search &amp; Replace: from n/a through 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37942 | WordPress BerqWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Unauthenticated Non-Blind Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37942</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Berqier Ltd BerqWP.This issue affects BerqWP: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38723 | WordPress Get Use APIs – JSON Content Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38723</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Bernhard Kux JSON Content Importer.This issue affects JSON Content Importer: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38728 | WordPress Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.9 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38728</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Seraphinite Solutions Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source.This issue affects Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source: from n/a through 2.16.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38730 | WordPress Magical Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.41 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38730</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Noor alam Magical Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Magical Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.41.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38692 | WordPress spiffy-calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.11 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38692</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins Spiffy Calendar allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Spiffy Calendar: from n/a through 4.9.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38701 | WordPress Academy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38701</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Academy LMS.This issue affects Academy LMS: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38708 | WordPress Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38708</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38755 | WordPress DirectoryPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38755</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Designinvento DirectoryPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects DirectoryPress: from n/a through 3.6.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38773 | WordPress formlift plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.17 - Unauthenticated Blind SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38773</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Adrian Tobey FormLift for Infusionsoft Web Forms allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects FormLift for Infusionsoft Web Forms: from n/a through 7.5.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38788 | WordPress UiPress lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.06 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38788</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Bởi Admin 2020 UiPress lite allows SQL Injection.This issue affects UiPress lite: from n/a through 3.4.06.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33933 | WordPress Elementor Header &amp;amp; Footer Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.35 - Contributor+ DOM-Based Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33933</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force, Nikhil Chavan Elementor – Header, Footer &amp; Blocks Template allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Elementor – Header, Footer &amp; Blocks Template: from n/a through 1.6.35.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35656 | WordPress Elementor Pro &amp;lt;= 3.21.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elementor Elementor Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Elementor Pro: from n/a through 3.21.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37097 | WordPress Shortcodes by United Themes plugin &amp;lt; 5.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37097</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UnitedThemes Shortcodes by United Themes allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Shortcodes by United Themes: from n/a before 5.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37100 | WordPress Elegant Themes Icons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37100</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mayur Somani, threeroutes media Elegant Themes Icons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elegant Themes Icons: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37101 | WordPress WP Post Author plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37101</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AF themes WP Post Author allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Post Author: from n/a through 3.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6542 | Livestatus injection in mknotifyd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6542</link><description>Improper neutralization of livestatus command delimiters in mknotifyd in Checkmk &lt;= 2.0.0p39, &lt; 2.1.0p47, &lt; 2.2.0p32 and &lt; 2.3.0p11 allows arbitrary livestatus command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34457 | Apache StreamPark IDOR Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34457</link><description>On versions before 2.1.4, after a regular user successfully logs in, they can manually make a request using the authorization token to view everyone's user flink information, including executeSQL and config.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37114 | WordPress My Favorites plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37114</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Takashi Matsuyama My Favorites allows Stored XSS.This issue affects My Favorites: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37116 | WordPress Sinatra theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37116</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sinatrateam Sinatra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sinatra: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38503 | Apache Syncope: HTML tags can be injected into Console or Enduser text fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38503</link><description>When editing a user, group or any object in the Syncope Console, HTML tags could be added to any text field and could lead to potential exploits.
The same vulnerability was found in the Syncope Enduser, when editing “Personal Information” or “User Requests”.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.8, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37117 | WordPress Uncanny Automator Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37117</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Uncanny Automator Pro: from n/a through 5.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37120 | WordPress Tabs plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37120</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Biplob Adhikari Tabs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tabs: from n/a through 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37121 | WordPress Shortcode Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in biplob018 Shortcode Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Shortcode Addons: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37122 | WordPress Accordions plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Biplob Adhikari Accordions allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accordions: from n/a through 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37199 | WordPress Enfold theme &amp;lt;= 5.6.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37199</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kriesi.At Enfold allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Enfold: from n/a through 5.6.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23321 | Apache RocketMQ: Unauthorized Exposure of Sensitive Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23321</link><description>For RocketMQ versions 5.2.0 and below, under certain conditions, there is a risk of exposure of sensitive Information to an unauthorized actor even if RocketMQ is enabled with authentication and authorization functions.

An attacker, possessing regular user privileges or listed in the IP whitelist, could potentially acquire the administrator's account and password through specific interfaces. Such an action would grant them full control over RocketMQ, provided they have access to the broker IP address list.

To mitigate these security threats, it is strongly advised that users upgrade to version 5.3.0 or newer. Additionally, we recommend users to use RocketMQ ACL 2.0 instead of the original RocketMQ ACL when upgrading to version Apache RocketMQ 5.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37206 | WordPress Demo Awesome plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37206</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Theme4Press Demo Awesome allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Demo Awesome: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37211 | WordPress AliExpress Dropshipping with AliNext Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37211</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ali2Woo Team Ali2Woo Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ali2Woo Lite: from n/a through 3.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37215 | WordPress Transition Slider – Responsive Image Slider and Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.20.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37215</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in creativeinteractivemedia Transition Slider – Responsive Image Slider and Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Transition Slider – Responsive Image Slider and Gallery: from n/a through 2.20.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37216 | WordPress Sketchfab Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37216</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rami Yushuvaev Sketchfab Embed allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sketchfab Embed: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37217 | WordPress Empty Cart Button for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37217</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ProWCPlugins Empty Cart Button for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Empty Cart Button for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37219 | WordPress Page Builder Sandwich plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37219</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PBN Hosting SL Page Builder Sandwich – Front-End Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Page Builder Sandwich – Front-End Page Builder: from n/a through 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37221 | WordPress Kimili Flash Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37221</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Bester Kimili Flash Embed allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kimili Flash Embed: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37223 | WordPress Restaurant Reservations plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37223</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nicdark Restaurant Reservations allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Restaurant Reservations: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37229 | WordPress Blogmentor – Blog Layouts for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37229</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AuburnForest Blogmentor – Blog Layouts for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blogmentor – Blog Layouts for Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37239 | WordPress Branda plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPMU DEV Branda allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Branda: from n/a through 3.4.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37244 | WordPress Ninja Beaver Add-ons for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ninja Team Ninja Beaver Add-ons for Beaver Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ninja Beaver Add-ons for Beaver Builder: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37245 | WordPress All In One Redirection plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vsourz Digital All In One Redirection allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects All In One Redirection: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37246 | WordPress Gallery Slideshow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37246</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jethin Gallery Slideshow allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gallery Slideshow: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37257 | WordPress Permalink Manager Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37257</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Maciej Bis Permalink Manager Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Permalink Manager Lite: from n/a through 2.4.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37258 | WordPress Social Rocket plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37258</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Social Rocket allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Social Rocket: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37259 | WordPress WP Extended plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37259</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Extended The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37261 | WordPress WP-Lister Lite for Amazon plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.16 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Lab WP-Lister Lite for Amazon allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP-Lister Lite for Amazon: from n/a through 2.6.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37262 | WordPress Online Booking &amp;amp; Scheduling Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vCita.Com Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita: from n/a through 4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37263 | WordPress Enter Addons – Ultimate Template Builder for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37263</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeLooks Enter Addons enteraddons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Enter Addons: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37264 | WordPress Groundhogg plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37264</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Groundhogg Inc. Groundhogg allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Groundhogg: from n/a through 3.4.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37265 | WordPress IdeaPush plugin &amp;lt;= 8.60 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37265</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Martin Gibson IdeaPush allows Stored XSS.This issue affects IdeaPush: from n/a through 8.60.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37267 | WordPress Striking theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37267</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kaptinlin Striking allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Striking: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37271 | WordPress Print My Blog plugin &amp;lt;= 3.27.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37271</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Nelson Print My Blog allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Print My Blog: from n/a through 3.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37275 | WordPress NextScripts plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37275</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NextScripts allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects NextScripts: from n/a through 4.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37278 | WordPress Cards for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37278</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pratik Chaskar Cards for Beaver Builder.This issue affects Cards for Beaver Builder: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37409 | WordPress PowerPack Lite for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37409</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Beaver Addons PowerPack Lite for Beaver Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PowerPack Lite for Beaver Builder: from n/a through 1.3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37414 | WordPress Depicter Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37414</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Depicter Slider and Popup by Averta Depicter Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37416 | WordPress WP Photo Album Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 8.8.00.002 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37416</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in J.N. Breetvelt a.K.A. OpaJaap WP Photo Album Plus allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Photo Album Plus: from n/a through 8.8.00.002.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37422 | WordPress Progress Planner plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37422</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Team Emilia Projects Progress Planner allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Progress Planner: from n/a through 0.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37428 | WordPress  All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37428</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesgrove WidgetKit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WidgetKit: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37429 | WordPress Login with phone number plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.35 - Admin+ Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37429</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hamid Alinia – idehweb Login with phone number allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Login with phone number: from n/a through 1.7.35.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37432 | WordPress Esteem theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37432</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGrill Esteem allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Esteem: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37433 | WordPress Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37433</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EverPress Mailster allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mailster: from n/a through 4.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37434 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 3.31 - Authenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37434</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Atarim allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through 3.31.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37436 | WordPress Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37436</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash: from n/a before 4.1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37445 | WordPress HTML5 Audio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.23 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37445</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Html5 Audio Player allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Html5 Audio Player: from n/a through 2.2.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37391 | ProtonVPN before 3.2.10 on Windows mishandles the drive installer path, which should use this: '"' + ExpandConstant('{autopf}\Proton\Drive')...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37391</link><description>ProtonVPN before 3.2.10 on Windows mishandles the drive installer path, which should use this: '"' + ExpandConstant('{autopf}\Proton\Drive') + '"' in Setup/setup.iss.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40430 | In SFTPGO 2.6.2, the JWT implementation lacks cerrtain security measures, such as using JWT ID (JTI) claims, nonces, and proper expiration a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40430</link><description>In SFTPGO 2.6.2, the JWT implementation lacks cerrtain security measures, such as using JWT ID (JTI) claims, nonces, and proper expiration and invalidation mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5004 | CM Popup Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt; 1.6.6 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5004</link><description>The CM Popup Plugin for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.6.6 does not sanitise and escape some of the campaign settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5529 | WP QuickLaTeX &amp;lt; 3.8.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5529</link><description>The WP QuickLaTeX WordPress plugin before 3.8.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5973 | MasterStudy LMS &amp;lt; 3.3.24 - Privilege Escalation to Instructor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5973</link><description>The MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin  WordPress plugin before 3.3.24 does not prevent students from creating instructor accounts, which could be used to get access to functionalities they shouldn't have.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6243 | HTML Forms &amp;lt; 1.3.33 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6243</link><description>The HTML Forms  WordPress plugin before 1.3.33 does not sanitize and escape the form message inputs, allowing high-privilege users, such as administrators, to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6244 | pz-frontend-manager &amp;lt; 1.0.6 - CSRF change user profile picture</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6244</link><description>The PZ Frontend Manager WordPress plugin before 1.0.6 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6271 | Community Events &amp;lt; 1.5 - Event Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6271</link><description>The Community Events WordPress plugin before 1.5 does not have CSRF check in place when deleting events, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin delete arbitrary events via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41709 | Backdrop CMS before 1.27.3 and 1.28.x before 1.28.2 does not sufficiently sanitize field labels before they are displayed in certain places....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41709</link><description>Backdrop CMS before 1.27.3 and 1.28.x before 1.28.2 does not sufficiently sanitize field labels before they are displayed in certain places. This vulnerability is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have a role with the "administer fields" permission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41703 | LibreChat through 0.7.4-rc1 has incorrect access control for message updates. (Work on a fixed version release has started in PR 3363.)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41703</link><description>LibreChat through 0.7.4-rc1 has incorrect access control for message updates. (Work on a fixed version release has started in PR 3363.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41704 | LibreChat through 0.7.4-rc1 does not validate the normalized pathnames of images. (Work on a fixed version release has started in PR 3363.)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41704</link><description>LibreChat through 0.7.4-rc1 does not validate the normalized pathnames of images. (Work on a fixed version release has started in PR 3363.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6970 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System staffcatadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /staffcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272124.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:10:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6969 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System get_patient_history.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6969</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax/get_patient_history.php. The manipulation of the argument patient_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272123.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 03:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6968 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System print_patients_visits.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /print_patients_visits.php. The manipulation of the argument from/to leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272122 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6967 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /employee_gatepass/admin/?page=employee/manage_employee. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272121 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6966 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System Login login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument user/pass leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272120.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6965 | Tenda O3 fromVirtualSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda O3 1.0.0.10 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromVirtualSet. The manipulation of the argument ip/localPort/publicPort/app leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272119. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6964 | Tenda O3 fromDhcpSetSer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda O3 1.0.0.10. Affected is the function fromDhcpSetSer. The manipulation of the argument dhcpEn/startIP/endIP/preDNS/altDNS/mask/gateway leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272118 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6963 | Tenda O3 formexeCommand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda O3 1.0.0.10. This issue affects the function formexeCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272117 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>