<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-4964 | Potential open redirect vulnerability in opentext SMAX and AMX product. </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4964</link><description>Potential open redirect vulnerability
in opentext Service Management Automation X
(SMAX)  versions 2020.05, 2020.08,
2020.11, 2021.02, 2021.05, 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11 and opentext Asset
Management X (AMX) versions 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11. The
vulnerability could allow attackers to redirect a user to
malicious websites.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5049 | The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rafflepress' and 'raffl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5049</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rafflepress' and 'rafflepress_gutenberg' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.12.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on 'giframe' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5164 | The Bellows Accordion Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5164</link><description>The Bellows Accordion Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5199 | The PHP to Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 0.3 via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5199</link><description>The PHP to Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 0.3 via the 'php-to-page' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above, to include local file and potentially execute code on the server. While subscribers may need to poison log files or otherwise get a file installed in order to achieve remote code execution, author and above users can upload files by default and achieve remote code execution easily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5250 | The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 via a shortcode attribute. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5250</link><description>The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 via a shortcode attribute. This allows subscriber-level, and above, attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files with arbitrary content can be uploaded and included. This is limited to .php files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5251 | The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5251</link><description>The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'grid_plus_save_layout_callback' and 'grid_plus_delete_callback' functions in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber privileges or above, to add, update or delete grid layout.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5252 | The FareHarbor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5252</link><description>The FareHarbor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5315 | The Google Maps made Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5315</link><description>The Google Maps made Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 0.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5335 | The Buzzsprout Podcasting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'buzzsprout' shortcode in versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5335</link><description>The Buzzsprout Podcasting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'buzzsprout' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5362 | The Carousel, Recent Post Slider and Banner Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'spice_post_slider'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5362</link><description>The Carousel, Recent Post Slider and Banner Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'spice_post_slider' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5565 | The Shortcode Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortmenu' shortcode in versions up to, and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5565</link><description>The Shortcode Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortmenu' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5566 | The Simple Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5566</link><description>The Simple Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5583 | The WP Simple Galleries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.34 via deserializatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5583</link><description>The WP Simple Galleries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.34 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'wpsimplegallery_gallery' post meta via 'wpsgallery' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5666 | The Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcpaccordion' shortcode in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5666</link><description>The Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcpaccordion' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5843 | The Ads by datafeedr.com plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 via the 'dfads_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5843</link><description>The Ads by datafeedr.com plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 via the 'dfads_ajax_load_ads' function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. The parameters of the callable function are limited, they cannot be specified arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5832 | Improper Input Validation in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5832</link><description>Improper Input Validation in GitHub repository mintplex-labs/anything-llm prior to 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5833 | Improper Access Control in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5833</link><description>Improper Access Control in GitHub repository mintplex-labs/anything-llm prior to 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42431 | Potential XSS on user preferences page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42431</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BlueSpiceAvatars extension of BlueSpice allows logged in user to inject arbitrary HTML into the profile image dialog on Special:Preferences. This only applies to the genuine user context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5844 | Unverified Password Change in pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5844</link><description>Unverified Password Change in GitHub repository pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle prior to 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45798 | Yettiesoft VestCert Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45798</link><description>In Yettiesoft VestCert versions 2.36 to 2.5.29, a vulnerability exists due to improper validation of third-party modules. This allows malicious actors to load arbitrary third-party modules, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45799 | MLSoft TCO!stream Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45799</link><description>In MLSoft TCO!stream versions 8.0.22.1115 and below, a vulnerability exists due to insufficient permission validation. This allows an attacker to make the victim download and execute arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45797 | DreamSecurity MagicLine Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45797</link><description>A Buffer overflow vulnerability in DreamSecurity MagicLine4NX versions 1.0.0.1 to 1.0.0.26 allows an attacker to remotely execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45746 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script. Affected pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45746</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script. Affected products/versions are as follows: Movable Type 7 r.5405 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Advanced 7 r.5405 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Premium 1.58 and earlier, Movable Type Premium Advanced 1.58 and earlier, Movable Type Cloud Edition (Version 7) r.5405 and earlier, and Movable Type Premium Cloud Edition 1.58 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44141 | Inkdrop prior to v5.6.0 allows a local attacker to conduct a code injection attack by having a legitimate user open a specially crafted mark...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44141</link><description>Inkdrop prior to v5.6.0 allows a local attacker to conduct a code injection attack by having a legitimate user open a specially crafted markdown file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46866 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccCLUT::Interp3d in IccProfLib/IccTagLut.cpp in libSampleICC.a attempts to access ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46866</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccCLUT::Interp3d in IccProfLib/IccTagLut.cpp in libSampleICC.a attempts to access array elements at out-of-bounds indexes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46867 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccXformMatrixTRC::GetCurve in IccCmm.cpp in libSampleICC.a has a NULL pointer derefe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46867</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccXformMatrixTRC::GetCurve in IccCmm.cpp in libSampleICC.a has a NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25736 | Windows kube-proxy LoadBalancer contention</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25736</link><description>Kube-proxy
 on Windows can unintentionally forward traffic to local processes 
listening on the same port (“spec.ports[*].port”) as a LoadBalancer 
Service when the LoadBalancer controller
 does not set the “status.loadBalancer.ingress[].ip” field. Clusters 
where the LoadBalancer controller sets the 
“status.loadBalancer.ingress[].ip” field are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46865 | /api/v1/company/upload-logo in CompanyController.php in crater through 6.0.6 allows a superadmin to execute arbitrary PHP code by placing th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46865</link><description>/api/v1/company/upload-logo in CompanyController.php in crater through 6.0.6 allows a superadmin to execute arbitrary PHP code by placing this code into an image/png IDAT chunk of a Company Logo image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5842 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in dolibarr/dolibarr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5842</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository dolibarr/dolibarr prior to 16.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46863 | Peppermint Ticket Management before 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/users/file/download?filepath=./../ P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46863</link><description>Peppermint Ticket Management before 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/users/file/download?filepath=./../ POST request.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46864 | Peppermint Ticket Management through 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/ticket/1/file/download?filepath=../...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46864</link><description>Peppermint Ticket Management through 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/ticket/1/file/download?filepath=../ POST request.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4393 | HTML and SMTP Injection in LiquidFiles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4393</link><description>HTML and SMTP injections on the registration page of LiquidFiles versions 3.7.13 and below, allow an attacker to perform more advanced phishing attacks against an organization.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2007-10003 | The Hackers Diet Plugin HTTP POST Request ajax_blurb.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2007-10003</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in The Hackers Diet Plugin up to 0.9.6b on WordPress. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ajax_blurb.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 0.9.7b is able to address this issue. The patch is named 7dd8acf7cd8442609840037121074425d363b694. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243803.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 17:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2005-10002 | almosteffortless secure-files Plugin secure-files.php sf_downloads path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2005-10002</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in almosteffortless secure-files Plugin up to 1.1 on WordPress. Affected is the function sf_downloads of the file secure-files.php. The manipulation of the argument downloadfile leads to path traversal. Upgrading to version 1.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is cab025e5fc2bcdad8032d833ebc38e6bd2a13c92. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243804.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33638 | Run copy with container in a malicious directory may cause container escaping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33638</link><description>When the isula cp command is used to copy files from a container to a host machine and the container is controlled by an attacker, the attacker can escape the container.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33635 | Pull malicious images may cause process to be hijacked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33635</link><description>When malicious images are pulled by isula pull, attackers can execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33636 | Load malicious images may cause process to be hijacked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33636</link><description>When the isula load command is used to load malicious images, attackers can execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33637 | Export container in a malicious directory may cause process to be hijacked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33637</link><description>When the isula export command is used to export a container to an image and the container is controlled by an attacker, the attacker can escape the container.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33634 | Malicious image running containers may cause DoS attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33634</link><description>iSulad uses the lcr+lxc runtime (default) to run malicious images, which can cause DOS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 07:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46862 | An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel through 6.5.9. During a race with SQ thread exit, an io_uring/fdinfo.c io_uring_show_fdinfo NULL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46862</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel through 6.5.9. During a race with SQ thread exit, an io_uring/fdinfo.c io_uring_show_fdinfo NULL pointer dereference can occur.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40685 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40685</link><description>Management Central as part of IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Navigator contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with command line access to the operating system can exploit this vulnerability to elevate privileges to gain root access to the operating system.  IBM X-Force ID:  264116.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40686 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40686</link><description>Management Central as part of IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Navigator contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with command line access to the operating system can exploit this vulnerability to elevate privileges to gain component access to the operating system.  IBM X-Force ID:  264114.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43041 | IBM QRadar information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43041</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to information exposure allowing a delegated Admin tenant user with a specific domain security profile assigned to see data from other domains.  This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-34352.  IBM X-Force ID:  266808.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46858 | Moodle 4.3 allows /grade/report/grader/index.php?searchvalue= reflected XSS when logged in as a teacher. NOTE: the Moodle Security FAQ link ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46858</link><description>Moodle 4.3 allows /grade/report/grader/index.php?searchvalue= reflected XSS when logged in as a teacher. NOTE: the Moodle Security FAQ link states "Some forms of rich content [are] used by teachers to enhance their courses ... admins and teachers can post XSS-capable content, but students can not."</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5838 | Insufficient Session Expiration in linkstackorg/linkstack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5838</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository linkstackorg/linkstack prior to v4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5839 | Privilege Chaining in hestiacp/hestiacp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5839</link><description>Privilege Chaining in GitHub repository hestiacp/hestiacp prior to 1.8.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5840 | Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password in linkstackorg/linkstack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5840</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password in GitHub repository linkstackorg/linkstack prior to v4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46854 | Proxmox proxmox-widget-toolkit before 4.0.9, as used in multiple Proxmox products, allows XSS via the edit notes feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46854</link><description>Proxmox proxmox-widget-toolkit before 4.0.9, as used in multiple Proxmox products, allows XSS via the edit notes feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 21:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5837 | AlexanderLivanov FotosCMS2 Cookie profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5837</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in AlexanderLivanov FotosCMS2 up to 2.4.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file profile.php of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243802 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 21:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5836 | SourceCodester Task Reminder System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Task Reminder System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file classes/Users.php?f=delete. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243800.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 21:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45897 | exfatprogs before 1.2.2 allows out-of-bounds memory access, such as in read_file_dentry_set.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45897</link><description>exfatprogs before 1.2.2 allows out-of-bounds memory access, such as in read_file_dentry_set.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5835 | hu60t hu60wap6 ubbparser.php markdown cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5835</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in hu60t hu60wap6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function markdown of the file src/class/ubbparser.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named a1cd9f12d7687243bfcb7ce295665acb83b9174e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243775.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5425 | The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5425</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pmdm_wp_change_user_meta and pmdm_wp_change_post_meta functions in versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to gain elevated (e.g., administrator) privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 11:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5426 | The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5426</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pmdm_wp_delete_user_meta,  pmdm_wp_delete_term_meta, and pmdm_wp_ajax_delete_meta functions in versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete user, term, and post meta belonging to arbitrary users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 11:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46215 | Apache Airflow Celery provider, Apache Airflow: Sensitive information logged as clear text when rediss, amqp, rpc protocols are used as Celery result backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46215</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Apache Airflow Celery provider, Apache Airflow.

Sensitive information logged as clear text when rediss, amqp, rpc protocols are used as Celery result backend
Note: the vulnerability is about the information exposed in the logs not about accessing the logs.

This issue affects Apache Airflow Celery provider: from 3.3.0 through 3.4.0; Apache Airflow: from 1.10.0 through 2.6.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade Airflow Celery provider to version 3.4.1 and Apache Airlfow to version 2.7.0 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 07:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46569 | An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32_fpu function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46569</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32_fpu function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46570 | An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32 function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46570</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in radare2 v.5.8.9 and before exists in the print_insn32 function of libr/arch/p/nds32/nds32-dis.h.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43322 | ZPE Systems, Inc Nodegrid OS v5.0.0 to v5.0.17, v5.2.0 to v5.2.19, v5.4.0 to v5.4.16, v5.6.0 to v5.6.13, v5.8.0 to v5.8.10, and v5.10.0 to v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43322</link><description>ZPE Systems, Inc Nodegrid OS v5.0.0 to v5.0.17, v5.2.0 to v5.2.19, v5.4.0 to v5.4.16, v5.6.0 to v5.6.13, v5.8.0 to v5.8.10, and v5.10.0 to v5.10.3 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the endpoint /v1/system/toolkit/files/.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46468 | An issue in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the custom plugin function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46468</link><description>An issue in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the custom plugin function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46467 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46467</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in juzawebCMS v.3.4 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the username parameter of the registration page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>