<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-14299 | Improper Content-Length Validation in HTTPS Requests on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14299</link><description>The HTTPS server on Tapo C200 V3 does not properly validate the Content-Length header, which can lead to an integer overflow. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can send crafted HTTPS requests to trigger excessive memory allocation, causing the device to crash and resulting in denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14300 | Unauthenticated Access to connectAP API Endpoint on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14300</link><description>The HTTPS service on Tapo C200 V3 exposes a connectAP interface without proper authentication. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can exploit this to modify the device’s Wi-Fi configuration, resulting in loss of connectivity and denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8065 | Buffer Overflow in ONVIF XML Parser on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8065</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ONVIF XML parser of Tapo C200 V3. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can send specially crafted SOAP XML requests, causing memory overflow and device crash, resulting in denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68613 | n8n Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Expression Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68613</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Versions starting with 0.211.0 and prior to 1.120.4, 1.121.1, and 1.122.0 contain a critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in their workflow expression evaluation system. Under certain conditions, expressions supplied by authenticated users during workflow configuration may be evaluated in an execution context that is not sufficiently isolated from the underlying runtime. An authenticated attacker could abuse this behavior to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the n8n process. Successful exploitation may lead to full compromise of the affected instance, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, modification of workflows, and execution of system-level operations. This issue has been fixed in versions 1.120.4, 1.121.1, and 1.122.0. Users are strongly advised to upgrade to a patched version, which introduces additional safeguards to restrict expression evaluation. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations: Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only; and/or deploy n8n in a hardened environment with restricted operating system privileges and network access to reduce the impact of potential exploitation. These workarounds do not fully eliminate the risk and should only be used as short-term measures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53945 | BrainyCP 1.0 Remote Code Execution via Authenticated Crontab Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53945</link><description>BrainyCP 1.0 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows logged-in users to inject arbitrary commands through the crontab configuration interface. Attackers can exploit the crontab endpoint by adding a malicious command that spawns a reverse shell to a specified IP and port.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53946 | Arcsoft PhotoStudio 6.0.0.172 Unquoted Service Path Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53946</link><description>Arcsoft PhotoStudio 6.0.0.172 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the ArcSoft Exchange Service that allows local attackers to escalate privileges. Attackers can place a malicious executable in the unquoted path and trigger the service to execute arbitrary code with system-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53947 | OCS Inventory NG 2.3.0.0 Unquoted Service Path Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53947</link><description>OCS Inventory NG 2.3.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to escalate privileges to system level. Attackers can place a malicious executable in the unquoted service path and trigger the service restart to execute code with elevated system privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53948 | Lilac-Reloaded for Nagios 2.0.8 Remote Code Execution via Autodiscovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53948</link><description>Lilac-Reloaded for Nagios 2.0.8 contains a remote code execution vulnerability in the autodiscovery feature that allows attackers to inject arbitrary commands. Attackers can exploit the lack of input filtering in the nmap_binary parameter to execute a reverse shell by sending a crafted POST request to the autodiscovery endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53949 | AspEmail 5.6.0.2 Local Privilege Escalation via Binary Permission Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53949</link><description>AspEmail 5.6.0.2 contains a binary permission vulnerability that allows local users to escalate privileges through the Persits Software EmailAgent service. Attackers can exploit full write permissions in the BIN directory to replace the service executable and gain elevated system access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53950 | InnovaStudio WYSIWYG Editor 5.4 Unrestricted File Upload via Filename Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53950</link><description>InnovaStudio WYSIWYG Editor 5.4 contains an unrestricted file upload vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass file extension restrictions through filename manipulation. Attackers can upload malicious ASP shells by using null byte techniques and alternate file extensions to circumvent upload controls in the asset manager.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53951 | Ever Gauzy v0.281.9 JWT Authentication Weakness via HMAC Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53951</link><description>Ever Gauzy v0.281.9 contains a JWT authentication vulnerability that allows attackers to exploit weak HMAC secret key implementation. Attackers can leverage the exposed JWT token to authenticate and gain unauthorized access with administrative permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53952 | Dotclear 2.25.3 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53952</link><description>Dotclear 2.25.3 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to upload malicious PHP files with .phar extension through the blog post creation interface. Attackers can upload files containing PHP system commands that execute when the uploaded file is accessed, enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53953 | WebsiteBaker 2.13.3 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Page Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53953</link><description>WebsiteBaker 2.13.3 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts when creating web pages. Attackers can craft malicious payloads in page titles that execute arbitrary JavaScript when the page is viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53954 | ActFax 10.10 Unquoted Path Services Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53954</link><description>ActFax 10.10 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially escalate privileges by exploiting the ActiveFaxServiceNT service configuration. Attackers with write permissions to Program Files directories can inject a malicious ActSrvNT.exe executable to gain elevated system access when the service restarts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53956 | Flatnux 2021-03.25 Authenticated File Upload Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53956</link><description>Flatnux 2021-03.25 contains an authenticated file upload vulnerability that allows administrative users to upload arbitrary PHP files through the file manager. Attackers with admin credentials can upload malicious PHP scripts to the web root directory, enabling remote code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53957 | Kimai 1.30.10 SameSite Cookie Vulnerability Session Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53957</link><description>Kimai 1.30.10 contains a SameSite cookie vulnerability that allows attackers to steal user session cookies through malicious exploitation. Attackers can trick victims into executing a crafted PHP script that captures and writes session cookie information to a file, enabling potential session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53958 | LDAP Tool Box Self Service Password 1.5.2 Account Takeover via HTTP Host Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53958</link><description>LDAP Tool Box Self Service Password 1.5.2 contains a password reset vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate HTTP Host headers during token generation. Attackers can craft malicious password reset requests that generate tokens sent to a controlled server, enabling potential account takeover by intercepting and using stolen reset tokens.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53959 | FileZilla Client 3.63.1 DLL Hijacking via Missing TextShaping.dll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53959</link><description>FileZilla Client 3.63.1 contains a DLL hijacking vulnerability that allows attackers to execute malicious code by placing a crafted TextShaping.dll in the application directory. Attackers can generate a reverse shell payload using msfvenom and replace the missing DLL to achieve remote code execution when the application launches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68481 | FastAPI Users Vulnerable to 1-click Account Takeover in Apps Using FastAPI SSO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68481</link><description>FastAPI Users allows users to quickly add a registration and authentication system to their FastAPI project. Prior to version 15.0.2, the OAuth login state tokens are completely stateless and carry no per-request entropy or any data that could link them to the session that initiated the OAuth flow. `generate_state_token()` is always called with an empty `state_data` dict, so the resulting JWT only contains the fixed audience claim plus an expiration timestamp. On callback, the library merely checks that the JWT verifies under `state_secret` and is unexpired; there is no attempt to match the state value to the browser that initiated the OAuth request, no correlation cookie, and no server-side cache. Any attacker can hit `/authorize`, capture the server-generated state, finish the upstream OAuth flow with their own provider account, and then trick a victim into loading `.../callback?code=&amp;amp;state=`. Because the state JWT is valid for any client for \~1 hour, the victim’s browser will complete the flow. This leads to login CSRF. Depending on the app’s logic, the login CSRF can lead to an account takeover of the victim account or to the victim user getting logged in to the attacker's account. Version 15.0.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14968 | code-projects Simple Stock System update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14968</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /market/update.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67712 | HTML injection issue in ArcGIS Web App Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67712</link><description>There is an HTML injection issue in Esri ArcGIS Web AppBuilder developer edition versions prior to 2.30 that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to potentially entice a user to click a link that causes arbitrary HTML to render in a victim's browser. There is no evidence of JavaScript execution, which limits the impact. At the time of submission, ArcGIS Web App Builder developer edition is retired and unsupported. ArcGIS Web App Builder 2.30 is not susceptible to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12874 | HTTP Request Smuggling in Quest Coexistence Manager for Notes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12874</link><description>Inconsistent Interpretation of HTTP Requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling') vulnerability in Quest Coexistence Manager for Notes (Free/Busy Connector modules) allows HTTP Request Smuggling via the Content-Length-Transfer-Encoding (CL.TE) attack vector. This could allow an attacker to bypass access controls, poison web caches, hijack sessions, or trigger unintended internal requests. This issue affects Coexistence Manager for Notes 3.8.2045. Other versions may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14966 | FastAdmin Backend Controller Backend.php selectpage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14966</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in FastAdmin up to 1.7.0.20250506. Affected is the function selectpage of the file application/common/controller/Backend.php of the component Backend Controller. Executing manipulation of the argument custom/searchField can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14967 | itsourcecode Student Management System candidates_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14967</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /candidates_report.php. The manipulation of the argument school_year leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14965 | 1541492390c yougou-mall ResourceController.java upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14965</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1541492390c yougou-mall up to 0a771fa817c924efe52c8fe0a9a6658eee675f9f. This impacts the function Upload of the file src/main/java/per/ccm/ygmall/extra/controller/ResourceController.java. Performing manipulation results in path traversal. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14964 | TOTOLINK T10 cstecgi.cgi sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14964</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5083_B20200521. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument loginAuthUrl leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14961 | code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System editedcampaign.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14961</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /editedcampaign.php. The manipulation of the argument campaignname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14962 | code-projects Simple Stock System chatuser.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14962</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /market/chatuser.php. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14959 | code-projects Simple Stock System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14959</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /market/signup.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14960 | code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System editeddonor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14960</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /editeddonor.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14958 | floooh sokol sokol_gfx.h _sg_pipeline_common_init heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14958</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in floooh sokol up to 33e2271c431bf21de001e972f72da17a984da932. This vulnerability affects the function _sg_pipeline_common_init in the library sokol_gfx.h. Performing manipulation results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The patch is named 33e2271c431bf21de001e972f72da17a984da932. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68430 | CVAT vulnerable to directory traversal via mounted share listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68430</link><description>CVAT is an open source interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. In versions 2.8.1 through 2.52.0, an attacker with an account on a CVAT instance is able to retrieve the contents of any file system directory accessible to the CVAT server. The exposed information is names of contained files and subdirectories. The contents of files are not accessible. Version 2.53.0 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68478 | Langflow Vulnerable to External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68478</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. Prior to version 1.7.0, if an arbitrary path is specified in the request body's `fs_path`, the server serializes the Flow object into JSON and creates/overwrites a file at that path. There is no path restriction, normalization, or allowed directory enforcement, so absolute paths (e.g., /etc/poc.txt) are interpreted as is. Version 1.7.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14957 | WebAssembly Binaryen IRBuilder wasm-ir-builder.cpp makeLocalTee null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14957</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WebAssembly Binaryen up to 125. This affects the function IRBuilder::makeLocalGet/IRBuilder::makeLocalSet/IRBuilder::makeLocalTee of the file src/wasm/wasm-ir-builder.cpp of the component IRBuilder. Such manipulation of the argument Index leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The name of the patch is 6fb2b917a79578ab44cf3b900a6da4c27251e0d4. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63665 | An issue in GT Edge AI Platform Versions before v2.0.10-dev allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted JSON payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63665</link><description>An issue in GT Edge AI Platform Versions before v2.0.10-dev allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted JSON payload into the Prompt window.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14809 | Address bar spoofing risk in ArcSearch on Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14809</link><description>ArcSearch for Android versions prior to 1.12.6 could display a different domain in the address bar than the content being shown, enabling address bar spoofing after user interaction via crafted web content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68457 | Orejime has executable code in HTML attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68457</link><description>Orejime is a consent manager that focuses on accessibility. On HTML elements handled by Orejime prior to version 2.3.2, one could run malicious code by embedding `javascript:` code within data attributes. When consenting to the related purpose, Orejime would turn data attributes into unprefixed ones (i.e. `data-href` into `href`), thus executing the code. This shouldn't have any impact on most setups, as elements handled by Orejime are generally hardcoded. The problem would only arise if somebody could inject HTML code within pages. The problem has been patched in version 2.3.2. As a workaround, the problem can be fixed outside of Orejime by sanitizing attributes which could contain executable code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68477 | Langflow vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68477</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. Prior to version 1.7.0, Langflow provides an API Request component that can issue arbitrary HTTP requests within a flow. This component takes a user-supplied URL, performs only normalization and basic format checks, and then sends the request using a server-side httpx client. It does not block private IP ranges (127[.]0[.]0[.]1, the 10/172/192 ranges) or cloud metadata endpoints (169[.]254[.]169[.]254), and it returns the response body as the result. Because the flow execution endpoints (/api/v1/run, /api/v1/run/advanced) can be invoked with just an API key, if an attacker can control the API Request URL in a flow, non-blind SSRF is possible—accessing internal resources from the server’s network context. This enables requests to, and collection of responses from, internal administrative endpoints, metadata services, and internal databases/services, leading to information disclosure and providing a foothold for further attacks. Version 1.7.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30971 | Gaia unauthenticated endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30971</link><description>Gotham Gaia application was found to be exposing multiple unauthenticated endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49587 | Glutton V1 endpoints missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49587</link><description>Glutton V1 service endpoints were exposed without any authentication on Gotham stacks, this could have allowed users that did not have any permission to hit glutton backend directly and read/update/delete data. The affected service has been patched and automatically deployed to all Apollo-managed Gotham Instances</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14812 | Address bar spoofing risk in Arc Search on iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14812</link><description>ArcSearch for iOS versions prior to 1.45.2 could display a different domain in the address bar than the content being shown after an iframe-triggered URI-scheme navigation, increasing spoofing risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14955 | Open5GS PFCP handler.c ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14955</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr in the library lib/pfcp/handler.c of the component PFCP. The manipulation results in improper initialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is identified as 773117aa5472af26fc9f80e608d3386504c3bdb7. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14956 | WebAssembly Binaryen wasm-binary.cpp readExport heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14956</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in WebAssembly Binaryen up to 125. Affected by this issue is the function WasmBinaryReader::readExport of the file src/wasm/wasm-binary.cpp. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: 4f52bff8c4075b5630422f902dd92a0af2c9f398. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58053 | Galette has a privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58053</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Prior to version 1.2.0, while updating any existing account with a self forged POST request, one can gain higher privileges. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65035 | GLPI Database Inventory Plugin Vulnerable to Stored Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65035</link><description>pluginsGLPI's Database Inventory Plugin "manages" the Teclib' inventory agents in order to perform an inventory of the databases present on the workstation. Prior to version 1.1.2, in certain conditions (database write access must first be obtained through another vulnerability or misconfiguration), user-controlled data is stored insecurely in the database via computergroup, and is later unserialized on every page load, allowing arbitrary PHP object instantiation. Version 1.1.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66580 | Dive has Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability that can escalate to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66580</link><description>Dive is an open-source MCP Host Desktop Application that enables integration with function-calling LLMs. A critical Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 0.11.1 in the Mermaid diagram rendering component. The application allows the execution of arbitrary JavaScript via `javascript:`. An attacker can exploit this to inject a malicious Model Context Protocol (MCP) server configuration, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the victim's machine when the node is clicked. Version 0.11.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58052 | Galette has groups managers access control bypass on Members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58052</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Starting in version 0.9.6 and prior to version 1.2.0, attackers with group manager role can bypass intended restrictions allowing unauthorized access and changes despite role-based controls. Since it requires privileged access initially, exploitation is restricted to malicious insiders or compromised group managers accounts. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14953 | Open5GS FAR-ID handler.c ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14953</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This impacts the function ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr in the library lib/pfcp/handler.c of the component FAR-ID Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to null pointer dereference. The attack may be performed from remote. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called 93a9fd98a8baa94289be3b982028201de4534e32. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14954 | Open5GS QER/FAR/URR/PDR context.c ogs_pfcp_qer_find_or_add assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14954</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. Affected is the function ogs_pfcp_pdr_find_or_add/ogs_pfcp_far_find_or_add/ogs_pfcp_urr_find_or_add/ogs_pfcp_qer_find_or_add in the library lib/pfcp/context.c of the component QER/FAR/URR/PDR. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 442369dcd964f03d95429a6a01a57ed21f7779b7. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67442 | EVE-NG 6.4.0-13-PRO is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The /api/export interface allows authenticated users to export lab files. This int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67442</link><description>EVE-NG 6.4.0-13-PRO is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The /api/export interface allows authenticated users to export lab files. This interface lacks effective input validation and filtering when processing file path parameters submitted by users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34433 | AVideo &amp;lt; 20.1 Unauthenticated RCE via Predictable Installation Salt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34433</link><description>AVideo versions 14.3.1 prior to 20.1 contain an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability caused by predictable generation of an installation salt using PHP uniqid(). The installation timestamp is exposed via a public endpoint, and a derived hash identifier is accessible through unauthenticated API responses, allowing attackers to brute-force the remaining entropy. The recovered salt can then be used to encrypt a malicious payload supplied to a notification API endpoint that evaluates attacker-controlled input, resulting in arbitrary code execution as the web server user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66905 | The Takes web framework's TkFiles take thru 2.0-SNAPSHOT fails to canonicalize HTTP request paths before resolving them against the filesyst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66905</link><description>The Takes web framework's TkFiles take thru 2.0-SNAPSHOT fails to canonicalize HTTP request paths before resolving them against the filesystem. A remote attacker can include ../ sequences in the request path to escape the configured base directory and read arbitrary files from the host system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53922 | Galette has access control bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53922</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Starting in version 1.1.4 and prior to version 1.2.0, a user who is logged in as group manager may bypass intended restrictions on Contributions and Transactions. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66906 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Turms Admin API thru v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to gain escalated privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66906</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Turms Admin API thru v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to gain escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50681 | igmpproxy 0.4 before commit 2b30c36 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted IGMPv3 membership...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50681</link><description>igmpproxy 0.4 before commit 2b30c36 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted IGMPv3 membership report packet with a malicious source address. Due to insufficient validation in the `recv_igmp()` function in src/igmpproxy.c, an invalid group record type can trigger a NULL pointer dereference when logging the address using `inet_fmtsrc()`. This vulnerability can be exploited by sending malformed multicast traffic to a host running igmpproxy, leading to a crash. igmpproxy is used in various embedded networking environments and consumer-grade IoT devices (such as home routers and media gateways) to handle multicast traffic for IPTV and other streaming services. Affected devices that rely on unpatched versions of igmpproxy may be vulnerable to remote denial-of-service attacks across a LAN .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66910 | Turms Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a plaintext password storage vulnerability in the administrator authentication system. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66910</link><description>Turms Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a plaintext password storage vulnerability in the administrator authentication system. The BaseAdminService class caches administrator passwords in plaintext within AdminInfo objects to optimize authentication performance. Upon successful login, raw passwords are stored unencrypted in memory in the rawPassword field. Attackers with local system access can extract these passwords through memory dumps, heap analysis, or debugger attachment, bypassing bcrypt protection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14952 | Campcodes Supplier Management System add_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14952</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_category.php. Performing manipulation of the argument txtCategoryName results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66908 | Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an improper file type validation vulnerability in the OCR image upload functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66908</link><description>Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an improper file type validation vulnerability in the OCR image upload functionality. The OcrController in turms-ai-serving/src/main/java/im/turms/ai/domain/ocr/controller/OcrController.java uses the @FormData(contentType = MediaTypeConst.IMAGE) annotation to restrict uploads to image files, but this constraint is not properly enforced. The system relies solely on client-provided Content-Type headers and file extensions without validating actual file content using magic bytes (file signatures). An attacker can upload arbitrary file types including executables, scripts, HTML, or web shells by setting the Content-Type header to "image/*" or using an image file extension. This bypass enables potential server-side code execution, stored XSS, or information disclosure depending on how uploaded files are processed and served.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14951 | code-projects Scholars Tracking System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14951</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Scholars Tracking System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /home.php. Such manipulation of the argument post_content leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66909 | Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an image decompression bomb denial of service vulnerability. The ExtendedOpenC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66909</link><description>Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an image decompression bomb denial of service vulnerability. The ExtendedOpenCVImage class in ai/djl/opencv/ExtendedOpenCVImage.java loads images using OpenCV's imread() function without validating dimensions or pixel count before decompression. An attacker can upload a specially crafted compressed image file (e.g., PNG) that is small when compressed but expands to gigabytes of memory when loaded. This causes immediate memory exhaustion, OutOfMemoryError, and service crash. No authentication is required if the OCR service is publicly accessible. Multiple requests can completely deny service availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66911 | Turms IM Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a broken access control vulnerability in the user online status query functionality. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66911</link><description>Turms IM Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a broken access control vulnerability in the user online status query functionality. The handleQueryUserOnlineStatusesRequest() method in UserServiceController.java allows any authenticated user to query the online status, device information, and login timestamps of arbitrary users without proper authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14950 | code-projects Scholars Tracking System delete_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14950</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Scholars Tracking System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /delete_post.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14946 | Libnbd: libnbd: arbitrary code execution via ssh argument injection through a malicious uri</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14946</link><description>A flaw was found in libnbd. A malicious actor could exploit this by convincing libnbd to open a specially crafted Uniform Resource Identifier (URI). This vulnerability arises because non-standard hostnames starting with '-o' are incorrectly interpreted as arguments to the Secure Shell (SSH) process, rather than as hostnames. This could lead to arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the user running libnbd.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14881 | Insecure direct object reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14881</link><description>Multiple API endpoints allowed access to sensitive files from other users by knowing the UUID of the file that were not intended to be accessible by UUID only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14882 | Insecure direct object reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14882</link><description>An API endpoint allowed access to sensitive files from other users by knowing the UUID of the file that were not intended to be accessible by UUID only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1928 | Improper Authentication in Restajet&amp;#x27;s Online Food Delivery System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1928</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Restajet Information Technologies Inc. Online Food Delivery System allows Password Recovery Exploitation.This issue affects Online Food Delivery System: through 19122025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1927 | CSRF in Restajet&amp;#x27;s Online Food Delivery System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1927</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Restajet Information Technologies Inc. Online Food Delivery System allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Online Food Delivery System: through 19122025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1885 | Open Redirect in Restajet&amp;#x27;s Online Food Delivery System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1885</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Restajet Information Technologies Inc. Online Food Delivery System allows Phishing, Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Online Food Delivery System: through 19122025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14847 | Zlib compressed protocol header length confusion may allow memory read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14847</link><description>Mismatched length fields in Zlib compressed protocol headers may allow a read of uninitialized heap memory by an unauthenticated client. This issue affects all MongoDB Server v7.0 prior to 7.0.28 versions, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.17, MongoDB Server v8.2 versions prior to 8.2.3, MongoDB Server v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.27, MongoDB Server v5.0 versions prior to 5.0.32, MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to 4.4.30, MongoDB Server v4.2 versions greater than or equal to 4.2.0, MongoDB Server v4.0 versions greater than or equal to 4.0.0, and MongoDB Server v3.6 versions greater than or equal to 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12361 | myCred – Points Management System For Gamification, Ranks, Badges, and Loyalty Program &amp;lt;= 2.9.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12361</link><description>The myCred – Points Management System For Gamification, Ranks, Badges, and Loyalty Program plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 2.9.7.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive information including user IDs, display names, and email addresses of all users on the site via the get_bank_accounts AJAX action. Passwords are not exposed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14455 | Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid &amp;lt;= 3.6.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Gallery Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14455</link><description>The Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform actions on gallery management functions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete, modify, or clone galleries created by any user, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66524 | Apache NiFi: Deserialization of Untrusted Data in GetAsanaObject Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66524</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.20.0 through 2.6.0 include the GetAsanaObject Processor, which requires integration with a configurable Distribute Map Cache Client Service for storing and retrieving state information. The GetAsanaObject Processor used generic Java Object serialization and deserialization without filtering. Unfiltered Java object deserialization does not provide protection against crafted state information stored in the cache server configured for GetAsanaObject. Exploitation requires an Apache NiFi system running with the GetAsanaObject Processor, and direct access to the configured cache server. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 2.7.0 is the recommended mitigation, which replaces Java Object serialization with JSON serialization. Removing the GetAsanaObject Processor located in the nifi-asana-processors-nar bundle also prevents exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11747 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.345 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11747</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the colibri_blog_posts shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.345 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14151 | SlimStat Analytics &amp;lt;= 5.3.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14151</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'outbound_resource' parameter in the slimtrack AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66502 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Page Templates Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66502</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Page Templates feature. A crafted payload can be stored as the template name, which is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script executes each time the affected PDF is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66519 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Layer Import Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66519</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Layer Import functionality. A crafted payload can be injected into the “Create new Layer” field during layer import and is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script executes when the Layers panel is accessed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66520 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Portfolio SVG Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66520</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Portfolio feature of the Foxit PDF Editor cloud (pdfonline.foxit.com). User-supplied SVG files are not properly sanitized or validated before being inserted into the HTML structure. As a result, embedded HTML or JavaScript within a crafted SVG may execute whenever the Portfolio file list is rendered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66521 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Trusted Certificates Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66521</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Trusted Certificates feature. A crafted payload can be injected as the certificate name, which is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script executes each time the Trusted Certificates view is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66522 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Digital IDs Common Name Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66522</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Digital IDs functionality of the Foxit PDF Editor Cloud (pdfonline.foxit.com). The application does not properly sanitize or encode the Common Name field of Digital IDs before inserting user-supplied content into the DOM. As a result, embedded HTML or JavaScript may execute whenever the Digital IDs dialog is accessed or when the affected PDF is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66500 | Foxit webplugins.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting via postMessage Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66500</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in webplugins.foxit.com. A postMessage handler fails to validate the message origin and directly assigns externalPath to a script source, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript when a crafted postMessage is received.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66501 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in eSign Predefined Text Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66501</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Predefined Text feature of the Foxit eSign section. A crafted payload can be stored via the Identity “First Name” field, which is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script may execute when predefined text is used or when viewing document properties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13008 | Session Token Disclosure in M-Files Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13008</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in M-Files Server before versions 25.12.15491.7, 25.8 LTS SR3, 25.2 LTS SR3 and 24.8 LTS SR5 allows an authenticated attacker using M-Files Web to capture session tokens of other active users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66493 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66493</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the AcroForm handling of Foxit PDF Reader and Foxit PDF Editor before 2025.2.1,14.0.1 and 13.2.1 

on Windows

. When opening a PDF containing specially crafted JavaScript, a pointer to memory that has already been freed may be accessed or dereferenced, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66494 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66494</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the PDF file parsing of Foxit PDF Reader before 2025.2.1, 14.0.1, and 13.2.1 on Windows. A PDF object managed by multiple parent objects could be freed while still being referenced, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66495 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66495</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader before 2025.2.1, 14.0.1, and 13.2.1 on Windows and MacOS. When opening a PDF containing specially crafted JavaScript, a pointer to memory that has already been freed may be accessed or dereferenced, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66496 | Foxit PDF Reader 3D Annotation Out-of-Bounds Memory Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66496</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the 3D annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing PRC data. When opening a PDF file containing malformed or specially crafted PRC content, out-of-bounds memory access may occur, resulting in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66497 | Foxit PDF Reader 3D Annotation Out-of-Bounds Memory Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66497</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the 3D annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing PRC data. When opening a PDF file containing malformed or specially crafted PRC content, out-of-bounds memory access may occur, resulting in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66498 | Foxit PDF Reader 3D Annotation Out-of-Bounds Memory Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66498</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the 3D annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing U3D data. When opening a PDF file containing malformed or specially crafted PRC content, out-of-bounds memory access may occur, resulting in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66499 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF Parsing Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66499</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PDF parsing of Foxit PDF Reader when processing specially crafted JBIG2 data. An integer overflow in the calculation of the image buffer size may occur, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13754 | Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9.16 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13754</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9.16. This is due to the plugin exposing its admin embed endpoint at `/wp-json/ssa/v1/embed-inner-admin` without authentication, which leaks plugin settings including staff names, business names, and configuration data that are not publicly displayed on the booking form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract private business configuration. In premium versions with integrations configured, this might also expose other sensitive data including API keys for external services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13999 | HTML5 Audio Player – The Ultimate No-Code Podcast, MP3 &amp;amp; Audio Player 2.4.0 - 2.5.1 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13999</link><description>The HTML5 Audio Player – The Ultimate No-Code Podcast, MP3 &amp; Audio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions from 2.4.0 up to, and including, 2.5.1 via the getIcyMetadata() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14449 | BA Book Everything &amp;lt;= 1.8.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via babe-search-form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14449</link><description>The BA Book Everything plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's babe-search-form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66173 | There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66173</link><description>There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for the serial port, an attacker with physical access could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the affected products and gaining access to an unrestricted shell environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66174 | There is an improper authentication vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66174</link><description>There is an improper authentication vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for the serial port, an attacker with physical access could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the affected products and run a series of commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14267 | Unintended temporary cached data included in a structure only copy intended to be empty of data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14267</link><description>Incomplete removal of sensitive information before transfer vulnerability in M-Files Corporation M-Files Server allows data leak exposure affecting versions before 25.12.15491.7</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13307 | Ocean Modal Window &amp;lt; 2.3.3 - Editor+ Remote Code Execution via Modal Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13307</link><description>The Ocean Modal Window WordPress plugin before 2.3.3 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via the modal display logic. These modals can be displayed under user-controlled conditions that Editors and Administrators can set (edit_pages capability). The conditions are then executed as part of an eval statement executed on every site page. This leads to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14546 | Versions of the package fastapi-sso before 0.19.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Request Forgery (CSRF) due to the improper validation of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14546</link><description>Versions of the package fastapi-sso before 0.19.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Request Forgery (CSRF) due to the improper validation of the OAuth state parameter during the authentication callback. While the get_login_url method allows for state generation, it does not persist the state or bind it to the user's session. Consequently, the verify_and_process method accepts the state received in the query parameters without verifying it against a trusted local value. This allows a remote attacker to trick a victim into visiting a malicious callback URL, which can result in the attacker's account being linked to the victim's internal account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 05:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14939 | code-projects Online Appointment Booking System deletemanager.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14939</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Appointment Booking System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/deletemanager.php. The manipulation of the argument managername results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14940 | code-projects Scholars Tracking System delete_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14940</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Scholars Tracking System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_user.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13941 | Foxit PDF Reader Update Service Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13941</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit PDF Reader/Editor Update Service. During plugin installation, incorrect file system permissions are assigned to resources used by the update service. A local attacker with low privileges could modify or replace these resources, which are later executed by the service, resulting in execution of arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14910 | Edimax BR-6208AC FTP Daemon Service handle_retr path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14910</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Edimax BR-6208AC 1.02. This impacts the function handle_retr of the component FTP Daemon Service. The manipulation results in path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Edimax confirms this issue: "This product is no longer available in the market and has been discontinued for five years. Consequently, Edimax no longer provides technical support, firmware updates, or security patches for this specific model. However, to ensure the safety of our remaining active users, we acknowledge this report and will take the following mitigation actions: (A) We will issue an official security advisory on our support website. (B) We will strongly advise users to disable the FTP service on this device to mitigate the reported risk, by which the product will still work for common use. (C) We will recommend users upgrade to newer, supported models." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52692 | Bypass Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52692</link><description>Successful exploitation of the vulnerability could allow an attacker with local network access to send a specially crafted URL to access certain administration functions without login credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67842 | The Static Asset API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the subdomain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67842</link><description>The Static Asset API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the subdomain parameter because any tenant's assets can be served on any other tenant's documentation site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67843 | A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the MDX Rendering Engine in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67843</link><description>A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the MDX Rendering Engine in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via inline JSX expressions in an MDX file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67844 | The GitHub Integration API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive repository metadata via the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67844</link><description>The GitHub Integration API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive repository metadata via the repository owner and name fields. It fails to validate that the repository owner and name fields provided during configuration belong to the specific GitHub App Installation ID associated with the user's organization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67845 | A Directory Traversal vulnerability in the Static Asset Proxy Endpoint in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67845</link><description>A Directory Traversal vulnerability in the Static Asset Proxy Endpoint in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted URL containing path traversal sequences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67846 | The Deployment Infrastructure in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to bypass security patches and execute downgrad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67846</link><description>The Deployment Infrastructure in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to bypass security patches and execute downgrade attacks via predictable deployment identifiers on the Vercel preview domain. An attacker can identify the URL structure of a previous deployment that contains unpatched vulnerabilities. By browsing directly to the specific git-ref or deployment-id subdomain, the attacker can force the application to load the vulnerable version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14909 | JeecgBoot SysUserOnlineController.java SysUserOnlineController user session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14909</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The impacted element is the function SysUserOnlineController of the file jeecg-boot/jeecg-module-system/jeecg-system-biz/src/main/java/org/jeecg/modules/system/controller/SysUserOnlineController.java. Executing manipulation can lead to manage user sessions. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This patch is called b686f9fbd1917edffe5922c6362c817a9361cfbd. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14908 | JeecgBoot Multi-Tenant Management SysTenantController.java improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14908</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file jeecg-boot/jeecg-module-system/jeecg-system-biz/src/main/java/org/jeecg/modules/system/controller/SysTenantController.java of the component Multi-Tenant Management Module. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The patch is named e1c8f00bf2a2e0edddbaa8119afe1dc92d9dc1d2/67795493bdc579e489d3ab12e52a1793c4f8a0ee. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11774 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in the Software Keyboard Function of GENESIS64, ICONICS Suite, Mobile HMI, and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11774</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in the software keyboard function (hereinafter referred to as "keypad function") of Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions GENESIS64 versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric ICONICS Suite versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions ICONICS Suite versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric MobileHMI versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions MobileHMI versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary executable files (EXE) when a legitimate user uses the keypad function by tampering with the configuration file for the function. This could allow the attacker to disclose, tamper with, delete, or destroy information stored on the PC where the affected product is installed, or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the system, through the execution of the EXE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14733 | WatchGuard Firebox iked Out of Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14733</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects both the Mobile User VPN with IKEv2 and the Branch Office VPN using IKEv2 when configured with a dynamic gateway peer.This vulnerability affects Fireware OS 11.10.2 up to and including 11.12.4_Update1, 12.0 up to and including 12.11.5 and 2025.1 up to and including 2025.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14899 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System Administrator Endpoint stateadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14899</link><description>A weakness has been identified in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/stateadd.php of the component Administrator Endpoint. This manipulation causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14900 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System Administrator Endpoint userdelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14900</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/userdelete.php of the component Administrator Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14897 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System Administrator Endpoint useragentdelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14897</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/useragentdelete.php of the component Administrator Endpoint. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14898 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System Administrator Endpoint userbuilderdelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14898</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/userbuilderdelete.php of the component Administrator Endpoint. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64675 | Azure Cosmos DB Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64675</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68398 | Weblate has git config file overwrite vulnerability that leads to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68398</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. In versions prior to 5.15.1, it was possible to overwrite Git configuration remotely and override some of its behavior. Version 5.15.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68279 | Weblate has an arbitrary file read via symbolic links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68279</link><description>Weblate is a web based localization tool. In versions prior to 5.15.1, it was possible to read arbitrary files from the server file system using crafted symbolic links in the repository. Version 5.15.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68422 | Kibana Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68422</link><description>Improper Authorization (CWE-285) in Kibana can lead to privilege escalation (CAPEC-233) by allowing an authenticated user to bypass intended permission restrictions via a crafted HTTP request. This allows an attacker who lacks the live queries - read permission to successfully retrieve the list of live queries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68386 | Kibana Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68386</link><description>Improper Authorization (CWE-285) in Kibana can lead to privilege escalation (CAPEC-233) by allowing an authenticated user to change a document's sharing type to "global," even though they do not have permission to do so, making it visible to everyone in the space via a crafted a HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68385 | Kibana Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68385</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') (CWE-79) allows an authenticated user to embed a malicious script in content that will be served to web browsers causing cross-site scripting (XSS) (CAPEC-63) via a method in Vega bypassing a previous Vega XSS mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68387 | Kibana Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68387</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') (CWE-79) allows an unauthenticated user to embed a malicious script in content that will be served to web browsers causing cross-site scripting (XSS) (CAPEC-63) via a vulnerability a function handler in the Vega AST evaluator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68389 | Kibana Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68389</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling (CWE-770) in Kibana can allow a low-privileged authenticated user to cause Excessive Allocation (CAPEC-130) of computing resources and a denial of service (DoS) of the Kibana process via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68390 | Elasticsearch Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68390</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling (CWE-770) in Elasticsearch can allow an authenticated user with snapshot restore privileges to cause Excessive Allocation (CAPEC-130) of memory and a denial of service (DoS) via crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64663 | Custom Question Answering Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64663</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64676 | Microsoft Purview eDiscovery Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64676</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64677 | Office Out-of-Box Experience Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64677</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65037 | Azure Container Apps Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65037</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65041 | Microsoft Partner Center Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65041</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65046 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65046</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68383 | Filebeat Improper Validation of Specified Index, Position, or Offset in Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68383</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Index, Position, or Offset in Input (CWE-1285) in Filebeat Syslog parser and the Libbeat Dissect processor can allow a user to trigger a Buffer Overflow (CAPEC-100) and cause a denial of service (panic/crash) of the Filebeat process via either a malformed Syslog message or a malicious tokenizer pattern in the Dissect configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68384 | Elasticsearch Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68384</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling (CWE-770) in Elasticsearch can allow a low-privileged authenticated user to cause Excessive Allocation (CAPEC-130) causing a persistent denial of service (OOM crash) via submission of oversized user settings data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13427 | Authentication Bypass in Dialogflow CX Messenger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13427</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in Google Cloud Dialogflow CX Messenger allowed unauthenticated users to interact with restricted chat agents, gaining access to the agents' knowledge and the ability to trigger their intents, by manipulating initialization parameters or crafting specific API requests. 

All versions after August 20th, 2025 have been updated to protect from this vulnerability. No user action is required for this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68382 | Packetbeat Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68382</link><description>Out-of-bounds read (CWE-125) allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to perform a buffer overflow (CAPEC-100) via the NFS protocol dissector, leading to a denial-of-service (DoS) through a reliable process crash when handling truncated XDR-encoded RPC messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68381 | Packetbeat Improper Bounds Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68381</link><description>Improper Bounds Check (CWE-787) in Packetbeat can allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to exploit a Buffer Overflow (CAPEC-100) and reliably crash the application or cause significant resource exhaustion via a single crafted UDP packet with an invalid fragment sequence number.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68388 | Packetbeat Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68388</link><description>Allocation of resources without limits or throttling (CWE-770) allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause excessive allocation (CAPEC-130) of memory and CPU via the integration of malicious IPv4 fragments, leading to denial-of-service in Packetbeat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34452 | Streama Subtitle Download Path Traversal and SSRF Leading to Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34452</link><description>Streama versions 1.10.0 through 1.10.5 and prior to commit b7c8767 contain a combination of path traversal and server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerabilities in that allow an authenticated attacker to write arbitrary files to the server filesystem. The issue exists in the subtitle download functionality, where user-controlled parameters are used to fetch remote content and construct file paths without proper validation. By supplying a crafted subtitle download URL and a path traversal sequence in the file name, an attacker can write files to arbitrary locations on the server, potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34449 | Genymobile/scrcpy &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 Global Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34449</link><description>Genymobile/scrcpy versions up to and including 3.3.3 and prior to commit 3e40b24 contain a global buffer overflow vulnerability in the function sc_read32be, invoked via sc_device_msg_deserialize() and process_msgs(). Processing crafted device messages can cause reads beyond the bounds of a global buffer, leading to memory corruption or crashes. This vulnerability can be exploited to cause a denial of service and, under certain conditions, may be leveraged for further exploitation depending on the execution environment and available mitigations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34450 | merbanan/rtl_433 &amp;lt;= 25.02 Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34450</link><description>merbanan/rtl_433 versions up to and including 25.02 and prior to commit 25e47f8 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the function parse_rfraw() located in src/rfraw.c. When processing crafted or excessively large raw RF input data, the application may write beyond the bounds of a stack buffer, resulting in memory corruption or a crash. This vulnerability can be exploited to cause a denial of service and, under certain conditions, may be leveraged for further exploitation depending on the execution environment and available mitigations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34451 | rofl0r/proxychains-ng &amp;lt;= 4.17 Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34451</link><description>rofl0r/proxychains-ng versions up to and including 4.17 and prior to commit cc005b7 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the function proxy_from_string() located in src/libproxychains.c. When parsing crafted proxy configuration entries containing overly long username or password fields, the application may write beyond the bounds of fixed-size stack buffers, leading to memory corruption or crashes. This vulnerability may allow denial of service and, under certain conditions, could be leveraged for further exploitation depending on the execution environment and applied mitigations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53710 | Network boundaries not respected in certain Foundry namespaces.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53710</link><description>Due to a product misconfiguration in certain deployment types, it was possible from different pods in the same namespace to communicate with each other. This issue resulted in bypass of access control due to the presence of a vulnerable endpoint in Foundry Container Service that executed user-controlled commands locally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68161 | Apache Log4j Core: Missing TLS hostname verification in Socket appender</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68161</link><description>The Socket Appender in Apache Log4j Core versions 2.0-beta9 through 2.25.2 does not perform TLS hostname verification of the peer certificate, even when the  verifyHostName https://logging.apache.org/log4j/2.x/manual/appenders/network.html#SslConfiguration-attr-verifyHostName  configuration attribute or the  log4j2.sslVerifyHostName https://logging.apache.org/log4j/2.x/manual/systemproperties.html#log4j2.sslVerifyHostName  system property is set to true.

This issue may allow a man-in-the-middle attacker to intercept or redirect log traffic under the following conditions:

  *  The attacker is able to intercept or redirect network traffic between the client and the log receiver.
  *  The attacker can present a server certificate issued by a certification authority trusted by the Socket Appender’s configured trust store (or by the default Java trust store if no custom trust store is configured).


Users are advised to upgrade to Apache Log4j Core version 2.25.3, which addresses this issue.

As an alternative mitigation, the Socket Appender may be configured to use a private or restricted trust root to limit the set of trusted certificates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46268 | Advantech WebAccess/SCADA SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46268</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/SCADA 
is vulnerable to SQL injection, which may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62003 | BullWall Server Intrusion Protection connection delay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62003</link><description>BullWall Server Intrusion Protection has a noticeable delay before the MFA check when connecting via RDP. A remote authenticated attacker with administrative privileges can potentially bypass detection during this window. Versions 4.6.0.0, 4.6.0.6, 4.6.0.7, and 4.6.1.4 were confirmed to be affected; other versions before and after may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62004 | BullWall Server Intrusion Protection initialization race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62004</link><description>BullWall Server Intrusion Protection services are initialized after login services. An authenticated attacker with administrative permissions can log in after boot and bypass MFA. SIP service does not retroactively enforce the challenge or disconnect unauthenticated sessions. Versions 4.6.0.0, 4.6.0.6, 4.6.0.7, and 4.6.1.4 were confirmed to be affected; other versions before and after may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67653 | Advantech WebAccess/SCADA Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67653</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/SCADA is vulnerable to directory traversal, which may allow an attacker to determine the existence of arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14848 | Advantech WebAccess/SCADA Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14848</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/SCADA
is vulnerable to absolute directory traversal, which may allow an attacker to determine the existence of arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14849 | Advantech WebAccess/SCADA Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14849</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/SCADA 
is vulnerable to unrestricted file upload, which may allow an attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14850 | Advantech WebAccess/SCADA Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14850</link><description>Advantech WebAccess/SCADA is vulnerable to directory traversal, which may allow an attacker to delete arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62000 | BullWall Ransomware Containment incomplete file inspection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62000</link><description>BullWall Ransomware Containment does not entirely inspect a file to determine if it is ransomware. An authenticated attacker could bypass detection by encrypting a file and leaving the first four bytes unaltered. Versions 4.6.0.0, 4.6.0.6, 4.6.0.7, and 4.6.1.4 were confirmed to be affected; other versions before and after may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62001 | BullWall Ransomware Containment hard-coded folder exclusions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62001</link><description>BullWall Ransomware Containment contains excluded file paths, such as '$recycle.bin' that are not monitored. An attacker with file write permissions could bypass detection by renaming a directory. Versions 4.6.0.0, 4.6.0.6, 4.6.0.7, and 4.6.1.4 were confirmed to be affected; other versions before and after may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62002 | BullWall Ransomware Containment large file encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62002</link><description>BullWall Ransomware Containment relies on the number of file modifications to trigger detection. An authenticated attacker could encrypt a single large file without triggering a detection alert. Versions 4.6.0.0, 4.6.0.6, 4.6.0.7, and 4.6.1.4 were confirmed to be affected; other versions before and after may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63949 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in yohanawi Hotel Management System (commit 87e004a) allows a remote attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63949</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in yohanawi Hotel Management System (commit 87e004a) allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web script via the 'error' parameter in pages/room.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63951 | An insecure deserialization vulnerability exists in the rss-mp3.php script of the MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID project through commit 4b2334f0a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63951</link><description>An insecure deserialization vulnerability exists in the rss-mp3.php script of the MiczFlor RPi-Jukebox-RFID project through commit 4b2334f0ae0e87c0568876fc41c48c38aa9a7014 (2025-10-07). The 'rss' GET parameter receives data that is passed directly to the unserialize() function without validation. This allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary PHP objects, causing the application to process them and leading to errors or a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13911 | Inductive Automation Ignition Execution with Unnecessary Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13911</link><description>The vulnerability affects Ignition SCADA applications where Python 
scripting is utilized for automation purposes. The vulnerability arises 
from the absence of proper security controls that restrict which Python 
libraries can be imported and executed within the scripting environment.
 The core issue lies in the Ignition service account having system 
permissions beyond what an Ignition privileged user requires. When an 
authenticated administrator uploads a malicious project file containing 
Python scripts with bind shell capabilities, the application executes 
these scripts with the same privileges as the Ignition Gateway process, 
which typically runs with SYSTEM-level permissions on Windows. 
Alternative code execution patterns could lead to similar results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59529 | simple protocol server ignores accepts unlimited connections and logs failures without limit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59529</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In versions up to and including 0.9-rc2, the simple protocol server ignores the documented client limit and accepts unlimited connections, allowing for easy local DoS. Although `CLIENTS_MAX` is defined, `server_work()` unconditionally `accept()`s and `client_new()` always appends the new client and increments `n_clients`. There is no check against the limit. When client cannot be accepted as a result of maximal socket number of avahi-daemon, it logs unconditionally error per each connection. Unprivileged local users can exhaust daemon memory and file descriptors, causing a denial of service system-wide for mDNS/DNS-SD. Exhausting local file descriptors causes increased system load caused by logging errors of each of request. Overloading prevents glibc calls using nss-mdns plugins to resolve `*.local.` names and link-local addresses. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available, but a candidate fix is available in pull request 808, and some workarounds are available. Simple clients are offered for nss-mdns package functionality. It is not possible to disable the unix socket `/run/avahi-daemon/socket`, but resolution requests received via DBus are not affected directly. Tools avahi-resolve, avahi-resolve-address and avahi-resolve-host-name are not affected, they use DBus interface. It is possible to change permissions of unix socket after avahi-daemon is started. But avahi-daemon does not provide any configuration for it. Additional access restrictions like SELinux can also prevent unwanted tools to access the socket and keep resolution working for trusted users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63947 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in phpMsAdmin version 2.2 in the database_mode.php file. An attacker can execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63947</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in phpMsAdmin version 2.2 in the database_mode.php file. An attacker can execute arbitrary web script or HTML via the dbname parameter after a user is authenticated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63948 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in phpMsAdmin version 2.2 in the database_mode.php file. An attacker can execute arbitrary SQL commands...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63948</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in phpMsAdmin version 2.2 in the database_mode.php file. An attacker can execute arbitrary SQL commands via the dbname parameter, potentially leading to information disclosure or database manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63950 | An insecure deserialization vulnerability exists in the download.php script of the to3k Twittodon application through commit b1c58a7d1dc664b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63950</link><description>An insecure deserialization vulnerability exists in the download.php script of the to3k Twittodon application through commit b1c58a7d1dc664b38deb486ca290779621342c0b (2023-02-28). The 'obj' parameter receives base64-encoded data that is passed directly to the unserialize() function without validation. This allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary PHP objects, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67163 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Machines Forum v2.1.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67163</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Machines Forum v2.1.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Forum Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53937 | Hubstaff 1.6.14 DLL Search Order Hijacking via wow64log Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53937</link><description>Hubstaff 1.6.14 contains a DLL search order hijacking vulnerability that allows attackers to replace a missing system32 wow64log.dll with a malicious library. Attackers can generate a custom DLL using Metasploit and place it in the system32 directory to obtain a reverse shell during application startup.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53940 | Codigo Markdown Editor 1.0.1 Electron Arbitrary Code Execution via Markdown File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53940</link><description>Codigo Markdown Editor 1.0.1 contains a code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to run arbitrary system commands by crafting a malicious markdown file. Attackers can embed a video source with an onerror event that executes shell commands through Node.js child_process module when the file is opened.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14889 | Campcodes Advanced Voting Management System Password voters_edit.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14889</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Advanced Voting Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/voters_edit.php of the component Password Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25228 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.47 Virtual Context Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25228</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to leak virtual context URLs via the HTTP Referer header when users interact with third-party domains. Sensitive virtual context information can be exposed to external domains through page builder interactions and link/image loading.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25229 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.29 MVC Forms Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25229</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated users with 'Read data' permissions to upload arbitrary file types via MVC form file uploader components. Attackers can manipulate file names and upload potentially malicious files to the system, enabling unauthorized file uploads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25230 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.0 User Widget Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25230</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated users to view sensitive system objects through the live site widget properties dialog. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to access unauthorized system information without proper access controls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36889 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.90 Administration Interface Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36889</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via error messages containing specially crafted object names. This allows malicious scripts to execute in users' browsers when administrators view error messages in the administration interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36890 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 10 Administrator Access Control Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36890</link><description>An access control bypass vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows administrators to modify global administrator user privileges via unauthorized requests. Attackers could potentially compromise global administrator accounts and invalidate security-sensitive macros by manipulating user privilege levels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36891 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.49 File Upload Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36891</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to upload files with spoofed Content-Type that do not match file extensions. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious files with manipulated MIME types, allowing malicious scripts to execute in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47711 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.52 Online Marketing Macros SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47711</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated editors to inject malicious SQL queries via online marketing macro method parameters. This enables unauthorized database access and potential data manipulation by exploiting macro method input validation weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47712 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.102 URL Hashing Cryptography Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47712</link><description>A cryptography vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to potentially manipulate URL hash values through existing hashing mechanisms. The hotfix introduces an additional security layer to prevent hash value reuse and potential exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50680 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.92 Email Marketing Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50680</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows administration users to inject malicious scripts via email marketing templates. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious scripts that could compromise user browsers and steal sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50681 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.88 Rich Text Editor Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50681</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via administration input fields in the Rich text editor component. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary scripts in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50682 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.79 Routing Engine CRLF Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50682</link><description>A CRLF injection vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to manipulate URL query string redirects via improper encoding in the routing engine. This could enable header injection and potentially facilitate further web application attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50683 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.74 Form Configuration Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50683</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via form redirect URL configuration. This allows malicious scripts to execute in users' browsers through unvalidated form configuration settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50684 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.71 Form Emails HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50684</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious HTML values into form submission emails via unencoded form fields. Unencoded form values could enable HTML content execution in recipient email clients, potentially compromising email security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50685 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.56 File Upload Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50685</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts via XML file uploads as page attachments or metafiles. Attackers can upload malicious XML files that enable stored XSS, allowing malicious scripts to execute in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50686 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0 Portal Engine Form Control Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50686</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to view sensitive stack trace details via Portal Engine form control error messages. Detailed error messages can expose internal system information and potentially reveal implementation details to unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53736 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.120 Administration Interface Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53736</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts in the administration interface. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary scripts within the administrative context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53737 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.101 Localization Application Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53737</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows global administrators to inject malicious payloads via the Localization application. Attackers can execute scripts that could affect multiple parts of the administration interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53738 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.109 Page Preview Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53738</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts via page preview URLs. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary scripts in users' browsers during page preview interactions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53934 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 12.0.98 GetResource Handler Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53934</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to launch DoS attacks via specially crafted requests to the GetResource handler. Improper input validation enables remote attackers to potentially disrupt service availability through maliciously constructed requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53935 | WBiz Desk 1.2 SQL Injection Vulnerability via ticket.php Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53935</link><description>WBiz Desk 1.2 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows non-admin users to manipulate database queries through the 'tk' parameter in ticket.php. Attackers can inject crafted SQL statements using UNION-based techniques to extract sensitive database information by sending malformed requests to the ticket endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53936 | Cameleon CMS 2.7.4 Authenticated Persistent Cross-Site Scripting via Post Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53936</link><description>Cameleon CMS 2.7.4 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious scripts into post titles. Attackers can create posts with embedded SVG scripts that execute when other users mouse over the post title, potentially stealing session cookies and executing arbitrary JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53938 | RockMongo 1.1.7 Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53938</link><description>RockMongo 1.1.7 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts through multiple unencoded input parameters. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by submitting crafted payloads in database, collection, and login parameters to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53939 | TinyWebGallery v2.5 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Folder Name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53939</link><description>TinyWebGallery v2.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts through the folder name parameter. Attackers can edit album folder names with script tags to execute arbitrary JavaScript when other users view the affected gallery pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53941 | EasyPHP Webserver 14.1 Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53941</link><description>EasyPHP Webserver 14.1 contains an OS command injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary system commands by injecting malicious payloads through the app_service_control parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to /index.php?zone=settings with crafted app_service_control values to execute commands with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53942 | File Thingie 2.5.7 Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53942</link><description>File Thingie 2.5.7 contains an authenticated file upload vulnerability that allows remote attackers to upload malicious PHP zip archives to the web server. Attackers can create a custom PHP payload, upload and unzip it, and then execute arbitrary system commands through a crafted PHP script with a command parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53943 | GLPI 9.5.7 Username Enumeration Vulnerability via Lost Password Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53943</link><description>GLPI 9.5.7 contains a username enumeration vulnerability in the lost password recovery mechanism that allows attackers to validate email addresses. Attackers can systematically test email addresses by submitting requests to the password reset endpoint and analyzing response differences to identify valid user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53944 | EasyPHP Webserver 14.1 Path Traversal via Directory Traversal Sequences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53944</link><description>EasyPHP Webserver 14.1 contains a path traversal vulnerability that allows remote users with low privileges to access files outside the document root by bypassing SecurityManager restrictions. Attackers can send GET requests with encoded directory traversal sequences like /..%5c..%5c to read system files such as /windows/win.ini.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58317 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.164 Cookie Security Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58317</link><description>A cookie security configuration vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to bypass SSL requirements when setting administration cookies via web.config. The vulnerability affects .NET Framework projects by incorrectly handling the 'requireSSL' attribute, potentially compromising session security and authentication state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58318 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.162 Rich Text Editor Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58318</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via the rich text editor component for page and form builders. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by entering malicious URIs, potentially allowing malicious scripts to execute in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58319 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.160 Pages Dashboard Widget Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58319</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via the Pages dashboard widget configuration dialog. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious scripts in administrative users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58320 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.159 Authentication Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58320</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows public users to access sensitive administration interface hostname details during authentication. Attackers can retrieve confidential hostname configuration information through a public endpoint, potentially exposing internal network details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58321 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.159 Form Validation Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58321</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via form validation rule configuration. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious scripts that will run in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58322 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.158 Shipping Options Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58322</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious code into shipping options configuration. This could lead to potential theft of sensitive data by executing malicious scripts in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58323 | Kentico Xperience &amp;lt;= 13.0.158 Checkbox Form Component Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58323</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows attackers to inject malicious scripts via the Checkbox form component. This allows malicious scripts to execute in users' browsers by exploiting HTML support in the form builder.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64400 | Insufficient permission checks when pre-enrolling users Summary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64400</link><description>Control Panel provides an API for pre-registering  into an enrollment and organization prior to a user's first login. The API for creating users checks that the account requesting a user creation has `edit` on the enrollment-level user directory, but is missing a separate check that the enrollment editor has access (or belongs to) the organization that they are adding a user to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65566 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. When the UPF ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65566</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. When the UPF receives a PFCP Session Report Response that is missing the mandatory Cause Information Element, the session report handler dereferences a nil pointer instead of rejecting the malformed message. This triggers a panic and terminates the UPF process. An attacker who can send PFCP Session Report Response messages to the UPF's N4/PFCP endpoint can exploit this flaw to repeatedly crash the UPF and disrupt user-plane services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65567 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. After PFCP as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65567</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. After PFCP association, a specially crafted PFCP Session Establishment Request with a CreatePDR that contains a malformed Flow-Description is not robustly validated. The Flow-Description parser (parseFlowDesc) can read beyond the bounds of the provided buffer, causing a panic and terminating the UPF process. An attacker who can send PFCP Session Establishment Request messages to the UPF's N4/PFCP endpoint can exploit this issue to repeatedly crash the UPF.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65568 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. After PFCP as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65568</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. After PFCP association, a PFCP Session Establishment Request that includes a CreateFAR with an empty or truncated IPv4 address field is not properly validated. During parsing, parseFAR() calls ip2int(), which performs an out-of-bounds read on the IPv4 address buffer and triggers an index-out-of-range panic. An attacker who can send PFCP Session Establishment Request messages to the UPF's N4/PFCP endpoint can exploit this issue to repeatedly crash the UPF and disrupt user-plane services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65562 | The free5GC UPF suffers from a lack of bounds checking on the SEID when processing PFCP Session Deletion Requests. An unauthenticated remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65562</link><description>The free5GC UPF suffers from a lack of bounds checking on the SEID when processing PFCP Session Deletion Requests. An unauthenticated remote attacker can send a request with a very large SEID (e.g., 0xFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFF) that causes an integer conversion/underflow in LocalNode.DeleteSess() / LocalNode.Sess() when a uint64 SEID is converted to int and used in index arithmetic. This leads to a negative index into n.sess and a Go runtime panic, resulting in a denial of service (UPF crash). The issue has been reproduced on free5GC v4.1.0 with crashes observed in the session lookup/deletion path in internal/pfcp/node.go; other versions may also be affected. No authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65563 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (component upf-epc/pfcpiface) up to at least version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65563</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (component upf-epc/pfcpiface) up to at least version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. When the UPF receives a PFCP Association Setup Request that is missing the mandatory NodeID Information Element, the association setup handler dereferences a nil pointer instead of validating the message, causing a panic and terminating the UPF process. An attacker who can send PFCP Association Setup Request messages to the UPF's N4/PFCP endpoint can exploit this issue to repeatedly crash the UPF and disrupt user-plane services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65564 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-upf (upf-epc-pfcpiface) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. When the UPF receives a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65564</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-upf (upf-epc-pfcpiface) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. When the UPF receives a PFCP Association Setup Request that is missing the mandatory Recovery Time Stamp Information Element, the association setup handler dereferences a nil pointer via IE.RecoveryTimeStamp() instead of validating the message. This results in a panic and terminates the UPF process. An attacker who can send PFCP Association Setup Request messages to the UPF's N4/PFCP endpoint can exploit this issue to repeatedly crash the UPF and disrupt user-plane services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65565 | A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. After PFCP as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65565</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the omec-project UPF (pfcpiface component) in version upf-epc-pfcpiface:2.1.3-dev. After PFCP association is established, a PFCP Session Establishment Request that is missing the mandatory F-SEID (CPF-SEID) Information Element is not properly validated. The session establishment handler calls IE.FSEID() on a nil pointer, which triggers a panic and terminates the UPF process. An attacker who can send PFCP Session Establishment Request messages to the UPF's N4/PFCP endpoint can exploit this issue to repeatedly crash the UPF and disrupt user-plane services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14885 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System Leads Generation user_leads.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14885</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user_leads.php of the component Leads Generation Module. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59949 | FreshRSS has Logout CSRF that Leads to DoS via &amp;lt;track src&amp;gt;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59949</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions prior to 1.27.1 have a logout cross-site request forgery vulnerability that can lead to denial of service via . Version 1.27.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65559 | An issue was discovered in Open5GS 2.7.5-49-g465e90f, when processing a PFCP Session Establishment Request (type=50), the UPF crashes with a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65559</link><description>An issue was discovered in Open5GS 2.7.5-49-g465e90f, when processing a PFCP Session Establishment Request (type=50), the UPF crashes with a reachable assertion in `lib/pfcp/context.c` (`ogs_pfcp_object_teid_hash_set`) if the CreatePDR?PDI?F-TEID has CH=1 and the F-TEID address-family flag(s) (IPv4/IPv6) do not match the GTP-U resource family configured for the selected DNN (Network Instance), resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65561 | An issue was discovered in function LocalNode.Sess in free5GC 4.1.0 allowing attackers to cause a denial of service or other unspecified imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65561</link><description>An issue was discovered in function LocalNode.Sess in free5GC 4.1.0 allowing attackers to cause a denial of service or other unspecified impacts via crafted header Local SEID to the PFCP Session Modification Request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67745 | Myhoard logs backup encryption key in plain text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67745</link><description>MyHoard is a daemon for creating, managing and restoring MySQL backups. Starting in version 1.0.1 and prior to version 1.3.0, in some cases, myhoard logs the whole backup info, including the encryption key. Version 1.3.0 fixes the issue. As a workaround, direct logs into /dev/null.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56157 | Default credentials in Dify thru 1.5.1. PostgreSQL username and password specified in the docker-compose.yaml file included in its source co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56157</link><description>Default credentials in Dify thru 1.5.1. PostgreSQL username and password specified in the docker-compose.yaml file included in its source code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63387 | Dify v1.9.1 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. An unauthenticated attacker can directly send HTTP GET requests to the /console/api/syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63387</link><description>Dify v1.9.1 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. An unauthenticated attacker can directly send HTTP GET requests to the /console/api/system-features endpoint without any authentication credentials or session tokens. The endpoint fails to implement proper authorization checks, allowing anonymous access to sensitive system configuration data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14739 | Uninitialized Pointer Vulnerability in TP-Link WR940N and WR941ND</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14739</link><description>Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability in TP-Link WR940N and WR941ND allows local unauthenticated attackers the ability to execute DoS attack 

and potentially arbitrary code execution

under the context of the ‘root’ user.This issue affects WR940N and WR941ND: ≤ WR940N v5 3.20.1 Build 200316, 

≤

 WR941ND v6 3.16.9 Build 151203.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14737 | Command Injection Vulnerability in TP-Link WA850RE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14737</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in TP-Link WA850RE (httpd modules) allows authenticated adjacent attacker to inject arbitrary commands.This issue affects: ≤ WA850RE V2_160527, 

≤ 

WA850RE V3_160922.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14738 | Configuration Disclosure Vulnerability in TP-Link WA850RE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14738</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in TP-Link WA850RE (httpd modules) allows unauthenticated attackers to download the configuration file.This issue affects: ≤ WA850RE V2_160527,

 ≤ 

 WA850RE V3_160922.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14879 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request onSSIDChange stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14879</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/onSSIDChange of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument ssid_index causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14884 | D-Link DIR-605 Firmware Update Service command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14884</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-605 202WWB03. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Firmware Update Service. Performing manipulation results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62960 | WordPress Construction Light theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62960</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sparkle WP Construction Light allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Construction Light: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62961 | WordPress Sparkle FSE theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62961</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sparkle WP Sparkle FSE allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sparkle FSE: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62998 | WordPress WP AI CoPilot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62998</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in WP Messiah WP AI CoPilot allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects WP AI CoPilot: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63002 | WordPress Sermon Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.30.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63002</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpforchurch Sermon Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sermon Manager: from n/a through 2.30.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63043 | WordPress Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.19 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63043</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in PickPlugins Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 2.3.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64235 | WordPress Tuturn plugin &amp;lt; 3.6 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64235</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in AmentoTech Tuturn allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Tuturn: from n/a before 3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14896 | due to insufficient sanitazation in Vega’s `convert()` function when `safeMode` is enabled and the spec variable is an array. An attacker ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14896</link><description>due to insufficient sanitazation in Vega’s `convert()` function when `safeMode` is enabled and the spec variable is an array. An attacker can craft a malicious Vega diagram specification that will allow them to send requests to any URL, including local file system paths, leading to exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64236 | WordPress Tuturn plugin &amp;lt; 3.6 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64236</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in AmentoTech Tuturn allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Tuturn: from n/a before 3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64282 | WordPress Radius Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64282</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in RadiusTheme Radius Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Radius Blocks: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64355 | WordPress JetElements For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64355</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetElements For Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects JetElements For Elementor: from n/a through 2.7.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66058 | WordPress Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.17 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66058</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PickPlugins Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 2.3.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14877 | Campcodes Supplier Management System add_retailer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14877</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_retailer.php. The manipulation of the argument cmbAreaCode leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14878 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request wirelessRestart stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14878</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/wirelessRestart of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument GO results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63386 | A Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) misconfiguration vulnerability exists in Dify v1.9.1 in the /console/api/setup endpoint. The endpoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63386</link><description>A Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) misconfiguration vulnerability exists in Dify v1.9.1 in the /console/api/setup endpoint. The endpoint implements an insecure CORS policy that reflects any Origin header and enables Access-Control-Allow-Credentials: true, permitting arbitrary external domains to make authenticated requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14823 | Certificate Signing Extension Returns Encrypted Values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14823</link><description>In deployments using the ScreenConnect™ Certificate Signing Extension, encrypted configuration values including an Azure Key Vault-related key, could be returned to unauthenticated users through a client-facing endpoint under certain conditions. The values remained encrypted and securely stored at rest; however, an encrypted representation could be exposed in client responses. Updating the Certificate Signing Extension to version 1.0.12 or higher ensures configuration handling occurs exclusively on the server side, preventing encrypted values from being transmitted to or rendered by client-side components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63390 | An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in AnythingLLM v1.8.5 in via the /api/workspaces endpoint. The endpoint fails to implement pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63390</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in AnythingLLM v1.8.5 in via the /api/workspaces endpoint. The endpoint fails to implement proper authentication checks, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to enumerate and retrieve detailed information about all configured workspaces. Exposed data includes: workspace identifiers (id, name, slug), AI model configurations (chatProvider, chatModel, agentProvider), system prompts (openAiPrompt), operational parameters (temperature, history length, similarity thresholds), vector search settings, chat modes, and timestamps.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68469 | ImageMagick vulnerable to heap-buffer-overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68469</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.1-14, ImageMagick crashes when processing a crafted TIFF file. Version 7.1.1-14 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63388 | A Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) misconfiguration vulnerability exists in Dify v1.9.1 in the /console/api/system-features endpoint. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63388</link><description>A Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) misconfiguration vulnerability exists in Dify v1.9.1 in the /console/api/system-features endpoint. The endpoint implements an overly permissive CORS policy that reflects arbitrary Origin headers and sets Access-Control-Allow-Credentials: true, allowing any external domain to make authenticated cross-origin requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68278 | tinacms vulnerable to arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68278</link><description>Tina is a headless content management system. In tinacms prior to version 3.1.1, tinacms uses the gray-matter package in an insecure way allowing attackers that can control the content of the processed markdown files, e.g., blog posts, to execute arbitrary code. tinacms version 3.1.1, @tinacms/cli version 2.0.4, and @tinacms/graphql version 2.0.3 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63389 | A critical authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Ollama platform's API endpoints in versions prior to and including v0.12.3. The pla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63389</link><description>A critical authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Ollama platform's API endpoints in versions prior to and including v0.12.3. The platform exposes multiple API endpoints without requiring authentication, enabling remote attackers to perform unauthorized model management operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63391 | An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Open-WebUI &lt;=0.6.32 in the /api/config endpoint. The endpoint lacks proper authentication a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63391</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Open-WebUI &lt;=0.6.32 in the /api/config endpoint. The endpoint lacks proper authentication and authorization controls, exposing sensitive system configuration data to unauthenticated remote attackers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64723 | Arduino IDE for macOS has TCC Bypass via Dynamic Library Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64723</link><description>Arduino IDE is an integrated development environment. Prior to version 2.3.7, Arduino IDE for macOS was configured with overly permissive security entitlements that could bypass macOS Hardened Runtime protections. This configuration allows attackers to inject malicious dynamic libraries into the application process, gaining access to all TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions granted to the application. The fix is included starting from the `2.3.7 ` release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64724 | Arduino IDE for macOS has Insecure File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64724</link><description>Arduino IDE is an integrated development environment. Prior to version 2.3.7, Arduino IDE for macOS is installed with world-writable file permissions on sensitive application components, allowing any local user to replace legitimate files with malicious code. When another user launches the application, the malicious code executes with that user's privileges, enabling privilege escalation and unauthorized access to sensitive data. The fix is included starting from the `2.3.7` release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65007 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in WODESYS WD-R608U router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65007</link><description>In WODESYS WD-R608U router (also known as WDR122B V2.0 and WDR28) due to lack of authentication in the configuration change module in the adm.cgi endpoint, the unauthenticated attacker can execute commands including backup creation, device restart and resetting the device to factory settings.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version WDR28081123OV1.01 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65008 | OS Command Injection in WODESYS WD-R608U router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65008</link><description>In WODESYS WD-R608U router (also known as WDR122B V2.0 and WDR28) due to lack of validation in the langGet parameter in the adm.cgi endpoint, the malicious attacker can execute system shell commands.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version WDR28081123OV1.01 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65009 | Insecure Password Storage in WODESYS WD-R608U router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65009</link><description>In WODESYS WD-R608U router (also known as WDR122B V2.0 and WDR28) admin password is stored in configuration file as plaintext and can be obtained by unauthorized user by direct references to the resource in question.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version WDR28081123OV1.01 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65010 | Missing authorizations for admin panel password change in WODESYS WD-R608U router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65010</link><description>WODESYS WD-R608U router (also known as WDR122B V2.0 and WDR28) is vulnerable to Broken Access Control in initial configuration wizard.cgi endpoint. Malicious attacker can change admin panel password without authorization. The vulnerability can also be exploited after the initial configuration has been set.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version WDR28081123OV1.01 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65011 | Unauthorized Access to files in WODESYS WD-R608U router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65011</link><description>In WODESYS WD-R608U router (also known as WDR122B V2.0 and WDR28) an unauthorised user can view configuration files by directly referencing the resource in question.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version WDR28081123OV1.01 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68323 | usb: typec: ucsi: fix use-after-free caused by uec-&amp;gt;work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68323</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: typec: ucsi: fix use-after-free caused by uec-&gt;work

The delayed work uec-&gt;work is scheduled in gaokun_ucsi_probe()
but never properly canceled in gaokun_ucsi_remove(). This creates
use-after-free scenarios where the ucsi and gaokun_ucsi structure
are freed after ucsi_destroy() completes execution, while the
gaokun_ucsi_register_worker() might be either currently executing
or still pending in the work queue. The already-freed gaokun_ucsi
or ucsi structure may then be accessed.

Furthermore, the race window is 3 seconds, which is sufficiently
long to make this bug easily reproducible. The following is the
trace captured by KASAN:

==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __run_timers+0x5ec/0x630
Write of size 8 at addr ffff00000ec28cc8 by task swapper/0/0
...
Call trace:
 show_stack+0x18/0x24 (C)
 dump_stack_lvl+0x78/0x90
 print_report+0x114/0x580
 kasan_report+0xa4/0xf0
 __asan_report_store8_noabort+0x20/0x2c
 __run_timers+0x5ec/0x630
 run_timer_softirq+0xe8/0x1cc
 handle_softirqs+0x294/0x720
 __do_softirq+0x14/0x20
 ____do_softirq+0x10/0x1c
 call_on_irq_stack+0x30/0x48
 do_softirq_own_stack+0x1c/0x28
 __irq_exit_rcu+0x27c/0x364
 irq_exit_rcu+0x10/0x1c
 el1_interrupt+0x40/0x60
 el1h_64_irq_handler+0x18/0x24
 el1h_64_irq+0x6c/0x70
 arch_local_irq_enable+0x4/0x8 (P)
 do_idle+0x334/0x458
 cpu_startup_entry+0x60/0x70
 rest_init+0x158/0x174
 start_kernel+0x2f8/0x394
 __primary_switched+0x8c/0x94

Allocated by task 72 on cpu 0 at 27.510341s:
 kasan_save_stack+0x2c/0x54
 kasan_save_track+0x24/0x5c
 kasan_save_alloc_info+0x40/0x54
 __kasan_kmalloc+0xa0/0xb8
 __kmalloc_node_track_caller_noprof+0x1c0/0x588
 devm_kmalloc+0x7c/0x1c8
 gaokun_ucsi_probe+0xa0/0x840  auxiliary_bus_probe+0x94/0xf8
 really_probe+0x17c/0x5b8
 __driver_probe_device+0x158/0x2c4
 driver_probe_device+0x10c/0x264
 __device_attach_driver+0x168/0x2d0
 bus_for_each_drv+0x100/0x188
 __device_attach+0x174/0x368
 device_initial_probe+0x14/0x20
 bus_probe_device+0x120/0x150
 device_add+0xb3c/0x10fc
 __auxiliary_device_add+0x88/0x130
...

Freed by task 73 on cpu 1 at 28.910627s:
 kasan_save_stack+0x2c/0x54
 kasan_save_track+0x24/0x5c
 __kasan_save_free_info+0x4c/0x74
 __kasan_slab_free+0x60/0x8c
 kfree+0xd4/0x410
 devres_release_all+0x140/0x1f0
 device_unbind_cleanup+0x20/0x190
 device_release_driver_internal+0x344/0x460
 device_release_driver+0x18/0x24
 bus_remove_device+0x198/0x274
 device_del+0x310/0xa84
...

The buggy address belongs to the object at ffff00000ec28c00
 which belongs to the cache kmalloc-512 of size 512
The buggy address is located 200 bytes inside of
 freed 512-byte region
The buggy address belongs to the physical page:
page: refcount:0 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0x0 pfn:0x4ec28
head: order:2 mapcount:0 entire_mapcount:0 nr_pages_mapped:0 pincount:0
flags: 0x3fffe0000000040(head|node=0|zone=0|lastcpupid=0x1ffff)
page_type: f5(slab)
raw: 03fffe0000000040 ffff000008801c80 dead000000000122 0000000000000000
raw: 0000000000000000 0000000080100010 00000000f5000000 0000000000000000
head: 03fffe0000000040 ffff000008801c80 dead000000000122 0000000000000000
head: 0000000000000000 0000000080100010 00000000f5000000 0000000000000000
head: 03fffe0000000002 fffffdffc03b0a01 00000000ffffffff 00000000ffffffff
head: ffffffffffffffff 0000000000000000 00000000ffffffff 0000000000000004
page dumped because: kasan: bad access detected

Memory state around the buggy address:
 ffff00000ec28b80: fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc fc
 ffff00000ec28c00: fa fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb
&gt;ffff00000ec28c80: fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb
                                              ^
 ffff00000ec28d00: fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb
 ffff00000ec28d80: fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb fb
================================================================
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68324 | scsi: imm: Fix use-after-free bug caused by unfinished delayed work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68324</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: imm: Fix use-after-free bug caused by unfinished delayed work

The delayed work item 'imm_tq' is initialized in imm_attach() and
scheduled via imm_queuecommand() for processing SCSI commands.  When the
IMM parallel port SCSI host adapter is detached through imm_detach(),
the imm_struct device instance is deallocated.

However, the delayed work might still be pending or executing
when imm_detach() is called, leading to use-after-free bugs
when the work function imm_interrupt() accesses the already
freed imm_struct memory.

The race condition can occur as follows:

CPU 0(detach thread)   | CPU 1
                       | imm_queuecommand()
                       |   imm_queuecommand_lck()
imm_detach()           |     schedule_delayed_work()
  kfree(dev) //FREE    | imm_interrupt()
                       |   dev = container_of(...) //USE
                           dev-&gt; //USE

Add disable_delayed_work_sync() in imm_detach() to guarantee proper
cancellation of the delayed work item before imm_struct is deallocated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68325 | net/sched: sch_cake: Fix incorrect qlen reduction in cake_drop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68325</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: sch_cake: Fix incorrect qlen reduction in cake_drop

In cake_drop(), qdisc_tree_reduce_backlog() is used to update the qlen
and backlog of the qdisc hierarchy. Its caller, cake_enqueue(), assumes
that the parent qdisc will enqueue the current packet. However, this
assumption breaks when cake_enqueue() returns NET_XMIT_CN: the parent
qdisc stops enqueuing current packet, leaving the tree qlen/backlog
accounting inconsistent. This mismatch can lead to a NULL dereference
(e.g., when the parent Qdisc is qfq_qdisc).

This patch computes the qlen/backlog delta in a more robust way by
observing the difference before and after the series of cake_drop()
calls, and then compensates the qdisc tree accounting if cake_enqueue()
returns NET_XMIT_CN.

To ensure correct compensation when ACK thinning is enabled, a new
variable is introduced to keep qlen unchanged.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63757 | Integer overflow vulnerability in the yuv2ya16_X_c_template function in libswscale/output.c in FFmpeg 8.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63757</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in the yuv2ya16_X_c_template function in libswscale/output.c in FFmpeg 8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64468 | Use-after-Free in sentry!sentry_span_set_data() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64468</link><description>There is a use-after-free vulnerability in sentry!sentry_span_set_data() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64469 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in LVResource::DetachResource() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64469</link><description>There is a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in LVResFile::FindRsrcListEntry() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7358 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Utarit Informatics&amp;#x27; SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7358</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Utarit Informatics Services Inc. SoliClub allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects SoliClub: before 5.3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64466 | Out-of-Bounds Read in lvre!ExecPostedProcRecPost() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64466</link><description>There is an out of bounds read vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in lvre!ExecPostedProcRecPost() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64467 | Out-of-Bounds Read in LVResFile::FindRsrcListEntry() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64467</link><description>There is an out of bounds read vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in LVResFile::FindRsrcListEntry() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7047 | Missing Authorization in Utarit Informatics&amp;#x27; SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7047</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Utarit Informatics Services Inc. SoliClub allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects SoliClub: before 5.3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1031 | IDOR in Utarit Informatics&amp;#x27; SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1031</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Utarit Informatics Services Inc. SoliClub allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects SoliClub: from 5.2.4 before 5.3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64462 | Out-of-Bounds Read in LVResFile::RGetMemFileHandle() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64462</link><description>There is an out of bounds read vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in LVResFile::RGetMemFileHandle() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64463 | Out-of-Bounds Read in LVResource::DetachResource() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64463</link><description>There is an out of bounds read vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in LVResource::DetachResource() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64464 | Out-of-Bounds Read in lvre!VisaWriteFromFile() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64464</link><description>There is an out of bounds read vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in lvre!VisaWriteFromFile() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64465 | Out-of-Bounds Read in lvre!DataSizeTDR() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64465</link><description>There is an out of bounds read vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in lvre!DataSizeTDR() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14744 | Filename spoofing via Unicode Right-to-Left Override in Firefox for iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14744</link><description>Unicode RTLO characters could allow malicious websites to spoof filenames in the downloads UI for Firefox for iOS, potentially tricking users into saving files of an unexpected file type. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 144.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14860 | Use-after-free in the Disability Access APIs component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14860</link><description>Use-after-free in the Disability Access APIs component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 146.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14861 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox 146.0.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14861</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 146. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 146.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1029 | Hardcoded Credentials in Utarit Informatics&amp;#x27; SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1029</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Utarit Information Services Inc. SoliClub allows Read Sensitive Constants Within an Executable.This issue affects SoliClub: from 5.2.4 before 5.3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1030 | Sensitive Data Exposure in Utarit Informatics&amp;#x27; SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1030</link><description>Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Utarit Informatics Services Inc. SoliClub allows Query System for Information.This issue affects SoliClub: from 5.2.4 before 5.3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64461 | Out of Bounds Write in mgocre_SH_25_3!RevBL() in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64461</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability in NI LabVIEW in mgocre_SH_25_3!RevBL() when parsing a corrupted VI file.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q3 (25.3) and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9787 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9787</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 177400 and below are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in the NOC view.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65000 | Exposure of SSH Private Keys in Remote Alert Handlers (Linux) Rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65000</link><description>SSH private keys of the "Remote alert handlers (Linux)" rule were exposed in the rule page's HTML source in Checkmk &lt;= 2.4.0p18 and all versions of Checkmk 2.3.0. This potentially allowed unauthorized triggering of predefined alert handlers on hosts where the handler was deployed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40891 | HTML injection in in Time Machine functionality in Guardian/CMC before 25.5.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40891</link><description>A Stored HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the Time Machine Snapshot Diff functionality due to improper validation of network traffic data. An unauthenticated attacker can send specially crafted network packets at two different times to inject HTML tags into asset attributes across two snapshots. Exploitation requires a victim to use the Time Machine Snapshot Diff feature on those specific snapshots and perform specific GUI actions, at which point the injected HTML renders in their browser, enabling phishing and open redirect attacks. Full XSS exploitation is prevented by input validation and Content Security Policy. Attack complexity is high due to multiple required conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40892 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Reports in Guardian/CMC before 25.5.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40892</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability was discovered in the Reports functionality due to improper validation of an input parameter. An authenticated user with report privileges can define a malicious report containing a JavaScript payload, or a victim can be socially engineered to import a malicious report template. When the victim views or imports the report, the XSS executes in their browser context, allowing the attacker to perform unauthorized actions as the victim, such as modify application data, disrupt application availability, and access limited sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40893 | HTML injection in Asset List in Guardian/CMC before 25.5.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40893</link><description>A Stored HTML Injection vulnerability was discovered in the Asset List functionality due to improper validation of network traffic data. An unauthenticated attacker can send specially crafted network packets to inject HTML tags into asset attributes. When a victim views the affected assets in the Asset List (and similar functions), the injected HTML renders in their browser, enabling phishing and possibly open redirect attacks. Full XSS exploitation and direct information disclosure are prevented by the existing input validation and Content Security Policy configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40898 | Path traversal in Import Arc data archive functionality in Guardian/CMC before 25.5.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40898</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was discovered in the Import Arc data archive functionality due to insufficient validation of the input file. An authenticated user with limited privileges, by uploading a specifically-crafted Arc data archive, can potentially write arbitrary files in arbitrary paths, altering the device configuration and/or affecting its availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13110 | HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.7.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via &amp;#x27;woof_add_subscr&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13110</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7.3 via the "woof_add_subscr" function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to create product messenger subscriptions on behalf of arbitrary users, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14277 | Prime Slider – Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.0.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14277</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.9 via the import_elementor_template AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14437 | Hummingbird &amp;lt;= 3.18.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14437</link><description>The Hummingbird Performance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.18.0 via the 'request' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including Cloudflare API credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14618 | Sweet Energy Efficiency &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Graph Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14618</link><description>The Sweet Energy Efficiency plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'sweet_energy_efficiency_action' AJAX handler in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to read, modify, and delete arbitrary graphs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10910 | Gaining remote control over Govee devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10910</link><description>A flaw in the binding process of Govee’s cloud platform and devices allows a remote attacker to bind an existing, online Govee device to the attacker’s account, resulting in full control of the device and removal of the device from its legitimate owner’s account.
The server‑side API allows device association using a set of identifiers: "device", "sku", "type", and a client‑computed "value", that are not cryptographically bound to a secret originating from the device itself.

The vulnerability has been verified for the Govee H6056 - lamp device in firmware version 1.08.13, but may affect also other Govee cloud‑connected devices. The vendor is not able to provide a list of affected products, but rolls out a firmware and server-side fixes. Devices that reached end‑of‑life for security support need replacement with newer models supporting updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40602 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability due to insufficient authorization in the SonicWall SMA1000 appliance management console (AMC).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40602</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability due to insufficient authorization in the SonicWall SMA1000 appliance management console (AMC).</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13641 | Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and Themes – NextGEN Gallery &amp;lt;= 3.59.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via &amp;#x27;template&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13641</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and Themes – NextGEN Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.59.12 via the 'template' shortcode parameter. This is due to insufficient path validation that allows absolute paths to be provided. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, bypassing web server restrictions like .htaccess. Successful exploitation could lead to information disclosure, code execution in the WordPress context, and potential remote code execution if combined with arbitrary file upload capabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13730 | OpenID Connect Generic Client &amp;lt;= 3.10.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13730</link><description>The OpenID Connect Generic Client plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'openid_connect_generic_auth_url' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14364 | Demo Importer Plus &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Site Reset and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14364</link><description>The Demo Importer Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data, loss of data, and privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the Ajax::handle_request() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to trigger a full site reset, dropping all database tables except users/usermeta and re-running wp_install(), which also assigns the Administrator role to the attacking subscriber account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64997 | Insufficient permission validation when showing agent information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64997</link><description>Insufficient permission validation in Checkmk versions prior to 2.4.0p17 and 2.3.0p42 allow low-privileged users to view agent information via the REST API, which could lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14874 | Nodemailer: nodemailer: denial of service via crafted email address header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14874</link><description>A flaw was found in Nodemailer. This vulnerability allows a denial of service (DoS) via a crafted email address header that triggers infinite recursion in the address parser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 08:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14318 | Improper access validation in M-Files Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14318</link><description>Improper access checks in M-Files Server before 25.12 allows users to download files through M-Files Web using Web Companion despite Print and Download Prevention module being enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10019 | WordPress Contact Form Email plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.60 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10019</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in codepeople Contact Form Email contact-form-to-email allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Contact Form Email: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.60.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12976 | Events Manager &amp;lt;= 7.2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;events_list_grouped&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12976</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'events_list_grouped' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13498 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.32 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Media Attachment Password Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13498</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of sensitive information in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.32. This is due to missing authorization and capability checks on the `wpdm_media_access` AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve passwords and access control settings for protected media attachments, which can then be used to bypass the intended media protection and download restricted files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14314 | WordPress PopupKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14314</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Roxnor PopupKit popup-builder-block allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects PopupKit: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49041 | WordPress Get Cash plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49041</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in The African Boss Get Cash get-cash allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Get Cash: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49359 | WordPress ShieldGroup theme &amp;lt;= 2.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49359</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes ShieldGroup shieldgroup allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ShieldGroup: from n/a through &lt;= 2.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49360 | WordPress Militarology theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49360</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Militarology militarology allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Militarology: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49361 | WordPress Mamita theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49361</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Mamita mamita allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Mamita: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49362 | WordPress Gracioza theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49362</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Gracioza gracioza allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Gracioza: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49363 | WordPress Kings &amp;amp; Queens theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49363</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Kings &amp; Queens kings-queens allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Kings &amp; Queens: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49364 | WordPress Ludos Paradise theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49364</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Ludos Paradise ludos-paradise allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Ludos Paradise: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49365 | WordPress Jack Well theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49365</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Jack Well jack-well allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Jack Well: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49366 | WordPress Hanani theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49366</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Hanani hanani allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Hanani: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49367 | WordPress Monyxi theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49367</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Monyxi monyxi allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Monyxi: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49368 | WordPress Palladio theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49368</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Palladio palladio allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Palladio: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49369 | WordPress Lettuce theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49369</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Lettuce lettuce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Lettuce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49370 | WordPress Lymcoin theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49370</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Lymcoin lymcoin allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Lymcoin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49371 | WordPress Strux theme &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49371</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Strux strux allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Strux: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49379 | WordPress Custom Fields Account Registration For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49379</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in silverplugins217 Custom Fields Account Registration For Woocommerce custom-fields-account-registration-for-woocommerce allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Custom Fields Account Registration For Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49902 | WordPress Login Page Customizer – Customizer Login Page, Admin Page, Custom Design plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49902</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in A WP Life Login Page Customizer &amp;#8211; Customizer Login Page, Admin Page, Custom Design customizer-login-page allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Login Page Customizer &amp;#8211; Customizer Login Page, Admin Page, Custom Design: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49914 | WordPress Restaurant Menu by MotoPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49914</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in jetmonsters Restaurant Menu by MotoPress mp-restaurant-menu allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Restaurant Menu by MotoPress: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49918 | WordPress VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp;amp; PMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49918</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in e4jvikwp VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS vikbooking allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49919 | WordPress eRoom plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49919</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in WPCenter eRoom eroom-zoom-meetings-webinar allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects eRoom: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49941 | WordPress GlamChic theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49941</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes GlamChic glamchic allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects GlamChic: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49942 | WordPress Gardis theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49942</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Gardis gardis allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Gardis: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49943 | WordPress Femme theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49943</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Femme femme allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Femme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52745 | WordPress Farm Agrico theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52745</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Farm Agrico farmagrico allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Farm Agrico: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52768 | WordPress Faith &amp;amp; Hope theme &amp;lt;= 2.13.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52768</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Faith &amp; Hope faith-hope allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Faith &amp; Hope: from n/a through &lt;= 2.13.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53429 | WordPress Exit Game theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53429</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Exit Game exit-game allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Exit Game: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53430 | WordPress Etta theme &amp;lt;= 1.14.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53430</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Etta etta allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Etta: from n/a through &lt;= 1.14.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53431 | WordPress Emberlyn theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53431</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Emberlyn emberlyn allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Emberlyn: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53432 | WordPress Echo theme &amp;lt;= 1.15.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53432</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Echo echo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Echo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.15.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53433 | WordPress EasyEat theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53433</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes EasyEat easyeat allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects EasyEat: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53434 | WordPress ChildHope theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53434</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes ChildHope childhope allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ChildHope: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53435 | WordPress Plan My Day theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53435</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Plan My Day planmyday allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Plan My Day: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53436 | WordPress Monki theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53436</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in BZOTheme Monki monki allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Monki: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53437 | WordPress Greenorganic theme &amp;lt;= 2.45 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53437</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Greenorganic greenorganic allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Greenorganic: from n/a through &lt;= 2.45.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53438 | WordPress FitLine theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53438</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes FitLine fitline allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects FitLine: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53439 | WordPress Harper theme &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53439</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Harper harper allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Harper: from n/a through &lt;= 1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53441 | WordPress Greeny theme &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53441</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Greeny greeny allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Greeny: from n/a through &lt;= 2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53442 | WordPress Rentic theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53442</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Rentic rentic allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Rentic: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53443 | WordPress Smash theme &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53443</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Smash smash allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Smash: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53445 | WordPress Catwalk theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53445</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Catwalk catwalk allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Catwalk: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53446 | WordPress Beautique theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53446</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Beautique beautique allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Beautique: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53447 | WordPress Assembly theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53447</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Assembly assembly allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Assembly: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53448 | WordPress Rally theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53448</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Rally rally allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Rally: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53449 | WordPress Convex theme &amp;lt;= 1.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53449</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Convex convex allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Convex: from n/a through &lt;= 1.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53453 | WordPress Hygia theme &amp;lt;= 1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53453</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Hygia hygia allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Hygia: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54723 | WordPress DentiCare Theme &amp;lt; 1.4.3 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54723</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes DentiCare denticare allows Object Injection.This issue affects DentiCare: from n/a through &lt; 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54741 | WordPress Super Blank Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54741</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyler Moore Super Blank super-blank allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Super Blank: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54743 | WordPress Download After Email Plugin 2.1.5-2.1.6 - Other Vulnerability Type Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54743</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in mkscripts Download After Email download-after-email allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Download After Email: from n/a through 2.1.5-2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54745 | WordPress miniOrange&amp;#x27;s Google Authenticator Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54745</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in miniOrange miniOrange's Google Authenticator miniorange-2-factor-authentication allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects miniOrange's Google Authenticator: from n/a through &lt;= 6.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54748 | WordPress MapSVG Plugin &amp;lt; 8.6.12 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54748</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG mapsvg allows Path Traversal.This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through &lt; 8.6.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54751 | WordPress PostX plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.36 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54751</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPXPO PostX ultimate-post allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PostX: from n/a through &lt;= 4.1.36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55707 | WordPress PostX Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.35 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55707</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in WPXPO PostX ultimate-post allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects PostX: from n/a through &lt;= 4.1.35.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57897 | WordPress Logtik theme &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57897</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in venusweb Logtik logtik allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Logtik: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58225 | WordPress Paragon theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58225</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Paragon paragon allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Paragon: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58706 | WordPress Woo Hoo theme &amp;lt;= 1.25 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58706</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Woo Hoo woohoo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Woo Hoo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58708 | WordPress 777 theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58708</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes 777 triple-seven allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects 777: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58709 | WordPress Legacy theme &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58709</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Legacy legacy allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Legacy: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58710 | WordPress Hotel Listing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58710</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in e-plugins Hotel Listing hotel-listing allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Hotel Listing: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58803 | WordPress Algenix theme &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58803</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Algenix algenix allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Algenix: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58877 | WordPress Javo Core plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0.529 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58877</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in javothemes Javo Core javo-core allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Javo Core: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.0.529.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58879 | WordPress Festy theme &amp;lt;= 1.13.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58879</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Festy festy allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Festy: from n/a through &lt;= 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58885 | WordPress Pathfinder theme &amp;lt;= 1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58885</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Pathfinder pathfinder allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pathfinder: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58888 | WordPress The Flash theme &amp;lt;= 1.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58888</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes The Flash theflash allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects The Flash: from n/a through &lt;= 1.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58889 | WordPress Towny theme &amp;lt;= 1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58889</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Towny towny allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Towny: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58890 | WordPress Playful theme &amp;lt;= 1.19.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58890</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Playful playful allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Playful: from n/a through &lt;= 1.19.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58891 | WordPress Sanger theme &amp;lt;= 1.24.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58891</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Sanger sanger allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Sanger: from n/a through &lt;= 1.24.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58892 | WordPress Tourimo theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58892</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Tourimo tourimo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Tourimo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58893 | WordPress Alright theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58893</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Alright alright allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Alright: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58894 | WordPress Good Mood theme &amp;lt;= 1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58894</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Good Mood good-mood allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Good Mood: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58895 | WordPress Integro theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58895</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Integro integro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Integro: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58896 | WordPress Otaku theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58896</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Otaku otaku allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Otaku: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58898 | WordPress HealthHub theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58898</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes HealthHub healthhub allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects HealthHub: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58899 | WordPress Frame theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58899</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Frame frame allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Frame: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58900 | WordPress UniTravel theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58900</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes UniTravel unitravel allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects UniTravel: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58901 | WordPress Takeout theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58901</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Takeout takeout allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Takeout: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58923 | WordPress Critique theme &amp;lt;= 1.17 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58923</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Critique critique allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Critique: from n/a through &lt;= 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58925 | WordPress Neptunus theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58925</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Neptunus neptunus allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Neptunus: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58926 | WordPress Cerebrum theme &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58926</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Cerebrum cerebrum allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Cerebrum: from n/a through &lt;= 1.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58927 | WordPress Stallion theme &amp;lt;= 1.17 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58927</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Stallion stallion allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Stallion: from n/a through &lt;= 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58928 | WordPress Heart theme &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58928</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Heart heart allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Heart: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58929 | WordPress Pantry theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58929</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Pantry pantry allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pantry: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58930 | WordPress FitFlex theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58930</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes FitFlex fitflex allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects FitFlex: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58931 | WordPress Palatio theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58931</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Palatio palatio allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Palatio: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58932 | WordPress Prisma theme &amp;lt;= 1.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58932</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Prisma prisma allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Prisma: from n/a through &lt;= 1.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58933 | WordPress Anubis theme &amp;lt;= 1.25 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58933</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Anubis anubis allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Anubis: from n/a through &lt;= 1.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58934 | WordPress The Gig theme &amp;lt;= 1.18.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58934</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes The Gig thegig allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects The Gig: from n/a through &lt;= 1.18.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58935 | WordPress Lunna theme &amp;lt;= 1.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58935</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Lunna lunna allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Lunna: from n/a through &lt;= 1.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58936 | WordPress Catamaran theme &amp;lt;= 1.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58936</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Catamaran catamaran allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Catamaran: from n/a through &lt;= 1.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58937 | WordPress Tacticool theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58937</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Tacticool tacticool allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Tacticool: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58938 | WordPress IDonatePro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58938</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeAtelier IDonatePro idonate-pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects IDonatePro: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58940 | WordPress Basil theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58940</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Basil basil allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Basil: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58941 | WordPress Fabric theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58941</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Fabric fabric allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fabric: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58942 | WordPress Dwell theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58942</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Dwell dwell allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dwell: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58943 | WordPress Agricola theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58943</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Agricola agricola allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Agricola: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58944 | WordPress Manufactory theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58944</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Manufactory manufactory allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Manufactory: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58945 | WordPress EcoGrow theme &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58945</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes EcoGrow ecogrow allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects EcoGrow: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58946 | WordPress Vocal theme &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58946</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Vocal vocal allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Vocal: from n/a through &lt;= 1.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58947 | WordPress Athos theme &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58947</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Athos athos allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Athos: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58948 | WordPress Aromatica theme &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58948</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Aromatica aromatica allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Aromatica: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58949 | WordPress Spock theme &amp;lt;= 1.17 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58949</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Spock spock allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Spock: from n/a through &lt;= 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58950 | WordPress Lione theme &amp;lt;= 1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58950</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Lione lione allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Lione: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58951 | WordPress Advance Seat Reservation Management for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58951</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in smartcms Advance Seat Reservation Management for WooCommerce scw-seat-reservation allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Advance Seat Reservation Management for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59134 | WordPress Sale! Immigration law, Visa services support, Migration Agent Consulting theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59134</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Jthemes Sale! Immigration law, Visa services support, Migration Agent Consulting immiex allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Sale! Immigration law, Visa services support, Migration Agent Consulting: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60042 | WordPress Chinchilla theme &amp;lt;= 1.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60042</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Chinchilla chinchilla allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Chinchilla: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60043 | WordPress Wanderic theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60043</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Wanderic wanderic allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Wanderic: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60044 | WordPress Fribbo theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60044</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Fribbo fribbo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fribbo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60045 | WordPress IDonatePro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60045</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeAtelier IDonatePro idonate-pro allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects IDonatePro: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60046 | WordPress HeartStar theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60046</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes HeartStar heartstar allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects HeartStar: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60047 | WordPress IPharm theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60047</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes IPharm ipharm allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects IPharm: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60048 | WordPress Tripster theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60048</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Tripster tripster allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Tripster: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60049 | WordPress Soleil theme &amp;lt;= 1.17 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60049</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Soleil soleil allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Soleil: from n/a through &lt;= 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60050 | WordPress Panda theme &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60050</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Panda panda allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Panda: from n/a through &lt;= 1.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60051 | WordPress Rare Radio theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.15.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60051</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Rare Radio rareradio allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Rare Radio: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.15.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60052 | WordPress W&amp;amp;D theme &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60052</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes W&amp;amp;D wd allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects W&amp;amp;D: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60053 | WordPress MaxCube theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60053</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes MaxCube maxcube allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects MaxCube: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60054 | WordPress OnLeash theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60054</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes OnLeash onleash allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects OnLeash: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60055 | WordPress Fabrica theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60055</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Fabrica fabrica allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fabrica: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60056 | WordPress Winger theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.16 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60056</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Winger winger allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Winger: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60057 | WordPress DJ Rainflow theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.13 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60057</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes DJ Rainflow dj-rainflow allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects DJ Rainflow: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60058 | WordPress DetailX theme &amp;lt;= 1.10.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60058</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes DetailX detailx allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects DetailX: from n/a through &lt;= 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60059 | WordPress smart SEO theme &amp;lt;= 2.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60059</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes smart SEO smartSEO allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects smart SEO: from n/a through &lt;= 2.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60060 | WordPress Pubzinne theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60060</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Pubzinne pubzinne allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pubzinne: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60061 | WordPress Kicker theme &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60061</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Kicker kicker allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Kicker: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60062 | WordPress tPlayer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60062</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in mmetrodw tPlayer tplayer-html5-audio-player-with-playlist allows SQL Injection.This issue affects tPlayer: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60063 | WordPress Rosalinda theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60063</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Rosalinda rosalinda allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Rosalinda: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60064 | WordPress Renewal theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60064</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Renewal renewal allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Renewal: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60065 | WordPress Pinevale theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60065</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Pinevale pinevale allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pinevale: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60066 | WordPress Katelyn theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60066</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Katelyn katelyn allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Katelyn: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60067 | WordPress Giardino theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60067</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Giardino giardino allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Giardino: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60068 | WordPress Javo Core plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0.266 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60068</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in javothemes Javo Core javo-core allows Code Injection.This issue affects Javo Core: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.0.266.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60069 | WordPress MinimogWP theme &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60069</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeMove MinimogWP minimog allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects MinimogWP: from n/a through &lt;= 3.9.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60070 | WordPress Molla - Multipurpose Responsive Shopify theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.13 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60070</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in The4 Molla molla allows Code Injection.This issue affects Molla: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60071 | WordPress Riode | Multi-Purpose WooCommerce theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.23 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60071</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in don-themes Riode | Multi-Purpose WooCommerce riode allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Riode | Multi-Purpose WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.23.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60072 | WordPress Anchor smooth scroll plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60072</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Processby Anchor smooth scroll anchor-smooth-scroll allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Anchor smooth scroll: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60076 | WordPress Ray Enterprise Translation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60076</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in jbhovik Ray Enterprise Translation lingotek-translation allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Ray Enterprise Translation: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60077 | WordPress YayPricing plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60077</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YayCommerce YayPricing yaypricing allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects YayPricing: from n/a through &lt;= 3.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60078 | WordPress Task Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60078</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Agence web Eoxia - Montpellier Task Manager task-manager allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Task Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60079 | WordPress Parallax Section block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Parallax Section block parallax-section allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Parallax Section block: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60080 | WordPress PDF for Gravity Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60080</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for Gravity Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder pdf-for-gravity-forms allows Object Injection.This issue affects PDF for Gravity Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60081 | WordPress PDF for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.4 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60081</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for Contact Form 7 pdf-for-contact-form-7 allows Object Injection.This issue affects PDF for Contact Form 7: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60082 | WordPress PDF for WPForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60082</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for WPForms pdf-for-wpforms allows Object Injection.This issue affects PDF for WPForms: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60083 | WordPress PDF Invoice Builder for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60083</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF Invoice Builder for WooCommerce pdf-for-woocommerce allows Object Injection.This issue affects PDF Invoice Builder for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60084 | WordPress PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60084</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder pdf-for-elementor-forms allows Object Injection.This issue affects PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60086 | WordPress WP Voting Contest plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60086</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Matt WP Voting Contest wp-voting-contest allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Voting Contest: from n/a through &lt;= 5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60088 | WordPress WebinarIgnition plugin &amp;lt;= 4.06.04 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60088</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saleswonder Team: Tobias WebinarIgnition webinar-ignition allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WebinarIgnition: from n/a through &lt;= 4.06.04.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60089 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms FreshDesk plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60089</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms FreshDesk Plugin gf-freshdesk allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms FreshDesk Plugin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60090 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Insightly plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60090</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Insightly gf-insightly allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Insightly: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60091 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Zoho CRM and Bigin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60091</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Zoho CRM and Bigin gf-zoho allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Zoho CRM and Bigin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60174 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Constant Contact Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60174</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Constant Contact Plugin gf-constant-contact allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Constant Contact Plugin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60178 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms HubSpot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60178</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms HubSpot gf-hubspot allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms HubSpot: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60180 | WordPress WP Gravity Forms Salesforce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60180</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Gravity Forms Salesforce gf-salesforce-crmperks allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Gravity Forms Salesforce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60182 | WordPress Support Board plugin &amp;lt; 3.8.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60182</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Schiocco Support Board supportboard allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Support Board: from n/a through &lt; 3.8.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63039 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63039</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro listingpro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64188 | WordPress Soledad theme &amp;lt;= 8.6.9 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64188</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in PenciDesign Soledad soledad allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Soledad: from n/a through &lt;= 8.6.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64189 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt; 5.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64189</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core et-core-plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through &lt; 5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64191 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt; 9.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64191</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 8theme XStore xstore allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through &lt; 9.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64192 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt; 9.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64192</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8theme XStore xstore allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through &lt; 9.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64193 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt; 9.6.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64193</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in 8theme XStore xstore allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through &lt; 9.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64203 | WordPress Mailster plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64203</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EverPress Mailster mailster allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mailster: from n/a through &lt; 4.1.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64205 | WordPress Jannah theme &amp;lt;= 7.6.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64205</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in TieLabs Jannah jannah allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Jannah: from n/a through &lt;= 7.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64206 | WordPress Jannah theme &amp;lt;= 7.6.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64206</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in TieLabs Jannah jannah allows Object Injection.This issue affects Jannah: from n/a through &lt;= 7.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64207 | WordPress Jannah theme &amp;lt;= 7.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64207</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in TieLabs Jannah jannah allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Jannah: from n/a through &lt;= 7.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64209 | WordPress Masterstudy theme &amp;lt; 4.8.122 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64209</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes Masterstudy masterstudy allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Masterstudy: from n/a through &lt; 4.8.122.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64213 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS Pro plugin &amp;lt; 4.7.16 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64213</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in StylemixThemes MasterStudy LMS Pro masterstudy-lms-learning-management-system-pro allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects MasterStudy LMS Pro: from n/a through &lt; 4.7.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64214 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS Pro plugin &amp;lt; 4.7.16 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64214</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes MasterStudy LMS Pro masterstudy-lms-learning-management-system-pro allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects MasterStudy LMS Pro: from n/a through &lt; 4.7.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64217 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64217</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGoods Photography photography allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Photography: from n/a through &lt;= 7.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64218 | WordPress Passster plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.19 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64218</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in WP Chill Passster content-protector allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Passster: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64221 | WordPress Reservation Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64221</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in designthemes Reservation Plugin dt-reservation-plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Reservation Plugin: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64222 | WordPress WooCommerce Recover Abandoned Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 24.6.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64222</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FantasticPlugins WooCommerce Recover Abandoned Cart rac allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Recover Abandoned Cart: from n/a through &lt;= 24.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64223 | WordPress PenNews theme &amp;lt; 6.7.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64223</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in PenciDesign PenNews pennews allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PenNews: from n/a through &lt; 6.7.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64225 | WordPress Stockie Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in colabrio Stockie Extra stockie-extra allows Code Injection.This issue affects Stockie Extra: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64227 | WordPress Client Invoicing by Sprout Invoices plugin &amp;lt;= 20.8.7 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64227</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldGrid Client Invoicing by Sprout Invoices sprout-invoices allows Object Injection.This issue affects Client Invoicing by Sprout Invoices: from n/a through &lt;= 20.8.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64230 | WordPress Filr plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64230</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WP Chill Filr filr-protection allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Filr: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64231 | WordPress WordPress Contact Form 7 PDF, Google Sheet &amp;amp; Database plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64231</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in RedefiningTheWeb WordPress Contact Form 7 PDF, Google Sheet &amp; Database rtwwcfp-wordpress-contact-form-7-pdf allows Using Malicious Files.This issue affects WordPress Contact Form 7 PDF, Google Sheet &amp; Database: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64233 | WordPress Codiqa theme &amp;lt; 1.2.8 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64233</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Codiqa codiqa allows Object Injection.This issue affects Codiqa: from n/a through &lt; 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64258 | WordPress Follow My Blog Post plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64258</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in wpweb Follow My Blog Post follow-my-blog-post allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Follow My Blog Post: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64260 | WordPress ANAC XML Bandi di Gara plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marco Milesi ANAC XML Bandi di Gara avcp allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ANAC XML Bandi di Gara: from n/a through &lt;= 7.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64266 | WordPress Booking and Rental Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64266</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in magepeopleteam Booking and Rental Manager booking-and-rental-manager-for-woocommerce allows Object Injection.This issue affects Booking and Rental Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64268 | WordPress Timetics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.44 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64268</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arraytics Timetics timetics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Timetics: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.44.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64270 | WordPress Masteriyo - LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64270</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in masteriyo Masteriyo - LMS learning-management-system allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Masteriyo - LMS: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64272 | WordPress Email marketing for WordPress by GetResponse Official plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64272</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in GetResponse Email marketing for WordPress by GetResponse Official getresponse-official allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Email marketing for WordPress by GetResponse Official: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64273 | WordPress Email marketing for WordPress by GetResponse Official plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64273</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GetResponse Email marketing for WordPress by GetResponse Official getresponse-official allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Email marketing for WordPress by GetResponse Official: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64295 | WordPress All In One SEO Pack plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.6.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64295</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Syed Balkhi All In One SEO Pack all-in-one-seo-pack allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects All In One SEO Pack: from n/a through &lt;= 4.8.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64371 | WordPress Traveler theme &amp;lt; 3.2.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64371</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in shinetheme Traveler traveler allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Traveler: from n/a through &lt; 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64372 | WordPress Traveler theme &amp;lt; 3.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64372</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in shinetheme Traveler traveler allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Traveler: from n/a through &lt; 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64373 | WordPress Traveler theme &amp;lt; 3.2.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64373</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in shinetheme Traveler traveler allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Traveler: from n/a through &lt; 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64374 | WordPress Motors theme &amp;lt;= 5.6.81 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64374</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in StylemixThemes Motors motors allows Using Malicious Files.This issue affects Motors: from n/a through &lt;= 5.6.81.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64375 | WordPress WP Social Ninja plugin &amp;lt;= 3.20.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64375</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mahmudul Hasan Arif WP Social Ninja wp-social-reviews allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Social Ninja: from n/a through &lt;= 3.20.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64376 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt; 2.9.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64376</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro listingpro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through &lt; 2.9.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64377 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt; 2.9.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64377</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro listingpro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through &lt; 2.9.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64378 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt; 2.9.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64378</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro listingpro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through &lt; 2.9.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66054 | WordPress LearnPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66054</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress learnpress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects LearnPress: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66068 | WordPress InstaWP Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66068</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in InstaWP InstaWP Connect instawp-connect allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects InstaWP Connect: from n/a through &lt;= 0.1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66070 | WordPress wpForo Forum plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66070</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tomdever wpForo Forum wpforo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66074 | WordPress WP Webhooks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66074</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Cozmoslabs WP Webhooks wp-webhooks allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WP Webhooks: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66078 | WordPress Hotel Booking Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66078</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in jetmonsters Hotel Booking Lite motopress-hotel-booking-lite allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects Hotel Booking Lite: from n/a through &lt;= 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66088 | WordPress PropertyHive plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66088</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Property Hive PropertyHive propertyhive allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66100 | WordPress RestroPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66100</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Magnigenie RestroPress restropress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects RestroPress: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66102 | WordPress FV Antispam plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66102</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FolioVision FV Antispam fv-antispam allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FV Antispam: from n/a through &lt;= 2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66104 | WordPress Offload, AI &amp;amp; Optimize with Cloudflare Images plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66104</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Anton Vanyukov Offload, AI &amp;amp; Optimize with Cloudflare Images cf-images allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Offload, AI &amp;amp; Optimize with Cloudflare Images: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66116 | WordPress Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66116</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in UserElements Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor ultimate-member-widgets-for-elementor allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66117 | WordPress Easy Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66117</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ays Pro Easy Form easy-form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Form: from n/a through &lt;= 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66118 | WordPress Sprout Clients plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66118</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BoldGrid Sprout Clients sprout-clients allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Sprout Clients: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66119 | WordPress Hostel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66119</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bob Hostel hostel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Hostel: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67546 | WordPress WP ERP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67546</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in weDevs WP ERP erp allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects WP ERP: from n/a through &lt;= 1.16.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6324 | WordPress Easy Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MatrixAddons Easy Invoice easy-invoice allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Easy Invoice: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6326 | WordPress Inset theme &amp;lt;= 1.18.0 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6326</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Inset inset allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Inset: from n/a through &lt;= 1.18.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68459 | RG - AP180, Indoor Wall Plate Wireless AP AP180 series provided by Ruijie Networks Co., Ltd. contain an OS command injection vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68459</link><description>RG - AP180, Indoor Wall Plate Wireless AP AP180 series provided by Ruijie Networks Co., Ltd. contain an OS command injection vulnerability. An arbitrary OS command may be executed on the product by an attacker who logs in to the CLI service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68463 | Bio.Entrez in Biopython through 186 allows doctype XXE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68463</link><description>Bio.Entrez in Biopython through 186 allows doctype XXE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27063 | Use After Free in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27063</link><description>Memory corruption during video playback when video session open fails with time out error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47319 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47319</link><description>Information disclosure while exposing internal TA-to-TA communication APIs to HLOS</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47320 | Out-of-bounds Write in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47320</link><description>Memory corruption while processing MFC channel configuration during music playback.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47321 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Core Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47321</link><description>Memory corruption while copying packets received from unix clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47322 | Use After Free in Automotive Linux OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47322</link><description>Memory corruption while handling IOCTL calls to set mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47323 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47323</link><description>Memory corruption while routing GPR packets between user and root when handling large data packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47325 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in TZ Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47325</link><description>Information disclosure while processing system calls with invalid parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47350 | Use After Free in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47350</link><description>Memory corruption while handling concurrent memory mapping and unmapping requests from a user-space application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47372 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Boot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47372</link><description>Memory Corruption when a corrupted ELF image with an oversized file size is read into a buffer without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47382 | Incorrect Authorization in Boot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47382</link><description>Memory corruption while loading an invalid firmware in boot loader.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47387 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47387</link><description>Memory Corruption when processing IOCTLs for JPEG data without verification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68462 | Freedombox before 25.17.1 does not set proper permissions for the backups-data directory, allowing the reading of dump files of databases.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68462</link><description>Freedombox before 25.17.1 does not set proper permissions for the backups-data directory, allowing the reading of dump files of databases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68461 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.12 and 1.6 before 1.6.12 is prone to a Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the animate tag in an SVG d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68461</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.12 and 1.6 before 1.6.12 is prone to a Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the animate tag in an SVG document.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68460 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.12 and 1.6 before 1.6.12 is prone to a information disclosure vulnerability in the HTML style sanitizer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68460</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.12 and 1.6 before 1.6.12 is prone to a information disclosure vulnerability in the HTML style sanitizer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 05:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12885 | Embed Any Document &amp;lt;= 2.7.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12885</link><description>The Embed Any Document – Embed PDF, Word, PowerPoint and Excel Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the sanitize_pdf_src function regex bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 03:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14856 | y_project RuoYi getnames code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14856</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in y_project RuoYi up to 4.8.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /monitor/cache/getnames. Such manipulation of the argument fragment leads to code injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 02:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14841 | OFFIS DCMTK dcmqrscp dcmqrdbi.cc startMoveRequest null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14841</link><description>A flaw has been found in OFFIS DCMTK up to 3.6.9. The impacted element is the function DcmQueryRetrieveIndexDatabaseHandle::startFindRequest/DcmQueryRetrieveIndexDatabaseHandle::startMoveRequest in the library dcmqrdb/libsrc/dcmqrdbi.cc of the component dcmqrscp. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack requires local access. Upgrading to version 3.7.0 is sufficient to resolve this issue. Patch name: ffb1a4a37d2c876e3feeb31df4930f2aed7fa030. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 02:04:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>