<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 15:10:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-47183 | Parse Server has user id/role name confusion with ACLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47183</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. If the Parse Server option allowCustomObjectId: true is set, an attacker that is allowed to create a new user can set a custom object ID for that new user that exploits the vulnerability and acquires privileges of a specific role. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.5.9 and 7.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 15:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47769 | IDURAR has a Path Traversal (unauthenticated user can read sensitive data)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47769</link><description>IDURAR is open source ERP CRM accounting invoicing software. The vulnerability exists in the corePublicRouter.js file. Using the reference usage here, it is identified that the public endpoint is accessible to an unauthenticated user. The user's input is directly appended to the join statement without additional checks. This allows an attacker to send URL encoded malicious payload. The directory structure can be escaped to read system files by adding an encoded string (payload) at subpath location.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47768 | Lif Authentication Server Has No Auth Check When Updating Password In Account Recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47768</link><description>Lif Authentication Server is a server used by Lif to do various tasks regarding Lif accounts. This vulnerability has to do with the account recovery system where there does not appear to be a check to make sure the user has been sent the recovery email and entered the correct code. If the attacker knew the email of the target, they could supply the email and immediately prompt the server to update the password without ever needing the code. This issue has been patched in version 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47765 | Minecraft MOTD Parser&amp;#x27;s HtmlGenerator vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47765</link><description>Minecraft MOTD Parser is a PHP library to parse minecraft server motd. The HtmlGenerator class is subject to potential cross-site scripting (XSS) attack through a parsed malformed Minecraft server MOTD. The HtmlGenerator iterates through objects of MotdItem that are contained in an object of MotdItemCollection to generate a HTML string. An attacker can make malicious inputs to the color and text properties of MotdItem to inject own HTML into a web page during web page generation. For example by sending a malicious MOTD from a Minecraft server under their control that was queried and passed to the HtmlGenerator. This XSS vulnerability exists because the values of these properties are neither filtered nor escaped. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9515 | D-Link DIR-605L formSetQoS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9515</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01 BETA. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formSetQoS of the file /goform/formSetQoS. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9514 | D-Link DIR-605L formSetDomainFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9514</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01 BETA. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetDomainFilter of the file /goform/formSetDomainFilter. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9410 | Ada.cx SSRF via Sentry Misconfiguration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9410</link><description>Ada.cx's Sentry configuration allowed for blind server-side request forgeries (SSRF) through the use of a data scraping endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47657 | Improper Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47657</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Shilpi Net Back Office due to improper access controls on certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a parameter dfclientid through API request URLs which could lead to unauthorized access to sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47789 | Credential Leakage Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47789</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** This vulnerability exists in D3D Security IP Camera due to usage of weak authentication scheme of the HTTP header protocol where authorization tag contain a Base-64 encoded username and password. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a HTTP packet leading to exposure of user credentials of the targeted device. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47790 | Missing Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47790</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** This vulnerability exists in D3D Security IP Camera due to usage of insecure Real-Time Streaming Protocol (RTSP) version for live video streaming.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a RTSP packet leading to unauthorized access to live feed of the targeted device.    NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8499 | Checkout Field Editor (Checkout Manager) for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via render_review_request_notice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8499</link><description>The Checkout Field Editor (Checkout Manager) for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘render_review_request_notice’ function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9483 | Uninitialized variable in digital signiture verification may crash the application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9483</link><description>A null-pointer-dereference in the signature verification module in AVG/Avast Antivirus signature &lt;24092400 released on 24/Sep/2024 on MacOS may allow a malformed xar file to crash the application during processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9484 | An null-pointer-derefrence in the engine module in AVG/Avast Antivirus signature &lt;24092400 released on 24/Sep/2024 on MacOS allows a malform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9484</link><description>An null-pointer-derefrence in the engine module in AVG/Avast Antivirus signature &lt;24092400 released on 24/Sep/2024 on MacOS allows a malformed xar file to crash the application during file processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9513 | Netadmin Software NetAdmin IAM HTTP POST Request ReturnUserQuestionsFilled information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9513</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netadmin Software NetAdmin IAM up to 3.5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /controller/api/Answer/ReturnUserQuestionsFilled of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to information exposure through discrepancy. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47652 | Insecure Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47652</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Shilpi Client Dashboard due to implementation of inadequate authentication mechanism in the login module wherein access to any users account is granted with just their corresponding mobile number. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing mobile number of targeted user, to obtain complete access to the targeted user account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47653 | Missing Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47653</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Shilpi Client Dashboard due to lack of authorization for modification and cancellation requests through certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing or cancelling requests through API request body leading to unauthorized modification of requests belonging to the other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47654 | No Rate Limiting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47654</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Shilpi Client Dashboard due to lack of rate limiting and Captcha protection for OTP requests in certain API endpoint. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoints, which could lead to the OTP bombing on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47655 | Unrestricted File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47655</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Shilpi Client Dashboard due to improper validation of files being uploaded other than the specified extension. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious file, which could lead to remote code execution on targeted application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47656 | User Enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47656</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Shilpi Client Dashboard due to missing restrictions for incorrect login attempts on its API based login. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by conducting a brute force attack on password, which could lead to gain unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9481 | Out of Bounds write on scan of malformed eml file may crash the application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9481</link><description>An out-of-bounds write in the engine module in AVG/Avast Antivirus signature &lt;24092400 released on 24/Sep/2024 on MacOS allows a malformed eml file to crash the application during file processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9482 | Out of Bounds write on scan of malformed Mach-O file may crash the application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9482</link><description>An out-of-bounds write in the engine module in AVG/Avast Antivirus signature &lt;24092400 released on 24/Sep/2024 on MacOS allows a malformed Mach-O file to crash the application during file processing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47651 | Parameter Pollution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47651</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Shilpi Client Dashboard due to improper handling of multiple parameters in the API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including multiple “userid” parameters in the API request body leading to unauthorized access of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6400 | Cleartext Storage of Username and Password in Finrota&amp;#x27;s Netahsilat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6400</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Finrota Netahsilat allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue solved in versions 1.21.10, 1.23.01, 1.23.08, 1.23.11 and 1.24.03.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 11:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9071 | Easy Demo Importer – A Modern One-Click Demo Import Solution &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9071</link><description>The Easy Demo Importer – A Modern One-Click Demo Import Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9271 | Re:WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9271</link><description>The Re:WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9306 | WP Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9306</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 10.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled. In addition, site administrators have the option to grant lower-level users with access to manage the plugin's settings which may extend this vulnerability to those users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 06:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9435 | ShiftController Employee Shift Scheduling &amp;lt;= 4.9.66 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9435</link><description>The ShiftController Employee Shift Scheduling plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via URL keys in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.66 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 06:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6444 | Bluetooth: ots: missing buffer length check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6444</link><description>No proper validation of the length of user input in olcp_ind_handler in zephyr/subsys/bluetooth/services/ots/ots_client.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 06:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6443 | zephyr: out-of-bound read in utf8_trunc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6443</link><description>In utf8_trunc in zephyr/lib/utils/utf8.c, last_byte_p can point to one byte before the string pointer if the string is empty.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 06:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47855 | util/JSONTokener.java in JSON-lib before 3.1.0 mishandles an unbalanced comment string.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47855</link><description>util/JSONTokener.java in JSON-lib before 3.1.0 mishandles an unbalanced comment string.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47854 | A vulnerability was discovered in Veritas Data Insight before 7.1. It allows a remote attacker to inject an arbitrary web script into an HTT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47854</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in Veritas Data Insight before 7.1. It allows a remote attacker to inject an arbitrary web script into an HTTP request that could reflect back to an authenticated user without sanitization if executed by that user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 05:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6442 | Bluetooth: ASCS Unchecked tailroom of the response buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6442</link><description>In ascs_cp_rsp_add in /subsys/bluetooth/audio/ascs.c, an unchecked tailroom could lead to a global buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 05:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8804 | Code Embed &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8804</link><description>The Code Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's script embed functionality in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient restrictions on who can utilize the functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 05:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9242 | Memberful – Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.73.7 - Authenticated (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9242</link><description>The Memberful – Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'memberful_buy_subscription_link' and 'memberful_podcasts_link' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.73.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 05:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47850 | CUPS cups-browsed before 2.5b1 will send an HTTP POST request to an arbitrary destination and port in response to a single IPP UDP packet re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47850</link><description>CUPS cups-browsed before 2.5b1 will send an HTTP POST request to an arbitrary destination and port in response to a single IPP UDP packet requesting a printer to be added, a different vulnerability than CVE-2024-47176. (The request is meant to probe the new printer but can be used to create DDoS amplification attacks.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8519 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8519</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'um_loggedin' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8520 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Membership Status Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8520</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the admin_init or user_action_hook function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify a users membership status via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8802 | Clio Grow &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8802</link><description>The Clio Grow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9204 | Smart Custom 404 Error Page &amp;lt;= 11.4.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9204</link><description>The Smart Custom 404 Error Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] in all versions up to, and including, 11.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9237 | Fish and Ships &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9237</link><description>The Fish and Ships – Most flexible shipping table rate. A WooCommerce shipping rate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9345 | Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9345</link><description>The Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This is only exploitable when notices are present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9349 | Auto Amazon Links – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9349</link><description>The Auto Amazon Links – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9353 | Popularis Extra &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9353</link><description>The Popularis Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9368 | Aggregator Advanced Settings &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9368</link><description>The Aggregator Advanced Settings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9372 | WP Blocks Hub &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9372</link><description>The WP Blocks Hub plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9375 | WordPress Captcha Plugin by Captcha Bank &amp;lt;= 4.0.36 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9375</link><description>The WordPress Captcha Plugin by Captcha Bank plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.36. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9384 | Quantity Dynamic Pricing &amp;amp; Bulk Discounts for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.8.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9384</link><description>The Quantity Dynamic Pricing &amp; Bulk Discounts for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9421 | Login Logout Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via class Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9421</link><description>The Login Logout Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9445 | Display Medium Posts &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via display_medium_posts Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9445</link><description>The Display Medium Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's display_medium_posts shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 04:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44204 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.0.1 and iPadOS 18.0.1. A user's saved passwords may be r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44204</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.0.1 and iPadOS 18.0.1. A user's saved passwords may be read aloud by VoiceOver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 23:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44207 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.0.1 and iPadOS 18.0.1. Audio messages in Messages may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44207</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.0.1 and iPadOS 18.0.1. Audio messages in Messages may be able to capture a few seconds of audio before the microphone indicator is activated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 23:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42417 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42417</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAEnergie is vulnerable to an SQL injection in the script Handler_CFG.ashx. An authenticated attacker may be able to exploit this issue to cause delay in the targeted product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43699 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43699</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAEnergie is vulnerable to an SQL injection in the script AM_RegReport.aspx. An unauthenticated attacker may be able to exploit this issue to obtain records contained in the targeted product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45367 | Optigo Networks ONS-S8 Spectra Aggregation Switch Weak Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45367</link><description>The web server for ONS-S8 - Spectra Aggregation Switch includes an incomplete authentication process, which can lead to an attacker authenticating without a password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41925 | Optigo Networks ONS-S8 Spectra Aggregation Switch PHP Remote File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41925</link><description>The web service for ONS-S8 - Spectra Aggregation Switch includes functions which do not properly validate user input, allowing an attacker to traverse directories, bypass authentication, and execute remote code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46658 | Syrotech SY-GOPON-8OLT-L3 v1.6.0_240629 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46658</link><description>Syrotech SY-GOPON-8OLT-L3 v1.6.0_240629 was discovered to contain an authenticated command injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 21:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9266 | Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9266</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Express. This vulnerability affects the use of the Express Response object. This issue impacts Express: from 3.4.5 before 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 19:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41585 | DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are affected by an OS command injection vulnerability that allows an attacker to leverage the recv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41585</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are affected by an OS command injection vulnerability that allows an attacker to leverage the recvCmd binary to escape from the emulated instance and inject arbitrary commands into the host machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41586 | A stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41586</link><description>A stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a long query string to the cgi-bin/ipfedr.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41587 | Stored XSS, by authenticated users, is caused by poor sanitization of the Login Page Greeting message in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41587</link><description>Stored XSS, by authenticated users, is caused by poor sanitization of the Login Page Greeting message in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41588 | The CGI endpoints v2x00.cgi and cgiwcg.cgi of DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are vulnerable to buffer overflows, by authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41588</link><description>The CGI endpoints v2x00.cgi and cgiwcg.cgi of DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are vulnerable to buffer overflows, by authenticated users, because of missing bounds checking on parameters passed through POST requests to the strncpy function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41589 | DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 use unencrypted HTTP for authentication requests.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41589</link><description>DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 use unencrypted HTTP for authentication requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41590 | Several CGI endpoints are vulnerable to buffer overflows, by authenticated users, because of missing bounds checking on parameters passed th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41590</link><description>Several CGI endpoints are vulnerable to buffer overflows, by authenticated users, because of missing bounds checking on parameters passed through POST requests to the strcpy function on DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41591 | DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 allow unauthenticated DOM-based reflected XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41591</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 allow unauthenticated DOM-based reflected XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41592 | DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 have a stack-based overflow when processing query string parameters because GetCGI mishandles extr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41592</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 have a stack-based overflow when processing query string parameters because GetCGI mishandles extraneous ampersand characters and long key-value pairs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41593 | DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the function ft_payload_dns(), because a byte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41593</link><description>DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the function ft_payload_dns(), because a byte sign-extension operation occurs for the length argument of a _memcpy call, leading to a heap-based Buffer Overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41594 | An issue in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information because the httpd server of the Vigo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41594</link><description>An issue in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information because the httpd server of the Vigor management UI uses a static string for seeding the PRNG of OpenSSL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41595 | DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allow a remote attacker to change settings or cause a denial of service via .cgi pages because of m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41595</link><description>DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 allow a remote attacker to change settings or cause a denial of service via .cgi pages because of missing bounds checks on read and write operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41596 | Buffer Overflow vulnerabilities exist in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 (in the Vigor management UI) because of improper retrieval...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41596</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerabilities exist in DrayTek Vigor310 devices through 4.3.2.6 (in the Vigor management UI) because of improper retrieval and handling of the CGI form parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41583 | DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are vulnerable to stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) by authenticated users due to poor sanitizatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41583</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are vulnerable to stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) by authenticated users due to poor sanitization of the router name.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41584 | DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are vulnerable to reflected XSS by authenticated users, caused by missing validation of the sFormA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41584</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3910 devices through 4.3.2.6 are vulnerable to reflected XSS by authenticated users, caused by missing validation of the sFormAuthStr parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37822 | Eufy HomeBase 2 model T8010X v3.2.8.3h was discovered to use the deprecated wireless protocol WPA2-PSK.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37822</link><description>Eufy HomeBase 2 model T8010X v3.2.8.3h was discovered to use the deprecated wireless protocol WPA2-PSK.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34535 | In Mastodon 4.1.6, API endpoint rate limiting can be bypassed by setting a crafted HTTP request header.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34535</link><description>In Mastodon 4.1.6, API endpoint rate limiting can be bypassed by setting a crafted HTTP request header.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41987 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in TEM Opera Plus FM Family Transmitter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41987</link><description>The TEM Opera Plus FM Family Transmitter application interface allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any validity checks to verify the requests. This can be exploited to perform certain actions with administrative privileges if a logged-in user visits a malicious web site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41988 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in TEM Opera Plus FM Family Transmitter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41988</link><description>TEM Opera Plus FM Family Transmitter allows access to an unprotected endpoint that allows MPFS File System binary image upload without authentication. This file system serves as the basis for the HTTP2 web server module but is also used by the SNMP module and is available to other applications that require basic read-only storage capabilities. This can be exploited to overwrite the flash program memory that holds the web server's main interfaces and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47762 | Unexpected visibility of environment variable configurations in @backstage/plugin-app-backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47762</link><description>Backstage is an open framework for building developer portals. Configuration supplied through APP_CONFIG_* environment variables, for example APP_CONFIG_backend_listen_port=7007, where unexpectedly ignoring the visibility defined in configuration schema. This occurred even if the configuration schema specified that they should have backend or secret visibility. This was an intended feature of the APP_CONFIG_* way of supplying configuration, but now clearly goes against the expected behavior of the configuration system. This behavior leads to a risk of potentially exposing sensitive configuration details intended to remain private or restricted to backend processes. The issue has been resolved in version 0.3.75 of the @backstage/plugin-app-backend package. As a temporary measure, avoid supplying secrets using the APP_CONFIG_ configuration pattern. Consider alternative methods for setting secrets, such as the environment substitution available for Backstage configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7824 | Type-confusion vulnerability that can cause the WRSA.exe service to crash and generate a crash dump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7824</link><description>Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type ('Type Confusion') vulnerability in Webroot SecureAnywhere - Web Shield on Windows, ARM, 64 bit, 32 bit (wrUrl.Dll modules) allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects SecureAnywhere - Web Shield: before 2.1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7825 | Type confusion that can cause the WRSA.exe service to crash and generate a crash dump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7825</link><description>Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type ('Type Confusion') vulnerability in Webroot SecureAnywhere - Web Shield on Windows, ARM, 64 bit, 32 bit (wrUrl.Dll modules) allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects SecureAnywhere - Web Shield: before 2.1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7826 | Unhandled exception vulnerability that can cause the WRSA.exe service to crash and generate a crash dump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7826</link><description>Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Webroot SecureAnywhere - Web Shield on Windows, ARM, 64 bit, 32 bit (wrURL.Dll modules) allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects SecureAnywhere - Web Shield: before 2.1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0125 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the nvdisam command line tool, where a user can cause a NULL pointer d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0125</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the nvdisam command line tool, where a user can cause a NULL pointer dereference by running nvdisasm on a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a limited denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0123 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm command line tool where an attacker may cause an improper...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0123</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm command line tool where an attacker may cause an improper validation in input issue by tricking the user into running nvdisasm on a malicious ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0124 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the nvdisam command line tool, where a user can cause nvdisasm to read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0124</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the nvdisam command line tool, where a user can cause nvdisasm to read freed memory by running it on a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a limited denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45871 | Bandisoft BandiView 7.05 is Incorrect Access Control via sub_0x232bd8 resulting in denial of service (DOS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45871</link><description>Bandisoft BandiView 7.05 is Incorrect Access Control via sub_0x232bd8 resulting in denial of service (DOS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45872 | Bandisoft BandiView 7.05 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via sub_0x410d1d. The vulnerability occurs due to insufficient validation of PSD f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45872</link><description>Bandisoft BandiView 7.05 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via sub_0x410d1d. The vulnerability occurs due to insufficient validation of PSD files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8508 | Unbounded name compression could lead to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8508</link><description>NLnet Labs Unbound up to and including version 1.21.0 contains a vulnerability when handling replies with very large RRsets that it needs to perform name compression for. Malicious upstreams responses with very large RRsets can cause Unbound to spend a considerable time applying name compression to downstream replies. This can lead to degraded performance and eventually denial of service in well orchestrated attacks. The vulnerability can be exploited by a malicious actor querying Unbound for the specially crafted contents of a malicious zone with very large RRsets. Before Unbound replies to the query it will try to apply name compression which was an unbounded operation that could lock the CPU until the whole packet was complete. Unbound version 1.21.1 introduces a hard limit on the number of name compression calculations it is willing to do per packet. Packets that need more compression will result in semi-compressed packets or truncated packets, even on TCP for huge messages, to avoid locking the CPU for long. This change should not affect normal DNS traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45870 | Bandisoft BandiView 7.05 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in sub_0x3d80fc via a crafted POC file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45870</link><description>Bandisoft BandiView 7.05 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in sub_0x3d80fc via a crafted POC file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25590 | Crafted responses can lead to a denial of service due to cache inefficiencies in the Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25590</link><description>An attacker can publish a zone containing specific Resource Record Sets.

 Repeatedly processing and caching results for these sets can lead to a 

denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36474 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the Compound Document Binary File format parser of the GNOME Project G Structured File Library (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36474</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the Compound Document Binary File format parser of the GNOME Project G Structured File Library (libgsf) version v1.14.52. A specially crafted file can result in an integer overflow when processing the directory from the file that allows for an out-of-bounds index to be used when reading and writing to an array. This can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39755 | A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Veertu Anka Build 1.42.0. The vulnerability occurs during Anka node agent update. A low p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39755</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Veertu Anka Build 1.42.0. The vulnerability occurs during Anka node agent update. A low privilege user can trigger the update action which can result in unexpected elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41163 | A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the archive download functionality of Veertu Anka Build 1.42.0. A specially crafted HTTP reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41163</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the archive download functionality of Veertu Anka Build 1.42.0. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a disclosure of arbitrary files. An attacker can make an unauthenticated HTTP request to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41922 | A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the log files download functionality of Veertu Anka Build 1.42.0. A specially crafted HTTP req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41922</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the log files download functionality of Veertu Anka Build 1.42.0. A specially crafted HTTP request can result in a disclosure of arbitrary files. An attacker can make an unauthenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42415 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the Compound Document Binary File format parser of v1.14.52 of the GNOME Project G Structured Fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42415</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the Compound Document Binary File format parser of v1.14.52 of the GNOME Project G Structured File Library (libgsf). A specially crafted file can result in an integer overflow that allows for a heap-based buffer overflow when processing the sector allocation table. This can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47614 | async-graphql vulnerable to Directive Overload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47614</link><description>async-graphql is a GraphQL server library implemented in Rust. async-graphql before 7.0.10 does not limit the number of directives for a field. This can lead to Service Disruption, Resource Exhaustion, and User Experience Degradation. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9460 | Codezips Online Shopping Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9460</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47617 | Reflected XSS Vulnerability in Sulu Media Bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47617</link><description>Sulu is a PHP content management system. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject arbitrary HTML/JavaScript code through the media download URL in Sulu CMS. It affects the SuluMediaBundle component. The vulnerability is a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) issue, which could potentially allow attackers to steal sensitive information, manipulate the website's content, or perform actions on behalf of the victim. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.6.5 and 2.5.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47618 | Sulu vulnerable to XSS via uploaded SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47618</link><description>Sulu is a PHP content management system. Sulu is vulnerable against XSS whereas a low privileged user with access to the “Media” section can upload an SVG file with a malicious payload. Once uploaded and accessed, the malicious javascript will be executed on the victims’ (other users including admins) browsers. This issue is fixed in 2.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5803 | Local privelage escalation via COM hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5803</link><description>The AVGUI.exe of AVG/Avast Antivirus before versions before 24.1 can allow a local attacker to escalate privileges via an COM hijack in a time-of-check to time-of-use (TOCTOU) when self protection is disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9100 | Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9100</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Analytics Plus versions before 5410 and Zoho Analytics On-Premise versions before 5410 are vulnerable to Path traversal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47554 | Apache Commons IO: Possible denial of service attack on untrusted input to XmlStreamReader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47554</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Apache Commons IO.

The org.apache.commons.io.input.XmlStreamReader class may excessively consume CPU resources when processing maliciously crafted input.


This issue affects Apache Commons IO: from 2.0 before 2.14.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.14.0 or later, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9313 | Authd PAM module before version 0.3.5 can allow broker-managed users to impersonate any other user managed by the same broker and perform an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9313</link><description>Authd PAM module before version 0.3.5 can allow broker-managed users to impersonate any other user managed by the same broker and perform any PAM operation with it, including authenticating as them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47561 | Apache Avro Java SDK: Arbitrary Code Execution when reading Avro schema (Java SDK)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47561</link><description>Schema parsing in the Java SDK of Apache Avro 1.11.3 and previous versions allows bad actors to execute arbitrary code.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.11.4  or 1.12.0, which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42504 | HPE IceWall Agent products, Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42504</link><description>A security vulnerability in HPE IceWall Agent products could be exploited remotely to cause a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the login flow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 06:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8159 | Deep Freeze 9.00.020.5760 - Out-of-bounds read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8159</link><description>Deep Freeze 9.00.020.5760 is vulnerable to an out-of-bounds read vulnerability by triggering the 0x70014 IOCTL code of the FarDisk.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 06:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8352 | Social Web Suite – Social Media Auto Post, Social Media Auto Publish &amp;lt;= 4.1.11 - Directory Traversal to Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8352</link><description>The Social Web Suite – Social Media Auto Post, Social Media Auto Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.11 via the download_log function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 03:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47134 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.14.0 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47134</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.14.0 and earlier. Having a user open a specially crafted project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, arbitrary code execution, and/or information disclosure because the issues exist in parsing of KPP project files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 03:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47135 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47135</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.14.0 and earlier. Having a user open a specially crafted project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, arbitrary code execution, and/or information disclosure because the issues exist in parsing of KPP project files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 03:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47136 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.14.0 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47136</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.14.0 and earlier. Having a user open a specially crafted project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, arbitrary code execution, and/or information disclosure because the issues exist in parsing of KPP project files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 03:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45519 | The postjournal service in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 8.8.15 Patch 46, 9 before 9.0.0 Patch 41, 10 before 10.0.9, and 10.1 before 10....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45519</link><description>The postjournal service in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) before 8.8.15 Patch 46, 9 before 9.0.0 Patch 41, 10 before 10.0.9, and 10.1 before 10.1.1 sometimes allows unauthenticated users to execute commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47616 | Pomerium&amp;#x27;s service account access token may grant unintended access to databroker API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47616</link><description>Pomerium is an identity and context-aware access proxy. The Pomerium databroker service is responsible for managing all persistent Pomerium application state. Requests to the databroker service API are authorized by the presence of a JSON Web Token (JWT) signed by a key known by all Pomerium services in the same deployment. However, incomplete validation of this JWT meant that some service account access tokens would incorrectly be treated as valid for the purpose of databroker API authorization. Improper access to the databroker API could allow exfiltration of user info, spoofing of user sessions, or tampering with Pomerium routes, policies, and other settings. A Pomerium deployment is susceptible to this issue if all of the following conditions are met, you have issued a service account access token using Pomerium Zero or Pomerium Enterprise, the access token has an explicit expiration date in the future, and the core Pomerium databroker gRPC API is not otherwise secured by network access controls. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28888 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reade 2024.1.0.23997 handles a checkbox  field object. A specially crafted Javascript...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28888</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reade 2024.1.0.23997 handles a checkbox  field object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24117 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P RGOS v.10.4(1)P2 Release (9736) allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24117</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P RGOS v.10.4(1)P2 Release (9736) allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via the login check state component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45962 | October 3.6.30 allows an authenticated admin account to upload a PDF file containing malicious JavaScript into the target system. If the fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45962</link><description>October 3.6.30 allows an authenticated admin account to upload a PDF file containing malicious JavaScript into the target system. If the file is accessed through the website, it could lead to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack or execute arbitrary code via a crafted JavaScript to the target.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45960 | Zenario 9.7.61188 allows authenticated admin users to upload PDF files containing malicious code into the target system. If the PDF file is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45960</link><description>Zenario 9.7.61188 allows authenticated admin users to upload PDF files containing malicious code into the target system. If the PDF file is accessed through the website, it can trigger a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45964 | Zenario 9.7.61188 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Image library via the "Organizer tags" field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45964</link><description>Zenario 9.7.61188 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Image library via the "Organizer tags" field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45965 | Contao 5.4.1 allows an authenticated admin account to upload a SVG file containing malicious javascript code into the target system. If the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45965</link><description>Contao 5.4.1 allows an authenticated admin account to upload a SVG file containing malicious javascript code into the target system. If the file is accessed through the website, it could lead to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack or execute arbitrary code via a crafted javascript to the target.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43795 | OpenC3 COSMOS vulnerable to cross-site scripting in Login functionality (`GHSL-2024-128`)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43795</link><description>OpenC3 COSMOS provides the functionality needed to send commands to and receive data from one or more embedded systems. The login functionality contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.19.0. Note: This CVE only affects Open Source Edition, and not OpenC3 COSMOS Enterprise Edition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46977 | OpenC3 COSMOS allows a path traversal via screen controller (`GHSL-2024-127`)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46977</link><description>OpenC3 COSMOS provides the functionality needed to send commands to and receive data from one or more embedded systems. A path traversal vulnerability inside of LocalMode's open_local_file method allows an authenticated user with adequate permissions to download any .txt via the ScreensController#show on the web server COSMOS is running on (depending on the file permissions). This vulnerability is fixed in 5.19.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47529 | OpenC3 COSMOS uses clear text storage of password/token (`GHSL-2024-129`)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47529</link><description>OpenC3 COSMOS provides the functionality needed to send commands to and receive data from one or more embedded systems. OpenC3 COSMOS stores the password of a user unencrypted in the LocalStorage of a web browser. This makes the user password susceptible to exfiltration via Cross-site scripting (see GHSL-2024-128). This vulnerability is fixed in 5.19.0. This only affects Open Source edition, and not OpenC3 COSMOS Enterprise Edition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8733 | HP One Agent Software – Potential Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8733</link><description>A potential security vulnerability
has been identified in the HP One Agent for certain HP PC products, which might
allow for escalation of privilege. HP is releasing software updates to mitigate
this potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9441 | Linear eMerge e3-Series Forgot Password Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9441</link><description>The Linear eMerge e3-Series through version 1.00-07 is vulnerable to an OS command injection vulnerability. A remote and unauthenticated attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands via the login_id parameter when invoking the forgot_password functionality over HTTP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9440 | Slim Select 2.0 createOption &amp;quot;text&amp;quot; XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9440</link><description>Slim Select 2.0 versions through 2.9.0 are affected by a potential cross-site scripting vulnerability. In select.ts:createOption(), the text variable from the user-provided Options object is assigned to an innerHTML without sanitation. Software that depends on this library to dynamically generate lists using unsanitized user-provided input may be vulnerable to cross-site scripting, resulting in attacker executed JavaScript. At this time, no patch is available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20498 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20498</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition in the AnyConnect service on an affected device.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of client-supplied parameters while establishing an SSL VPN session. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted HTTPS request to the VPN server of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server to restart, resulting in the failure of the established SSL VPN connections and forcing remote users to initiate a new VPN connection and reauthenticate. A sustained attack could prevent new SSL VPN connections from being established.
Note: When the attack traffic stops, the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server recovers gracefully without requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20499 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20499</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition in the AnyConnect service on an affected device.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of client-supplied parameters while establishing an SSL VPN session. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted HTTPS request to the VPN server of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server to restart, resulting in the failure of the established SSL VPN connections and forcing remote users to initiate a new VPN connection and reauthenticate. A sustained attack could prevent new SSL VPN connections from being established.
Note: When the attack traffic stops, the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server recovers gracefully without requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20500 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20500</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition in the AnyConnect service on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient resource management when establishing TLS/SSL sessions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted TLS/SSL messages to the VPN server of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server to stop accepting new connections, preventing new SSL VPN connections from being established. Existing SSL VPN sessions are not impacted.
Note: When the attack traffic stops, the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server recovers gracefully without requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20501 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20501</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition in the AnyConnect service on an affected device.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of client-supplied parameters while establishing an SSL VPN session. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted HTTPS request to the VPN server of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server to restart, resulting in the failure of the established SSL VPN connections and forcing remote users to initiate a new VPN connection and reauthenticate. A sustained attack could prevent new SSL VPN connections from being established.
Note: When the attack traffic stops, the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server recovers gracefully without requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20502 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20502</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient resource management while establishing SSL VPN sessions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted HTTPS requests to the VPN server of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server to stop accepting new connections, preventing new SSL VPN connections from being established. Existing SSL VPN sessions are not impacted.
Note: When the attack traffic stops, the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server recovers gracefully without requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20509 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Session Takeover and Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20509</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to hijack an AnyConnect VPN session or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition for individual users of the AnyConnect VPN service on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to weak entropy for handlers that are used during the VPN authentication process as well as a race condition that exists in the same process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by correctly guessing an authentication handler and then sending crafted HTTPS requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to take over the AnyConnect VPN session from a target user or prevent the target user from establishing an AnyConnect VPN session with the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20513 | Cisco Meraki MX and Z3 Teleworker Gateway AnyConnect VPN Targeted Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20513</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco AnyConnect VPN server of Cisco Meraki MX and Cisco Meraki Z Series Teleworker Gateway devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition for targeted users of the AnyConnect service on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient entropy for handlers that are used during SSL VPN session establishment. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by brute forcing valid session handlers. An authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the AnyConnect VPN service of an affected device to retrieve a valid session handler and, based on that handler, predict further valid session handlers. The attacker would then send a crafted HTTPS request using the brute-forced or predicted session handler to the AnyConnect VPN server of the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to terminate targeted SSL VPN sessions, forcing remote users to initiate new VPN connections and reauthenticate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24116 | An issue in Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P RGOS v.10.4(1)P2 Release(9736) allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via the system/config_menu.htm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24116</link><description>An issue in Ruijie RG-NBS2009G-P RGOS v.10.4(1)P2 Release(9736) allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via the system/config_menu.htm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24122 | A remote code execution vulnerability in the project management of Wanxing Technology's Yitu project which allows an attacker to use the exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24122</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability in the project management of Wanxing Technology's Yitu project which allows an attacker to use the exp.adpx file as a zip compressed file to construct a special file name, which can be used to decompress the project file into the system startup folder, restart the system, and automatically execute the constructed attack script.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20365 | Cisco Integrated Management Controller Redfish Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20365</link><description>A vulnerability in the Redfish API of Cisco UCS B-Series, Cisco UCS Managed C-Series, and Cisco UCS X-Series Servers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to perform command injection attacks on an affected system and elevate privileges to root.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands through the Redfish API on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20385 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator SSL Certificate Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20385</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS implementation of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator (NDO) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to intercept sensitive information from an affected device.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability exists because the Cisco NDO Validate Peer Certificate site management feature validates the certificates for Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC), Cisco Cloud Network Controller (CNC), and Cisco Nexus Dashboard only when a new site is added or an existing one is reregistered. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using machine-in-the-middle techniques to intercept the traffic between the affected device and Cisco NDO and then using a crafted certificate to impersonate the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to learn sensitive information during communications between these devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20393 | Cisco RV340, RV340W, RV345, and RV345P Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20393</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV340, RV340W, RV345, and RV345P Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface discloses sensitive information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP input to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to elevate privileges from guest to admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20432 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Web UI Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20432</link><description>A vulnerability in the REST API and web UI of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack against an affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper user authorization and insufficient validation of command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted commands to an affected REST API endpoint or through the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the CLI of a Cisco NDFC-managed device with network-admin privileges.
&amp;nbsp;
Note: This vulnerability does not affect Cisco NDFC when it is configured for storage area network (SAN) controller deployment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20438 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Unauthorized REST API Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20438</link><description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoints of Cisco NDFC could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to read or write files on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because of missing authorization controls on some REST API endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to an affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform limited network-admin functions such as reading device configuration information, uploading files, and modifying uploaded files.
Note: This vulnerability only affects a subset of REST API endpoints and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20441 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Unauthorized API Endpoint Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20441</link><description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API endpoint of Cisco NDFC could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to learn sensitive information on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization controls on the affected REST API endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to the&amp;nbsp;affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download config only or full backup files and learn sensitive configuration information. This vulnerability only affects a specific REST API endpoint and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20442 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Unauthorized API Endpoints Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20442</link><description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoints of Cisco Nexus Dashboard could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to perform limited Administrator actions on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization controls on some REST API endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to an affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform limited Administrator functions such as viewing portions of the web UI, generating config only or full backup files, and deleting tech support files. This vulnerability only affects a subset of REST API endpoints and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20444 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller REST API Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20444</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC), formerly Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM), could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with network-admin privileges to perform a command injection attack against an affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted command arguments to a specific REST API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite sensitive files or crash a specific container, which would restart on its own, causing a low-impact denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20448 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Credential Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20448</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) software, formerly Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM), could allow an attacker with access to a backup file to view sensitive information.

This vulnerability is due to the improper storage of sensitive information within config only and full backup files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by parsing the contents of a backup file that is generated from an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive information, including NDFC-connected device credentials, the NDFC site manager private key, and the scheduled backup file encryption key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20449 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20449</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to execute arbitrary code on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper path validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) to upload malicious code to an affected device using path traversal techniques. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary&amp;nbsp;code in a specific container with the privileges of root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20470 | Cisco RV340, RV340W, RV345, and RV345P Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20470</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV340, RV340W, RV345, and RV345P Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid admin credentials.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not sufficiently validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP input to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20477 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller Unauthorized REST API Endpoint Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20477</link><description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API endpoint of Cisco NDFC could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to upload or delete files on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because of missing authorization controls on the affected REST API endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to the affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload files into a specific container or delete files from a specific folder within that container. This vulnerability only affects a specific REST API endpoint and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20490 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller and Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20490</link><description>A vulnerability in a logging function of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) and Cisco Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator (NDO) could allow an attacker with access to a tech support file to view sensitive information.

This vulnerability exists because HTTP proxy credentials could be recorded in an internal log that is stored in the tech support file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a tech support file that is generated from an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view HTTP proxy server admin credentials in clear text that are configured on Nexus Dashboard to reach an external network.
Note: Best practice is to store debug logs and tech support files safely and to share them only with trusted parties because they may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20491 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Insights Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20491</link><description>A vulnerability in a logging function of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Insights could allow an attacker with access to a tech support file to view sensitive information.

This vulnerability exists because remote controller credentials are recorded in an internal log that is stored in the tech support file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a tech support file that is generated from an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view remote controller admin credentials in clear text.
Note: Best practice is to store debug logs and tech support files safely and to share them only with trusted parties because they may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20492 | Cisco Expressway Series Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20492</link><description>A vulnerability in the restricted shell of Cisco Expressway Series could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have Administrator-level credentials with read-write privileges on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a series of crafted CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted shell and gain root privileges on the underlying operating system of the affected device.
Note: Cisco Expressway Series refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20515 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20515</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper data protection mechanisms for certain configuration settings. An attacker with Read-Only Administrator privileges could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view device credentials that are normally not visible to Read-Only Administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20516 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20516</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input that is in incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20517 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20517</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input that is in incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20518 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Remote Command Execution Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20518</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20519 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Remote Command Execution Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20519</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20520 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Remote Command Execution Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20520</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20521 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Remote Command Execution Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20521</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20522 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20522</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input that is in incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20523 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20523</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input that is in incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20524 | Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20524</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV042, RV042G, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, Administrator-level, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device.
&amp;nbsp;
This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input that is in incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41290 | FlatPress CMS v1.3.1 1.3 was discovered to use insecure methods to store authentication data via the cookie's component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41290</link><description>FlatPress CMS v1.3.1 1.3 was discovered to use insecure methods to store authentication data via the cookie's component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46626 | OS4ED openSIS-Classic v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via a crafted payload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46626</link><description>OS4ED openSIS-Classic v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47803 | Jenkins 2.478 and earlier, LTS 2.462.2 and earlier does not redact multi-line secret values in error messages generated for form submissions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47803</link><description>Jenkins 2.478 and earlier, LTS 2.462.2 and earlier does not redact multi-line secret values in error messages generated for form submissions involving the `secretTextarea` form field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47804 | If an attempt is made to create an item of a type prohibited by `ACL#hasCreatePermission2` or `TopLevelItemDescriptor#isApplicableIn(ItemGro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47804</link><description>If an attempt is made to create an item of a type prohibited by `ACL#hasCreatePermission2` or `TopLevelItemDescriptor#isApplicableIn(ItemGroup)` through the Jenkins CLI or the REST API and either of these checks fail, Jenkins 2.478 and earlier, LTS 2.462.2 and earlier creates the item in memory, only deleting it from disk, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to save the item to persist it, effectively bypassing the item creation restriction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47805 | Jenkins Credentials Plugin 1380.va_435002fa_924 and earlier, except 1371.1373.v4eb_fa_b_7161e9, does not redact encrypted values of credenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47805</link><description>Jenkins Credentials Plugin 1380.va_435002fa_924 and earlier, except 1371.1373.v4eb_fa_b_7161e9, does not redact encrypted values of credentials using the `SecretBytes` type when accessing item `config.xml` via REST API or CLI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47806 | Jenkins OpenId Connect Authentication Plugin 4.354.v321ce67a_1de8 and earlier does not check the `aud` (Audience) claim of an ID Token, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47806</link><description>Jenkins OpenId Connect Authentication Plugin 4.354.v321ce67a_1de8 and earlier does not check the `aud` (Audience) claim of an ID Token, allowing attackers to subvert the authentication flow, potentially gaining administrator access to Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47807 | Jenkins OpenId Connect Authentication Plugin 4.354.v321ce67a_1de8 and earlier does not check the `iss` (Issuer) claim of an ID Token, allowi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47807</link><description>Jenkins OpenId Connect Authentication Plugin 4.354.v321ce67a_1de8 and earlier does not check the `iss` (Issuer) claim of an ID Token, allowing attackers to subvert the authentication flow, potentially gaining administrator access to Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33210 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in Flatpress 1.3. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33210</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in Flatpress 1.3. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts into web pages viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9423 | Certain HP LaserJet Printers – Potential Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9423</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet printers may potentially experience a denial of service when a user sends a raw JPEG file to the printer. The printer displays a “JPEG Unsupported” message which may not clear, potentially blocking queued print jobs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33209 | FlatPress v1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into the "Add New Entry" sectio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33209</link><description>FlatPress v1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into the "Add New Entry" section, which allows them to execute arbitrary code in the context of a victim's web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6360 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Vertica.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6360</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in OpenText™ Vertica could allow Privilege Abuse and result in unauthorized access or privileges to Vertica agent apikey.
This issue affects Vertica: from 10.0 through 10.X, from 11.0 through 11.X, from 12.0 through 12.X, from 23.0 through 23.X, from 24.0 through 24.X.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44193 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.3 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44193</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.3 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate  their privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47611 | XZ Utils on Microsoft Windows platform are vulnerable to argument injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47611</link><description>XZ Utils provide a general-purpose data-compression library plus command-line tools. When built for native Windows (MinGW-w64 or MSVC), the command line tools from XZ Utils 5.6.2 and older have a command line argument injection vulnerability. If a command line contains Unicode characters (for example, filenames) that don't exist in the current legacy code page, the characters are converted to similar-looking characters with best-fit mapping. Some best-fit mappings result in ASCII characters that change the meaning of the command line, which can be exploited with malicious filenames to do argument injection or directory traversal attacks. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.6.3. Command line tools built for Cygwin or MSYS2 are unaffected. liblzma is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47612 | XSS in Special:DataDump when displaying dump status</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47612</link><description>DataDump is a MediaWiki extension that provides dumps of wikis. Several interface messages are unescaped (more specifically, (datadump-table-column-queued), (datadump-table-column-in-progress), (datadump-table-column-completed), (datadump-table-column-failed)). If these messages are edited (which requires the (editinterface) right by default), anyone who can view Special:DataDump (which requires the (view-dump) right by default) can be XSSed. This vulnerability is fixed with 601688ee8e8808a23b102fa305b178f27cbd226d.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44097 | According to the researcher: "The TLS connections are encrypted against tampering or eavesdropping. However, the application does not valida...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44097</link><description>According to the researcher: "The TLS connections are encrypted against tampering or eavesdropping. However, the application does not validate the server certificate properly while initializing the TLS connection. This allows for a network attacker to intercept the connection and read the data. The attacker could the either send the client a malicious response, or forward the (possibly modified) data to the real server."</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9429 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System filter2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9429</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /filter2.php. The manipulation of the argument from/to leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "from" to be affected. But it must be assumed that parameter "to" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8885 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability in the Device Encryption component of Sophos Intercept X for Windows older than version 2024.3 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8885</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability in the Device Encryption component of Sophos Intercept X for Windows older than version 2024.3 allows writing of arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35294 | Schneider Elektronik Series 700 prone to missing authentication for traffic capture function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35294</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use the devices traffic capture without authentication to grab plaintext administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7558 | JUJU_CONTEXT_ID is a predictable authentication secret. On a Juju machine (non-Kubernetes) or Juju charm container (on Kubernetes), an unpri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7558</link><description>JUJU_CONTEXT_ID is a predictable authentication secret. On a Juju machine (non-Kubernetes) or Juju charm container (on Kubernetes), an unprivileged user in the same network namespace can connect to an abstract domain socket and guess the JUJU_CONTEXT_ID value. This gives the unprivileged user access to the same information and tools as the Juju charm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8037 | Vulnerable juju hook tool abstract UNIX domain socket. When combined with an attack of JUJU_CONTEXT_ID, any user on the local system with ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8037</link><description>Vulnerable juju hook tool abstract UNIX domain socket. When combined with an attack of JUJU_CONTEXT_ID, any user on the local system with access to the default network namespace may connect to the @/var/lib/juju/agents/unit-xxxx-yyyy/agent.socket and perform actions that are normally reserved to a juju charm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8038 | Vulnerable juju introspection abstract UNIX domain socket. An abstract UNIX domain socket responsible for introspection is available without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8038</link><description>Vulnerable juju introspection abstract UNIX domain socket. An abstract UNIX domain socket responsible for introspection is available without authentication locally to network namespace users. This enables denial of service attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35293 | Schneider Elektronik Series 700 prone to missing authentication for critical reset function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35293</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a missing authentication for critical function vulnerability to reboot or erase the affected devices resulting in data loss and/or a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8282 | Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8282</link><description>The Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’ attribute within the 'wp:ive/ive-productscarousel' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8505 | WordPress Infinite Scroll - Ajax Load More &amp;lt;= 7.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via button_label Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8505</link><description>The WordPress Infinite Scroll – Ajax Load More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘button_label’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44017 | WordPress MH Board plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44017</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in MinHyeong Lim MH Board allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects MH Board: from n/a through 1.3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44030 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP plugin &amp;lt;= 8.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44030</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 8.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9218 | Magazine Blocks – Blog Designer, Magazine &amp;amp; Newspaper Website Builder, Page Builder with Posts Blocks, Post Grid &amp;lt;= 1.3.14 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9218</link><description>The Magazine Blocks – Blog Designer, Magazine &amp; Newspaper Website Builder, Page Builder with Posts Blocks, Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 08:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9344 | BerqWP – Automated All-In-One PageSpeed Optimization Plugin for Core Web Vitals, Cache, CDN, Images, CSS, and JavaScript &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9344</link><description>The BerqWP – Automated All-In-One PageSpeed Optimization Plugin for Core Web Vitals, Cache, CDN, Images, CSS, and JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 08:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9378 | YML for Yandex Market &amp;lt;= 4.7.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9378</link><description>The YML for Yandex Market plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 08:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8800 | RabbitLoader – Website Speed Optimization for improving Core Web Vital metrics with Cache, Image Optimization, and more &amp;lt;= 2.21.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8800</link><description>The RabbitLoader – Website Speed Optimization for improving Core Web Vital metrics with Cache, Image Optimization, and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.21.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8967 | PWA — easy way to Progressive Web App &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8967</link><description>The PWA — easy way to Progressive Web App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9172 | Demo Importer Plus &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9172</link><description>The Demo Importer Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9210 | MC4WP: Mailchimp Top Bar &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9210</link><description>The MC4WP: Mailchimp Top Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9222 | Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 2.12.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9222</link><description>The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9225 | SEOPress – On-site SEO &amp;lt;= 8.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9225</link><description>The SEOPress – On-site SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 8.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8254 | Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.7.34 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8254</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.34. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 06:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7315 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid &amp;lt; 0.9.106 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7315</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging  WordPress plugin before 0.9.106 does not use sufficient randomness in the filename that is created when generating a backup, which could be bruteforced by attackers to leak sensitive information about said backups.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 06:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9333 | Permission bypass in M-Files Connector for Copilot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9333</link><description>Permissions bypass in M-Files Connector for Copilot before version 24.9.3 allows authenticated user to access limited amount of documents via incorrect access control list calculation</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 06:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9174 | Stored HTML Injection in Hubshare social module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9174</link><description>Stored HTML Injection in Social Module in M-Files Hubshare before version 5.0.8.6 allows authenticated user to spoof UI</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 05:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21530 | Versions of the package cocoon before 0.4.0 are vulnerable to Reusing a Nonce, Key Pair in Encryption when the encrypt, wrap, and dump funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21530</link><description>Versions of the package cocoon before 0.4.0 are vulnerable to Reusing a Nonce, Key Pair in Encryption when the encrypt, wrap, and dump functions are sequentially called. An attacker can generate the same ciphertext by creating a new encrypted message with the same cocoon object.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;The issue does NOT affect objects created with Cocoon::new which utilizes ThreadRng.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 05:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45186 | FileSender before 2.49 allows server-side template injection (SSTI) for retrieving credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45186</link><description>FileSender before 2.49 allows server-side template injection (SSTI) for retrieving credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 04:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33662 | Portainer before 2.20.2 improperly uses an encryption algorithm in the AesEncrypt function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33662</link><description>Portainer before 2.20.2 improperly uses an encryption algorithm in the AesEncrypt function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 04:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7855 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7855</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the update_review() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 04:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>