<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-38876 | A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions &gt;= R9.2), Omnivise T3000 Domain Controller (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38876</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions &gt;= R9.2), Omnivise T3000 Domain Controller (All versions &gt;= R9.2), Omnivise T3000 Product Data Management (PDM) (All versions &gt;= R9.2), Omnivise T3000 Terminal Server (All versions &gt;= R9.2), Omnivise T3000 Thin Client (All versions &gt;= R9.2), Omnivise T3000 Whitelisting Server (All versions &gt;= R9.2). The affected application regularly executes user modifiable code as a privileged user. This could allow a local authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38877 | A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Domain Controller (All versions), Om...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38877</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Domain Controller (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Network Intrusion Detection System (NIDS) (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Product Data Management (PDM) (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Security Server (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Terminal Server (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Thin Client (All versions), Omnivise T3000 Whitelisting Server (All versions). The affected devices stores initial system credentials without sufficient protection.  An attacker with remote shell access or physical access could retrieve the credentials leading to confidentiality loss allowing the attacker to laterally move within the affected network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38878 | A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions). Affected devices allow authenticated users to expor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38878</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions). Affected devices allow authenticated users to export diagnostics data. The corresponding API endpoint is susceptible to path traversal and could allow an authenticated attacker to download arbitrary files from the file system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38879 | A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions). The affected system exposes the port of an internal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38879</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Omnivise T3000 Application Server (All versions). The affected system exposes the port of an internal application on the public network interface allowing an attacker to circumvent authentication and directly access the exposed application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7204 | Ai3 QbiBot - Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7204</link><description>Ai3 QbiBot does not properly filter user input, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to insert JavaScript code into the chat box. Once the recipient views the message, they will be subject to a Stored XSS attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40723 | CHANGING Information Technology HWATAIServiSign Windows Version - Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40723</link><description>The specific API in HWATAIServiSign Windows Version from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate the length of server-side inputs. When a user visits a spoofed website, unauthenticated remote attackers can cause a stack-based buffer overflow in the HWATAIServiSign, temporarily disrupting its service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40722 | CHANGING Information Technology TCBServiSign Windows Version - Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40722</link><description>The specific API in TCBServiSign Windows Version from CHANGING Information Technology does does not properly validate the length of server-side input. When a user visits a spoofed website, unauthenticated remote attackers can cause a stack-based buffer overflow in the TCBServiSign, temporarily disrupting its service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40720 | CHANGING Information Technology TCBServiSign Windows Version - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40720</link><description>The specific API in TCBServiSign Windows Version from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate server-side input. When a user visits a spoofed website, unauthenticated remote attackers can modify the `HKEY_CURRENT_USER` registry to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40721 | CHANGING Information Technology TCBServiSign Windows Version - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40721</link><description>The specific API in TCBServiSign Windows Version from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate server-side input. When a user visits a spoofed website, unauthenticated remote attackers can cause the TCBServiSign to load a DLL from an arbitrary path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40719 | CHANGING Information Technology TCBServiSign Windows Version - Inadequate Encryption Strength</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40719</link><description>The encryption strength of the authorization keys in CHANGING Information Technology TCBServiSign Windows Version is insufficient. When a remote attacker tricks a victim into visiting a malicious website, TCBServiSign will treat that website as a legitimate server and interact with it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36268 | Apache InLong TubeMQ Client: Remote Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36268</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.10.0 through 1.12.0, which could lead to Remote Code Execution. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 1.13.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/10251</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27182 | Apache Linkis  Basic management services: Engine material management Arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27182</link><description>In Apache Linkis &lt;= 1.5.0,

Arbitrary file deletion in Basic management services on 

A user with an administrator account could delete any file accessible by the Linkis system user

.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.6.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4643 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4643</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘end_redirect_link’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27181 | Apache Linkis Basic management services: Privilege Escalation Attack vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27181</link><description>In Apache Linkis &lt;= 1.5.0,

Privilege Escalation in Basic management services where the attacking user is 

a trusted account

 allows access to Linkis's Token information. Users are advised to upgrade to version 1.6.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38776 | WordPress WP GoToWebinar plugin &amp;lt;= 15.7 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38776</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP GoToWebinar allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects WP GoToWebinar: from n/a through 15.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42459 | In the Elliptic package 6.5.6 for Node.js, EDDSA signature malleability occurs because there is a missing signature length check, and thus z...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42459</link><description>In the Elliptic package 6.5.6 for Node.js, EDDSA signature malleability occurs because there is a missing signature length check, and thus zero-valued bytes can be removed or appended.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42460 | In the Elliptic package 6.5.6 for Node.js, ECDSA signature malleability occurs because there is a missing check for whether the leading bit ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42460</link><description>In the Elliptic package 6.5.6 for Node.js, ECDSA signature malleability occurs because there is a missing check for whether the leading bit of r and s is zero.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42461 | In the Elliptic package 6.5.6 for Node.js, ECDSA signature malleability occurs because BER-encoded signatures are allowed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42461</link><description>In the Elliptic package 6.5.6 for Node.js, ECDSA signature malleability occurs because BER-encoded signatures are allowed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39392 | Adobe Indesign 2024 EPS File Parsing Heap Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39392</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID18.5.2, ID19.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39396 | Adobe Indesign 2024 PCX File Parsing Out Of Bound Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39396</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID18.5.2, ID19.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3238 | WordPress Menu Plugin — Superfly Responsive Menu &amp;lt;= 5.0.29 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3238</link><description>The WordPress Menu Plugin — Superfly Responsive Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.29. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ajax_handle_delete_icons() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please not the CSRF was patched in 5.0.28, however, adequate directory traversal protection wasn't introduced until 5.0.30.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5595 | Essential Blocks &amp;lt; 4.7.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5595</link><description>The Essential Blocks  WordPress plugin before 4.7.0 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3827 | Spectra Pro &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Block IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3827</link><description>The Spectra Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via block ids in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 05:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7389 | Forminator &amp;lt;= 1.29.1 - HubSpot Developer API Key Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7389</link><description>The Forminator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.29.1 via class-forminator-addon-hubspot-wp-api.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract the HubSpot integration developer API key and make unauthorized changes to the plugin's HubSpot integration or expose personally identifiable information from plugin users using the HubSpot integration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 04:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38482 | CloudLink, versions 7.1.x and 8.x, contain an Improper check or handling of Exceptional Conditions Vulnerability in Cluster Component. A hig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38482</link><description>CloudLink, versions 7.1.x and 8.x, contain an Improper check or handling of Exceptional Conditions Vulnerability in Cluster Component. A highly privileged malicious user with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execute unauthorized actions and retrieve sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 04:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42458 | server.c in Neat VNC (aka neatvnc) before 0.8.1 does not properly validate the security type.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42458</link><description>server.c in Neat VNC (aka neatvnc) before 0.8.1 does not properly validate the security type.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 04:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7378 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System manage_question.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7378</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_question.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273362 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7377 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System view_result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7377</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view_result.php. The manipulation of the argument qid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273361 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6567 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8001 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6567</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 5.8001. This is due to the plugin utilizing fpdi-protection and not preventing direct access to test files that have display_errors set to true. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7376 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System print_quiz_records.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7376</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /print_quiz_records.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273360.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22278 | Harbor fails to validate the user permissions when updating project configurations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22278</link><description>Incorrect user permission validation in Harbor &lt;v2.10.3 allows authenticated users to modify configurations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 01:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7375 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System my_quiz_result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7375</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /my_quiz_result.php. The manipulation of the argument quiz leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273359.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 01:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7374 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7374</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273358 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 01:06:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7373 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7373</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=load_answered. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273357 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 01:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7372 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System quiz_board.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7372</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /quiz_board.php. The manipulation of the argument quiz leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273356.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7371 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System quiz_view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7371</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /quiz_view.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273355.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39626 | WordPress Pretty Simple Popup Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39626</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 5 Star Plugins Pretty Simple Popup Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pretty Simple Popup Builder: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39627 | WordPress Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and Themes – NextGEN Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.59.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39627</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Imagely NextGEN Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NextGEN Gallery: from n/a through 3.59.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7370 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System manage_quiz.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_quiz.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273354 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39629 | WordPress Himalayas theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39629</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGrill Himalayas allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Himalayas: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39631 | WordPress Contest Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 23.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Contest Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contest Gallery: from n/a through 23.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39643 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RegistrationMagic Forms RegistrationMagic allows Stored XSS.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 6.0.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39644 | WordPress Black Widgets For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39644</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Modernaweb Studio Black Widgets For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Black Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39646 | WordPress Custom 404 Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.11.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kunal Nagar Custom 404 Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Custom 404 Pro: from n/a through 3.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39647 | WordPress Message Filter for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kofi Mokome Message Filter for Contact Form 7 allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Message Filter for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.6.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41956 | Soft Serve allows arbitrary code execution by crafting git-lfs requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41956</link><description>Soft Serve is a self-hostable Git server for the command line. Prior to 0.7.5, it is possible for a user who can commit files to a repository hosted by Soft Serve to execute arbitrary code via environment manipulation and Git. The issue is that Soft Serve passes all environment variables given by the client to git subprocesses. This includes environment variables that control program execution, such as LD_PRELOAD. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.7.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41948 | biscuit-java vulnerable to public key confusion in third party block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41948</link><description>biscuit-java is the java implementation of Biscuit, an authentication and authorization token for microservices architectures. Third-party blocks can be generated without transferring the whole token to the third-party authority. Instead, a ThirdPartyBlock request can be sent, providing only the necessary info to generate a third-party block and to sign it, which includes the public key of the previous block (used in the signature) and the public keys part of the token symbol table (for public key interning in datalog expressions). A third-part block request forged by a malicious user can trick the third-party authority into generating datalog trusting the wrong keypair. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41949 | biscuit-rust vulnerable to public key confusion in third party block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41949</link><description>biscuit-rust is the Rust implementation of Biscuit, an authentication and authorization token for microservices architectures. Third-party blocks can be generated without transferring the whole token to the third-party authority. Instead, a ThirdPartyBlock request can be sent, providing only the necessary info to generate a third-party block and to sign it, which includes the public key of the previous block (used in the signature) and the public keys part of the token symbol table (for public key interning in datalog expressions). A third-part block request forged by a malicious user can trick the third-party authority into generating datalog trusting the wrong keypair.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7369 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System Login ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=login of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273353 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32862 | exacqVision CORS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32862</link><description>Under certain circumstances the ExacqVision Web Services does not provide sufficient protection from untrusted domains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39648 | WordPress Eventin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themewinter Eventin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Eventin: from n/a through 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39649 | WordPress  Essential Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.26 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39649</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Essential Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 5.9.26.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32758 | exacqVision - Key exchanges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32758</link><description>Under certain circumstances the communication between exacqVision Client and exacqVision Server will use insufficient key length and exchange</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39652 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Vouchers plugin &amp;lt; 4.9.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39652</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPWeb Elite WooCommerce PDF Vouchers allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Vouchers: from n/a before 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39655 | WordPress LiquidPoll plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.77 - Unauthenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LiquidPoll LiquidPoll – Advanced Polls for Creators and Brands.This issue affects LiquidPoll – Advanced Polls for Creators and Brands: from n/a through 3.3.77.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39656 | WordPress Tin Canny Reporting for LearnDash plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.0.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Tin Canny Reporting for LearnDash allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tin Canny Reporting for LearnDash: from n/a through 4.3.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39659 | WordPress WP-PostRatings plugin &amp;lt;= 1.91.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39659</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lester ‘GaMerZ’ Chan WP-PostRatings allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-PostRatings: from n/a through 1.91.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41965 | Vim &amp;lt; v9.1.0648 has a double-free in dialog_changed()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41965</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. double-free in dialog_changed() in Vim &lt; v9.1.0648. When abandoning a buffer, Vim may ask the user what to do with the modified buffer. If the user wants the changed buffer to be saved, Vim may create a new Untitled file, if the buffer did not have a name yet. However, when setting the buffer name to Unnamed, Vim will falsely free a pointer twice, leading to a double-free and possibly later to a heap-use-after-free, which can lead to a crash. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.0648.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39660 | WordPress Photo Engine (Media Organizer &amp;amp; Lightroom) plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39660</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jordy Meow Photo Engine allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Photo Engine: from n/a through 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39661 | WordPress Kubio AI Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Authenticated Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39661</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ExtendThemes Kubio AI Page Builder.This issue affects Kubio AI Page Builder: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39662 | WordPress Black Widgets For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Modernaweb Studio Black Widgets For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Black Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39663 | WordPress WP Fast Total Search plugin &amp;lt;= 1.68.232 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Epsiloncool WP Fast Total Search allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Fast Total Search: from n/a through 1.68.232.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41957 | Vim double free in src/alloc.c:616</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41957</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. Vim &lt; v9.1.0647 has double free in src/alloc.c:616. When closing a window, the corresponding tagstack data will be cleared and freed. However a bit later, the quickfix list belonging to that window will also be cleared and if that quickfix list points to the same tagstack data, Vim will try to free it again, resulting in a double-free/use-after-free access exception. Impact is low since the user must intentionally execute vim with several non-default flags,
but it may cause a crash of Vim. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.0647</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39665 | WordPress Filter &amp;amp; Grids plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in YMC Filter &amp; Grids allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Filter &amp; Grids: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39667 | WordPress Element Pack Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Element Pack Elementor Addons: from n/a through 5.6.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39668 | WordPress Extensions for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39668</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in petesheppard84 Extensions for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Extensions for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.31.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7368 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7368</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=save_quiz. The manipulation of the argument title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273352.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38761 | WordPress Zephyr Project Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.99 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Export File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38761</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Dylan James Zephyr Project Manager.This issue affects Zephyr Project Manager: from n/a through 3.3.99.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39636 | WordPress Better Find and Replace plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39636</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CodeSolz Better Find and Replace.This issue affects Better Find and Replace: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39637 | WordPress Edubin theme &amp;lt;= 9.2.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39637</link><description>Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Pixelcurve Edubin edubin.This issue affects Edubin: from n/a through 9.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32931 | exacqVison - Token Disclosed in URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32931</link><description>Under certain circumstances the exacqVision Web Service can expose authentication token details within communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32865 | exacqVison - TLS certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32865</link><description>Under certain circumstances the exacqVision Server will not properly validate TLS certificates provided by connected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32864 | exacqVison - HTTPS Session Establishment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32864</link><description>Under certain circumstances exacqVision Web Services will not enforce secure web communications (HTTPS)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7093 | Server-Side Template Injection in Dispatch Message Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7093</link><description>Dispatch's notification service uses Jinja templates to generate messages to users. Jinja permits code execution within blocks, which were neither properly sanitized nor sandboxed. This vulnerability enables users to construct command line scripts in their custom message templates, which are then executed whenever these notifications are rendered and sent out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52209 | WordPress WPForms User Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Authenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52209</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in WPForms, LLC. WPForms User Registration allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects WPForms User Registration: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32863 | exacqVison - CSRF issues with Web Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32863</link><description>Under certain circumstances the exacqVision Web Services may be susceptible to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38746 | WordPress MakeStories (for Google Web Stories) plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Arbitrary File Download and SSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38746</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in MakeStories Team MakeStories (for Google Web Stories) allows Path Traversal, Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects MakeStories (for Google Web Stories): from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38768 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin  &amp;lt;= 2.0.8.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38768</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor addons allows PHP Local File Inclusion, Path Traversal.This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.0.8.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7367 | SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System ajax.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7367</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Simple Realtime Quiz System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=save_user. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273351.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38770 | WordPress Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule plugin &amp;lt;= 1.22.20 - Authentication Bypass and Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38770</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Revmakx Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule allows Privilege Escalation, Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule: from n/a through 1.22.20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38772 | WordPress JetWidgets for Elementor and WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Contributor+ Limited Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38772</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetWidgets for Elementor and WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects JetWidgets for Elementor and WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38775 | WordPress CTX Feed plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.6 - Arbitrary Options Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38775</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in WebAppick CTX Feed allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects CTX Feed: from n/a through 6.5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38791 | WordPress AI ENGINE plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38791</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Jordy Meow AI Engine: ChatGPT Chatbot allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects AI Engine: ChatGPT Chatbot: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39619 | WordPress ListingPro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39619</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39621 | WordPress ListingPro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39621</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39624 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39624</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39630 | WordPress Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.13 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39630</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MotoPress Timetable and Event Schedule allows Object Injection.This issue affects Timetable and Event Schedule: from n/a through 2.4.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39633 | WordPress PowerPack for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.33.0 - Contributor+ Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39633</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in IdeaBox PowerPack for Beaver Builder allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects PowerPack for Beaver Builder: from n/a through 2.33.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39634 | WordPress PowerPack Pro for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.14 - Contributor+ Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39634</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in IdeaBox PowerPack Pro for Elementor allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects PowerPack Pro for Elementor: from n/a through 2.10.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41259 | Use of insecure hashing algorithm in the Gravatar's service in Navidrome v0.52.3 allows attackers to manipulate a user's account information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41259</link><description>Use of insecure hashing algorithm in the Gravatar's service in Navidrome v0.52.3 allows attackers to manipulate a user's account information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7366 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System Login ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=login of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273345 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7365 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_establishment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_establishment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273344.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7364 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_records.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7364</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_records.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273343.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7363 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_person.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7363</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_person.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273342 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7362 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7362</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273341 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4353 | Concrete CMS version 9 Generate Dashboard Name input Field Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4353</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 through 9.3.2 are affected by a stored XSS vulnerability in the generate dashboard board
instance functionality. The Name input field does not check the input sufficiently letting a rogue administrator hav the capability to inject malicious
JavaScript code. The Concrete CMS security team gave this vulnerability a CVSS v3.1 score of 3.1 with a vector of  AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator  and a CVSS v4 score of 1.8 with a vector of CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N Thanks fhAnso for reporting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6990 | Uninitialized Use in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6990</link><description>Uninitialized Use in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7255 | Out of bounds read in WebTransport in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7255</link><description>Out of bounds read in WebTransport in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7256 | Insufficient data validation in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7256</link><description>Insufficient data validation in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7361 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7361</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=save_establishment. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273340.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7360 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System ajax.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7360</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273339.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23600 | PingIDM OpenIDM Query Filter Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23600</link><description>Improper Input Validation of query search results for private field data in PingIDM OPENIDM (Query Filter module) allows for a potentially efficient brute forcing approach leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7211 | Vulnerable Identity Server on 1E Platform may permit URL redirections to untrusted sites.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7211</link><description>The Identity Server used by 1E Platform could enable URL redirection to untrusted sites. 

Note: The Identity Server on 1E Platform has been updated with the necessary patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41962 | Bostr Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41962</link><description>Bostr is an nostr relay aggregator proxy that acts like a regular nostr relay. bostr let everyone in even having authorized_keys being set when noscraper is set to true. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7359 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7359</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_establishment. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273338 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41265 | A TLS certificate verification issue discovered in cortex v0.42.1 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the makeOperatorReque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41265</link><description>A TLS certificate verification issue discovered in cortex v0.42.1 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the makeOperatorRequest function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6873 | Specially crafted request could caused undefined behaviour which may lead to Remote Code Execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6873</link><description>It is possible to crash or redirect the execution flow of the ClickHouse server process from an unauthenticated vector by sending a specially crafted request to the ClickHouse server native interface. This redirection is limited to what is available within a 256-byte range of memory at the time of execution, and no known remote code execution (RCE) code has been produced or exploited.

 Fixes have been merged to all currently supported version of ClickHouse. If you are maintaining your own forked version of ClickHouse or using an older version and cannot upgrade, the fix for this vulnerability can be found in this commit  https://github.com/ClickHouse/ClickHouse/pull/64024 .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41264 | An issue discovered in casdoor v1.636.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41264</link><description>An issue discovered in casdoor v1.636.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() method.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6040 | Missing client_id in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6040</link><description>In parisneo/lollms-webui version v9.8, the lollms_binding_infos is missing the client_id parameter, which leads to multiple security vulnerabilities. Specifically, the endpoints /reload_binding, /install_binding, /reinstall_binding, /unInstall_binding, /set_active_binding_settings, and /update_binding_settings are susceptible to CSRF attacks and local attacks. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform unauthorized actions on the victim's machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41260 | A static initialization vector (IV) in the encrypt function of netbird v0.28.4 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41260</link><description>A static initialization vector (IV) in the encrypt function of netbird v0.28.4 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6242 | Rockwell Automation Chassis Restrictions Bypass Vulnerability in Select Logix Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6242</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation affected products that allows a threat actor to bypass the Trusted® Slot feature in a ControlLogix® controller. If exploited on any affected module in a 1756 chassis, a threat actor could potentially execute CIP commands that modify user projects and/or device configuration on a Logix controller in the chassis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41961 | Elektra vulnerable to remote code execution in universal search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41961</link><description>Elektra is an opinionated Openstack Dashboard for Operators and Consumers of Openstack Services. A code injection vulnerability was found in the live search functionality of the Ruby on Rails based Elektra web application. An authenticated user can craft a search term containing Ruby code, which later flows into an `eval` sink which executes the code. Fixed in commit 8bce00be93b95a6512ff68fe86bf9554e486bc02.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29977 | Malicious remote can create arbitrary reactions on arbitrary posts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29977</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6 fail to properly validate synced reactions, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to create arbitrary reactions on arbitrary posts</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36492 | Existing local user overwritten by malicious remote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36492</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow the modification of local users when syncing users in shared channels. which allows a malicious remote to overwrite an existing local user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39274 | Malicious remote can add users to arbitrary teams and channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39274</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5 and 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to properly validate that the channel that comes from the sync message is a shared channel, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to add users to arbitrary teams and channels</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39777 | Malicious remote can invite itself to an arbitrary local channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39777</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5 and 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow unsolicited invites to expose access to local channels, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to send an invite with the ID of an existing local channel, and that local channel will then become shared without the consent of the local admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39832 | Permanently local data deletion by malicious remote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39832</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to properly safeguard an error handling which allows a malicious remote to permanently delete local data by abusing dangerous error handling, when share channels were enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39837 | Malicious remote can create arbitrary channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39837</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6 fail to properly restrict channel creation which allows a malicious remote to create arbitrary channels, when shared channels were enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39839 | Remote username set to an arbitrary string by remote user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39839</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow users to set their own remote username, when shared channels were enabled, which allows a user on a remote to set their remote username prop to an arbitrary string, which would be then synced to the local server as long as the user hadn't been synced before.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41123 | REXML DoS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41123</link><description>REXML is an XML toolkit for Ruby. The REXML gem before 3.3.2 has some DoS vulnerabilities when it parses an XML that has many specific characters such as whitespace character, `&gt;]` and `]&gt;`. The REXML gem 3.3.3 or later include the patches to fix these vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41144 | Malicious remote can create/update/delete arbitrary posts in arbitrary channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41144</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to properly validate synced posts, when shared channels are enabled,  which allows a malicious remote to create/update/delete arbitrary posts in arbitrary channels</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41162 | Malicious remote can make an arbitrary local channel read-only</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41162</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5 and 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow the modification of local channels by a remote, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to make an arbitrary local channel read-only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41926 | Malicious remote can claim that a user was synced from another remote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41926</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6 fail to validate the source of sync messages and only allow the correct remote IDs, which allows a malicious remote to set arbitrary RemoteId values for synced users and therefore claim that a user was synced from another remote.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41946 | REXML DoS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41946</link><description>REXML is an XML toolkit for Ruby. The REXML gem 3.3.2 has a DoS vulnerability when it parses an XML that has many entity expansions with SAX2 or pull parser API. The REXML gem 3.3.3 or later include the patch to fix the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6923 | Email header injection due to unquoted newlines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6923</link><description>There is a MEDIUM severity vulnerability affecting CPython.

The 
email module didn’t properly quote newlines for email headers when 
serializing an email message allowing for header injection when an email
 is serialized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7358 | Point B Ltd Getscreen Agent Installation getscreen.msi temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7358</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Point B Ltd Getscreen Agent 2.19.6 on Windows. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file getscreen.msi of the component Installation. The manipulation leads to creation of temporary file with insecure permissions. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273337 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but was not able to provide a technical response in time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7357 | D-Link DIR-600 soap.cgi soapcgi_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7357</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600 up to 2.18. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function soapcgi_main of the file /soap.cgi. The manipulation of the argument service leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273329 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2455 | Element Pack - Addon for Elementor Page Builder WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.9.0 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Wrapper Link URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2455</link><description>The Element Pack - Addon for Elementor Page Builder WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the widget wrapper link URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6346 | Post Grid, Form Maker, Popup Maker, WooCommerce Blocks, Post Blocks, Post Carousel – Combo Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.85a - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via redirectURL Parameter of Date Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6346</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the redirectURL parameter of the Date Countdown widget, in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.85a due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28972 | Dell InsightIQ, Verion 5.0.0, contains a use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28972</link><description>Dell InsightIQ, Verion 5.0.0, contains a use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38481 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38481</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25948 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25948</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38489 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior contains Out of bound write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38489</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior contains Out of bound write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service (partial) event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38490 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38490</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25947 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain an Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25947</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain an Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5678 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5678</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 170900 and below are vulnerable to the authenticated admin-only SQL Injection in the Create Monitor feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5330 | Breakdance &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5330</link><description>The Breakdance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the breakdance_css_file_paths_cache parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5331 | Breakdance &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5331</link><description>The Breakdance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to export form submissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7302 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 7.5.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7302</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 3gp2 file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 7.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the 3gp2 file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1747 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 30.2 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1747</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 30.2 does not have authorisation and CSRF in various AJAX actions, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber, to call them and update/delete/create customer metadata, also leading to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to the lack of escaping of said metadata values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2843 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 30.1 - User Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2843</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 30.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin users delete users via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2872 | Swift Framework &amp;lt; 2024.04.30 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2872</link><description>The socialdriver-framework WordPress plugin before 2024.04.30 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3983 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 30.1 - Bulk Action via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3983</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 30.1 does not have CSRF checks in some bulk actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins perform unwanted actions, such as deleting customers via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4090 | My Sticky Bar &amp;lt; 2.7.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4090</link><description>The Floating Notification Bar, Sticky Menu on Scroll, Announcement Banner, and Sticky Header for Any   WordPress plugin before 2.7.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6496 | Light Poll &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Polls Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6496</link><description>The Light Poll WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks when deleting polls, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6529 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt; 1.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6529</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings WordPress plugin before 1.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7343 | Baidu UEditor cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7343</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baidu UEditor 1.4.2. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ueditor142/php/controller.php?action=catchimage. The manipulation of the argument source[] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 05:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2090 | Remote Content Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2090</link><description>The Remote Content Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 via the remote_content shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7342 | Baidu UEditor unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7342</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baidu UEditor 1.4.3.3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /ueditor/php/controller.php?action=uploadfile&amp;amp;encode=utf-8. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273273 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7339 | TVT DVR TD-2104TS-CL queryDevInfo information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7339</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TVT DVR TD-2104TS-CL, DVR TD-2108TS-HP, Provision-ISR DVR SH-4050A5-5L(MM) and AVISION DVR AV108T and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /queryDevInfo. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273262 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1715 | AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp;amp; Ads.txt &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Ad Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1715</link><description>The AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp; Ads.txt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the adfoxly_ad_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable and disable ads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6698 | FundEngine – Donation and Crowdfunding Platform &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6698</link><description>The FundEngine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying user meta updated through the update_user_meta function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta which can be leveraged to update their capabilities to gain administrator access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7338 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7338</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. This affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7337 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7336 | TOTOLINK EX200 cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7336</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected by this vulnerability is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6687 | CTT Expresso para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Information Exposure via Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6687</link><description>The CTT Expresso para WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information exposure in all versions up to and including 3.2.12 via the /wp-content/uploads/cepw directory. The generated .pdf and log files are publicly accessible and contain sensitive information such as sender and receiver names, phone numbers, physical addresses, and email addresses</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7335 | TOTOLINK EX200 getSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34021 | Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted file may be uploade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34021</link><description>Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted file may be uploaded to the affected product by a logged-in user with an administrative privilege, resulting in an arbitrary OS command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39607 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted request may be sent to the affected product by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39607</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted request may be sent to the affected product by a logged-in user with an administrative privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40883 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. Viewing a malicious page while logging in to the affected pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40883</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. Viewing a malicious page while logging in to the affected product with an administrative privilege, the user may be directed to perform unintended operations such as changing the login ID, login password, etc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7333 | TOTOLINK N350RT cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7333</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7334 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7334</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7332 | TOTOLINK CP450 Telnet Service product.ini hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7331 | TOTOLINK A3300R cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7330 | YouDianCMS ydLib.php curl_exec server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7330</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in YouDianCMS 7 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function curl_exec of the file /App/Core/Extend/Function/ydLib.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273253 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38182 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38182</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7329 | YouDianCMS image_upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7329</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in YouDianCMS 7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Public/ckeditor/plugins/multiimage/dialogs/image_upload.php. The manipulation of the argument files leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273252. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7328 | YouDianCMS information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7328</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in YouDianCMS 7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /t.php?action=phpinfo. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273251. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7327 | Xinhu RockOA openmodhetongAction.php dataAction sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7327</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Xinhu RockOA 2.6.2. This vulnerability affects the function dataAction of the file /webmain/task/openapi/openmodhetongAction.php. The manipulation of the argument nickName leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273250 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41262 | mmudb v1.9.3 was discovered to use the HTTP protocol in the ShowMetricsRaw and ShowMetricsAsText functions, possibly allowing attackers to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41262</link><description>mmudb v1.9.3 was discovered to use the HTTP protocol in the ShowMetricsRaw and ShowMetricsAsText functions, possibly allowing attackers to intercept communications via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 21:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41258 | An issue was discovered in filestash v0.4. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowing at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41258</link><description>An issue was discovered in filestash v0.4. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowing attackers to obtain sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 21:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41256 | Default configurations in the ShareProofVerifier function of filestash v0.4 causes the application to skip the TLS certificate verification ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41256</link><description>Default configurations in the ShareProofVerifier function of filestash v0.4 causes the application to skip the TLS certificate verification process when sending out email verification codes, possibly allowing attackers to access sensitive data via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41254 | An issue was discovered in litestream v0.3.13. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41254</link><description>An issue was discovered in litestream v0.3.13. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowing attackers to obtain sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-3772 | A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager versions prior to 2.6.40.3154 that could allow an attacker to cause a system reboot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3772</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager versions prior to 2.6.40.3154 that could allow an attacker to cause a system reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6197 | A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6197</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6198 | A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6198</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4001 | An authentication bypass vulnerability could allow an attacker to access API functions without authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4001</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability could allow an attacker to access API functions without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4002 | A command injection vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to execute operating system commands as root via a specially crafted API...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4002</link><description>A command injection vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to execute operating system commands as root via a specially crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4003 | A denial-of-service vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to trigger an internal service restart via a specially crafted API reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4003</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to trigger an internal service restart via a specially crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1577 | A path hijacking vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Driver Manager prior to version 3.1.1307.1308 that could allow a local user to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1577</link><description>A path hijacking vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Driver Manager prior to version 3.1.1307.1308 that could allow a local user to execute code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41255 | filestash v0.4 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification when using the FTPS protocol, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41255</link><description>filestash v0.4 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification when using the FTPS protocol, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via the Init function of index.go.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7326 | IObit DualSafe Password Manager BPL RTL120.BPL uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7326</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in IObit DualSafe Password Manager 1.4.0.3. This affects an unknown part in the library RTL120.BPL of the component BPL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The identifier VDB-273249 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41253 | goframe v2.7.2 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41253</link><description>goframe v2.7.2 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via the gclient component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4187 | Stored XSS vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Filr. The vulnerability could cause users to not be warned when clicking links to external sites.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4187</link><description>Stored XSS vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Filr product, affecting versions 24.1.1 and 24.2. The vulnerability could cause users to not be warned when clicking links to external sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40464 | An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sendMail function located in beego/core/logs/sm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40464</link><description>An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sendMail function located in beego/core/logs/smtp.go file</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40465 | An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the getCacheFileName function in file.go file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40465</link><description>An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the getCacheFileName function in file.go file</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41660 | slpd-lite unauthenticated memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41660</link><description>slpd-lite is a unicast SLP UDP server. Any OpenBMC system that includes the slpd-lite package is impacted. Installing this package is the default when building OpenBMC. Nefarious users can send slp packets to the BMC using UDP port 427 to cause memory overflow issues within the slpd-lite daemon on the BMC. Patches will be available in the latest openbmc/slpd-lite repository.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7325 | IObit Driver Booster BPL VCL120.BPL uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7325</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Driver Booster 11.0.0.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality in the library VCL120.BPL of the component BPL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Attacking locally is a requirement. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273248. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41951 | PheonixAppAPI has visible Encoding Maps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41951</link><description>Pheonix App is a Python application designed to streamline various tasks, from managing files to playing mini-games. The issue is that the map of encoding/decoding languages are visible in code. The Problem was patched in 0.2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41954 | FOG Weak file permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41954</link><description>FOG is a cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. The application stores plaintext service account credentials in the "/opt/fog/.fogsettings" file. This file is by default readable by all users on the host. By exploiting these credentials, a malicious user could create new accounts for the web application and much more. The vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.10.41.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41955 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) has an Open Redirect in Login Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41955</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is a security research platform for mobile applications in Android, iOS and Windows Mobile. An open redirect vulnerability exist in MobSF authentication view. Update to MobSF v4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41108 | FOG Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41108</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. The hostinfo page has missing/improper access control since only the host's mac address is required to obtain the configuration information. This data can only be retrieved if a task is pending on that host. Otherwise, an error message containing "Invalid tasking!" will be returned. The domainpassword in the hostinfo dump is hidden even to authenticated users, as it is displayed as a row of asterisks when navigating to the host's Active Directory settings.  This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.10.41.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40645 | FOG Authenticated File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40645</link><description>FOG is a cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. An improperly restricted file upload feature allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary code on the fogproject server. The Rebranding feature has a check on the client banner image requiring it to be 650 pixels wide and 120 pixels high. Apart from that, there are no checks on things like file extensions. This can be abused by appending a PHP webshell to the end of the image and changing the extension to anything the PHP web server will parse. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.10.41.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41630 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC18 V15.03.3.10_EN allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ssid param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41630</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC18 V15.03.3.10_EN allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ssid parameter at ip/goform/fast_setting_wifi_set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28149 | An issue was discovered in the IhisiServiceSmm module in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.2 before 05.28.42, 5.3 before 05.37.42, 5.4 before 0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28149</link><description>An issue was discovered in the IhisiServiceSmm module in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.2 before 05.28.42, 5.3 before 05.37.42, 5.4 before 05.45.39, 5.5 before 05.53.39, and 5.6 before 05.60.39 that could allow an attacker to modify UEFI variables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23444 | Elasticsearch elasticsearch-certutil csr fails to encrypt private key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23444</link><description>It was discovered by Elastic engineering that when elasticsearch-certutil CLI tool is used with the csr option in order to create a new Certificate Signing Requests, the associated private key that is generated is stored on disk unencrypted even if the --pass parameter is passed in the command invocation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7324 | IObit iTop Data Recovery Pro BPL madbasic_.bpl uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7324</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit iTop Data Recovery Pro 4.4.0.687. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library madbasic_.bpl of the component BPL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Local access is required to approach this attack. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273247. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6973 | Remote Code Execution in Cato Windows SDP client via crafted URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6973</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Windows SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6974 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Local Privilege Escalation via self-upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6974</link><description>Untrusted Search Path, Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6975 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Local Privilege Escalation via openssl configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6975</link><description>Untrusted Search Path vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6977 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Sensitive data in trace logs can lead to account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6977</link><description>A vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows the insertion of sensitive information into the log file, which can lead to an account takeover. However, the attack requires bypassing protections on modifying the tunnel token on a the attacker's system.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6978 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Local root certificates can be installed by low-privileged users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6978</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows Command Injection.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.28.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41953 | Zitadel improperly sanitizes HTML in emails and Console UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41953</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management system. ZITADEL uses HTML for emails and renders certain information such as usernames dynamically. That information can be entered by users or administrators. Due to a missing output sanitization, these emails could include malicious code. This may potentially lead to a threat where an attacker, without privileges, could send out altered notifications that are part of the registration processes. An attacker could create a malicious link, where the injected code would be rendered as part of the email. On the user's detail page, the username was also not sanitized and would also render HTML, giving an attacker the same vulnerability. While it was possible to inject HTML including javascript, the execution of such scripts would be prevented by most email clients and the Content Security Policy in Console UI. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.58.1, 2.57.1, 2.56.2, 2.55.5, 2.54.8 2.53.9, and 2.52.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41952 | Zitadel has an &amp;quot;Ignoring unknown usernames&amp;quot; vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41952</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management system. ZITADEL administrators can enable a setting called "Ignoring unknown usernames" which helps mitigate attacks that try to guess/enumerate usernames. If enabled, ZITADEL will show the password prompt even if the user doesn't exist and report "Username or Password invalid". Due to a implementation change to prevent deadlocks calling the database, the flag would not be correctly respected in all cases and an attacker would gain information if an account exist within ZITADEL, since the error message shows "object not found" instead of the generic error message. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.58.1, 2.57.1, 2.56.2, 2.55.5, 2.54.8, and 2.53.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41950 | Insecure Jinja2 templates rendered in Haystack Components can lead to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41950</link><description>Haystack is an end-to-end LLM framework that allows you to build applications powered by LLMs, Transformer models, vector search and more. Haystack clients that let their users create and run Pipelines from scratch are vulnerable to remote code executions. Certain Components in Haystack use Jinja2 templates, if anyone can create and render that template on the client machine they run any code. The vulnerability has been fixed with Haystack `2.3.1`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39694 | Duende IdentityServer Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39694</link><description>Duende IdentityServer is an OpenID Connect and OAuth 2.x framework for ASP.NET Core. It is possible for an attacker to craft malicious Urls that certain functions in IdentityServer will incorrectly treat as local and trusted. If such a Url is returned as a redirect, some browsers will follow it to a third-party, untrusted site. Note: by itself, this vulnerability does **not** allow an attacker to obtain user credentials, authorization codes, access tokens, refresh tokens, or identity tokens. An attacker could however exploit this vulnerability as part of a phishing attack designed to steal user credentials. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.6, 6.3.10, 6.2.5, 6.1.8, and 6.0.5. Duende.IdentityServer 5.1 and earlier and all versions of IdentityServer4 are no longer supported and will not be receiving updates. If upgrading is not possible, use `IUrlHelper.IsLocalUrl` from ASP.NET Core to validate return Urls in user interface code in the IdentityServer host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39318 | Ibexa Admin UI vulnerable to DOM-based Cross-site Scripting in file upload widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39318</link><description>The Ibexa Admin UI Bundle contains all the necessary parts to run the Ibexa DXP Back Office interface. The file upload widget is vulnerable to XSS payloads in filenames. Access permission to upload files is required. As such, in most cases only authenticated editors and administrators will have the required permission. It is not persistent, i.e. the payload is only executed during the upload. In effect, an attacker will have to trick an editor/administrator into uploading a strangely named file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41947 | XWiki Platform XSS through conflict resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41947</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. By creating a conflict when another user with more rights is currently editing a page, it is possible to execute JavaScript snippets on the side of the other user, which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.10.8 and 16.3.0RC1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37898 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to document deletion and overwrite from edit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37898</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When a user has view but not edit right on a page in XWiki, that user can delete the page and replace it by a page with new content without having delete right. The previous version of the page is moved into the recycle bin and can be restored from there by an admin. As the user is recorded as deleter, the user would in theory also be able to view the deleted content, but this is not directly possible as rights of the previous version are transferred to the new page and thus the user still doesn't have view right on the page. It therefore doesn't seem to be possible to exploit this to gain any rights. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.6 by cancelling save operations by users when a new document shall be saved despite the document's existing already.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37900 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting through attachment filename in uploader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37900</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When uploading an attachment with a malicious filename, malicious JavaScript code could be executed. This requires a social engineering attack to get the victim into uploading a file with a malicious name. The malicious code is solely executed during the upload and affects only the user uploading the attachment. While this allows performing actions in the name of that user, it seems unlikely that a user wouldn't notice the malicious filename while uploading the attachment. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37901 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to remote code execution from account via SearchSuggestConfigSheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37901</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any user with edit right on any page can perform arbitrary remote code execution by adding instances of `XWiki.SearchSuggestConfig` and `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7340 | W&amp;amp;B Weave server remote arbitrary file leak and privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7340</link><description>The Weave server API allows remote users to fetch files from a specific directory, but due to a lack of input validation, it is possible to traverse and leak arbitrary files remotely. In various common scenarios, this allows a low-privileged user to assume the role of the server admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37135 | DM5500 5.16.0.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A local attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37135</link><description>DM5500 5.16.0.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A local attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31199 | A “CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')” allows malicious users to permanently injec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31199</link><description>A “CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')” allows malicious users to permanently inject arbitrary Javascript code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31200 | A “CWE-201: Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31200</link><description>A “CWE-201: Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access to the machine to retrieve the password in cleartext when an administrative session is open in the browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31201 | A “CWE-428: Unquoted Search Path or Element” affects the ThermoscanIP_Scrutation service. Such misconfiguration could be abused in scenarios...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31201</link><description>A “CWE-428: Unquoted Search Path or Element” affects the ThermoscanIP_Scrutation service. Such misconfiguration could be abused in scenarios where incorrect permissions were assigned to the C:\ path to attempt a privilege escalation on the local machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31202 | A “CWE-732: Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource” in the ThermoscanIP installation folder allows a local attacker to perfor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31202</link><description>A “CWE-732: Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource” in the ThermoscanIP installation folder allows a local attacker to perform a Local Privilege Escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31203 | A “CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow” in the wd210std.dll dynamic library packaged with the ThermoscanIP installer allows a local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31203</link><description>A “CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow” in the wd210std.dll dynamic library packaged with the ThermoscanIP installer allows a local attacker to possibly trigger a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition on the target component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3082 | A “CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access to the machine to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3082</link><description>A “CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access to the machine to retrieve the password in cleartext.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3083 | A “CWE-352: Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)” can be exploited by remote attackers to perform state-changing operations with administrative...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3083</link><description>A “CWE-352: Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)” can be exploited by remote attackers to perform state-changing operations with administrative privileges by luring authenticated victims into visiting a malicious web page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39379 | T5 Acrobat Vulnerability - JP2KTile::ReadHdrAndInit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39379</link><description>Acrobat for Edge versions 126.0.2592.81 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read access. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to read contents from a location in memory past the buffer boundary, potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6208 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.2.97 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6208</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpdm_all_packages' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.97 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'cols' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7321 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System User Registration signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7321</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file signup.php of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument user leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273232.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7320 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System Admin Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7320</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/index.php of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273231.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6725 | Formidable Forms &amp;lt;= 6.11.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6725</link><description>The Formidable Forms – Contact Form Plugin, Survey, Quiz, Payment, Calculator Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘html’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with form editing permissions and Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7135 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 0.21.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7135</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.21.7. The function is also vulnerable to directory traversal. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7311 | code-projects Online Bus Reservation Site register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7311</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Bus Reservation Site 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file register.php. The manipulation of the argument Email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273203.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7310 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7310</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file sort_user.php. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273202 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7309 | SourceCodester Record Management System entry.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7309</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file entry.php. The manipulation of the argument school leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273201 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7308 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System view_bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7308</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view_bill.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273200.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37129 | Dell Inventory Collector, versions prior to 12.3.0.6 contains a Path Traversal vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user could pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37129</link><description>Dell Inventory Collector, versions prior to 12.3.0.6 contains a Path Traversal vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32857 | Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability.  An attacker could potentially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32857</link><description>Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability.  An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability through preloading malicious DLL or symbolic link exploitation, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2508 | WP Mobile Menu &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.4 - Missing Authorization to _mobmenu_icon Post Meta Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2508</link><description>The WP Mobile Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_menu_item_icon function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.4.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add the '_mobmenu_icon' post meta to arbitrary posts with an arbitrary (but sanitized) value. NOTE: Version 2.8.4.4 contains a partial fix for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37127 | Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37127</link><description>Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability through preloading malicious DLL or symbolic link exploitation, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7307 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_billing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7307</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_billing.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273199.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37142 | Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37142</link><description>Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability through preloading malicious DLL or symbolic link exploitation, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7264 | ASN.1 date parser overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7264</link><description>libcurl's ASN1 parser code has the `GTime2str()` function, used for parsing an
ASN.1 Generalized Time field. If given an syntactically incorrect field, the
parser might end up using -1 for the length of the *time fraction*, leading to
a `strlen()` getting performed on a pointer to a heap buffer area that is not
(purposely) null terminated.

This flaw most likely leads to a crash, but can also lead to heap contents
getting returned to the application when
[CURLINFO_CERTINFO](https://curl.se/libcurl/c/CURLINFO_CERTINFO.html) is used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28074 | Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition 4.1.5 and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions 4.0 through 4.6.1 and version 5.0 contain a buffer over...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28074</link><description>Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition 4.1.5 and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions 4.0 through 4.6.1 and version 5.0 contain a buffer over-read vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7306 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_block.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7306</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_block.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273198 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7303 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System Send Blood Request Page request.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7303</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /request.php of the component Send Blood Request Page. The manipulation of the argument Address/bloodgroup leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273185 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6980 | Verbose error handling issue in GravityZone Update Server proxy service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6980</link><description>A verbose error handling issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-5 running only on premise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7300 | Bolt CMS Showcase Creation showcases cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7300</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Bolt CMS 3.7.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /bolt/editcontent/showcases of the component Showcase Creation Handler. The manipulation of the argument textarea leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273168. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7299 | Bolt CMS Entry Preview page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7299</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Bolt CMS 3.7.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /preview/page of the component Entry Preview Handler. The manipulation of the argument body leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273167. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6165 | WANotifier &amp;lt; 2.6.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6165</link><description>The WANotifier  WordPress plugin before 2.6.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6272 | SpiderContacts &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6272</link><description>The SpiderContacts WordPress plugin through 1.1.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6408 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.57 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6408</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.57 does not sanitise and escape its Slider Title, which could allow high privilege users such as editors and above to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6412 | HTML Forms – Simple WordPress Forms Plugin &amp;lt; 1.3.34 - Bulk Delete via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6412</link><description>The HTML Forms  WordPress plugin before 1.3.34 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6695 | profile-builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.8 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6695</link><description>it's possible for an attacker to gain administrative access without having any kind of account on the targeted site and perform unauthorized actions. This is due to improper logic flow on the user registration process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7290 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_tenant.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7290</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /manage_tenant.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273159.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7205 | sharing unnecessary device-sensitive information allows Secondary user able to take over devices as primary user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7205</link><description>When the device is shared, the homepage module are before 2.19.0  in eWeLink Cloud Service allows Secondary user to take over devices as primary user via sharing unnecessary device-sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42381 | os/linux/elf.rb in Homebrew brew before 4.2.20 uses ldd to load ELF files obtained from untrusted sources, which allows attackers to achieve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42381</link><description>os/linux/elf.rb in Homebrew brew before 4.2.20 uses ldd to load ELF files obtained from untrusted sources, which allows attackers to achieve code execution via an ELF file with a custom .interp section. NOTE: this code execution would occur during an un-sandboxed binary relocation phase, which occurs before a user would expect execution of downloaded package content. (237d1e783f7ee261beaba7d3f6bde22da7148b0a was the tested vulnerable version.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7289 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7289</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273158 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6770 | Lifetime free Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress VForm &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6770</link><description>The Lifetime free Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress VForm plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7288 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7288</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_block. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273157 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7287 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7287</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273156.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7286 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System Login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7286</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273155.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39948 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39948</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39949 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39949</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39950 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39950</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities to initiate device initialization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7285 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7285</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39944 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.Attackers
can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities,
ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39944</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.Attackers
can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities,
causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39945 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.  After
obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a
carefu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39945</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.  After
obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a
carefully crafted data packet to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing
the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39946 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a carefull...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39946</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a carefully crafted data packet to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing device initialization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39947 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the ordinary user's username and password, the attacker can send a carefull...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39947</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the ordinary user's username and password, the attacker can send a carefully crafted data packet to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7284 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7284</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument about leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273153 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7283 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7283</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273152.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7282 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System manage_model.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7282</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage_model.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273151.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7281 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7281</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php?page=manage_lot. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273150 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 01:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7280 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System view_reserved.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7280</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/view_reserved.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273149 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7279 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7279</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273148.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6255 | Arbitrary File Deletion via Directory Traversal in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6255</link><description>A vulnerability in the JSON file handling of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240410 allows any user to delete any JSON file on the server, including critical configuration files such as `config.json` and `ds_config_chatbot.json`. This issue arises due to improper validation of file paths, enabling directory traversal attacks. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to disrupt the functioning of the system, manipulate settings, or potentially cause data loss or corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7278 | itsourcecode Alton Management System team_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7278</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/team_save.php. The manipulation of the argument team leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273147.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>