<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-13137 | wangl1989 mysiteforme SiteController RestResponse cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13137</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangl1989 mysiteforme 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function RestResponse of the file src/main/java/com/mysiteforme/admin/controller/system/SiteController. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13136 | wangl1989 mysiteforme ShiroConfig.java rememberMeManager deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13136</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangl1989 mysiteforme 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function rememberMeManager of the file src/main/java/com/mysiteforme/admin/config/ShiroConfig.java. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 09:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13135 | Emlog Pro Subpage twitter.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13135</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Emlog Pro 2.4.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/twitter.php of the component Subpage Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 08:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13134 | ZeroWdd studentmanager TeacherController. java editTeacher unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13134</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ZeroWdd studentmanager 1.0. Affected is the function addTeacher/editTeacher of the file src/main/Java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/TeacherController. java. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 08:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0219 | Trimble SPS851 Receiver Status Identity Tab cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0219</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Trimble SPS851 488.01. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Receiver Status Identity Tab. The manipulation of the argument System Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 05:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13133 | ZeroWdd studentmanager StudentController. java editStudent unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13133</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ZeroWdd studentmanager 1.0. This issue affects the function addStudent/editStudent of the file src/main/Java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/StudentController. java. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13132 | Emlog Pro Subpage article.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13132</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/article.php of the component Subpage Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 04:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13131 | Dahua IPC-HFW1200S Web Interface webCapsConfig information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13131</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Dahua IPC-HFW1200S, IPC-HFW2300R-Z, IPC-HFW5220E-Z and IPC-HDW1200S up to 20241222. This affects an unknown part of the file /web_caps/webCapsConfig of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 03:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13130 | Dahua IPC-HFW1200S Web Interface Sha1Account1 path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13130</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dahua IPC-HFW1200S, IPC-HFW2300R-Z, IPC-HFW5220E-Z and IPC-HDW1200S up to 20241222. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ../mtd/Config/Sha1Account1 of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 01:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0214 | TMD Custom Header Menu index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0214</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TMD Custom Header Menu 4.0.0.1 on OpenCart. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument headermenu_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0213 | Campcodes Project Management System update_forms.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0213</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Project Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forms/update_forms.php?action=change_pic2&amp;amp;id=4. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 16:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0212 | Campcodes Student Grading System view_students.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0212</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Student Grading System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /view_students.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0211 | Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41763 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41763</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3  uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41765 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41765</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41766 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41766</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3  could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service using a complex regular expression.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41767 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41767</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify, or delete information in the back-end database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41768 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing unhandled SLL exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41768</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to cause an unhandled SSL exception which could leave the connection in an unexpected or insecure state.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0210 | Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0210</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10957 | UpdraftPlus: WP Backup &amp;amp; Migration Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.24.11 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10957</link><description>The UpdraftPlus: WP Backup &amp; Migration Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.24.11 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'recursive_unserialized_replace' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must perform a search and replace action to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 13:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0208 | code-projects Online Shoe Store summary.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0208</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /summary.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0207 | code-projects Online Shoe Store login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0207</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /function/login.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0206 | code-projects Online Shoe Store index.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0206</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12195 | WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts &amp;lt;= 2.6.16 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12195</link><description>The WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'project_id' parameter of the /wp-json/pm/v2/projects/2/task-lists REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, who have been granted access to a project, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 11:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12279 | WP Social AutoConnect &amp;lt;= 4.6.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12279</link><description>The WP Social AutoConnect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12475 | WP Multi Store Locator &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12475</link><description>The WP Multi Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12221 | Turnkey bbPress by WeaverTheme &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via _wpnonce Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12221</link><description>The Turnkey bbPress by WeaverTheme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_wpnonce’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 09:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0205 | code-projects Online Shoe Store details2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0205</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /details2.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 09:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11930 | Taskbuilder – WordPress Project &amp;amp; Task Management plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wppm_tasks Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11930</link><description>The Taskbuilder – WordPress Project &amp; Task Management plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wppm_tasks shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 08:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12583 | Dynamics 365 Integration &amp;lt;= 1.3.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution and Arbitrary File Read via Twig Server-Side Template Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12583</link><description>The Dynamics 365 Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.23 via Twig Server-Side Template Injection. This is due to missing input validation and sanitization on the render function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 08:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0204 | code-projects Online Shoe Store details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0204</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10932 | Backup Migration &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via &amp;#x27;recursive_unserialize_replace&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10932</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'recursive_unserialize_replace' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must create a staging site in order to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11974 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.23 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via smc_settings_tab, unattachfixit-action, and woofixit-action Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11974</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘smc_settings_tab', 'unattachfixit-action', and 'woofixit-action’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12047 | WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp;amp; Speed Optimization &amp;lt;= 6.30.03 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via custom_server Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12047</link><description>The WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp; Speed Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_server’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.30.03 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12545 | Scratch &amp;amp; Win – Giveaways and Contests &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via reset_installation Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12545</link><description>The Scratch &amp; Win – Giveaways and Contests. Boost subscribers, traffic, repeat visits,  referrals, sales and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the reset_installation() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin’s installation via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12701 | WP Smart Import : Import any XML File to WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12701</link><description>The WP Smart Import : Import any XML File to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0203 | code-projects Student Management System DbFunction.php showSubject1 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0203</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function showSubject1 of the file /config/DbFunction.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0202 | TCS BaNCS REPORTS_SHOW_FILE.jsp file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0202</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TCS BaNCS 10. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /REPORTS/REPORTS_SHOW_FILE.jsp. The manipulation of the argument FilePath leads to file inclusion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 05:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0201 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System update_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0201</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/update_account.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 04:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0200 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System search_num.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0200</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/search_num.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22383 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity input validation issue exists in the Commerce B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22383</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity input validation issue exists in the Commerce B2B application, affecting the Contact Us functionality. This allows visitors to send e-mail messages that could contain unfiltered HTML markup in specific scenarios.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22384 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue concerning business logic exists in the C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22384</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue concerning business logic exists in the Commerce B2B application, which allows storefront visitors to purchase discontinued products in specific scenarios where requests are altered before reaching the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22385 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. For newly created accounts, the Commerce B2B application does not...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22385</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. For newly created accounts, the Commerce B2B application does not require email confirmation. This medium-severity issue allows the mass creation of accounts. This could affect database storage; also, non-requested storefront accounts can be created on behalf of visitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22386 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity session issue exists in the Commerce B2B applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22386</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity session issue exists in the Commerce B2B application, affecting the longevity of active sessions in the storefront. This allows session tokens tied to logged-out sessions to still be active and usable.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22387 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue exists in requests for resources where th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22387</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue exists in requests for resources where the session token is submitted as a URL parameter. This exposes information about the authenticated session, which can be leveraged for session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22388 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.22.0. A high-severity Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22388</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.22.0. A high-severity Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the CMS, allowing malicious actors to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code, potentially compromising user data, escalating privileges, or executing unauthorized actions. The issue exists in multiple areas, including content editing, link management, and file uploads.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22389 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS, where the applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22389</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS, where the application does not properly validate uploaded files. This allows the upload of potentially malicious file types, including .docm .html. When accessed by application users, these files can be used to execute malicious actions or compromise users' systems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22390 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS due to insufficie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22390</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS due to insufficient enforcement of password complexity requirements. The application permits users to set passwords with a minimum length of 6 characters, lacking adequate complexity to resist modern attack techniques such as password spraying or offline password cracking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55897 | IBM PowerHA SystemMirror for i information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55897</link><description>IBM PowerHA SystemMirror for i 7.4 and 7.5 

does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0199 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System minus_cart.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0199</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/minus_cart.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11733 | WordPress Popular Posts &amp;lt;= 7.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11733</link><description>The The WordPress Popular Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12237 | Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp;amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12237</link><description>The Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.15 via the rjg_get_youtube_info_justified_gallery_callback function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to retrieve limited information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55896 | IBM PowerHA SystemMirror for i clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55896</link><description>IBM PowerHA SystemMirror for i 7.4 and 7.5 contains improper restrictions when rendering content via iFrames.  This vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain improper access and perform unauthorized actions on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13129 | Roxy-WI roxy.py action_service os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Roxy-WI up to 8.1.3. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function action_service of the file app/modules/roxywi/roxy.py. The manipulation of the argument action/service leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 8.1.4 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 32313928eb9ce906887b8a30bf7b9a3d5c0de1be. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 21:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22376 | In Net::OAuth::Client in the Net::OAuth package before 0.29 for Perl, the default nonce is a 32-bit integer generated from the built-in rand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22376</link><description>In Net::OAuth::Client in the Net::OAuth package before 0.29 for Perl, the default nonce is a 32-bit integer generated from the built-in rand() function, which is not cryptographically strong.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 21:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0198 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System search_result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0198</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/search_result.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 20:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56332 | Next.js Vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) with Server Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56332</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. Starting in version 13.0.0 and prior to versions 13.5.8, 14.2.21, and 15.1.2, Next.js is vulnerable to a Denial of Service (DoS) attack that allows attackers to construct requests that leaves requests to Server Actions hanging until the hosting provider cancels the function execution. This vulnerability can also be used as a Denial of Wallet (DoW) attack when deployed in providers billing by response times. (Note: Next.js server is idle during that time and only keeps the connection open. CPU and memory footprint are low during that time.). Deployments without any protection against long running Server Action invocations are especially vulnerable. Hosting providers like Vercel or Netlify set a default maximum duration on function execution to reduce the risk of excessive billing. This is the same issue as if the incoming HTTP request has an invalid `Content-Length` header or never closes. If the host has no other mitigations to those then this vulnerability is novel. This vulnerability affects only Next.js deployments using Server Actions. The issue was resolved in Next.js 13.5.8, 14.2.21, and 15.1.2. We recommend that users upgrade to a safe version. There are no official workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 20:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0197 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0197</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/search.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0196 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System plist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0196</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/plist.php. The manipulation of the argument cat leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35365 | FFmpeg version n6.1.1 has a double-free vulnerability in the fftools/ffmpeg_mux_init.c component of FFmpeg, specifically within the new_stre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35365</link><description>FFmpeg version n6.1.1 has a double-free vulnerability in the fftools/ffmpeg_mux_init.c component of FFmpeg, specifically within the new_stream_audio function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36613 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the DXA demuxer of the libavformat library allowing for an integer overflow, potentially resulting in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36613</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the DXA demuxer of the libavformat library allowing for an integer overflow, potentially resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or other undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0195 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System del_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/del_product.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56410 | PhpSpreadsheet has Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in custom properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56410</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 have a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in custom properties. The HTML page is generated without clearing custom properties. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56411 | PhpSpreadsheet has Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability of the hyperlink base in the HTML page header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56411</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 have a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability of the hyperlink base in the HTML page header. The HTML page is formed without sanitizing the hyperlink base. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56412 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to bypass of the XSS sanitizer using the javascript protocol and special characters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56412</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to bypass of the cross-site scripting sanitizer using the javascript protocol and special characters. An attacker can use special characters, so that the library processes the javascript protocol with special characters and generates an HTML link. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56366 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to unauthorized reflected  XSS in the Accounting.php file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56366</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to unauthorized reflected cross-site scripting in the `Accounting.php` file. Using the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/Wizards/NumberFormat/Accounting.php` script, an attacker can perform a cross-site scripting attack. Versions  3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56409 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to unauthorized reflected XSS in Currency.php file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56409</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to unauthorized reflected cross-site scripting in the `Currency.php` file. Using the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/Wizards/NumberFormat/Currency.php` script, an attacker can perform a cross-site scripting attack. Versions  3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56365 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to unauthorized reflected XSS in the constructor of the Downloader class</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56365</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to unauthorized reflected cross-site scripting in the constructor of the `Downloader` class. Using the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/download.php` script, an attacker can perform a cross-site scripting attack. Versions  3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21610 | Trix allows Cross-site Scripting via `javascript:` url in a link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21610</link><description>Trix is a what-you-see-is-what-you-get rich text editor for everyday writing. Versions prior to 2.1.12 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when pasting malicious code in the link field. An attacker could trick the user to copy&amp;amp;paste a malicious `javascript:` URL as a link that would execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's session, potentially leading to unauthorized actions being performed or sensitive information being disclosed. Users should upgrade to Trix editor version 2.1.12 or later to receive a patch. In addition to upgrading, affected users can disallow browsers that don't support a Content Security Policy (CSP) as a workaround for this and other cross-site scripting vulnerabilities. Set CSP policies such as script-src 'self' to ensure that only scripts hosted on the same origin are executed, and explicitly prohibit inline scripts using script-src-elem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21609 | SiYuan has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21609</link><description>SiYuan is self-hosted, open source personal knowledge management software. SiYuan Note version 3.1.18 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability. The vulnerability exists in the `POST /api/history/getDocHistoryContent` endpoint. An attacker can craft a payload to exploit this vulnerability, resulting in the deletion of arbitrary files on the server. Commit d9887aeec1b27073bec66299a9a4181dc42969f3 fixes this vulnerability and is expected to be available in version 3.1.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56513 | Karmada PULL Mode Cluster Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56513</link><description>Karmada is a Kubernetes management system that allows users to run cloud-native applications across multiple Kubernetes clusters and clouds. Prior to version 1.12.0, the PULL mode clusters registered with the `karmadactl register` command have excessive privileges to access control plane resources. By abusing these permissions, an attacker able to authenticate as the karmada-agent to a karmada cluster would be able to obtain administrative privileges over the entire federation system including all registered member clusters. Since Karmada v1.12.0, command `karmadactl register` restricts the access permissions of pull mode member clusters to control plane resources. This way, an attacker able to authenticate as the karmada-agent cannot control other member clusters in Karmada. As a workaround, one may restrict the access permissions of pull mode member clusters to control plane resources according to Karmada Component Permissions Docs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56514 | Karmada Tar Slips in CRDs archive extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56514</link><description>Karmada is a Kubernetes management system that allows users to run cloud-native applications across multiple Kubernetes clusters and clouds. Prior to version 1.12.0, both in karmadactl and karmada-operator, it is possible to supply a filesystem path, or an HTTP(s) URL to retrieve the custom resource definitions(CRDs) needed by Karmada. The CRDs are downloaded as a gzipped tarfile and are vulnerable to a TarSlip vulnerability. An attacker able to supply a malicious CRD file into a Karmada initialization could write arbitrary files in arbitrary paths of the filesystem. From Karmada version 1.12.0, when processing custom CRDs files, CRDs archive verification is utilized to enhance file system robustness. A workaround is available. Someone who needs to set flag `--crd` to customize the CRD files required for Karmada initialization when using `karmadactl init` to set up Karmada can manually inspect the CRD files to check whether they contain sequences such as `../` that would alter file paths, to determine if they potentially include malicious files. When using karmada-operator to set up Karmada, one must upgrade one's karmada-operator to one of the fixed versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55507 | An issue in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the delete_e.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55507</link><description>An issue in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the delete_e.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56408 | Phpspreadsheet allows unauthorized Reflected XSS in `Convert-Online.php` file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56408</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 have is no sanitization in the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/Engineering/Convert-Online.php` file, which leads to the possibility of a cross-site scripting attack. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56324 | GoCD vulnerable to XXE injection via abuse of pipeline XML &amp;quot;snippet&amp;quot; editing by group admins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56324</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions prior to 24.4.0 can allow GoCD "group admins" to abuse ability to edit the raw XML configuration for groups they administer to trigger XML External Entity (XXE) injection on the GoCD server. Theoretically, the XXE vulnerability can result in additional attacks such as SSRF, information disclosure from the GoCD server, and directory traversal, although these additional attacks have not been explicitly demonstrated as exploitable. This issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. Some workarounds are available. One may temporarily block access to  `/go/*/pipelines/snippet` routes from an external reverse proxy or WAF if one's "group admin" users do not need the functionality to edit the XML of pipelines directly (rather than using the UI, or using a configuration repository). One may also prevent external access from one's GoCD server to arbitrary locations using some kind of environment egress control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56322 | GoCD vulnerable to XXE injection via abuse of unused XML configuration repository functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56322</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions 16.7.0 through 24.4.0 (inclusive) can allow GoCD admins to abuse a hidden/unused configuration repository (pipelines as code) feature to allow XML External Entity (XXE) injection on the GoCD Server which will be executed when GoCD periodically scans configuration repositories for pipeline updates, or is triggered by an administrator or config repo admin. In practice the impact of this vulnerability is limited, in most cases without combining with another vulnerability, as only GoCD (super) admins have the ability to abuse this vulnerability. Typically a malicious GoCD admin can cause much larger damage than that they can do with XXE injection. The issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. As a workaround, prevent external access from the GoCD server to arbitrary locations using some kind of environment egress control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:55:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56321 | GoCD before 24.5.0 can allow malicious GoCD admins to abuse backup configuration to gain additional host access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56321</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions 18.9.0 through 24.4.0 (inclusive) can allow GoCD admins to abuse the backup configuration "post-backup script" feature to potentially execute arbitrary scripts on the hosting server or container as GoCD's user, rather than pre-configured scripts. In practice the impact of this vulnerability is limited, as in most configurations a user who can log into the GoCD UI as an admin also has host administration permissions for the host/container that GoCD runs on, in order to manage artifact storage and other service-level configuration options. Additionally, since a GoCD admin has ability to configure and schedule pipelines tasks on all GoCD agents available to the server, the fundamental functionality of GoCD allows co-ordinated task execution similar to that of post-backup-scripts. However in restricted environments where the host administration is separated from the role of a GoCD admin, this may be unexpected. The issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. Post-backup scripts can no longer be executed from within certain sensitive locations on the GoCD server. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56320 | GoCD before 24.5.0 is vulnerable to admin privilege escalation by a malicious internal/existing authenticated user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56320</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions prior to 24.5.0 are vulnerable to admin privilege escalation due to improper authorization of access to the admin "Configuration XML" UI feature, and its associated API. A malicious insider/existing authenticated GoCD user with an existing GoCD user account could abuse this vulnerability to access information intended only for GoCD admins, or to escalate their privileges to that of a GoCD admin in a persistent manner. it is not possible for this vulnerability to be abused prior to authentication/login. The issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. GoCD users who are not able to immediate upgrade can mitigate this issue by using a reverse proxy, WAF or similar to externally block access paths with a `/go/rails/` prefix. Blocking this route causes no loss of functionality. If it is not possible to upgrade or block the above route, consider reducing the GoCD user base to more trusted set of users, including temporarily disabling use of plugins such as the guest-login-plugin, which allow limited anonymous access as a regular user account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48814 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Silverpeas 6.4.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ViewType parameter of the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48814</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Silverpeas 6.4.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ViewType parameter of the findbywhereclause function</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41780 | IBM Jazz Foundation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41780</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1.0 could 

could allow a physical user to obtain sensitive information due to not masking passwords during entry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55078 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /adminUser/updateImg of WukongCRM-11.0-JAVA v11.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55078</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /adminUser/updateImg of WukongCRM-11.0-JAVA v11.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5591 | IBM Jazz Foundation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5591</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9140 | Moxa’s cellular routers, secure routers, and network security appliances are affected by a critical vulnerability, CVE-2024-9140. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9140</link><description>Moxa’s cellular routers, secure routers, and network security appliances are affected by a critical vulnerability, CVE-2024-9140. This vulnerability allows OS command injection due to improperly restricted commands, potentially enabling attackers to execute arbitrary code. This poses a significant risk to the system’s security and functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12132 | WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12132</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.4 due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create jobs for companies that are unaffiliated with the attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9138 | Privilege Escalation in Cellular Router, Secure Router, and Network Security Appliances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9138</link><description>Moxa’s cellular routers, secure routers, and network security appliances are affected by a high-severity vulnerability, CVE-2024-9138. This vulnerability involves hard-coded credentials, enabling an authenticated user to escalate privileges and gain root-level access to the system, posing a significant security risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22275 | iTerm2 3.5.6 through 3.5.10 before 3.5.11 sometimes allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from terminal commands by readin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22275</link><description>iTerm2 3.5.6 through 3.5.10 before 3.5.11 sometimes allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from terminal commands by reading the /tmp/framer.txt file. This can occur for certain it2ssh and SSH Integration configurations, during remote logins to hosts that have a common Python installation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 05:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11624 | there is a possible to add apps to bypass VPN due to Undeclared Permission . This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11624</link><description>there is a possible to add apps to bypass VPN due to Undeclared Permission . This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47032 | In construct_transaction_from_cmd of lwis_ioctl.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47032</link><description>In construct_transaction_from_cmd of lwis_ioctl.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53833 | In prepare_response_locked of  lwis_transaction.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53833</link><description>In prepare_response_locked of  lwis_transaction.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53834 | In sms_DisplayHexDumpOfPrivacyBuffer of sms_Utilities.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53834</link><description>In sms_DisplayHexDumpOfPrivacyBuffer of sms_Utilities.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53835 | there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53835</link><description>there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53836 | In wbrc_bt_dev_write of wb_regon_coordinator.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53836</link><description>In wbrc_bt_dev_write of wb_regon_coordinator.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53837 | In prepare_response of lwis_periodic_io.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53837</link><description>In prepare_response of lwis_periodic_io.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53838 | In Exynos_parsing_user_data_registered_itu_t_t35 of VendorVideoAPI.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53838</link><description>In Exynos_parsing_user_data_registered_itu_t_t35 of VendorVideoAPI.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53839 | In GetCellInfoList() of protocolnetadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53839</link><description>In GetCellInfoList() of protocolnetadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53840 | there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53840</link><description>there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53841 | In startListeningForDeviceStateChanges, there is a possible Permission Bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53841</link><description>In startListeningForDeviceStateChanges, there is a possible Permission Bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53842 | In cc_SendCcImsInfoIndMsg of cc_MmConManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53842</link><description>In cc_SendCcImsInfoIndMsg of cc_MmConManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0176 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System add_cart.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0176</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/add_cart.php. The manipulation of the argument id/qty leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0175 | code-projects Online Shop view.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Shop 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view.php. The manipulation of the argument name/details leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0174 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System Parameter search_result2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0174</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/search_result2.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43077 | In DevmemValidateFlags of devicemem_server.c , there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43077</link><description>In DevmemValidateFlags of devicemem_server.c , there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43097 | In resizeToAtLeast of SkRegion.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43097</link><description>In resizeToAtLeast of SkRegion.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43762 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to avoid unbinding of a service from the system due to a logic error in the code. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43762</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to avoid unbinding of a service from the system due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43764 | In onPrimaryClipChanged of ClipboardListener.java, there is a possible way to partially bypass lock screen. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43764</link><description>In onPrimaryClipChanged of ClipboardListener.java, there is a possible way to partially bypass lock screen. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43767 | In prepare_to_draw_into_mask of SkBlurMaskFilterImpl.cpp, there is a possible heap overflow due to improper input validation. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43767</link><description>In prepare_to_draw_into_mask of SkBlurMaskFilterImpl.cpp, there is a possible heap overflow due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43768 | In skia_alloc_func of SkDeflate.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43768</link><description>In skia_alloc_func of SkDeflate.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43769 | In isPackageDeviceAdmin of PackageManagerService.java, there is a possible edge case which could prevent the uninstallation of CloudDpc due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43769</link><description>In isPackageDeviceAdmin of PackageManagerService.java, there is a possible edge case which could prevent the uninstallation of CloudDpc due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>