<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:57:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2022-32505 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. It is possible to send multiple BLE malformed packets to block some of the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32505</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. It is possible to send multiple BLE malformed packets to block some of the functionality and reboot the device. This affects Nuki Smart Lock 3.0 before 3.3.5 and Nuki Smart Lock 2.0 before 2.12.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32508 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. By sending a malformed HTTP verb, it is possible to force a reboot of the de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32508</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. By sending a malformed HTTP verb, it is possible to force a reboot of the device. This affects Nuki Bridge v1 before 1.22.0 and v2 before 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32503 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. An attacker with physical access to this JTAG port may be able to connect to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32503</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. An attacker with physical access to this JTAG port may be able to connect to the device and bypass both hardware and software security protections. This affects Nuki Keypad before 1.9.2 and Nuki Fob before 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32506 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. An attacker with physical access to the circuit board could use the SWD debu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32506</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. An attacker with physical access to the circuit board could use the SWD debug features to control the execution of code on the processor and debug the firmware, as well as read or alter the content of the internal and external flash memory. This affects Nuki Smart Lock 3.0 before 3.3.5, Nuki Smart Lock 2.0 before 2.12.4, as well as Nuki Bridge v1 before 1.22.0 and v2 before 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32510 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. The HTTP API exposed by a Bridge used an unencrypted channel to provide an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32510</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. The HTTP API exposed by a Bridge used an unencrypted channel to provide an administrative interface. A token can be easily eavesdropped by a malicious actor to impersonate a legitimate user and gain access to the full set of API endpoints. This affects Nuki Bridge v1 before 1.22.0 and v2 before 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32502 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. There is a buffer overflow over the encrypted token parsing logic in the HTT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32502</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. There is a buffer overflow over the encrypted token parsing logic in the HTTP service that allows remote code execution. This affects Nuki Bridge v1 before 1.22.0 and v2 before 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32507 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. Some BLE commands, which should have been designed to be only called from pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32507</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. Some BLE commands, which should have been designed to be only called from privileged accounts, could also be called from unprivileged accounts. This demonstrates that no access controls were implemented for the different BLE commands across the different accounts. This affects Nuki Smart Lock 3.0 before 3.3.5 and Nuki Smart Lock 2.0 before 2.12.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32504 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. The code used to parse the JSON objects received from the WebSocket service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32504</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. The code used to parse the JSON objects received from the WebSocket service provided by the device leads to a stack buffer overflow. An attacker would be able to exploit this to gain arbitrary code execution on a KeyTurner device. This affects Nuki Smart Lock 3.0 before 3.3.5 and 2.0 before 2.12.4, as well as Nuki Bridge v1 before 1.22.0 and v2 before 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32509 | An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. Lack of certificate validation on HTTP communications allows attackers to in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32509</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain Nuki Home Solutions devices. Lack of certificate validation on HTTP communications allows attackers to intercept and tamper data. This affects Nuki Smart Lock 3.0 before 3.3.5, Nuki Bridge v1 before 1.22.0 and Nuki Bridge v2 before 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4684 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System exam_timetable_grade_wise.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4684</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /view/exam_timetable_grade_wise.php. The manipulation of the argument exam leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263625 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22910 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CrushFTP v.10.6.0 and v.10.5.5 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22910</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CrushFTP v.10.6.0 and v.10.5.5 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34220 | Sourcecodester Human Resource Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'leave' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34220</link><description>Sourcecodester Human Resource Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'leave' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4683 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System exam_timetable_insert_form.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4683</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/exam_timetable_insert_form.php. The manipulation of the argument exam leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263624.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24157 | Gnuboard g6 / https://github.com/gnuboard/g6 commit c2cc1f5069e00491ea48618d957332d90f6d40e4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24157</link><description>Gnuboard g6 / https://github.com/gnuboard/g6 commit c2cc1f5069e00491ea48618d957332d90f6d40e4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via board.py.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4545 | EDB Postgres Advanced Server (EPAS) authenticated file read permissions bypass using edbldr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4545</link><description>All versions of EnterpriseDB Postgres Advanced Server (EPAS) from 15.0 prior to 15.7.0 and from 16.0 prior to 16.3.0 may allow users using edbldr to bypass role permissions from pg_read_server_files. This could allow low privilege users to read files to which they would not otherwise have access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29881 | phpok 6.4.003 is vulnerable to SQL injection in the function index_f() in phpok64/framework/api/call_control.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29881</link><description>phpok 6.4.003 is vulnerable to SQL injection in the function index_f() in phpok64/framework/api/call_control.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34338 | A Blind command injection vulnerability in Tenda O3V2 V1.0.0.12 and earlier allows remote attackers to execute operating system commands via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34338</link><description>A Blind command injection vulnerability in Tenda O3V2 V1.0.0.12 and earlier allows remote attackers to execute operating system commands via dest parameter in /goform/getTraceroute</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31953 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 8.0.0 on macOS. Because it is possible to tamper with the directory and executable files used du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31953</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 8.0.0 on macOS. Because it is possible to tamper with the directory and executable files used during the installation process, an attacker can escalate privileges through arbitrary code execution. (The attacker must already have user privileges, and an administrator password must be entered during the program installation stage for privilege escalation.)</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31954 | An issue was discovered in the installer in Samsung Portable SSD for T5 1.6.10 on Windows. Because it is possible to tamper with the directo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31954</link><description>An issue was discovered in the installer in Samsung Portable SSD for T5 1.6.10 on Windows. Because it is possible to tamper with the directory and DLL files used during the installation process, an attacker can escalate privileges through arbitrary code execution. (An attacker must already have user privileges)</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31952 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 8.0.0 on macOS. Because symlinks are used during the installation process, an attacker can escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31952</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 8.0.0 on macOS. Because symlinks are used during the installation process, an attacker can escalate privileges via arbitrary file permission writes. (The attacker must already have user privileges, and an administrator password must be entered during the program installation stage for privilege escalation.)</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4682 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System exam_timetable_update_form.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4682</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/exam_timetable_update_form.php. The manipulation of the argument exam leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263623.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4681 | Campcodes Legal Case Management System Setting general-setting unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4681</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Legal Case Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/general-setting of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument favicon/logo leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263622 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32616 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in H5O__dtype_encode_helper in H5Odtype.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32616</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in H5O__dtype_encode_helper in H5Odtype.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32617 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read caused by the unsafe use of strdup in H5MM_xstrdup in H5MM.c (called from...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32617</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read caused by the unsafe use of strdup in H5MM_xstrdup in H5MM.c (called from H5G__ent_to_link in H5Glink.c).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32618 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T__get_native_type in H5Tnative.c, resulting in the corruption of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32618</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T__get_native_type in H5Tnative.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32619 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T_copy_reopen in H5T.c, resulting in the corruption of the instructio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32619</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T_copy_reopen in H5T.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32620 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in H5F_addr_decode_len in H5Fint.c, resulting in the corruption of the in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32620</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in H5F_addr_decode_len in H5Fint.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32621 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5HG_read in H5HG.c (called from H5VL__native_blob_get in H5VLnative_bl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32621</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5HG_read in H5HG.c (called from H5VL__native_blob_get in H5VLnative_blob.c), resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32622 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a out-of-bounds read operation in H5FL_arr_malloc in H5FL.c (called from H5S_set_extent_simple in H5S.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32622</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a out-of-bounds read operation in H5FL_arr_malloc in H5FL.c (called from H5S_set_extent_simple in H5S.c).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32623 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5VM_array_fill in H5VM.c (called from H5S_select_elements in H5Spoint....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32623</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5VM_array_fill in H5VM.c (called from H5S_select_elements in H5Spoint.c).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32624 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T__ref_mem_setnull in H5Tref.c (called from H5T__conv_ref in H5Tconv....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32624</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T__ref_mem_setnull in H5Tref.c (called from H5T__conv_ref in H5Tconv.c), resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33873 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer overflow in H5D__scatter_mem in H5Dscatgath.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33873</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer overflow in H5D__scatter_mem in H5Dscatgath.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33874 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap buffer overflow in H5O__mtime_new_encode in H5Omtime.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33874</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap buffer overflow in H5O__mtime_new_encode in H5Omtime.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33875 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer overflow in H5O__layout_encode in H5Olayout.c, resulting in the corruption of the instru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33875</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer overflow in H5O__layout_encode in H5Olayout.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33876 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap buffer overflow in H5S__point_deserialize in H5Spoint.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33876</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap buffer overflow in H5S__point_deserialize in H5Spoint.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33877 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T__conv_struct_opt in H5Tconv.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33877</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer overflow in H5T__conv_struct_opt in H5Tconv.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52654 | io_uring/af_unix: disable sending io_uring over sockets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52654</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/af_unix: disable sending io_uring over sockets

File reference cycles have caused lots of problems for io_uring
in the past, and it still doesn't work exactly right and races with
unix_stream_read_generic(). The safest fix would be to completely
disallow sending io_uring files via sockets via SCM_RIGHT, so there
are no possible cycles invloving registered files and thus rendering
SCM accounting on the io_uring side unnecessary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27393 | xen-netfront: Add missing skb_mark_for_recycle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27393</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xen-netfront: Add missing skb_mark_for_recycle

Notice that skb_mark_for_recycle() is introduced later than fixes tag in
commit 6a5bcd84e886 ("page_pool: Allow drivers to hint on SKB recycling").

It is believed that fixes tag were missing a call to page_pool_release_page()
between v5.9 to v5.14, after which is should have used skb_mark_for_recycle().
Since v6.6 the call page_pool_release_page() were removed (in
commit 535b9c61bdef ("net: page_pool: hide page_pool_release_page()")
and remaining callers converted (in commit 6bfef2ec0172 ("Merge branch
'net-page_pool-remove-page_pool_release_page'")).

This leak became visible in v6.8 via commit dba1b8a7ab68 ("mm/page_pool: catch
page_pool memory leaks").</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27394 | tcp: Fix Use-After-Free in tcp_ao_connect_init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27394</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: Fix Use-After-Free in tcp_ao_connect_init

Since call_rcu, which is called in the hlist_for_each_entry_rcu traversal
of tcp_ao_connect_init, is not part of the RCU read critical section, it
is possible that the RCU grace period will pass during the traversal and
the key will be free.

To prevent this, it should be changed to hlist_for_each_entry_safe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27395 | net: openvswitch: Fix Use-After-Free in ovs_ct_exit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27395</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: openvswitch: Fix Use-After-Free in ovs_ct_exit

Since kfree_rcu, which is called in the hlist_for_each_entry_rcu traversal
of ovs_ct_limit_exit, is not part of the RCU read critical section, it
is possible that the RCU grace period will pass during the traversal and
the key will be free.

To prevent this, it should be changed to hlist_for_each_entry_safe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27396 | net: gtp: Fix Use-After-Free in gtp_dellink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27396</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: gtp: Fix Use-After-Free in gtp_dellink

Since call_rcu, which is called in the hlist_for_each_entry_rcu traversal
of gtp_dellink, is not part of the RCU read critical section, it
is possible that the RCU grace period will pass during the traversal and
the key will be free.

To prevent this, it should be changed to hlist_for_each_entry_safe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27397 | netfilter: nf_tables: use timestamp to check for set element timeout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27397</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: use timestamp to check for set element timeout

Add a timestamp field at the beginning of the transaction, store it
in the nftables per-netns area.

Update set backend .insert, .deactivate and sync gc path to use the
timestamp, this avoids that an element expires while control plane
transaction is still unfinished.

.lookup and .update, which are used from packet path, still use the
current time to check if the element has expired. And .get path and dump
also since this runs lockless under rcu read size lock. Then, there is
async gc which also needs to check the current time since it runs
asynchronously from a workqueue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32611 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 may use an uninitialized value in H5A__attr_release_table in H5Aint.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32611</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 may use an uninitialized value in H5A__attr_release_table in H5Aint.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32612 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in H5HL__fl_deserialize in H5HLcache.c, resulting in the corruption of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32612</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in H5HL__fl_deserialize in H5HLcache.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer, a different vulnerability than CVE-2024-32613.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32613 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in the function H5HL__fl_deserialize in H5HLcache.c, a different vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32613</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer over-read in the function H5HL__fl_deserialize in H5HLcache.c, a different vulnerability than CVE-2024-32612.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32614 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a SEGV in H5VM_memcpyvv in H5VM.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32614</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a SEGV in H5VM_memcpyvv in H5VM.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32615 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5Z__nbit_decompress_one_byte in H5Znbit.c, caused by the earlier use o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32615</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 contains a heap-based buffer overflow in H5Z__nbit_decompress_one_byte in H5Znbit.c, caused by the earlier use of an initialized pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34200 | TOTOLINK CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setIpQosRules function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34200</link><description>TOTOLINK CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setIpQosRules function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34201 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the getSaveConfig function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34201</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the getSaveConfig function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34202 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setMacFilterRules function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34202</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setMacFilterRules function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34203 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setLanguageCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34203</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setLanguageCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34209 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setIpPortFilterRules function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34209</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setIpPortFilterRules function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34213 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the SetPortForwardRules function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34213</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the SetPortForwardRules function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29161 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5A__attr_release_table, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29161</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5A__attr_release_table, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29162 | HDF5 through 1.13.3 and/or 1.14.2 contains a stack buffer overflow in H5HG_read, resulting in denial of service or potential code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29162</link><description>HDF5 through 1.13.3 and/or 1.14.2 contains a stack buffer overflow in H5HG_read, resulting in denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29163 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5T__bit_find, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29163</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5T__bit_find, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29164 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a stack buffer overflow in H5R__decode_heap, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29164</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a stack buffer overflow in H5R__decode_heap, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29165 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a buffer overflow in H5Z__filter_fletcher32, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29165</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a buffer overflow in H5Z__filter_fletcher32, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29166 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a buffer overflow in H5O__linfo_decode, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29166</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a buffer overflow in H5O__linfo_decode, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32605 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer over-read in H5VM_memcpyvv in H5VM.c (called from H5D__compact_readvv in H5Dcompact.c).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32605</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a heap-based buffer over-read in H5VM_memcpyvv in H5VM.c (called from H5D__compact_readvv in H5Dcompact.c).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32606 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 may attempt to dereference uninitialized values in h5tools_str_sprint in tools/lib/h5tools_str.c (called from h5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32606</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 may attempt to dereference uninitialized values in h5tools_str_sprint in tools/lib/h5tools_str.c (called from h5tools_dump_simple_data in tools/lib/h5tools_dump.c).</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32607 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a SEGV in H5A__close in H5Aint.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32607</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a SEGV in H5A__close in H5Aint.c, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32609 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 allows stack consumption in the function H5E_printf_stack in H5Eint.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32609</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 allows stack consumption in the function H5E_printf_stack in H5Eint.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32610 | HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a SEGV in H5T_close_real in H5T.c, resulting in a corrupted instruction pointer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32610</link><description>HDF5 Library through 1.14.3 has a SEGV in H5T_close_real in H5T.c, resulting in a corrupted instruction pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34204 | TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the setUpgradeFW function v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34204</link><description>TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the setUpgradeFW function via the FileName parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34205 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the download_firmware function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34205</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the download_firmware function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34206 | TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the setWebWlanIdx function ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34206</link><description>TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the setWebWlanIdx function via the webWlanIdx parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34207 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setStaticDhcpConfig function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34207</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setStaticDhcpConfig function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34215 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setUrlFilterRules function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34215</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the setUrlFilterRules function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34217 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the addWlProfileClientMode function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34217</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the addWlProfileClientMode function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29157 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5HG_read, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29157</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5HG_read, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29158 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a stack buffer overflow in H5FL_arr_malloc, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29158</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a stack buffer overflow in H5FL_arr_malloc, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29159 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a buffer overflow in H5Z__filter_scaleoffset, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29159</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a buffer overflow in H5Z__filter_scaleoffset, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29160 | HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5HG__cache_heap_deserialize, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29160</link><description>HDF5 through 1.14.3 contains a heap buffer overflow in H5HG__cache_heap_deserialize, resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34351 | Next.js Server-Side Request Forgery in Server Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34351</link><description>Next.js is a React framework that can provide building blocks to create web applications. A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability was identified in Next.js Server Actions. If the `Host` header is modified, and the below conditions are also met, an attacker may be able to make requests that appear to be originating from the Next.js application server itself. The required conditions are 1) Next.js is running in a self-hosted manner; 2) the Next.js application makes use of Server Actions; and 3) the Server Action performs a redirect to a relative path which starts with a `/`. This vulnerability was fixed in Next.js `14.1.1`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34350 | Next.js Vulnerable to HTTP Request Smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34350</link><description>Next.js is a React framework that can provide building blocks to create web applications. Prior to 13.5.1, an inconsistent interpretation of a crafted HTTP request meant that requests are treated as both a single request, and two separate requests by Next.js, leading to desynchronized responses. This led to a response queue poisoning vulnerability in the affected Next.js versions. For a request to be exploitable, the affected route also had to be making use of the [rewrites](https://nextjs.org/docs/app/api-reference/next-config-js/rewrites) feature in Next.js. The vulnerability is resolved in Next.js `13.5.1` and newer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33454 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in esp-idf v.5.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the Bluetooth stac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33454</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in esp-idf v.5.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the Bluetooth stack component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32736 | CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32736</link><description>A sql injection vulnerability exists in CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise prior to v2.8.3. An unauthenticated remote attacker can leak sensitive information via the "query_utask_verbose" function within MCUDBHelper.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32737 | CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32737</link><description>A sql injection vulnerability exists in CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise prior to v2.8.3. An unauthenticated remote attacker can leak sensitive information via the "query_contract_result" function within MCUDBHelper.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32738 | CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32738</link><description>A sql injection vulnerability exists in CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise prior to v2.8.3. An unauthenticated remote attacker can leak sensitive information via the "query_ptask_lean" function within MCUDBHelper.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32739 | CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32739</link><description>A sql injection vulnerability exists in CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise prior to v2.8.3. An unauthenticated remote attacker can leak sensitive information via the "query_ptask_verbose" function within MCUDBHelper.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3727 | Containers/image: digest type does not guarantee valid type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3727</link><description>A flaw was found in the github.com/containers/image library. This flaw allows attackers to trigger unexpected authenticated registry accesses on behalf of a victim user, causing resource exhaustion, local path traversal, and other attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32735 | CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32735</link><description>An issue regarding missing authentication for certain utilities exists in CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise prior to v2.8.3. An unauthenticated remote attacker can access the PDNU REST APIs, which may result in compromise of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34345 | @cyclonedx/cyclonedx-library Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34345</link><description>The CycloneDX JavaScript library contains the core functionality of OWASP CycloneDX for JavaScript. In 6.7.0, XML External entity injections were possible, when running the provided XML Validator on arbitrary input. This issue was fixed in version 6.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34354 | CMSaasStarter: JWT Token Not Verified on Server Session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34354</link><description>CMSaaSStarter is a SaaS template/boilerplate built with SvelteKit, Tailwind, and Supabase. Any forks of the CMSaaSStarter template before commit 7904d416d2c72ec75f42fbf51e9e64fa74062ee6 are impacted. The issue is the user JWT Token is not verified on server session. You should take the patch 7904d416d2c72ec75f42fbf51e9e64fa74062ee6 into your fork.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34352 | Arbitrary file write vulnerability in 1Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34352</link><description>1Panel is an open source Linux server operation and maintenance management panel. Prior to  v1.10.3-lts, there are many command injections in the project, and some of them are not well filtered, leading to arbitrary file writes, and ultimately leading to RCEs. The mirror configuration write symbol `&gt;` can be used to achieve arbitrary file writing. This vulnerability is fixed in  v1.10.3-lts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32655 | Npgsql Vulnerable to SQL Injection via Protocol Message Size Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32655</link><description>Npgsql is the .NET data provider for PostgreSQL. In 8.0.2 and earlier, The `WriteBind()` method in `src/Npgsql/Internal/NpgsqlConnector.FrontendMessages.cs` uses `int` variables to store the message length and the sum of parameter lengths. Both variables overflow when the sum of parameter lengths becomes too large. This causes Npgsql to write a message size that is too small when constructing a Postgres protocol message to send it over the network to the database. When parsing the message, the database will only read a small number of bytes and treat any following bytes as new messages while they belong to the old message. Attackers can abuse this to inject arbitrary Postgres protocol messages into the connection, leading to the execution of arbitrary SQL statements on the application's behalf.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34074 | Frappe vuilnerable to an open redirect on login page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34074</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 15.26.0 and 14.74.0, the login page accepts redirect argument and it allowed redirect to untrusted external URls. This behaviour can be used by malicious actors for phishing. This vulnerability is fixed in 15.26.0 and 14.74.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4678 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System find_friends.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/find_friends.php. The manipulation of the argument my_type leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263599.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32874 | In Frigate, Malicious Long Unicode filenames may cause a Multiple Application-level Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32874</link><description>Frigate is a network video recorder (NVR) with realtime local object detection for IP cameras. Below 0.13.2 Release, when uploading a file or retrieving the filename, a user may intentionally use a large Unicode filename which would lead to a application-level denial of service. This is due to no limitation set on the length of the filename and the costy use of the Unicode normalization with the form NFKD under the hood of `secure_filename()`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34210 | TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the CloudACMunualUpdate fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34210</link><description>TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the CloudACMunualUpdate function via the FileName parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34211 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow.sample, which allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34211</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow.sample, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34212 | TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the CloudACMunualUpdate function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34212</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in the CloudACMunualUpdate function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34219 | TOTOLINK CP450 V4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a vulnerability in the SetTelnetCfg function, which allows attackers to log ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34219</link><description>TOTOLINK CP450 V4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a vulnerability in the SetTelnetCfg function, which allows attackers to log in through telnet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31803 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in emp-ot v.0.2.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the FerretCOT&lt;T&gt;::read_pre_data128_fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31803</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in emp-ot v.0.2.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the FerretCOT::read_pre_data128_from_file function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34218 | TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the NTPSyncWithHost functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34218</link><description>TOTOLINK outdoor CPE CP450 v4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability in the NTPSyncWithHost function via the hostTime parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4677 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System my_student_exam_marks1.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4677</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/my_student_exam_marks1.php. The manipulation of the argument year leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4317 | PostgreSQL pg_stats_ext and pg_stats_ext_exprs lack authorization checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4317</link><description>Missing authorization in PostgreSQL built-in views pg_stats_ext and pg_stats_ext_exprs allows an unprivileged database user to read most common values and other statistics from CREATE STATISTICS commands of other users. The most common values may reveal column values the eavesdropper could not otherwise read or results of functions they cannot execute. Installing an unaffected version only fixes fresh PostgreSQL installations, namely those that are created with the initdb utility after installing that version. Current PostgreSQL installations will remain vulnerable until they follow the instructions in the release notes. Within major versions 14-16, minor versions before PostgreSQL 16.3, 15.7, and 14.12 are affected. Versions before PostgreSQL 14 are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4676 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System range_grade_text.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/range_grade_text.php. The manipulation of the argument count leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263597 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23473 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Hard-Coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23473</link><description>The SolarWinds Access Rights Manager was found to contain a hard-coded credential authentication bypass vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability allows access to the RabbitMQ management console. 

We thank Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) for its ongoing partnership in coordinating with SolarWinds on responsible disclosure of this and other potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28075 | SolarWinds ARM Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28075</link><description>The SolarWinds Access Rights Manager was susceptible to Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to abuse SolarWinds service resulting in remote code execution. 

We thank Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) for its ongoing partnership in coordinating with SolarWinds on responsible disclosure of this and other potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32712 | WordPress Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32712</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Podlove Podlove Podcast Publisher.This issue affects Podlove Podcast Publisher: from n/a through 4.0.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32717 | WordPress SchedulePress plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32717</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper SchedulePress.This issue affects SchedulePress: from n/a through 5.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32719 | WordPress WP Club Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32719</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Club Manager.This issue affects WP Club Manager: from n/a through 2.2.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32724 | WordPress SharkDropship and Affiliate for AliExpress, eBay, Amazon, Etsy plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32724</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo product importer Sharkdropship dropshipping for Aliexpress, eBay, Amazon, etsy.This issue affects Sharkdropship dropshipping for Aliexpress, eBay, Amazon, etsy: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34549 | WordPress WP Job Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34549</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Automattic WP Job Manager.This issue affects WP Job Manager: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34550 | WordPress Dynamics 365 Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.17 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34550</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in AlexaCRM Dynamics 365 Integration.This issue affects Dynamics 365 Integration: from n/a through 1.3.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34556 | WordPress Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp;amp; Order Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Exported File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34556</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34433 | WordPress One Click Demo Import plugin &amp;lt;=3.2.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34433</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in OCDI One Click Demo Import.This issue affects One Click Demo Import: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34559 | WordPress Ghost plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34559</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Ghost Foundation Ghost.This issue affects Ghost: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4606 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons, Woocommerce Builder, EDD Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4606</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BdThemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons.This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34427 | WordPress WP Favorite Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34427</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Huseyin Berberoglu WP Favorite Posts.This issue affects WP Favorite Posts: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34439 | WordPress DS Site Message plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34439</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in divSpot DS Site Message.This issue affects DS Site Message: from n/a through 1.14.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34557 | WordPress Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp;amp; Order Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34557</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29800 | WordPress Timber plugin &amp;lt;= 1.23.0 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29800</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Timber Team &amp; Contributors Timber.This issue affects Timber: from n/a through 1.23.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34415 | WordPress Thim Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34415</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThimPress Thim Elementor Kit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Thim Elementor Kit: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34417 | WordPress Viet Nam Affiliate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34417</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Toidicode.Com (thanhtaivtt) Viet Nam Affiliate allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Viet Nam Affiliate: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34418 | WordPress WPCS ( WordPress Custom Search ) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34418</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tech9logy Creators WPCS ( WordPress Custom Search ) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPCS ( WordPress Custom Search ): from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34419 | WordPress Configure Login Timeout plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34419</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nathan Vonnahme Configure Login Timeout allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Configure Login Timeout: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4675 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System show_events.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4675</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view/show_events.php. The manipulation of the argument event_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263596.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34420 | WordPress Comments Evolved for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34420</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in talspotim Comments Evolved for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Comments Evolved for WordPress: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34421 | WordPress BlogLentor – Blog Designer Pack for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34421</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpsurface BlogLentor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BlogLentor: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34422 | WordPress Viet Affiliate Link plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34422</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in trinhtuantai Viet Affiliate Link allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Viet Affiliate Link: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34423 | WordPress Forty Four – 404 Plugin for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34423</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in phpbits Forty Four – 404 Plugin for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Forty Four – 404 Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34424 | WordPress Featured Content Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34424</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in iePlexus Featured Content Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Featured Content Gallery: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34425 | WordPress QuickieBar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34425</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Phil Baylog QuickieBar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects QuickieBar: from n/a through 1.8.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34426 | WordPress Brozzme Scroll Top plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34426</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Benoti Brozzme Scroll Top allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Brozzme Scroll Top: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34428 | WordPress AWSOM News Announcement plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34428</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Harknell AWSOM News Announcement allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AWSOM News Announcement: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34429 | WordPress Simple Website Banner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34429</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Orchestrated Corona Virus (COVID-19) Banner &amp; Live Data allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Corona Virus (COVID-19) Banner &amp; Live Data: from n/a through 1.8.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34430 | WordPress TT Custom Post Type Creator plugin  &amp;lt;=1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34430</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rashed Latif TT Custom Post Type Creator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TT Custom Post Type Creator: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34431 | WordPress WP etracker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34431</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP-etracker WP etracker allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP etracker: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34432 | WordPress Better Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34432</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BetterAddons Better Elementor Addons better-elementor-addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Better Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34436 | WordPress SKT Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34436</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes SKT Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SKT Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:08:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34437 | WordPress Form Maker by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.24 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 10Web Form Builder Team Form Maker by 10Web allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Form Maker by 10Web: from n/a through 1.15.24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34441 | WordPress Easy Affiliate Links plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34441</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bootstrapped Ventures Easy Affiliate Links allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Affiliate Links: from n/a through 3.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34445 | WordPress SKT Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34445</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes SKT Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SKT Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4674 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System show_friend_request.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4674</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /view/show_friend_request.php. The manipulation of the argument my_index leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263595.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3459 | KioWare for Windows (versions all through 8.34) allows to escape the environment by downloading PDF files, which then by default are opened ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3459</link><description>KioWare for Windows (versions all through 8.34) allows to escape the environment by downloading PDF files, which then by default are opened in an external PDF viewer. By using built-in functions of that viewer it is possible to launch a web browser, search through local files and, subsequently, launch any program with user privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3460 | In KioWare for Windows (versions all through 8.34) it is possible to exit this software and use other already opened applications utilizing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3460</link><description>In KioWare for Windows (versions all through 8.34) it is possible to exit this software and use other already opened applications utilizing a short time window before the forced automatic logout occurs. Then, by using some built-in function of these applications, one may launch any other programs. 
In order to exploit this vulnerability external applications must be left running when the KioWare software is launched. Additionally, an attacker must know the PIN set for this Kioware instance and also slow down the application with some specific task which extends the usable time window.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3461 | KioWare for Windows (versions all through 8.35) allows to brute force the PIN number, which protects the application from being closed, as t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3461</link><description>KioWare for Windows (versions all through 8.35) allows to brute force the PIN number, which protects the application from being closed, as there are no mechanisms preventing a user from excessively guessing the number.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4673 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System show_student_grade_subject.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4673</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/show_student_grade_subject.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4423 | Authentication bypass in CemiPark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4423</link><description>The access control in CemiPark software does not properly validate user-entered data, which allows the authentication bypass. An attacker who has network access to the login panel can log in with administrator rights to the application.This issue affects CemiPark software: 4.5, 4.7, 5.03 and potentially others. The vendor refused to provide the specific range of affected products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4424 | Stored XSS in CemiPark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4424</link><description>The access control in CemiPark software does not properly validate user-entered data, which allows the stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. The parameters used to enter data into the system do not have appropriate validation, which makes possible to smuggle in HTML/JavaScript code. This code will be executed in the user's browser space.This issue affects CemiPark software: 4.5, 4.7, 5.03 and potentially others. The vendor refused to provide the specific range of affected products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4425 | Storing credentials in plaintext in CemiPark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4425</link><description>The access control in CemiPark software stores integration (e.g. FTP or SIP) credentials in plain-text. An attacker who gained unauthorized access to the device can retrieve clear text passwords used by the system.This issue affects CemiPark software: 4.5, 4.7, 5.03 and potentially others. The vendor refused to provide the specific range of affected products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32672 | A Segmentation Fault issue discovered in

 Samsung Open Source Escargot JavaScript engine

 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32672</link><description>A Segmentation Fault issue discovered in

 Samsung Open Source Escargot JavaScript engine

 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted input.

This issue affects Escargot: 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34365 | Apache Karaf Cave: Cave SSRF and arbitrary file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34365</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Karaf Cave.This issue affects all versions of Apache Karaf Cave.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3016 | NEC Platforms DT900 and DT900S Series 5.0.0.0 – v5.3.4.4, v5.4.0.0 – v5.6.0.20 allows an attacker to access a non-documented the system sett...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3016</link><description>NEC Platforms DT900 and DT900S Series 5.0.0.0 – v5.3.4.4, v5.4.0.0 – v5.6.0.20 allows an attacker to access a non-documented the system settings to change settings via local network with unauthenticated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5971 | Save as PDF &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5971</link><description>The Save as PDF Plugin by Pdfcrowd WordPress plugin before 3.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32669 | Possible stack overflow due to a string encoding processing error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32669</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Samsung Open Source escargot JavaScript engine allows Overflow Buffers.
However, it occurs in the test code and does not include in the release.

This issue affects escargot: 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3582 | Ungallery &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3582</link><description>The UnGallery WordPress plugin through 2.2.4 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3590 | LetterPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Subscriber Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3590</link><description>The LetterPress  WordPress plugin through 1.2.2 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks, such as delete arbitrary subscribers</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3903 | Add Custom CSS and JS &amp;lt;= 1.20 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3903</link><description>The Add Custom CSS and JS WordPress plugin through 1.20 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in as author and above add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29857 | An issue was discovered in Bouncy Castle Java Cryptography APIs before BC 1.78. Importing an EC certificate with crafted F2m parameters can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29857</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bouncy Castle Java Cryptography APIs before BC 1.78. Importing an EC certificate with crafted F2m parameters can lead to excessive CPU consumption during the evaluation of the curve parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30171 | An issue was discovered in Bouncy Castle Java TLS API and JSSE Provider before 1.78. Timing-based leakage may occur in RSA based handshakes ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30171</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bouncy Castle Java TLS API and JSSE Provider before 1.78. Timing-based leakage may occur in RSA based handshakes because of exception processing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30172 | An issue was discovered in Bouncy Castle Java Cryptography APIs before 1.78. An Ed25519 verification code infinite loop can occur via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30172</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bouncy Castle Java Cryptography APIs before 1.78. An Ed25519 verification code infinite loop can occur via a crafted signature and public key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4672 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System show_student_subject.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4672</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/show_student_subject.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263593 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 03:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6682 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6682</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Discord Integrations Chat Messages can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6688 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6688</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2454 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2454</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.11 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. The pins endpoint is susceptible to DoS through a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2651 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2651</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted markdown content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4539 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4539</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2 where abusing the API to filter branch and tags could lead to Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4597 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4597</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27793 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.2 for Windows. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27793</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.13.2 for Windows. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26517 | SQL Injection vulnerability in School Task Manager v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26517</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in School Task Manager v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the delete-task.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27280 | A buffer-overread issue was discovered in StringIO 3.0.1, as distributed in Ruby 3.0.x through 3.0.6 and 3.1.x through 3.1.4. The ungetbyte ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27280</link><description>A buffer-overread issue was discovered in StringIO 3.0.1, as distributed in Ruby 3.0.x through 3.0.6 and 3.1.x through 3.1.4. The ungetbyte and ungetc methods on a StringIO can read past the end of a string, and a subsequent call to StringIO.gets may return the memory value. 3.0.3 is the main fixed version; however, for Ruby 3.0 users, a fixed version is stringio 3.0.1.1, and for Ruby 3.1 users, a fixed version is stringio 3.0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27281 | An issue was discovered in RDoc 6.3.3 through 6.6.2, as distributed in Ruby 3.x through 3.3.0. When parsing .rdoc_options (used for configur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27281</link><description>An issue was discovered in RDoc 6.3.3 through 6.6.2, as distributed in Ruby 3.x through 3.3.0. When parsing .rdoc_options (used for configuration in RDoc) as a YAML file, object injection and resultant remote code execution are possible because there are no restrictions on the classes that can be restored. (When loading the documentation cache, object injection and resultant remote code execution are also possible if there were a crafted cache.) The main fixed version is 6.6.3.1. For Ruby 3.0 users, a fixed version is rdoc 6.3.4.1. For Ruby 3.1 users, a fixed version is rdoc 6.4.1.1. For Ruby 3.2 users, a fixed version is rdoc 6.5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27282 | An issue was discovered in Ruby 3.x through 3.3.0. If attacker-supplied data is provided to the Ruby regex compiler, it is possible to extra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27282</link><description>An issue was discovered in Ruby 3.x through 3.3.0. If attacker-supplied data is provided to the Ruby regex compiler, it is possible to extract arbitrary heap data relative to the start of the text, including pointers and sensitive strings. The fixed versions are 3.0.7, 3.1.5, 3.2.4, and 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28759 | A crafted network packet may cause a buffer overrun in Wind River VxWorks 7 through 23.09.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28759</link><description>A crafted network packet may cause a buffer overrun in Wind River VxWorks 7 through 23.09.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34196 | Totolink AC1200 Wireless Dual Band Gigabit Router A3002RU_V3 Firmware V3.0.0-B20230809.1615 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. The "boa" prog...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34196</link><description>Totolink AC1200 Wireless Dual Band Gigabit Router A3002RU_V3 Firmware V3.0.0-B20230809.1615 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. The "boa" program allows attackers to modify the value of the "vwlan_idx" field via "formMultiAP". This can lead to a stack overflow through the "formWlEncrypt" CGI function by constructing malicious HTTP requests and passing a WLAN SSID value exceeding the expected length, potentially resulting in command execution or denial of service attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34308 | TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function urldecode.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34308</link><description>TOTOLINK LR350 V9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function urldecode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33382 | An issue in Open5GS v.2.7.0 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via the 64 unsuccessful UE/gnb registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33382</link><description>An issue in Open5GS v.2.7.0 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via the 64 unsuccessful UE/gnb registration</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25532 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the bt_id parameter at /include/get_dict.aspx.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25532</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the bt_id parameter at /include/get_dict.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25533 | Error messages in RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to leak the physical path of the website (/WorkFlow/OfficeFileUpdate.aspx). This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25533</link><description>Error messages in RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to leak the physical path of the website (/WorkFlow/OfficeFileUpdate.aspx). This vulnerability can allow attackers to write files to the server or execute arbitrary commands via crafted SQL statements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34257 | TOTOLINK EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 has a vulnerability in the apcliEncrypType parameter that allows unauthorized execution of arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34257</link><description>TOTOLINK EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 has a vulnerability in the apcliEncrypType parameter that allows unauthorized execution of arbitrary commands, allowing an attacker to obtain device administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25528 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /PersonalAffair/worklog_template_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25528</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /PersonalAffair/worklog_template_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34244 | libmodbus v3.1.10 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the modbus_write_bits function. This issue can be triggered when the function is fed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34244</link><description>libmodbus v3.1.10 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the modbus_write_bits function. This issue can be triggered when the function is fed with specially crafted input, which leads to out-of-bounds read and can potentially cause a crash or other unintended behaviors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25527 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /PersonalAffair/worklog_template_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25527</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /PersonalAffair/worklog_template_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22460 | Dell PowerProtect DM5500 version 5.15.0.0 and prior contains an insecure deserialization Vulnerability. A remote attacker with high privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22460</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DM5500 version 5.15.0.0 and prior contains an insecure deserialization Vulnerability. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution on the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25530 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the PageID parameter at /WebUtility/get_find_condictio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25530</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the PageID parameter at /WebUtility/get_find_condiction.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24908 | Dell PowerProtect DM5500 version 5.15.0.0 and prior contain an Arbitrary File Delete via Path Traversal vulnerability. A remote attacker wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24908</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DM5500 version 5.15.0.0 and prior contain an Arbitrary File Delete via Path Traversal vulnerability. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to deletion of arbitrary files stored on the server filesystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25531 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the PageID parameter at /WebUtility/SearchCondiction.a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25531</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the PageID parameter at /WebUtility/SearchCondiction.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31961 | A SQL injection vulnerability in unit.php in Sonic Shopfloor.guide before 3.1.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31961</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in unit.php in Sonic Shopfloor.guide before 3.1.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the level2 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28971 | Dell Update Manager Plugin, versions 1.4.0 through 1.5.0, contains a Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in Log file. A remote high pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28971</link><description>Dell Update Manager Plugin, versions 1.4.0 through 1.5.0, contains a Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in Log file. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24787 | Arbitrary code execution during build on Darwin in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24787</link><description>On Darwin, building a Go module which contains CGO can trigger arbitrary code execution when using the Apple version of ld, due to usage of the -lto_library flag in a "#cgo LDFLAGS" directive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24788 | Malformed DNS message can cause infinite loop in net</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24788</link><description>A malformed DNS message in response to a query can cause the Lookup functions to get stuck in an infinite loop.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25529 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_office_file_history_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25529</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_office_file_history_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25520 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /SysManage/sys_blogtemplate_new.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25520</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /SysManage/sys_blogtemplate_new.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25521 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the txt_keyword parameter at get_company.aspx.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25521</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the txt_keyword parameter at get_company.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25526 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the project_id parameter at /ProjectManage/pm_gatt_inc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25526</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the project_id parameter at /ProjectManage/pm_gatt_inc.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26579 | Apache Inlong JDBC Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26579</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.7.0 through 1.11.0, 

 the attackers can bypass using malicious parameters.

Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 1.12.0 or cherry-pick [1], [2] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/9694 

[2]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/9707</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21793 | BIG-IP Central Manager OData Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21793</link><description>An OData injection vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Next Central Manager API (URI).  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25524 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkPlan/WorkPla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25524</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkPlan/WorkPlanAttachDownLoad.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25525 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the filename parameter at /WorkFlow/OfficeFileDownload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25525</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the filename parameter at /WorkFlow/OfficeFileDownload.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25560 | TMM Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25560</link><description>When BIG-IP AFM is licensed and provisioned, undisclosed DNS traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26026 | BIG-IP Central Manager SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26026</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Next Central Manager API (URI).  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27202 | BIG-IP TMUI XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27202</link><description>A DOM-based cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28132 | BIG-IP NEXT CNF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28132</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists in the GSLB container, which may allow an authenticated attacker with local access to view sensitive information.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28883 | BIG-IP APM browser network access VPN client vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28883</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability exists in 

BIG-IP APM browser network access VPN client 



 for Windows, macOS and Linux which may allow an attacker to bypass F5 endpoint inspection. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28889 |  BIG-IP SSL vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28889</link><description>When an SSL profile with alert timeout is configured with a non-default value on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic along with conditions beyond the attacker's control can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31156 | BIG-IP Configuration utility XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31156</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32049 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32049</link><description>BIG-IP Next Central Manager (CM) may allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain the BIG-IP Next LTM/WAF instance credentials. 

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32761 | BIG-IP TMM tenants on VELOS and rSeries vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32761</link><description>Under certain conditions, a potential data leak may occur in the Traffic Management Microkernels (TMMs) of BIG-IP tenants running on VELOS and rSeries platforms. However, this issue cannot be exploited by an attacker because it is not consistently reproducible and is beyond an attacker's control.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33604 | BIG-IP Configuration utility XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33604</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exist in undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33608 | BIG-IP IPsec vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33608</link><description>When IPsec is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33612 | BIG-IP Next Central Manager vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33612</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next Central Manager and may allow an attacker to impersonate an Instance Provider system. A successful exploit of this vulnerability can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4654 | BlueNet Technology Clinical Browsing System cloudInterface.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4654</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlueNet Technology Clinical Browsing System 1.2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /xds/cloudInterface.php. The manipulation of the argument INSTI_CODE leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263499.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25523 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the file_id parameter at /filemanage/file_memo.aspx.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25523</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the file_id parameter at /filemanage/file_memo.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25519 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the idlist parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_work_print.aspx.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25519</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the idlist parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_work_print.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25522 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the office_missive_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_work_f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25522</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the office_missive_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_work_form_save.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32113 | Apache OFBiz: Path traversal leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32113</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.13.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.13, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25517 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the tbTable argument at /WebUtility/MF.aspx.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25517</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the tbTable argument at /WebUtility/MF.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25518 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the template_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_get_fields_a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25518</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the template_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_get_fields_approve.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3951 | Cross-site Scripting in PTC Codebeamer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3951</link><description>PTC Codebeamer is vulnerable to a cross site scripting vulnerability that could allow an attacker to inject and execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25515 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_work...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25515</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_work_finish_file_down.aspx.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32980 | Spin contains a potential network sandbox escape for specifically configured Spin applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32980</link><description>Spin is the developer tool for building and running serverless applications powered by WebAssembly. Prior to 2.4.3, some specifically configured Spin applications that use `self` requests without a specified URL authority can be induced to make requests to arbitrary hosts via the `Host` HTTP header. The following conditions need to be met for an application to be vulnerable: 1. The environment Spin is deployed in routes requests to the Spin runtime based on the request URL instead of the `Host` header, and leaves the `Host` header set to its original value; 2. The Spin application's component handling the incoming request is configured with an `allow_outbound_hosts` list containing `"self"`; and 3. In reaction to an incoming request, the component makes an outbound request whose URL doesn't include the hostname/port. Spin 2.4.3 has been released to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4653 | BlueNet Technology Clinical Browsing System outIndex.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlueNet Technology Clinical Browsing System 1.2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /xds/outIndex.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263498 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34347 | @hoppscotch/cli affected by Sandbox Escape in @hoppscotch/js-sandbox leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34347</link><description>@hoppscotch/cli is a CLI to run Hoppscotch Test Scripts in CI environments. Prior to 0.8.0, the @hoppscotch/js-sandbox package provides a Javascript sandbox that uses the Node.js vm module. However, the vm module is not safe for sandboxing untrusted Javascript code. This is because code inside the vm context can break out if it can get a hold of any reference to an object created outside of the vm. In the case of @hoppscotch/js-sandbox, multiple references to external objects are passed into the vm context to allow pre-request scripts interactions with environment variables and more. But this also allows the pre-request script to escape the sandbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32886 | Vitess vulnerable to infinite memory consumption and vtgate crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32886</link><description>Vitess is a database clustering system for horizontal scaling of MySQL. When executing the following simple query, the `vtgate` will go into an endless loop that also keeps consuming memory and eventually will run out of memory. This vulnerability is fixed in 19.0.4, 18.0.5, and 17.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4651 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_attendance_history1.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4651</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/student_attendance_history1.php. The manipulation of the argument year leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263495.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4652 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System show_teacher2.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4652</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/show_teacher2.php. The manipulation of the argument month leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263496.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33573 | WordPress EPROLO Dropshipping plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33573</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EPROLO EPROLO Dropshipping.This issue affects EPROLO Dropshipping: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33574 | WordPress Vitepos plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33574</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in appsbd Vitepos.This issue affects Vitepos: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24833 | WordPress Happy Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.1 - Broken Access Control on Post Clone vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24833</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leevio Happy Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Happy Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 3.10.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4649 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_exam_mark_insert_form1.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4649</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /view/student_exam_mark_insert_form1.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263493 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4650 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_due_payment.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4650</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view/student_due_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument due_month leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263494 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30459 | WordPress AI WP Writer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30459</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AIpost AI WP Writer.This issue affects AI WP Writer: from n/a through 3.6.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31270 | WordPress ARForms Form Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31270</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Repute InfoSystems ARForms Form Builder.This issue affects ARForms Form Builder: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4233 | Broken Access Control vulnerability in multiple WordPress plugins by Tyche Softwares</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4233</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce, Tyche Softwares Arconix Shortcodes, Tyche Softwares Arconix FAQ.This issue affects Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.8.1; Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.10; Arconix FAQ: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1438 | WordPress Rolo Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1438</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PressFore Rolo Slider.This issue affects Rolo Slider: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4647 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_first_payment.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4647</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/student_first_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument index leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263491.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4648 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_exam_mark_update_form.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4648</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/student_exam_mark_update_form.php. The manipulation of the argument std_index leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263492.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34255 | jizhicms v2.5.1 contains a Cross-Site Scripting(XSS) vulnerability in the message function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34255</link><description>jizhicms v2.5.1 contains a Cross-Site Scripting(XSS) vulnerability in the message function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4645 | SourceCodester Prison Management System changepassword.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4645</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/changepassword.php. The manipulation of the argument txtold_password/txtnew_password/txtconfirm_password leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263489 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4646 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_payment_details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4646</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/student_payment_details.php. The manipulation of the argument index leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40218 | WordPress TH Advance Product Search plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40218</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeHunk Advance WordPress Search Plugin.This issue affects Advance WordPress Search Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34414 | WordPress Raindrops theme &amp;lt;= 1.600 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34414</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nobita allows Stored XSS.This issue affects raindrops: from n/a through 1.600.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34546 | WordPress Sticky Social Link plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34546</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HabibCoder Sticky Social Link allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sticky Social Link: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34547 | WordPress Magical Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.34 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34547</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Noor alam Magical Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Magical Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4644 | SourceCodester Prison Management System changepassword.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4644</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Employee/changepassword.php. The manipulation of the argument txtold_password/txtnew_password/txtconfirm_password leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263488.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34548 | WordPress All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesgrove WidgetKit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WidgetKit: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34553 | WordPress Stockholm Core plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Reflected  Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Select-Themes Stockholm Core allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Stockholm Core: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34558 | WordPress WOLF plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 WOLF allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WOLF: from n/a through 1.0.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34560 | WordPress gee Search Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34560</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GOMO gee Search Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects gee Search Plus: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34561 | WordPress Real3D Flipbook PDF Viewer Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.71 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative interactive media 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 3.71.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34562 | WordPress Move Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34562</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Moveaddons Move Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Move Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34563 | WordPress Gold Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34563</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GoldAddons Gold Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gold Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34564 | WordPress Counter Up plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34564</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LogicHunt Inc. Counter Up allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Counter Up: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34565 | WordPress Debug Info plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34565</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Debug Info allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Debug Info: from n/a through 1.3.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34566 | WordPress Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Johan van der Wijk Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget): from n/a through 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34568 | WordPress LetterPress Newsletter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34568</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeqx LetterPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LetterPress: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3507 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Lunar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3507</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Lunar software that affects versions 6.0.2 through 6.6.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a secondary process injection into the Lunar application and abuse those rights to access sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34569 | WordPress Zotpress plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34569</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Katie Seaborn Zotpress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Zotpress: from n/a through 7.3.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34570 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34571 | WordPress Himalayas theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGrill Himalayas allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Himalayas: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4135 | The WP Latest Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.7. This is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4135</link><description>The WP Latest Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.7. This is due to the plugin allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a user-supplied value prior to using that value in a call to do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4281 | The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'link-library' shortcode in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4281</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'link-library' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34572 | WordPress Fancy Elementor Flipbox plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34572</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemePrix Fancy Elementor Flipbox fancy-elementor-flipbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fancy Elementor Flipbox: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34573 | WordPress Pootle Pagebuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pootlepress Pootle Pagebuilder – WordPress Page builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pootle Pagebuilder – WordPress Page builder: from n/a through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41651 | WordPress Multi-column Tag Map plugin &amp;lt;= 17.0.26 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41651</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Multi-column Tag Map.This issue affects Multi-column Tag Map: from n/a through 17.0.26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34574 | WordPress Table Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wpsoul Table Maker allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Table Maker: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4436 | Etcd: incomplete fix for cve-2022-41723 in openstack platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4436</link><description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-41723. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4437 | Etcd: incomplete fix for cve-2021-44716 in openstack platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4437</link><description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2021-44716. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4438 | Etcd: incomplete fix for cve-2023-39325/cve-2023-44487 in openstack platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4438</link><description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-39325/CVE-2023-44487, known as Rapid Reset. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1076 | SSL Zen &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Unauthenticated Private Keys Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1076</link><description>The SSL Zen  WordPress plugin before 4.6.0 only relies on the use of .htaccess to prevent visitors from accessing the site's generated private keys, which allows an attacker to read them if the site runs on a server who doesn't support .htaccess files, like NGINX.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3494 | The Mesmerize Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mesmerize_contact_form' shortcod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3494</link><description>The Mesmerize Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mesmerize_contact_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.148 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22264 | VMware Avi Load Balancer updates address multiple vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22264</link><description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges on VMware Avi Load Balancer can create, modify, execute and delete files as a root user on the host system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22266 | VMware Avi Load Balancer updates address multiple vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22266</link><description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with access to the system logs can view cloud connection credentials in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 04:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32674 | Heateor Social Login WordPress prior to 1.1.32 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32674</link><description>Heateor Social Login WordPress prior to 1.1.32 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4393 | The Social Connect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insuffi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4393</link><description>The Social Connect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insufficient verification on the OpenID server being supplied during the social login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4418 | Libvirt: stack use-after-free in virnetclientioeventloop()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4418</link><description>A race condition leading to a stack use-after-free flaw was found in libvirt. Due to a bad assumption in the virNetClientIOEventLoop() method, the `data` pointer to a stack-allocated virNetClientIOEventData structure ended up being used in the virNetClientIOEventFD callback while the data pointer's stack frame was concurrently being "freed" when returning from virNetClientIOEventLoop(). The 'virtproxyd' daemon can be used to trigger requests. If libvirt is configured with fine-grained access control, this issue, in theory, allows a user to escape their otherwise limited access. This flaw allows a local, unprivileged user to access virtproxyd without authenticating. Remote users would need to authenticate before they could access it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4162 | KW Watcher Vulnerability ALlows Malicious Read Access to Memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4162</link><description>A buffer error in Panasonic KW Watcher versions 1.00 through 2.83 may allow attackers malicious read access to memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1929 | Local Root Exploit via Configuration Dictionary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1929</link><description>Local Root Exploit via Configuration Dictionary  in dnf5daemon-server before 5.1.17 allows a malicious user to impact Confidentiality and Integrity via Configuration Dictionary.

There are issues with the D-Bus interface long before Polkit is invoked. The `org.rpm.dnf.v0.SessionManager.open_session` method takes a key/value map of configuration entries. A sub-entry in this map, placed under the "config" key, is another key/value map. The configuration values found in it will be forwarded as configuration overrides to the `libdnf5::Base` configuration. 

Practically all libdnf5 configuration aspects can be influenced here. Already when opening the session via D-Bus, the libdnf5 will be initialized using these override configuration values. There is no sanity checking of the content of this "config" map, which is untrusted data. It is possible to make the library loading a plug-in shared library under control of an unprivileged user, hence achieving root access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1930 | No Limit on Number of Open Sessions / Bad Session Close Behaviour</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1930</link><description>No Limit on Number of Open Sessions / Bad Session Close Behaviour  in dnf5daemon-server before 5.1.17 allows a malicious user to impact Availability via No Limit on Number of Open Sessions.

There is no limit on how many sessions D-Bus clients may create using the `open_session()` D-Bus method. For each session a thread is created in dnf5daemon-server. This spends a couple of hundred megabytes of memory in the process. Further connections will become impossible, likely because no more threads can be spawned by the D-Bus service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2746 | Incomplete fix for CVE-2024-1929</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2746</link><description>Incomplete fix for CVE-2024-1929

The problem with CVE-2024-1929 was that the dnf5 D-Bus daemon accepted arbitrary configuration parameters from unprivileged users, which allowed a
local root exploit by tricking the daemon into loading a user controlled "plugin". All of this happened before Polkit authentication was even started.

The dnf5 library code does not check whether non-root users control the directory in question. 

On one hand, this poses a Denial-of-Service attack vector by making the daemonoperate on a blocking file (e.g. named FIFO special file) or a very large file
that causes an out-of-memory situation (e.g. /dev/zero). On the other hand, this can be used to let the daemon process privileged files like /etc/shadow.
The file in question is parsed as an INI file. Error diagnostics resulting from parsing privileged files could cause information leaks, if these diagnostics
are accessible to unprivileged users. In the case of libdnf5, no such user accessible diagnostics should exist, though.

Also, a local attacker can place a valid repository configuration file in this directory. This configuration file allows to specify
a plethora of additional configuration options. This makes various additional code paths in libdnf5 accessible to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2860 | The PostgreSQL implementation in Brocade SANnav versions before 2.3.0a is vulnerable to an incorrect local authentication flaw. An attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2860</link><description>The PostgreSQL implementation in Brocade SANnav versions before 2.3.0a is vulnerable to an incorrect local authentication flaw. An attacker accessing the VM where the Brocade SANnav is installed can gain access to sensitive data inside the PostgreSQL database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4456 | In affected versions of Octopus Server with certain access levels it was possible to embed a Cross-Site Scripting payload on the audit page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4456</link><description>In affected versions of Octopus Server with certain access levels it was possible to embed a Cross-Site Scripting payload on the audit page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34947 | NETGEAR R7800 net-cgi Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34947</link><description>NETGEAR R7800 net-cgi Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR R7800 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of the soap_block_table file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-13055.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34948 | Foxit PDF Reader Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34948</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Square annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14272.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34949 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34949</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14273.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34950 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34950</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14396.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34951 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34951</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14395.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34952 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34952</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14729.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34953 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34953</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14658.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34954 | Foxit PDF Editor StrikeOut Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34954</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor StrikeOut Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14355.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34955 | Foxit PDF Editor Stamp Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34955</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Stamp Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14356.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34956 | Foxit PDF Editor Underline Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34956</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Underline Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14357.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34957 | Foxit PDF Editor Highlight Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34957</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Highlight Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14358.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34958 | Foxit PDF Editor Text Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34958</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Text Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14359.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34959 | Foxit PDF Editor Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34959</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14360.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34960 | Foxit PDF Editor Circle Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34960</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Circle Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14362.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34961 | Foxit PDF Editor Ink Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34961</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Ink Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14363.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34962 | Foxit PDF Editor Caret Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34962</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Caret Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14364.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34963 | Foxit PDF Editor PolyLine Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34963</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor PolyLine Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14365.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34964 | Foxit PDF Editor Polygon Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34964</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Polygon Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14366.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34965 | Foxit PDF Editor Squiggly Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34965</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Squiggly Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14361.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34966 | Foxit PDF Editor FileAttachment Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34966</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor FileAttachment Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14367.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34967 | Foxit PDF Editor Line Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34967</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Line Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14368.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34968 | Foxit PDF Editor transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34968</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14370.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34969 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34969</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14622.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34970 | Foxit PDF Reader print Method Use of Externally-Controlled Format String Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34970</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader print Method Use of Externally-Controlled Format String Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the print method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it as a format specifier. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14849.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34971 | Foxit PDF Reader JPG2000 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34971</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader JPG2000 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14812.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34972 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34972</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14975.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34973 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34973</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14968.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34974 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34974</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15167.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34975 | Foxit PDF Reader transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34975</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15218.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34976 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34976</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14659.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34981 | Linux Kernel Bluetooth CMTP Module Double Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34981</link><description>Linux Kernel Bluetooth CMTP Module Double Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Linux Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CMTP module. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing further free operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11977.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34982 | NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34982</link><description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the httpd service, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. When parsing the strings file, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.




. Was ZDI-CAN-13709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34983 | NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34983</link><description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the httpd service, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to system configuration information. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-13708.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34999 | OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34999</link><description>OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of OpenBSD Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of multicast routing. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-14540.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35000 | OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35000</link><description>OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of OpenBSD Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of multicast routing. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-16112.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35001 | BMC Track-It! GetData Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35001</link><description>BMC Track-It! GetData Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of BMC Track-It!. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the GetData endpoint. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-14527.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35002 | BMC Track-It! Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35002</link><description>BMC Track-It! Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of BMC Track-It!. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of email attachments. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-14122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-0369 | Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Restore Workspace Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0369</link><description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Restore Workspace Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the Restore Workspace feature. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17227.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43651 | Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43651</link><description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18960.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43652 | Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43652</link><description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18981.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43653 | Bentley View SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43653</link><description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. Crafted data in an SKP file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19084.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43654 | NETGEAR CAX30S SSO Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43654</link><description>NETGEAR CAX30S SSO Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR CAX30S routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the token parameter provided to the sso.php endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18227.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43655 | Bentley View FBX File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43655</link><description>Bentley View FBX File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FBX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18491.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43656 | Bentley View FBX File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43656</link><description>Bentley View FBX File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FBX files. Crafted data in an FBX file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18492.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27321 | OPC Foundation UA .NET Standard ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27321</link><description>OPC Foundation UA .NET Standard ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of OPC Foundation UA .NET Standard. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OPC UA ConditionRefresh requests. By sending a large number of requests, an attacker can consume all available resources on the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20505.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35748 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35748</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20076.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35749 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35749</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20077.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35757 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time NTP Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35757</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time NTP Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20085.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37325 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List Missing Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37325</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List Missing Authentication Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to make unauthorized changes to device configuration on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to manipulate wireless authentication settings. Was ZDI-CAN-20104.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40490 | Maxon Cinema 4D SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40490</link><description>Maxon Cinema 4D SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Maxon Cinema 4D. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21438.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23551 | HCL BigFix Compliance is potentially affected by Oracle database credentials stored at endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23551</link><description>Database scanning using username and password stores the credentials in plaintext or encoded format within files at the endpoint. This has been identified as a significant security risk. This will lead to exposure of sensitive information for unauthorized access, potentially leading to severe consequences such as data breaches, unauthorized data manipulation, and compromised system integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40694 | IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40694</link><description>IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores 4.0.0 through 4.8.4 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  264838.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0022 | In multiple functions of CompanionDeviceManagerService.java, there is a possible launch NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity of another us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0022</link><description>In multiple functions of CompanionDeviceManagerService.java, there is a possible launch NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity of another user profile due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0024 | In multiple methods of UserManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0024</link><description>In multiple methods of UserManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0025 | In sendIntentSender of ActivityManagerService.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0025</link><description>In sendIntentSender of ActivityManagerService.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0026 | In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible persistent denial of service due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0026</link><description>In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible persistent denial of service due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0027 | In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible way to cause a boot loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0027</link><description>In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible way to cause a boot loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0042 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible confusion of OEM and DRM certificates due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local bypass of D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0042</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible confusion of OEM and DRM certificates due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local bypass of DRM content protection with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0043 | In multiple locations, there is a possible notification listener grant to an app running in the work profile due to a logic error in the cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0043</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible notification listener grant to an app running in the work profile due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23704 | In onCreate of WifiDialogActivity.java, there is a possible way to bypass the DISALLOW_ADD_WIFI_CONFIG restriction due to a missing permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23704</link><description>In onCreate of WifiDialogActivity.java, there is a possible way to bypass the DISALLOW_ADD_WIFI_CONFIG restriction due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23705 | In multiple locations, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input validation. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23705</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23706 | In multiple locations, there is a possible bypass of health data permissions due to an improper input validation. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23706</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible bypass of health data permissions due to an improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23707 | In multiple locations, there is a possible permissions bypass due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23707</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible permissions bypass due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23708 | In multiple functions of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible way to not show a toast message when a clipboard message has b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23708</link><description>In multiple functions of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible way to not show a toast message when a clipboard message has been accessed. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23709 | In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23709</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23710 | In assertPackageWithSharedUserIdIsPrivileged of InstallPackageHelper.java, there is a possible execution of arbitrary app code as a privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23710</link><description>In assertPackageWithSharedUserIdIsPrivileged of InstallPackageHelper.java, there is a possible execution of arbitrary app code as a privileged app due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23712 | In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way to saturate the content of /data/system/appops_accesses.xml due to reso...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23712</link><description>In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way to saturate the content of /data/system/appops_accesses.xml due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23713 | In migrateNotificationFilter of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist notifications settings due to improp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23713</link><description>In migrateNotificationFilter of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist notifications settings due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34346 | Deno contains a permission escalation via open of privileged files with missing `--deny` flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34346</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime with secure defaults. The Deno sandbox may be unexpectedly weakened by allowing file read/write access to privileged files in various locations on Unix and Windows platforms. For example, reading `/proc/self/environ` may provide access equivalent to `--allow-env`, and writing `/proc/self/mem` may provide access equivalent to `--allow-all`. Users who grant read and write access to the entire filesystem may not realize that these access to these files may have additional, unintended consequences. The documentation did not reflect that this practice should be undertaken to increase the strength of the security sandbox. Users who run code with `--allow-read` or `--allow-write` may unexpectedly end up granting additional permissions via file-system operations. Deno 1.43 and above require explicit `--allow-all` access to read or write `/etc`, `/dev` on unix platform (as well as `/proc` and `/sys` on linux platforms), and any path starting with `\\` on Windows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4030 | tempfile.mkdtemp() may be readable and writeable by all users on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4030</link><description>On Windows a directory returned by tempfile.mkdtemp() would not always have permissions set to restrict reading and writing to the temporary directory by other users, instead usually inheriting the correct permissions from the default location. Alternate configurations or users without a profile directory may not have the intended permissions.

If you’re not using Windows or haven’t changed the temporary directory location then you aren’t affected by this vulnerability. On other platforms the returned directory is consistently readable and writable only by the current user.

This issue was caused by Python not supporting Unix permissions on Windows. The fix adds support for Unix “700” for the mkdir function on Windows which is used by mkdtemp() to ensure the newly created directory has the proper permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27273 | IBM AIX privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27273</link><description>IBM AIX's Unix domain (AIX 7.2, 7.3, VIOS 3.1, and VIOS 4.1) datagram socket implementation could potentially expose applications using Unix domain datagram sockets with SO_PEERID operation and may lead to privilege escalation.  IBM X-Force ID:  284903.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4558 | Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4558</link><description>Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4559 | Heap buffer overflow in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4559</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25511 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_new.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25511</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_new.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25513 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the file_id parameter at /CorporateCulture/kaizen_down...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25513</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the file_id parameter at /CorporateCulture/kaizen_download.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25514 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the template_id parameter at /SysManage/wf_template_ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25514</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the template_id parameter at /SysManage/wf_template_child_field_list.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25509 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25509</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_file_download.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25510 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_show.a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25510</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34314 | CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fetch_action method...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34314</link><description>CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fetch_action method of /admin/template_admin.php. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34315 | CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fckedit_action meth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34315</link><description>CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fckedit_action method of /admin/template_admin.php. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42757 | Process Explorer before 17.04 allows attackers to make it functionally unavailable (a denial of service for analysis) by renaming an executa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42757</link><description>Process Explorer before 17.04 allows attackers to make it functionally unavailable (a denial of service for analysis) by renaming an executable file to a new extensionless 255-character name and launching it with NtCreateUserProcess. This can occur through an issue in wcscat_s error handling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34517 | The Cypher component in Neo4j before 5.19.0 mishandles IMMUTABLE privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34517</link><description>The Cypher component in Neo4j before 5.19.0 mishandles IMMUTABLE privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25507 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the email_attach_id parameter at /LHMail/AttachDown.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25507</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the email_attach_id parameter at /LHMail/AttachDown.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25512 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the attach_id parameter at /Bulletin/AttachDownLoad.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25512</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the attach_id parameter at /Bulletin/AttachDownLoad.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34397 | An issue was discovered in GNOME GLib before 2.78.5, and 2.79.x and 2.80.x before 2.80.1. When a GDBus-based client subscribes to signals fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34397</link><description>An issue was discovered in GNOME GLib before 2.78.5, and 2.79.x and 2.80.x before 2.80.1. When a GDBus-based client subscribes to signals from a trusted system service such as NetworkManager on a shared computer, other users of the same computer can send spoofed D-Bus signals that the GDBus-based client will wrongly interpret as having been sent by the trusted system service. This could lead to the GDBus-based client behaving incorrectly, with an application-dependent impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25508 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /bulletin/bulletin_template_show.a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25508</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /bulletin/bulletin_template_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29150 | An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29150</link><description>An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.01.10.728. Because of improper privilege management, an authenticated attacker is able to create symlinks to sensitive and protected data in locations that are used for debugging files. Given that the process of gathering debug logs is carried out with root privileges, any file referenced in the symlink is consequently written to the debug archive, thereby granting accessibility to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29149 | An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29149</link><description>An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.01.10.728. Because of a time-of-check time-of-use vulnerability, an authenticated attacker is able to replace the verified firmware image with malicious firmware during the update process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29209 | A medium severity vulnerability has been identified in the update mechanism of the Phish Alert Button for Outlook, which could allow an atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29209</link><description>A medium severity vulnerability has been identified in the update mechanism of the Phish Alert Button for Outlook, which could allow an attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code on the host machine. The vulnerability arises from the application's failure to securely verify the authenticity and integrity of the update server.

The application periodically checks for updates by querying a specific URL. However, this process does not enforce strict SSL/TLS verification, nor does it validate the digital signature of the received update files. An attacker with the capability to perform DNS spoofing can exploit this weakness. By manipulating DNS responses, the attacker can redirect the application's update requests to a malicious server under their control.

Once the application queries the spoofed update URL, the malicious server can respond with a crafted update package. Since the application fails to properly verify the authenticity of the update file, it will accept and execute the package, leading to arbitrary code execution on the host machine.

Impact:
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability allows an attacker to execute code with elevated privileges, potentially leading to data theft, installation of further malware, or other malicious activities on the host system.

Affected Products:
Phish Alert Button (PAB) for Outlook versions 1.10.0-1.10.11
Second Chance Client versions 2.0.0-2.0.9
PIQ Client versions 1.0.0-1.0.15

Remediation:
Automated updates will be pushed to address this issue. Users of affected versions should verify the latest version is applied and, if not, apply the latest updates provided by KnowBe4, which addresses this vulnerability by implementing proper SSL/TLS checks of the update server. It is also recommended to ensure DNS settings are secure to prevent DNS spoofing attacks.

Workarounds:
Use secure corporate networks or VPN services to secure network communications, which can help mitigate the risk of DNS spoofing.

Credits:
This vulnerability was discovered by Ceri Coburn at Pen Test Partners, who reported it responsibly to the vendor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29210 | A local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerability has been identified in Phish Alert Button for Outlook (PAB), specifically within its config...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29210</link><description>A local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerability has been identified in Phish Alert Button for Outlook (PAB), specifically within its configuration management functionalities. This vulnerability allows a regular user to modify the application's configuration file to redirect update checks to an arbitrary server, which can then be exploited in conjunction with CVE-2024-29209 to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.

The issue stems from improper permission settings on the application's configuration file, which is stored in a common directory accessible to all users. This file includes critical parameters, such as the update server URL. By default, the application does not enforce adequate access controls on this file, allowing non-privileged users to modify it without administrative consent.

An attacker with regular user access can alter the update server URL specified in the configuration file to point to a malicious server. When the application performs its next update check, it will contact the attacker-controlled server. If the system is also vulnerable to CVE-2024-29209, the attacker can deliver a malicious update package that, when executed, grants them elevated privileges.

Impact:
This vulnerability can lead to a regular user executing code with administrative privileges. This can result in unauthorized access to sensitive data, installation of additional malware, and a full takeover of the affected system.

Affected Products:
Phish Alert Button (PAB) for Outlook versions 1.10.0-1.10.11
Second Chance Client versions 2.0.0-2.0.9
PIQ Client versions 1.0.0-1.0.15

Remediation:
KnowBe4 has released a patch that corrects the permission settings on the configuration file to prevent unauthorized modifications. Automated updates will be pushed to address this issue. Users of affected versions should verify the latest version is applied and, if not, apply the latest updates provided by KnowBe4.

Workarounds:
Manually set the correct permissions on the configuration file to restrict write access to administrators only.

Credits:
This vulnerability was discovered by Ceri Coburn at Pen Test Partners, who reported it responsibly to the vendor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33149 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the myProcessList function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33149</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the myProcessList function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33164 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authUserList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33164</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authUserList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33153 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the commentList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33153</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the commentList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33148 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the list function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33148</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the list function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27982 | The team has identified a critical vulnerability in the http server of the most recent version of Node, where malformed headers can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27982</link><description>The team has identified a critical vulnerability in the http server of the most recent version of Node, where malformed headers can lead to HTTP request smuggling. Specifically, if a space is placed before a content-length header, it is not interpreted correctly, enabling attackers to smuggle in a second request within the body of the first.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29206 | An Improper Access Control could allow a malicious actor authenticated in the API to enable Android Debug Bridge (ADB) and make unsupported ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29206</link><description>An Improper Access Control could allow a malicious actor authenticated in the API to enable Android Debug Bridge (ADB) and make unsupported changes to the system.

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Access G2 Reader Pro (Version 1.2.172 and earlier)

UniFi Access Reader Pro (Version 2.7.238 and earlier)

UniFi Access Intercom (Version 1.0.66 and earlier)

UniFi Access Intercom Viewer (Version 1.0.5 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.   

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Access G2 Reader Pro Version 1.3.37 or later.

Update UniFi Access Reader Pro Version 2.8.19 or later.

Update UniFi Access Intercom Version 1.1.32 or later.

Update UniFi Access Intercom Viewer Version 1.1.6 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later. 

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29207 | An Improper Certificate Validation could allow a malicious actor with access to an adjacent network to take control of the system. 

 

Affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29207</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation could allow a malicious actor with access to an adjacent network to take control of the system. 

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect Application (Version 3.7.9 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29208 | An Unverified Password Change could allow a malicious actor with API access to the device to change the system password without knowing the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29208</link><description>An Unverified Password Change could allow a malicious actor with API access to the device to change the system password without knowing the previous password.

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33147 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authRoleList function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33147</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authRoleList function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33155 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the getDeptList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33155</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the getDeptList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33161 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the unallocatedList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33161</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the unallocatedList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33859 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. HTML code sent through logs wasn't being escaped in the "Interesting Field" Web UI, leadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33859</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. HTML code sent through logs wasn't being escaped in the "Interesting Field" Web UI, leading to XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33860 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. It allows Local File Inclusion (LFI) when an arbitrary File Path is used within the File S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33860</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. It allows Local File Inclusion (LFI) when an arbitrary File Path is used within the File System Collector. The content of the file specified can be viewed in the incoming logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33857 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. Due to a lack of input validation on URLs in threat intelligence, an attacker with low-lev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33857</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. Due to a lack of input validation on URLs in threat intelligence, an attacker with low-level access to the system can trigger Server Side Request Forgery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33858 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. A path injection vulnerability is seen while adding a CSV enrichment source. The source_na...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33858</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. A path injection vulnerability is seen while adding a CSV enrichment source. The source_name parameter could be changed to an absolute path; this will write the CSV file to that path inside the /tmp directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33856 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. An attacker can enumerate a valid list of usernames by observing the response time at the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33856</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. An attacker can enumerate a valid list of usernames by observing the response time at the Forgot Password endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33146 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the export function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33146</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the export function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33144 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findApplyedTasksPage function in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33144</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findApplyedTasksPage function in BpmTaskMapper.xml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4596 | Kimai Session information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4596</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kimai up to 2.15.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Session Handler. The manipulation of the argument PHPSESSIONID leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. Upgrading to version 2.16.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-263318 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33139 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findpage function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33139</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findpage function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33748 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the search function in MvnRepository MS Basic 2.1.18.3 and earlier.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33748</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the search function in MvnRepository MS Basic 2.1.18.3 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34341 | The Trix Editor Contains an Arbitrary Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34341</link><description>Trix is a rich text editor. The Trix editor, versions prior to 2.1.1, is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution when copying and pasting content from the web or other documents with markup into the editor. The vulnerability stems from improper sanitization of pasted content, allowing an attacker to embed malicious scripts which are executed within the context of the application. Users should upgrade to Trix editor version 2.1.1 or later, which incorporates proper sanitization of input from copied content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32867 | Suricata&amp;#x27;s defrag contains various issues leading to policy bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32867</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to 7.0.5 and 6.0.19, various problems in handling of fragmentation anomalies can lead to mis-detection of rules and policy. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.5 or 6.0.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34523 | AChecker 1.5 allows remote attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files via the download.php path parameter by using Unauthenticated Pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34523</link><description>AChecker 1.5 allows remote attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files via the download.php path parameter by using Unauthenticated Path Traversal. This occurs through readfile in PHP. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32371 | An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a regular user account to escalate their privileges and gain a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32371</link><description>An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a regular user account to escalate their privileges and gain administrative access by changing the type parameter from 1 to 0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32664 | Suricata&amp;#x27;s base64 contains an out of bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32664</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to 7.0.5 and 6.0.19, specially crafted traffic or datasets can cause a limited buffer overflow. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.5 and 6.0.19. Workarounds include not use rules with `base64_decode` keyword with `bytes` option with value 1, 2 or 5 and for 7.0.x, setting `app-layer.protocols.smtp.mime.body-md5` to false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4595 | SEMCMS function.php locate sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SEMCMS up to 4.8 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function locate of the file function.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263317 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32370 | An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32370</link><description>An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the id parameter in the mliSystemUsers.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32663 | Suricata &amp;#x27;s http2 parser contains an improper compressed header handling can lead to resource starvation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32663</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to 7.0.5 and 6.0.19, a small amount of HTTP/2 traffic can lead to Suricata using a large amount of memory. The issue has been addressed in Suricata 7.0.5 and 6.0.19. Workarounds include disabling the HTTP/2 parser and reducing `app-layer.protocols.http2.max-table-size` value (default is 65536).</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32369 | SQL Injection vulnerability in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.18 and earlier allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32369</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.18 and earlier allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the start and limit parameter in the mliWhiteList.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33122 | Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the topic parameter in the list() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33122</link><description>Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the topic parameter in the list() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33120 | Roothub v2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability via the customPath parameter in the upload() function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33120</link><description>Roothub v2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability via the customPath parameter in the upload() function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted JSP file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33124 | Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the nodeTitle parameter in the parentNode() function..</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33124</link><description>Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the nodeTitle parameter in the parentNode() function..</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34342 | react-pdf&amp;#x27;s PDF.js vulnerable to arbitrary JavaScript execution upon opening a malicious PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34342</link><description>react-pdf displays PDFs in React apps. If PDF.js is used to load a malicious PDF, and PDF.js is configured with `isEvalSupported` set to `true` (which is the default value), unrestricted attacker-controlled JavaScript will be executed in the context of the hosting domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.7.3 and 8.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4594 | DedeCMS sys_safe.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4594</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DedeCMS 5.7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/dede/sys_safe.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263316. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34084 | Minder&amp;#x27;s Github Webhook Handler vulnerable to denial of service from un-validated requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34084</link><description>Minder's `HandleGithubWebhook` is susceptible to a denial of service attack from an untrusted HTTP request. The vulnerability exists before the request has been validated, and as such the request is still untrusted at the point of failure. This allows an attacker with the ability to send requests to `HandleGithubWebhook` to crash the Minder controlplane and deny other users from using it. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.0.48.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46012 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability LINKSYS EA7500 3.0.1.207964 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via an HTTP request to the IGD ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46012</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability LINKSYS EA7500 3.0.1.207964 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via an HTTP request to the IGD UPnP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29889 | GLPI contains an SQL injection through the saved searches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29889</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the saved searches feature to alter another user account data take control of it. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31456 | GLPI contains an authenticated SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31456</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability from map search. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33782 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function OTExtensionWithMatrix::extend in /OT/OTExtensionWithMatrix.cpp. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33782</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function OTExtensionWithMatrix::extend in /OT/OTExtensionWithMatrix.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33783 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::SilentMultiPprfReceiver::expand in /Tools/Sile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33783</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::SilentMultiPprfReceiver::expand in /Tools/SilentPprf.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33780 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::copyOut at /Tools/SilentPprf.cpp. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33780</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::copyOut at /Tools/SilentPprf.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33781 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function octetStream::get_bytes in /Tools/octetStream.cpp. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33781</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function octetStream::get_bytes in /Tools/octetStream.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4592 | DedeCMS sys_group_edit.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4592</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in DedeCMS 5.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /src/dede/sys_group_edit.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263314 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4593 | DedeCMS sys_multiserv.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4593</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in DedeCMS 5.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /src/dede/sys_multiserv.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263315. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33434 | An issue in tiagorlampert CHAOS before 1b451cf62582295b7225caf5a7b506f0bad56f6b and 24c9e109b5be34df7b2bce8368eae669c481ed5e allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33434</link><description>An issue in tiagorlampert CHAOS before 1b451cf62582295b7225caf5a7b506f0bad56f6b and 24c9e109b5be34df7b2bce8368eae669c481ed5e allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the unsafe concatenation of the `filename` argument into the `buildStr` string without any sanitization or filtering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28148 | Apache Superset: Incorrect datasource authorization on explore REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28148</link><description>An authenticated user could potentially access metadata for a datasource they are not authorized to view by submitting a targeted REST API request.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4590 | DedeCMS sys_info.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4590</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/sys_info.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263312. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4591 | DedeCMS sys_group_add.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4591</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DedeCMS 5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/dede/sys_group_add.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7240 | Broken Access Control leading to SSRF in NetIQ Identity Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7240</link><description>An improper authorization level has been detected in the login panel. It may lead to
unauthenticated Server Side Request Forgery and allows to perform open services
enumeration. Server makes query to provided server (Server IP/DNS field) and is
triggering connection to arbitrary address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4536 | Eclipse EDC: OAuth2 Credential Exfiltration Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4536</link><description>In Eclipse Dataspace Components from version 0.2.1 to 0.6.2, in the EDC Connector component ( https://github.com/eclipse-edc/Connector ), an attacker might obtain OAuth2 client secrets from the vault.

In Eclipse Dataspace Components from version 0.2.1 to 0.6.2, we have identified a security vulnerability in the EDC Connector component ( https://github.com/eclipse-edc/Connector ) regarding the OAuth2-protected data sink feature. When using a custom, OAuth2-protected data sink, the OAuth2-specific data address properties are resolved by the provider data plane. Problematically, the consumer-provided clientSecretKey, which indicates the OAuth2 client secret to retrieve from a secrets vault, is resolved in the context of the provider's vault, not the consumer. This secret's value is then sent to the tokenUrl, also consumer-controlled, as part of an OAuth2 client credentials grant. The returned access token is then sent as a bearer token to the data sink URL.

This feature is now disabled entirely, because not all code paths necessary for a successful realization were fully implemented.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31234 | WordPress Tilda Publishing plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.23 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31234</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tilda Publishing.This issue affects Tilda Publishing: from n/a through 0.3.23.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4588 | DedeCMS mytag_add.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4588</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/dede/mytag_add.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4589 | DedeCMS mytag_edit.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4589</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/mytag_edit.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263311. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4586 | DedeCMS shops_delivery.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4586</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DedeCMS 5.7 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /src/dede/shops_delivery.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263308. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4587 | DedeCMS tpl.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4587</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /src/dede/tpl.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263309 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4585 | DedeCMS member_type.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4585</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DedeCMS 5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/dede/member_type.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263307. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4537 | IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4537</link><description>IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software affecting version 4.3r10. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to obtain the download URL of another user to obtain the purchased ticket.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4538 | IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4538</link><description>IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software affecting version 4.3r10. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to obtain a user's event ticket by creating a specific request with the ticket reference ID, leading to the exposure of sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4584 | Faraday GM8181/GM828x command_port.ini information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4584</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Faraday GM8181 and GM828x up to 20240429. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /command_port.ini. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263306 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4601 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Socomec Net Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4601</link><description>An incorrect authentication vulnerability has been found in Socomec Net Vision affecting version 7.20. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a brute force attack on the application and recover a valid session, because the application uses a five-digit integer value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4600 | Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Socomec Net Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4600</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Socomec Net Vision, version 7.20. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to trick registered users into performing critical actions, such as adding and updating accounts, due to lack of proper sanitisation of the ‘set_param.cgi’ file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4582 | Faraday GM8181/GM828x NTP Service os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4582</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Faraday GM8181 and GM828x up to 20240429. Affected is an unknown function of the component NTP Service. The manipulation of the argument ntp_srv leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263304.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4583 | Faraday GM8181/GM828x Request information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Faraday GM8181 and GM828x up to 20240429. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Request Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-263305 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4599 | Denial of service vulnerability in LAN Messenger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4599</link><description>Remote denial of service vulnerability in LAN Messenger affecting version 3.4.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to crash the LAN Messenger service by sending a long string directly and continuously over the UDP protocol.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6810 | The ClickCease Click Fraud Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to an improper capability check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6810</link><description>The ClickCease Click Fraud Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to an improper capability check on the get_settings function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author access and above, to retrieve the plugin's configured API keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4345 | The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4345</link><description>The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'process' function in the 'startklarDropZoneUploadProcess' class in versions up to, and including, 1.7.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4346 | The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.13. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4346</link><description>The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.13. This is due to the plugin not properly validating the path of an uploaded file prior to deleting it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, including the wp-config.php file, which can make site takeover and remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23808 | Arkcompiler ets frontend has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23808</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free or cause DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27217 | MSDP has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27217</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31078 | Bluetooth Service has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31078</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause service crash through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3757 | Arkcompiler runtime has an integer  overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3757</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause service crash through integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3758 | Hmdfs has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3758</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in TCB through heap buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3759 | Hmdfs has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3759</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in TCB through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3628 | EasyEvent &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3628</link><description>The EasyEvent WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4186 | The Build App Online plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.5. This is due to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4186</link><description>The Build App Online plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.5. This is due to the 'eb_user_email_verification_key' default value is empty, and the not empty check is missing in the 'eb_user_email_verify' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id. This can only be exploited if the 'Email Verification' setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22472 | Long S0 frames received by 500 series Z-Wave devices may cause buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22472</link><description>A buffer Overflow vulnerability in Silicon Labs 500 Series Z-Wave devices may allow Denial of Service, and potential Remote Code execution

This issue affects all versions of Silicon Labs 500 Series SDK prior to v6.85.2

running on Silicon Labs 500 series Z-wave devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20855 | Improper access control vulnerability in multitasking framework prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access unlocked...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20855</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in multitasking framework prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access unlocked screen for a while.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20821 | A vulnerability possible to reconfigure OTP allows local attackers to transit RMA(Return Merchandise Authorization) mode, which disables sec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20821</link><description>A vulnerability possible to reconfigure OTP allows local attackers to transit RMA(Return Merchandise Authorization) mode, which disables security features. This attack needs additional privilege to control TEE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20856 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Secure Folder prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access Secure Folder wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20856</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Secure Folder prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access Secure Folder without proper authentication in a specific scenario.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20857 | Improper access control vulnerability in startListening of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20857</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in startListening of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access information of current application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20858 | Improper access control vulnerability in setCocktailHostCallbacks of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20858</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in setCocktailHostCallbacks of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access information of current application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20859 | Improper access control vulnerability in FactoryCamera prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to take pictures without privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20859</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in FactoryCamera prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to take pictures without privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20860 | Improper export of android application components vulnerability in TelephonyUI prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to reb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20860</link><description>Improper export of android application components vulnerability in TelephonyUI prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to reboot the device without proper permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20861 | Use after free vulnerability in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20861</link><description>Use after free vulnerability in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20862 | Out-of-bounds write in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20862</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20863 | Out of bounds write vulnerability in SNAP in HAL prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20863</link><description>Out of bounds write vulnerability in SNAP in HAL prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20864 | Improper access control vulnerability in DarManagerService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to monitor system resource...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20864</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in DarManagerService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to monitor system resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20865 | Authentication bypass in bootloader prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to flash arbitrary images.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20865</link><description>Authentication bypass in bootloader prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to flash arbitrary images.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20866 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in Setupwizard prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to skip activation step.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20866</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in Setupwizard prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to skip activation step.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20867 | Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.91.14 allows local attackers to access sensitive informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20867</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.91.14 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20868 | Improper input validation in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.15 allows local attackers to delete files with Samsung Notes privilege under...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20868</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.15 allows local attackers to delete files with Samsung Notes privilege under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20869 | Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Internet prior to version 25.0.0.41 allows local attackers to bypass protection for c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20869</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Internet prior to version 25.0.0.41 allows local attackers to bypass protection for cookies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20870 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.71.8 allows local attackers to writ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20870</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.71.8 allows local attackers to write arbitrary files with the privilege of Galaxy Store.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20871 | Improper authorization vulnerability in Samsung Keyboard prior to version One UI 5.1.1 allows physical attackers to partially bypass the fac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20871</link><description>Improper authorization vulnerability in Samsung Keyboard prior to version One UI 5.1.1 allows physical attackers to partially bypass the factory reset protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20872 | Improper handling of insufficient privileges vulnerability in TalkbackSE prior to version Android 14 allows local attackers to modify settin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20872</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient privileges vulnerability in TalkbackSE prior to version Android 14 allows local attackers to modify setting value of TalkbackSE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>