<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:40:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-13084 | Opto 22 groov View Exposure of Sensitive Information Through Metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13084</link><description>The users endpoint in the groov View API returns a list of all users and
 associated metadata including their API keys. This endpoint requires an
 Editor role to access and will display API keys for all users, 
including Administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2486 | UEFI Shell accessible in AAVMF with Secure Boot enabled on Ubuntu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2486</link><description>The Ubuntu edk2 UEFI firmware packages accidentally allowed the UEFI Shell to be accessed in Secure Boot environments, possibly allowing bypass of Secure Boot constraints. Versions 2024.05-2ubuntu0.3 and 2024.02-2ubuntu0.3 disable the Shell. Some previous versions inserted a secure-boot-based decision to continue running inside the Shell itself, which is believed to be sufficient to enforce Secure Boot restrictions. This is an additional repair on top of the incomplete fix for CVE-2023-48733.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65236 | OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Session ID parameter in the /occ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65236</link><description>OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Session ID parameter in the /occontrolpanel/index.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65235 | OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 Version 6.13.11 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the ID parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65235</link><description>OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 Version 6.13.11 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the ID parameter in the getSubUsersByProvider function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65237 | A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Jav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65237</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65238 | Incorrect access control in the getSubUsersByProvider function of OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 Version 6.13.11 allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65238</link><description>Incorrect access control in the getSubUsersByProvider function of OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release: 5 Version 6.13.11 allows attackers with low-level privileges to dump user records and access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46175 | Ruoyi v4.8.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. There is a missing checkUserDataScope permission check in the authRole method of Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46175</link><description>Ruoyi v4.8.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. There is a missing checkUserDataScope permission check in the authRole method of SysUserController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63938 | Tinyproxy through 1.11.2 contains an integer overflow vulnerability in the strip_return_port() function within src/reqs.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63938</link><description>Tinyproxy through 1.11.2 contains an integer overflow vulnerability in the strip_return_port() function within src/reqs.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65239 | Incorrect access control in the /aux1/ocussd/trace endpoint of OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release:5, version 6.13.11 allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65239</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /aux1/ocussd/trace endpoint of OpenCode Systems USSD Gateway OC Release:5, version 6.13.11 allows attackers with low-level privileges to read server logs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46174 | Ruoyi v4.8.0 vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. There is a missing checkUserDataScope permission check in the resetPwd Method of SysUse...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46174</link><description>Ruoyi v4.8.0 vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. There is a missing checkUserDataScope permission check in the resetPwd Method of SysUserController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56396 | An issue was discovered in Ruoyi 4.8.1 allowing attackers to gain escalated privileges due to the owning department having higher rights tha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56396</link><description>An issue was discovered in Ruoyi 4.8.1 allowing attackers to gain escalated privileges due to the owning department having higher rights than the active user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50402 | FAST FAC1200R F400_FAC1200R_Q is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function sub_80435780 via the parameter string fac_password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50402</link><description>FAST FAC1200R F400_FAC1200R_Q is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function sub_80435780 via the parameter string fac_password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45311 | Insecure permissions in fail2ban-client v0.11.2 allows attackers with limited sudo privileges to perform arbitrary operations as root.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45311</link><description>Insecure permissions in fail2ban-client v0.11.2 allows attackers with limited sudo privileges to perform arbitrary operations as root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50399 | FAST FAC1200R F400_FAC1200R_Q is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function sub_80435780 via the parameter password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50399</link><description>FAST FAC1200R F400_FAC1200R_Q is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function sub_80435780 via the parameter password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62354 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('command injection') in Cursor allows an unauthorized attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62354</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('command injection') in Cursor allows an unauthorized attacker to execute commands that are outside of those specified in the allowlist, resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13601 | Glib: integer overflow in in g_escape_uri_string()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13601</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow problem was found in glib through an incorrect calculation of buffer size in the g_escape_uri_string() function. If the string to escape contains a very large number of unacceptable characters (which would need escaping), the calculation of the length of the escaped string could overflow, leading to a potential write off the end of the newly allocated string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 14:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9163 | Houzez &amp;lt;= 4.1.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9163</link><description>The Houzez theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping in the houzez_property_img_upload() and houzez_property_attachment_upload() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9191 | Houzez &amp;lt;= 4.1.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection via Saved Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9191</link><description>The Houzez theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.6 via deserialization of untrusted input in saved-search-item.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13674 | Access of Uninitialized Pointer in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13674</link><description>BPv7 dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59390 | Apache Druid: Kerberos authenticaton chooses a cryptographically unsecure secret if not configured explicitly.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59390</link><description>Apache Druid’s Kerberos authenticator uses a weak fallback secret when the `druid.auth.authenticator.kerberos.cookieSignatureSecret` configuration is not explicitly set. In this case, the secret is generated using `ThreadLocalRandom`,
 which is not a crypto-graphically secure random number generator. This 
may allow an attacker to predict or brute force the secret used to sign 
authentication cookies, potentially enabling token forgery or 
authentication bypass. Additionally, each process generates its own 
fallback secret, resulting in inconsistent secrets across nodes. This 
causes authentication failures in distributed or multi-broker 
deployments, effectively leading to a incorrectly configured clusters. Users are 
advised to configure a strong `druid.auth.authenticator.kerberos.cookieSignatureSecret`



This issue affects Apache Druid: through 34.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 35.0.0, which fixes the issue making it mandatory to set `druid.auth.authenticator.kerberos.cookieSignatureSecret` when using the Kerberos authenticator. Services will fail to come up if the secret is not set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62728 | Apache Hive: SQL injection vulnerability when processing delete column statistics requests via the HMS Thrift APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62728</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Hive Metastore Server (HMS) when processing delete column statistics requests via the Thrift APIs. The vulnerability is only exploitable by trusted/authorized users/applications that are allowed to call directly the Thrift APIs. In most real-world deployments, HMS is accessible to only a handful of applications (e.g., Hiveserver2) thus the vulnerability is not exploitable. Moreover, the vulnerable code cannot be reached when metastore.try.direct.sql property is set to false.

This issue affects Apache Hive: from 4.1.0 before 4.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.2.0, which fixes the issue. Users who cannot upgrade directly are encouraged to set metastore.try.direct.sql property to false if the HMS Thrift APIs are exposed to general public.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13735 | Out-of-bounds Read in nr flc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13735</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in ASR1903、ASR3901 in ASR Lapwing_Linux on Linux (nr_fw modules). This vulnerability is associated with program files Code/nr_fw/DLP/src/NrCgi.C.

This issue affects Lapwing_Linux: before 2025/11/26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 06:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12061 | Tax Service Electronic HDM &amp;lt; 1.2.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary SQL Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12061</link><description>The TAX SERVICE Electronic HDM WordPress plugin before 1.2.1 does not authorization and CSRF checks in an AJAX action, allowing unauthenticated users to import and execute arbitrary SQL statements</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 06:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59820 | In KDE Krita before 5.2.13, loading a manipulated TGA file could result in a heap-based buffer overflow in plugins/impex/tga/kis_tga_import....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59820</link><description>In KDE Krita before 5.2.13, loading a manipulated TGA file could result in a heap-based buffer overflow in plugins/impex/tga/kis_tga_import.cpp (aka KisTgaImport). Control flow proceeds even when a number of pixels becomes negative.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 05:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9557 | Bluetooth: Mesh: Out-of-Bound Write in gen_prov_cont</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9557</link><description>‭An out-of-bound write can lead to an arbitrary code execution. Even on devices with some form of memory protection, this can still lead to‬ ‭a crash and a resultant denial of service.‬</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 05:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9558 | Bluetooth: Mesh: Out-of-Bound Write in gen_prov_start</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9558</link><description>There is a potential OOB Write vulnerability in the gen_prov_start function in pb_adv.c. The full length of the received data is copied into the link.rx.buf receiver buffer without any validation on the data size.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 05:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55174 | In KDE Skanpage before 25.08.0, an attempt at file overwrite can result in the contents of the new file at the beginning followed by the par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55174</link><description>In KDE Skanpage before 25.08.0, an attempt at file overwrite can result in the contents of the new file at the beginning followed by the partial contents of the old file at the end, because of use of QIODevice::ReadWrite instead of QODevice::WriteOnly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 05:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64983 | Smart Video Doorbell firmware versions prior to 2.01.078 contain an active debug code vulnerability that allows an attacker to connect via T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64983</link><description>Smart Video Doorbell firmware versions prior to 2.01.078 contain an active debug code vulnerability that allows an attacker to connect via Telnet and gain access to the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 04:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66022 | FACTION Unauthenticated Custom Extension Upload leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66022</link><description>FACTION is a PenTesting Report Generation and Collaboration Framework. Prior to version 1.7.1, an extension execution path in Faction’s extension framework permits untrusted extension code to execute arbitrary system commands on the server when a lifecycle hook is invoked, resulting in remote code execution (RCE) on the host running Faction. Due to a missing authentication check on the /portal/AppStoreDashboard endpoint, an attacker can access the extension management UI and upload a malicious extension without any authentication, making this vulnerability exploitable by unauthenticated users. This issue has been patched in version 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 03:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66025 | Caido Improperly Handles External Links in Markdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66025</link><description>Caido is a web security auditing toolkit. Prior to version 0.53.0, the Markdown renderer used in Caido’s Findings page improperly handled user-supplied Markdown, allowing attacker-controlled links to be rendered without confirmation. When a user opened a finding generated through the scanner, or other plugins, clicking these injected links could redirect the Caido application to an attacker-controlled domain, enabling phishing style attacks. This issue has been patched in version 0.53.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 03:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66026 | REDAXO is Vulnerable to Reflected XSS in Mediapool Info Banner via args[types]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66026</link><description>REDAXO is a PHP-based CMS. Prior to version 5.20.1, a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Mediapool view where the request parameter args[types] is rendered into an info banner without HTML-escaping. This allows arbitrary JavaScript execution in the backend context when an authenticated user visits a crafted link while logged in. This issue has been patched in version 5.20.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 03:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12848 | XSS vulnerability when rendering filename in Webform Multiform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12848</link><description>Webform Multiple File Upload module for Drupal 7.x contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the file name renderer. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by uploading a file with a malicious
filename containing JavaScript code (e.g., "&lt;img src="1" /&gt;") to a Webform node with a Multifile field where file type validation is disabled. This allows the execution of arbitrary scripts
in the context of the victim's browser.
 
The issue is present in a third-party library and has been addressed in a patch available at  https://github.com/fyneworks/multifile/pull/44 . Users are advised to apply the provided patch or update to a fixed version of the module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66020 | Valibot has a ReDoS vulnerability in `EMOJI_REGEX`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66020</link><description>Valibot helps validate data using a schema. In versions from 0.31.0 to 1.1.0, the EMOJI_REGEX used in the emoji action is vulnerable to a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) attack. A short, maliciously crafted string (e.g., &lt;100 characters) can cause the regex engine to consume excessive CPU time (minutes), leading to a Denial of Service (DoS) for the application. This issue has been patched in version 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66021 | OWASP Java HTML Sanitizer is vulnerable to XSS via noscript tag and improper style tag sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66021</link><description>OWASP Java HTML Sanitizer is a configureable HTML Sanitizer written in Java, allowing inclusion of HTML authored by third-parties in web applications while protecting against XSS. In version 20240325.1,  OWASP java html sanitizer is vulnerable to XSS if HtmlPolicyBuilder allows noscript and style tags with allowTextIn inside the style tag. This could lead to XSS if the payload is crafted in such a way that it does not sanitise the CSS and allows tags which is not mentioned in HTML policy. At time of publication no known patch is available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66266 | Insecure SYSTEM Service Permissions in UPSilon2000V6.0 (RupsMon.exe) leading to trivial Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66266</link><description>The RupsMon.exe service executable in UPSilon 2000 has insecure permissions, allowing the 'Everyone' group Full Control. A local attacker can replace the executable with a malicious binary to execute code with SYSTEM privileges or simply change the config path of the service to a command; starting and stopping the service to immediately achieve code execution and privilege escalation</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66269 | Unquoted Service Path in UPSilon2000V6.0(RupsMon and USBMate) running as SYSTEM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66269</link><description>The RupsMon and USBMate services in UPSilon 2000 run with SYSTEM privileges and contain unquoted service paths. This allows a local attacker to perform path interception and escalate privileges if they have write permissions to the directories proceeding that of which the real service executables live in</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66258 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting via XML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66258</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting via XML Injection in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Stored XSS via crafted filenames injected into patchlist.xml.
User-controlled filenames are directly concatenated into `patchlist.xml` without encoding, allowing injection of malicious JavaScript payloads via crafted filenames (e.g., `&lt;img src="x" /&gt;.bin`). The XSS executes when ajax.js processes and renders the XML file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66259 | Authenticated Root Remote Code Execution through improper filtering of HTTP post request parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66259</link><description>Authenticated Root Remote Code Execution via improrer user input filtering in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform in main_ok.php user supplied data/hour/time is passed directly into date shell command</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66260 | PostgreSQL SQL Injection (status_sql.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66260</link><description>PostgreSQL SQL Injection (status_sql.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform SQL injection via sw1 and sw2 parameters in status_sql.php.
The `status_sql.php` endpoint constructs SQL UPDATE queries by directly concatenating user-controlled `sw1` and `sw2` parameters without using parameterized queries or `pg_escape_string()`. While PostgreSQL's `pg_exec` limitations prevent stacked queries, attackers can inject subqueries for data exfiltration and leverage verbose error messages for reconnaissance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66261 | Unauthenticated OS Command Injection (restore_settings.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66261</link><description>Unauthenticated OS Command Injection (restore_settings.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform URL-decoded name parameter passed to exec() allows remote code execution.
The `/var/tdf/restore_settings.php` endpoint passes user-controlled `$_GET["name"]` parameter through `urldecode()` directly into `exec()` without validation or escaping. Attackers can inject arbitrary shell commands using metacharacters (`;`, `|`, `&amp;&amp;`, etc.) to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution as the web server user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66262 | Arbitrary File Overwrite via Tar Extraction Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66262</link><description>Arbitrary File Overwrite via Tar Extraction Path Traversal in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Tar extraction with -C / allow arbitrary file overwrite via crafted archive.
The `restore_mozzi_memories.sh` script extracts user-controlled tar archives with `-C /` flag, depositing contents to the filesystem root without path validation. When combined with the unauthenticated file upload vulnerabilities (CVE-01, CVE-06, CVE-07), attackers can craft malicious .tgz archives containing path-traversed filenames (e.g., `etc/shadow`, `var/www/index.php`) to overwrite critical system files in writable directories, achieving full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66263 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Null Byte Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66263</link><description>Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Null Byte Injection in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Null byte injection in download_setting.php allows reading arbitrary files.
The `/var/tdf/download_setting.php` endpoint constructs file paths by concatenating user-controlled `$_GET['filename']` with a forced `.tgz` extension. Running on PHP 5.3.2 (pre-5.3.4), the application is vulnerable to null byte injection (%00), allowing attackers to bypass the extension restriction and traverse paths. By requesting `filename=../../../../etc/passwd%00`, the underlying C functions treat the null byte as a string terminator, ignoring the appended `.tgz` and enabling unauthenticated arbitrary file disclosure of any file readable by the web server user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66264 | Unquoted Service path in UPSilon2000V6.0 SYSTEM privilege service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66264</link><description>The CMService.exe service runs with SYSTEM privileges and contains an unquoted service path. This allows a local attacker with write privileges to the filesystem to insert a malicious executable in the path, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66265 | Insecure permissions in configuration directory (C:\\usr)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66265</link><description>CMService.exe creates the C:\\usr directory and subdirectories with insecure permissions, granting write access to all authenticated users. This allows attackers to replace configuration files (such as snmp.conf) or hijack DLLs to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66250 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload (status_contents.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66250</link><description>Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload (status_contents.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Allows unauthenticated arbitrary file upload via /var/tdf/status_contents.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66251 | Unauthenticated Path Traversal with Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66251</link><description>Unauthenticated Path Traversal with Arbitrary File Deletion in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform The deletehidden parameter allows path traversal deletion of arbitrary .tgz files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66252 | Infinite Loop Denial of Service via Failed File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66252</link><description>Infinite Loop Denial of Service via Failed File Deletion in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Infinite loop when unlink() fails in status_contents.php causing DoS. Due to the fact that the unlink operation is done in a while loop; if an immutable file is specified or otherwise a file in which the process has no permissions to delete; it would repeatedly attempt to do in a loop.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66253 | Unauthenticated OS Command Injection (start_upgrade.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66253</link><description>Unauthenticated OS Command Injection (start_upgrade.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform User input passed directly to exec() allows remote code execution via start_upgrade.php. The `/var/tdf/start_upgrade.php` endpoint passes user-controlled `$_GET["filename"]` directly into `exec()` without sanitization or shell escaping. Attackers can inject arbitrary shell commands using metacharacters (`;`, `|`, etc.) to achieve remote code execution as the web server user (likely root).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66254 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion (upgrade_contents.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66254</link><description>Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion (upgrade_contents.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform The deleteupgrade parameter allows unauthenticated deletion of arbitrary files. 

The `deleteupgrade` parameter in `/var/www/upgrade_contents.php` allows unauthenticated deletion of arbitrary files in `/var/www/upload/` without any extension restriction or path sanitization, enabling attackers to remove critical system files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66255 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload (upgrade_contents.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66255</link><description>Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload (upgrade_contents.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Missing signature validation allows uploading malicious firmware packages. 
The firmware upgrade endpoint in `upgrade_contents.php` accepts arbitrary file uploads without validating file headers, cryptographic signatures, or enforcing .tgz format requirements, allowing malicious firmware injection. This endpoint also subsequently provides ways for arbitrary file uploads and subsequent remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66256 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload (patch_contents.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66256</link><description>Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload (patch_contents.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform Unrestricted file upload in patch_contents.php allows uploading malicious files.

The `/var/tdf/patch_contents.php` endpoint allows unauthenticated arbitrary file uploads without file type validation, MIME checking, or size restrictions beyond 16MB, enabling attackers to upload malicious files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66257 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion (patch_contents.php)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66257</link><description>Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion (patch_contents.php) in DB Electronica Telecomunicazioni S.p.A. Mozart FM Transmitter versions 30, 50, 100, 300, 500, 1000, 2000, 3000, 3500, 6000, 7000 allows an attacker to perform The deletepatch parameter allows unauthenticated deletion of arbitrary files.
The `deletepatch` parameter in `patch_contents.php` allows unauthenticated deletion of arbitrary files in `/var/www/patch/` directory without sanitization or access control checks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64656 | Azure Application Gateway Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64656</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64657 | Azure Application Gateway Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64657</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 02:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65963 | CFiles Unauthorized Folder/ZIP Access in Public Spaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65963</link><description>Files is a module for managing files inside spaces and user profiles. Prior to versions 0.16.11 and 0.17.2, insufficient authorization checks allow non-member users to create new folders, up- and download files as a ZIP archive in public spaces. Private spaces are not affected. This issue has been patched in versions 0.16.11 and 0.17.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66019 | pypdf manipulated LZWDecode streams can exhaust RAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66019</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to version 6.4.0, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to a memory usage of up to 1 GB per stream. This requires parsing the content stream of a page using the LZWDecode filter. This issue has been patched in version 6.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65957 | Core Bot is Leaking Sensitive Credentials in Logs, Errors, and Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65957</link><description>Core Bot Is an Open Source discord bot made for maple hospital servers. Prior to commit dffe050, the API keys (SUPABASE_API_KEY, TOKEN) are loaded using environment variables, but there are cases in code (error handling, summaries, webhooks) where configuration summaries may inadvertently leak sensitive data (e.g., by failing to redact data in summary embeds or logs). This issue has been patched via commit dffe050.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65956 | Formwork CMS Has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Blog Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65956</link><description>Formwork is a flat file-based Content Management System (CMS). Prior to version 2.2.0, inserting unsanitized data into the blog tag field results in stored cross‑site scripting (XSS). Any user with credentials to the Formwork CMS who accesses or edits an affected blog post will have attacker‑controlled script executed in their browser. The issue is persistent and impacts privileged administrative workflows. This issue has been patched in version 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65953 | NanoMQ UAF of retain message due to invalid MQTTV5 properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65953</link><description>NanoMQ MQTT Broker (NanoMQ) is an all-around Edge Messaging Platform. Prior to version 0.22.5, a Heap-Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability exists in the TCP transport component of NanoMQ, which relies on the underlying NanoNNG library (specifically in src/sp/transport/mqtt/broker_tcp.c). The vulnerability is due to improper resource management and premature cleanup of message and pipe structures under specific malformed MQTTV5 retain message traffic conditions. This issue has been patched in version 0.22.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65952 | Console is vulnerable to path traversal regarding custom assets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65952</link><description>Console is a network used to control Gorilla Tag mods' users and other users on the network. Prior to version 2.8.0, a path traversal vulnerability exists where complicated combinations of backslashes and periods can be used to escape the Gorilla Tag path and write to unwanted directories. This issue has been patched in version 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13595 | CIBELES AI &amp;lt;= 1.10.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13595</link><description>The CIBELES AI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing capability check in the 'actualizador_git.php' file in all versions up to, and including, 1.10.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary GitHub repositories and overwrite plugin files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13597 | AI Feeds &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13597</link><description>The AI Feeds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing capability check in the 'actualizador_git.php' file in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary GitHub repositories and overwrite plugin files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65942 | VictoriaMetrics Snappy Decoder DoS Vulnerability is Causing OOM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65942</link><description>VictoriaMetrics is a scalable solution for monitoring and managing time series data. In versions from 1.0.0 to before 1.110.23, from 1.111.0 to before 1.122.8, and from 1.123.0 to before 1.129.1, affected versions are vulnerable to DoS attacks because the snappy decoder ignored VictoriaMetrics request size limits allowing malformed blocks to trigger excessive memory use. This could lead to OOM errors and service instability. The fix enforces block-size checks based on MaxRequest limits. This issue has been patched in versions 1.110.23, 1.122.8, and 1.129.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64704 | WebAssembly Micro Runtime vulnerable to a segmentation fault in v128.store instruction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64704</link><description>WebAssembly Micro Runtime (WAMR) is a lightweight standalone WebAssembly (Wasm) runtime. Prior to version 2.4.4, WAMR is susceptible to a segmentation fault in v128.store instruction. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64713 | WebAssembly Micro Runtime frame_offset_bottom array bounds overflow in fast Interpreter mode when handling GET_GLOBAL(I32) followed by if opcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64713</link><description>WebAssembly Micro Runtime (WAMR) is a lightweight standalone WebAssembly (Wasm) runtime. Prior to version 2.4.4, an out-of-bounds array access issue exists in WAMR's fast interpreter mode during WASM bytecode loading. When frame_ref_bottom and frame_offset_bottom arrays are at capacity and a GET_GLOBAL(I32) opcode is encountered, frame_ref_bottom is expanded but frame_offset_bottom may not be. If this is immediately followed by an if opcode that triggers preserve_local_for_block, the function traverses arrays using stack_cell_num as the upper bound, causing out-of-bounds access to frame_offset_bottom since it wasn't expanded to match the increased stack_cell_num. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21621 | GeoServer Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WMS GetFeatureInfo HTML format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21621</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. Prior to version 2.25.0, a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the WMS GetFeatureInfo HTML output format that enables a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in a victim's browser through specially crafted SLD_BODY parameters. This issue has been patched in version 2.25.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62703 | Fugue is Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution by Pickle Deserialization via FlaskRPCServer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62703</link><description>Fugue is a unified interface for distributed computing that lets users execute Python, Pandas, and SQL code on Spark, Dask, and Ray with minimal rewrites. In version 0.9.2 and prior, there is a remote code execution vulnerability by pickle deserialization via FlaskRPCServer. The Fugue framework implements an RPC server system for distributed computing operations. In the core functionality of the RPC server implementation, I found that the _decode() function in fugue/rpc/flask.py directly uses cloudpickle.loads() to deserialize data without any sanitization. This creates a remote code execution vulnerability when malicious pickle data is processed by the RPC server. The vulnerability exists in the RPC communication mechanism where the client can send arbitrary serialized Python objects that will be deserialized on the server side, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code on the victim's machine. This issue has been patched via commit 6f25326.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63735 | A reflected Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Ruckus Unleashed 200.13.6.1.319 via the name parameter to the the captive-portal end...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63735</link><description>A reflected Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Ruckus Unleashed 200.13.6.1.319 via the name parameter to the the captive-portal endpoint selfguestpass/guestAccessSubmit.jsp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51741 | An issue was discovered in Veal98 Echo Open-Source Community System 2.2 thru 2.3 allowing an unauthenticated attacker to cause the server to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51741</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veal98 Echo Open-Source Community System 2.2 thru 2.3 allowing an unauthenticated attacker to cause the server to send email verification messages to arbitrary users via the /sendEmailCodeForResetPwd endpoint potentially causing a denial of service to the server or the downstream users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 21:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51743 | An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /materialCategory/addMaterialCategory endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserializ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51743</link><description>An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /materialCategory/addMaterialCategory endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51744 | An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /user/addUser endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51744</link><description>An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /user/addUser endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51745 | An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /role/addcan endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51745</link><description>An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /role/addcan endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51746 | An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /serialNumber/addSerialNumber endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51746</link><description>An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /serialNumber/addSerialNumber endpoint is vulnerable to fastjson deserialization attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58360 | GeoServer is vulnerable to an Unauthenticated XML External Entities (XXE) attack via WMS GetMap feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58360</link><description>GeoServer is an open source server that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. From version 2.26.0 to before 2.26.2 and before 2.25.6, an XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability was identified. The application accepts XML input through a specific endpoint /geoserver/wms operation GetMap. However, this input is not sufficiently sanitized or restricted, allowing an attacker to define external entities within the XML request. This issue has been patched in GeoServer 2.25.6, GeoServer 2.26.3, and GeoServer 2.27.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66017 | CGGMP21 presignatures can be used in the way that significantly reduces security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66017</link><description>CGGMP24 is a state-of-art ECDSA TSS protocol that supports 1-round signing (requires 3 preprocessing rounds), identifiable abort, and a key refresh protocol. In versions 0.6.3 and prior of cggmp21 and version 0.7.0-alpha.1 of cggmp24, presignatures can be used in the way that significantly reduces security. cggmp24 version 0.7.0-alpha.2 release contains API changes that make it impossible to use presignatures in contexts in which it reduces security.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51742 | An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /material/getMaterialEnableSerialNumberList endpoint passes the search query parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51742</link><description>An issue was discovered in jishenghua JSH_ERP 2.3.1. The /material/getMaterialEnableSerialNumberList endpoint passes the search query parameter directly to parseObject(), introducing a Fastjson deserialization vulnerability that can lead to RCE via JDBC payloads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66016 | CGGMP24 is missing a check in the ZK proof used in CGGMP21</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66016</link><description>CGGMP24 is a state-of-art ECDSA TSS protocol that supports 1-round signing (requires 3 preprocessing rounds), identifiable abort, and a key refresh protocol. Prior to version 0.6.3, there is a missing check in the ZK proof that enables an attack in which single malicious signer can reconstruct full private key. This issue has been patched in version 0.6.3, for full mitigation it is recommended to upgrade to cggmp24 version 0.7.0-alpha.2 as it contains more security checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65647 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in the Track order function in PHPGURUKUL Online Shopping Portal 2.1 allows information disclosure v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65647</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in the Track order function in PHPGURUKUL Online Shopping Portal 2.1 allows information disclosure via the oid parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9624 | OpenSearch 3.2.0 - Nested Boolean/Disjunction asymmetric DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9624</link><description>A vulnerability in OpenSearch allows attackers to cause Denial of Service (DoS) by submitting complex query_string inputs.



This issue affects all OpenSearch versions below 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65965 | Grype has a credential disclosure vulnerability in Grype JSON output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65965</link><description>Grype is a vulnerability scanner for container images and filesystems. A credential disclosure vulnerability was found in Grype, affecting versions 0.68.0 through 0.104.0. If registry credentials are defined and the output of grype is written using the --file or --output json= option, the registry credentials will be included unsanitized in the output file. This issue has been patched in version 0.104.1. Users running affected versions of grype can work around this vulnerability by redirecting stdout to a file instead of using the --file or --output options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12816 | CVE-2025-12816</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12816</link><description>An interpretation-conflict (CWE-436) vulnerability in node-forge versions 1.3.1 and earlier enables unauthenticated attackers to craft ASN.1 structures to desynchronize schema validations, yielding a semantic divergence that may bypass downstream cryptographic verifications and security decisions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34350 | UnForm Server &amp;lt; 10.1.15 Doc Flow Unauthenticated File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34350</link><description>UnForm Server versions &lt; 10.1.15 contain an unauthenticated arbitrary file read and SMB coercion vulnerability in the Doc Flow feature’s 'arc' endpoint. The Doc Flow module uses the 'arc' handler to retrieve and render pages or resources specified by the user-supplied 'pp' parameter, but it does so without enforcing authentication or restricting path inputs. As a result, an unauthenticated remote attacker can supply local filesystem paths to read arbitrary files accessible to the service account. On Windows deployments, providing a UNC path can also coerce the server into initiating outbound SMB authentication, potentially exposing NTLM credentials for offline cracking or relay. This issue may lead to sensitive information disclosure and, in some environments, enable further lateral movement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65961 | Contao is vulnerable to cross-site scripting in templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65961</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. From version 4.0.0 to before 4.13.57, before 5.3.42, and before 5.6.5, it is possible to inject code into the template output that will be executed in the browser in the front end and back end. This issue has been patched in versions 4.13.57, 5.3.42, and 5.6.5. A workaround for this issue involves not using the affected templates or patch them manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65960 | Contao is vulnerable to remote code execution in template closures</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65960</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. From version 4.0.0 to before 4.13.57, before 5.3.42, and before 5.6.5, back end users with precise control over the contents of template closures can execute arbitrary PHP functions that do not have required parameters. This issue has been patched in versions 4.13.57, 5.3.42, and 5.6.5. A workaround for this issue involves manually patching the Contao\Template::once() method.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61167 | SIGB PMB v8.0.1.14 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in the /opac_css/ajax_selector.php component via the id ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61167</link><description>SIGB PMB v8.0.1.14 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in the /opac_css/ajax_selector.php component via the id and datas parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61168 | An issue in the cms_rest.php component of SIGB PMB v8.0.1.14 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via unserializing an arbitrary file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61168</link><description>An issue in the cms_rest.php component of SIGB PMB v8.0.1.14 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via unserializing an arbitrary file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64067 | Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 API endpoints responsible for retrieving object-specific or filtered data (e.g., user profiles, project records) f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64067</link><description>Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 API endpoints responsible for retrieving object-specific or filtered data (e.g., user profiles, project records) fail to implement sufficient server-side validation to confirm that the requesting user is authorized to access the requested object or dataset. This vulnerability can be exploited in two ways: Direct ID manipulation and IDOR, by changing an ID parameter (e.g., user_id, project_id) in the request, an attacker can access the object and data belonging to another user; and filter Omission, by omitting the filtering parameter entirely, an attacker can cause the endpoint to return an entire unfiltered dataset of all stored records for all users. This flaw leads to the unauthorized exposure of sensitive personal and organizational information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64063 | Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 API endpoints fail to enforce sufficient authorization checks when processing requests. Specifically, a standard u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64063</link><description>Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 API endpoints fail to enforce sufficient authorization checks when processing requests. Specifically, a standard user can exploit this flaw by sending direct HTTP requests to administrative endpoints, bypassing the UI restrictions. This allows the attacker to manipulate data outside their assigned scope, including: Unauthorized Account modification, modifying/deleting arbitrary user accounts and changing passwords by sending a direct request to the user management API endpoint; Confidential Data Access, accessing and downloading sensitive organizational documents via a direct request to the document retrieval API; Privilege escalation, This vulnerability can lead to complete compromise of data integrity and confidentiality, and Privilege Escalation by manipulating core system functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64064 | Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 /api/v2/pp_users endpoint fails to adequately check user permissions before processing a PATCH request to modify t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64064</link><description>Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 /api/v2/pp_users endpoint fails to adequately check user permissions before processing a PATCH request to modify the PP_SECURITY_PROFILE_ID. Because of weak access controls any low level user can use this API and change their permission to Administrator by using PP_SECURITY_PROFILE_ID=2 inside body of request and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64065 | The Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 API /api/V2/pp_udfv_admin endpoint, fails to perform necessary server-side validation. The administrative Logi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64065</link><description>The Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 API /api/V2/pp_udfv_admin endpoint, fails to perform necessary server-side validation. The administrative LoginAs or user impersonation feature is vulnerable to a access control failure. This flaw allows any authenticated low-privileged user to execute a direct PATCH request, enabling them to impersonate any other arbitrary user, including application Administrators. This is due to a Broken Function Level Authorization failure (the function doesn't check the caller's privilege) compounded by an Insecure Design that permits a session switch without requiring the target user's password or an administrative token and only needs email of user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33197 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a NULL pointer dereference. A successful exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33197</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a NULL pointer dereference. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33198 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a resource to be reused. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33198</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a resource to be reused. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33199 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause incorrect control flow behavior. A successfu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33199</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause incorrect control flow behavior. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33200 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a resource to be reused. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33200</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a resource to be reused. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33203 | NVIDIA NeMo Agent Toolkit UI for Web contains a vulnerability in the chat API endpoint where an attacker may cause a Server-Side Request For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33203</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Agent Toolkit UI for Web contains a vulnerability in the chat API endpoint where an attacker may cause a Server-Side Request Forgery. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33204 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP and LLM components, where malicious data created by an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33204</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP and LLM components, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33205 | NVIDIA NeMo framework contains a vulnerability in a predefined variable, where an attacker could cause inclusion of functionality from an un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33205</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo framework contains a vulnerability in a predefined variable, where an attacker could cause inclusion of functionality from an untrusted control sphere by use of a predefined variable. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64062 | The Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 /api/V2/pp_users?email endpoint is used for user data filtering but lacks proper server-side validation agains...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64062</link><description>The Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 /api/V2/pp_users?email endpoint is used for user data filtering but lacks proper server-side validation against the authenticated session. By manipulating the email parameter to an arbitrary value (e.g., otheruser@user.com), an attacker can assume the session and gain full access to the target user's data and privileges. Also, if the email parameter is left blank, the application defaults to the first user in the list, who is typically the application administrator, resulting in an immediate Privilege Escalation to the highest level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33187 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT, where an attacker could use privileged access to gain access to SoC protected areas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33187</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT, where an attacker could use privileged access to gain access to SoC protected areas. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, data tampering, denial of service, or escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33188 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in hardware resources where an attacker could tamper with hardware controls. A successful exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33188</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in hardware resources where an attacker could tamper with hardware controls. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33189 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause an out-of-bound write. A successful exploit ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33189</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause an out-of-bound write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, data tampering, denial of service, information disclosure, or escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33190 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware where an attacker could cause an out-of-bound write. A successful exploit o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33190</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware where an attacker could cause an out-of-bound write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, data tampering, denial of service, or escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33191 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in OSROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause an invalid memory read. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33191</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in OSROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause an invalid memory read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33192 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause an arbitrary memory read. A successful explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33192</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause an arbitrary memory read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33193 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause improper validation of integrity. A successf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33193</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause improper validation of integrity. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33194 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause improper processing of input data. A success...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33194</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause improper processing of input data. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33195 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause unexpected memory buffer operations. A succe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33195</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause unexpected memory buffer operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering, denial of service, or escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33196 | NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a resource to be reused. A successful exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33196</link><description>NVIDIA DGX Spark GB10 contains a vulnerability in SROOT firmware, where an attacker could cause a resource to be reused. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64066 | Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 REST /api/v2/user/register endpoint suffers from a Broken Access Control vulnerability. The endpoint fails to impl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64066</link><description>Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 REST /api/v2/user/register endpoint suffers from a Broken Access Control vulnerability. The endpoint fails to implement any authorization checks, allowing unauthenticated attackers to perform POST requests to register new user accounts in the application's local database. This bypasses the intended security architecture, which relies on an external Identity Provider for initial user registration and assumes that internal user creation is an administrative-only function. This vector can also be chained with other vulnerabilities for privilege escalation and complete compromise of application. This specific request can be used to also enumerate already registered user accounts, aiding in social engineering or further targeted attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65084 | Out-of-bounds Write in Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, Cobalt Share</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65084</link><description>An Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability is present in Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, and Cobalt Share versions 12.6.1204.207 and prior that could allow an attacker to disclose information or execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65085 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow in Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, Cobalt Share</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65085</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability is present in Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, and Cobalt Share versions 12.6.1204.207 and prior that could allow an attacker to disclose information or execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13483 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in SiRcom SMART Alert (SiSA)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13483</link><description>SiRcom SMART Alert (SiSA) allows unauthorized access to backend APIs. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass the login screen using browser developer tools, gaining access to restricted parts of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64061 | Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 /api/v2/users endpoint is vulnerable to unauthorized data exposure due to deficient access control mechanisms. Any...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64061</link><description>Primakon Pi Portal 1.0.18 /api/v2/users endpoint is vulnerable to unauthorized data exposure due to deficient access control mechanisms. Any authenticated user, regardless of their privilege level (including standard or low-privileged users), can make a GET request to this endpoint and retrieve a complete, unfiltered list of all registered application users. Crucially, the API response body for this endpoint includes password hashes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63729 | An issue was discovered in Syrotech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT SYRO_3.7L_3.1.02-240517 allowing attackers to exctract the SSL Private Key, CA Certif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63729</link><description>An issue was discovered in Syrotech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT SYRO_3.7L_3.1.02-240517 allowing attackers to exctract the SSL Private Key, CA Certificate, SSL Certificate, and Client Certificates in .pem format in firmware in etc folder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13467 | Org.keycloak.storage.ldap: keycloak: deserialization of untrusted data in ldap user federation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13467</link><description>A flaw was found in the Keycloak LDAP User Federation provider. This vulnerability allows an authenticated realm administrator to trigger deserialization of untrusted Java objects via a malicious LDAP server configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60739 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version v4.7.18.0.eden and before, Logic Version v6.00 - 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60739</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version v4.7.18.0.eden and before, Logic Version v6.00 - 2025_07_21 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /bh_web_backend component</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40890 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Dashboards in Guardian/CMC before 25.4.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40890</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability was discovered in the Dashboards functionality due to improper validation of an input parameter.



An authenticated low-privilege user can craft a malicious dashboard containing a JavaScript payload and share it with victim users, or a victim can be socially engineered to import a malicious dashboard template. When the victim views or imports the dashboard, the XSS executes in their browser context, allowing the attacker to perform unauthorized actions as the victim, such as modify application data, disrupt application availability, and access limited sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64049 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the module management component in REDAXO CMS 5.20.0 allows remote users to inject arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64049</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the module management component in REDAXO CMS 5.20.0 allows remote users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Output code field in modules. The payload is executed when a user views or edits an article by adding slice that uses the compromised module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64050 | A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the template management component in REDAXO CMS 5.20.0 allows remote authenticated administra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64050</link><description>A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the template management component in REDAXO CMS 5.20.0 allows remote authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary operating system commands by injecting PHP code into an active template. The payload is executed when visitors access frontend pages using the compromised template.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0248 | HCL iNotes is susceptible to a Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0248</link><description>HCL iNotes is susceptible to a Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused by improper validation of user-supplied input. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can specially craft a URL to execute script in a victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting Web site and/or steal the victim's cookie-based authentication credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36134 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36134</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5 and 6.2.1.1 could disclose sensitive information due to a missing or insecure SameSite attribute for a sensitive cookie.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 14:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13502 | Webkit: webkitgtk / wpe webkit: out-of-bounds read and integer underflow vulnerability leading to dos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13502</link><description>A flaw was found in WebKitGTK and WPE WebKit. This vulnerability allows an out-of-bounds read and integer underflow, leading to a UIProcess crash (DoS) via a crafted payload to the GLib remote inspector server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 08:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12003 | A path traversal vulnerability has been identified in WebDAV, which may allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the integrity of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12003</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been identified in WebDAV, which may allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the integrity of the device.
Refer to the ' Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12025 | YouTube Subscribe &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Title and Channel ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12025</link><description>The YouTube Subscribe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12032 | ZWeb - Social Mobile &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12032</link><description>The Zweb Social Mobile – Ứng Dụng Nút Gọi Mobile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘vithanhlam_zsocial_save_messager’, 'vithanhlam_zsocial_save_zalo', 'vithanhlam_zsocial_save_hotline', and 'vithanhlam_zsocial_save_contact' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12040 | Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Wishlist Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12040</link><description>The Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 via several functions in class-th-wishlist-frontend.php due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify other user's wishlists</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12043 | Autochat Automatic Conversation &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12043</link><description>The Autochat Automatic Conversation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_auycht_saveCid' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to connect and disconnect the client ID.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12525 | Locker Content &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12525</link><description>The Locker Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in version 1.0.0 via the 'lockerco_submit_post' AJAX endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract content from posts that has been protected by the plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12586 | Conditional Maintenance Mode for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12586</link><description>The Conditional Maintenance Mode for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation when toggling the maintenance mode status. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable or disable the site's maintenance mode via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12587 | Peer Publish &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12587</link><description>The Peer Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the website management pages. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete website configurations via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12634 | Refund Request for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Refund Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12634</link><description>The Refund Request for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_refund_status' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update refund statuses to approved or rejected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12645 | Inline frame – Iframe &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12645</link><description>The Inline frame – Iframe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'embedsite' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13311 | Just Highlight &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Highlight Color&amp;#x27; Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13311</link><description>The Just Highlight plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Highlight Color' setting in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the plugin's settings page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13370 | ProjectList &amp;lt;= 0.3.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13370</link><description>The ProjectList plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13376 | ProjectList &amp;lt;= 0.3.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13376</link><description>The ProjectList plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13380 | AI Engine for WordPress: ChatGPT, GPT Content Generator &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13380</link><description>The AI Engine for WordPress: ChatGPT, GPT Content Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied file paths in the 'lqdai_update_post' AJAX endpoint and the use of file_get_contents() with user-controlled URLs without protocol restrictions in the insert_image() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13382 | Frontend File Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 23.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Renaming</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13382</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 23.4. This is due to the plugin not validating file ownership before processing file rename requests in the '/wpfm/v1/file-rename' REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to rename files uploaded by other users via the 'fileid' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13383 | Job Board by BestWebSoft &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via $_GET Array Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13383</link><description>The Job Board by BestWebSoft plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This is due to the plugin storing the entire unsanitized `$_GET` superglobal array directly into the database via `update_user_meta()` when users save search results, and later outputting this data without proper escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute whenever a user accesses the saved search or views their profile, granted they can trick the user into performing the search and saving the results.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13385 | Bookme &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;filter[status]&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13385</link><description>The Bookme – Free Online Appointment Booking and Scheduling Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the `filter[status]` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with admin-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13386 | Social Images Widget &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Settings Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13386</link><description>The Social Images Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'options_update' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13389 | Admin and Customer Messages After Order for WooCommerce: OrderConvo &amp;lt;= 14 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13389</link><description>The Admin and Customer Messages After Order for WooCommerce: OrderConvo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the `get_order_by_id()` function in all versions up to, and including, 14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view sensitive WooCommerce order details and private conversation messages between customers and store administrators for any order by supplying an arbitrary order ID.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13404 | atec Duplicate Page &amp;amp; Post &amp;lt;= 1.2.20 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Duplication and Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13404</link><description>The atec Duplicate Page &amp; Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post duplication due to missing authorization validation on the duplicate_post() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.20. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to duplicate arbitrary posts, including private and password-protected posts, leading to data exposure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13405 | Ace Post Type Builder &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Custom Taxonomy Deletion via &amp;#x27;taxonomy&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13405</link><description>The Ace Post Type Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized custom taxonomy deletion due to missing authorization validation on the cptb_delete_custom_taxonomy() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary custom taxonomies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13414 | Chamber Dashboard Business Directory &amp;lt;= 3.3.11 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Business Information Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13414</link><description>The Chamber Dashboard Business Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data export due to a missing capability check on the cdash_watch_for_export() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export business directory information, including sensitive business details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13452 | Admin and Customer Messages After Order for WooCommerce: OrderConvo &amp;lt;= 14 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated User Impersonation in Order Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13452</link><description>The Admin and Customer Messages After Order for WooCommerce: OrderConvo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 14. This is due to a flawed permission check in the REST API permission callback that returns true when no nonce is provided. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to impersonate any WordPress user and inject arbitrary messages into any WooCommerce order conversation by directly calling the REST endpoint with controlled user_id, order_id, and context parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59365 | A stack buffer overflow vulnerability has been identified in certain router models. An authenticated attacker may trigger this vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59365</link><description>A stack buffer overflow vulnerability has been identified in certain router models. An authenticated attacker may trigger this vulnerability by sending a crafted request, potentially impacting the availability of the device. 
Refer to the ' Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59366 | An authentication-bypass vulnerability exists in AiCloud. This vulnerability can be triggered by an unintended side effect of the Samba func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59366</link><description>An authentication-bypass vulnerability exists in AiCloud. This vulnerability can be triggered by an unintended side effect of the Samba functionality, potentially leading to allow execution of specific functions without proper authorization.


Refer to the Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59368 | An integer underflow vulnerability has been identified in Aicloud. An authenticated attacker may trigger this vulnerability by sending a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59368</link><description>An integer underflow vulnerability has been identified in Aicloud. An authenticated attacker may trigger this vulnerability by sending a crafted request, potentially impacting the availability of the device. 
Refer to the ' Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59369 | A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in bwdpi. A remote, authenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59369</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in bwdpi. A remote, authenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to potentially execute arbitrary SQL queries, leading to unauthorized data access. 
Refer to the 'Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59370 | A command injection vulnerability has been identified in bwdpi. A remote, authenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59370</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been identified in bwdpi. A remote, authenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to potentially execute arbitrary commands, leading to the device executing unintended instructions.
Refer to the 'Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59371 | An authentication bypass vulnerability has been identified in the IFTTT integration feature. A remote, authenticated attacker could leverage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59371</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability has been identified in the IFTTT integration feature. A remote, authenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to potentially gain unauthorized access to the device. This vulnerability does not affect Wi-Fi 7 series models.
Refer to the 'Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59372 | A path traversal vulnerability has been identified in certain router models. A remote, authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59372</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been identified in certain router models. A remote, authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to write files outside the intended directory, potentially affecting device integrity.
Refer to the 'Security Update for ASUS Router Firmware' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59485 | Incorrect default permissions issue exists in Security Point (Windows) of MaLion prior to Ver.5.3.4. If this vulnerability is exploited, an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59485</link><description>Incorrect default permissions issue exists in Security Point (Windows) of MaLion prior to Ver.5.3.4. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary file could be placed in the specific folder by a user who can log in to the system where the product's Windows client is installed. If the file is a specially crafted DLL file, arbitrary code could be executed with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62691 | Security Point (Windows) of MaLion and MaLionCloud contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in processing HTTP headers. Receivin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62691</link><description>Security Point (Windows) of MaLion and MaLionCloud contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in processing HTTP headers. Receiving a specially crafted request from a remote unauthenticated attacker could lead to arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64693 | Security Point (Windows) of MaLion and MaLionCloud contains a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in processing Content-Length. Receivi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64693</link><description>Security Point (Windows) of MaLion and MaLionCloud contains a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in processing Content-Length. Receiving a specially crafted request from a remote unauthenticated attacker could lead to arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 07:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12742 | Remote Code Execution in Looker via Teradata JDBC Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12742</link><description>A Looker user with a Developer role could cause Looker to execute a malicious command, due to insecure processing of Teradata driver parameters.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.108+
  *  24.18.200+
  *  25.0.78+
  *  25.6.65+
  *  25.8.47+
  *  25.12.10+
  *  25.14+</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 05:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13644 | MongoDB may be susceptible to Invariant Failure due to batched delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13644</link><description>MongoDB Server may experience an invariant failure during batched delete operations when handling documents. The issue arises when the server mistakenly assumes the presence of multiple documents in a batch based solely on document size exceeding BSONObjMaxSize. This issue affects MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.26, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.13, and MongoDB Server v8.1 versions prior to 8.1.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 05:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13643 | MongoDB Server may allow queries to be terminated by unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13643</link><description>A user with access to the cluster with a limited set of privilege actions may be able to terminate queries that are being executed by other users. This may cause a denial of service by preventing a fraction of queries from successfully completing. This issue affects MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.26 and MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.14</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 05:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12893 | Improper Certificate Validation May Allow Successful TLS Handshaking Despite Invalid Extended Key Usage Fields in MongoDB Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12893</link><description>Clients may successfully perform a TLS handshake with a MongoDB server despite presenting a client certificate not aligning with the documented Extended Key Usage (EKU) requirements. A certificate that specifies extendedKeyUsage but is missing extendedKeyUsage = clientAuth may still be successfully authenticated via the TLS handshake as a client. This issue is specific to MongoDB servers running on Windows or Apple as the expected validation behavior functions correctly on Linux systems.

Additionally, MongoDB servers may successfully establish egress TLS connections with servers that present server certificates not aligning with the documented Extended Key Usage (EKU) requirements. A certificate that specifies extendedKeyUsage but is missing extendedKeyUsage = serverAuth may still be successfully authenticated via the TLS handshake as a server. This issue is specific to MongoDB servers running on Apple as the expected validation behavior functions correctly on both Linux and Windows systems. 

This vulnerability affects MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.26, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.16 and MongoDB Server v8.2 versions prior to 8.2.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 05:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13507 | Time-series operations may cause internal BSON size limit to be exceed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13507</link><description>Inconsistent object size validation in time series processing logic may result in later processing of oversized BSON documents leading to an assert failing and process termination. 
This issue impacts MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.26, v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.16 and MongoDB server v8.2 versions prior to 8.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13068 | Telegram Bot &amp;amp; Channel &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Telegram Username</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13068</link><description>The Telegram Bot &amp; Channel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Telegram username in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13558 | Blog2Social &amp;lt;= 8.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Trashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13558</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'deleteUserCcDraftPost' function in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the status of arbitrary posts to trash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13559 | EduKart Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13559</link><description>The EduKart Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the 'edukart_pro_register_user_front_end' function not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62497 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W versions prior to Ver.2.8.0. If a user accesses a specially crafted webpage wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62497</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W versions prior to Ver.2.8.0. If a user accesses a specially crafted webpage while logged in, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64730 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W all versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64730</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W all versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64304 | "FOD" App uses hard-coded cryptographic keys, which may allow a local unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the cryptographic keys.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64304</link><description>"FOD" App uses hard-coded cryptographic keys, which may allow a local unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the cryptographic keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10646 | Search Exclude &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 – Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Search Settings Modification via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10646</link><description>The Search Exclude plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a insufficient capability check on the Base::get_rest_permission() method in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to modify plugin settings, such as adding arbitrary posts to the search exclusion list.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 03:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6389 | Sneeit Framework &amp;lt;= 8.3 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution in sneeit_articles_pagination_callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6389</link><description>The Sneeit Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 8.3 via the sneeit_articles_pagination_callback() function. This is due to the function accepting user input and then passing that through call_user_func(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server which can be leveraged to inject backdoors or, for example, create new administrative user accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 03:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59373 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in 

 the restore mechanism of 

ASUS System Control Interface. It can be triggered when a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59373</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in 

 the restore mechanism of 

ASUS System Control Interface. It can be triggered when an unprivileged actor copies files without proper validation into protected system paths, potentially leading to arbitrary files being executed as SYSTEM.
For more information, please refer to section Security Update for MyAsus in the ASUS Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 03:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64761 | OpenBao Privileged Operator Identity Group Root Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64761</link><description>OpenBao is an open source identity-based secrets management system. Prior to version 2.4.4, a privileged operator could use the identity group subsystem to add a root policy to a group identity group, escalating their or another user's permissions in the system. Specifically this is an issue when: an operator in the root namespace has access to identity/groups endpoints and an operator does not have policy access. Otherwise, an operator with policy access could create or modify an existing policy to grant root-equivalent permissions through the sudo capability. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65944 | Sentry-Javascript deals with leaked sensitive headers when `sendDefaultPii` is set to `true`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65944</link><description>Sentry-Javascript is an official Sentry SDKs for JavaScript. From version 10.11.0 to before 10.27.0, when a Node.js application using the Sentry SDK has sendDefaultPii: true it is possible to inadvertently send certain sensitive HTTP headers, including the Cookie header, to Sentry. Those headers would be stored within a Sentry organization as part of the associated trace. A person with access to the Sentry organization could then view and use these sensitive values to impersonate or escalate their privileges within the application. This issue has been patched in version 10.27.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65951 | Inside Track / Entropy Derby Timelock Encryption Bypassed via Pre-Computed VDF Output Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65951</link><description>Inside Track / Entropy Derby is a research-grade horse-racing betting engine. Prior to commit 2d38d2f, the VDF-based timelock encryption system fails to enforce sequential delay against the betting operator. Bettors pre-compute the entire Wesolowski VDF and include vdfOutputHex in their encrypted bet ticket, allowing the house to decrypt immediately using fast proof verification instead of expensive VDF evaluation. This issue has been patched via commit 2d38d2f.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9803 | Improper Authentication in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9803</link><description>lunary-ai/lunary version 1.9.34 is vulnerable to an account takeover due to improper authentication in the Google OAuth integration. The application fails to verify the 'aud' (audience) field in the access token issued by Google, which is crucial for ensuring the token is intended for the application. This oversight allows attackers to use tokens issued to malicious applications to gain unauthorized access to user accounts. The issue is resolved in version 1.9.35.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62155 | QuantumNous New API Has SSRF Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62155</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. Prior to version 0.9.6, a recently patched SSRF vulnerability contains a bypass method that can bypass the existing security fix and still allow SSRF to occur.
Because the existing fix only applies security restrictions to the first URL request, a 302 redirect can bypass existing security measures and successfully access the intranet. This issue has been patched in version 0.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65018 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow in `png_combine_row` triggered via `png_image_finish_read`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65018</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From version 1.6.0 to before 1.6.51, there is a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the libpng simplified API function png_image_finish_read when processing 16-bit interlaced PNGs with 8-bit output format. Attacker-crafted interlaced PNG files cause heap writes beyond allocated buffer bounds. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64720 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a buffer overflow in `png_image_read_composite` via incorrect palette premultiplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64720</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From version 1.6.0 to before 1.6.51, an out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in png_image_read_composite when processing palette images with PNG_FLAG_OPTIMIZE_ALPHA enabled. The palette compositing code in png_init_read_transformations incorrectly applies background compositing during premultiplication, violating the invariant component ≤ alpha × 257 required by the simplified PNG API. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64505 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow in `png_do_quantize` via malformed palette index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64505</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. Prior to version 1.6.51, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in libpng's png_do_quantize function when processing PNG files with malformed palette indices. The vulnerability occurs when palette_lookup array bounds are not validated against externally-supplied image data, allowing an attacker to craft a PNG file with out-of-range palette indices that trigger out-of-bounds memory access. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64506 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a heap buffer over-read in `png_write_image_8bit` with grayscale+alpha or RGB/RGBA images</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64506</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From version 1.6.0 to before 1.6.51, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in libpng's png_write_image_8bit function when processing 8-bit images through the simplified write API with convert_to_8bit enabled. The vulnerability affects 8-bit grayscale+alpha, RGB/RGBA, and images with incomplete row data. A conditional guard incorrectly allows 8-bit input to enter code expecting 16-bit input, causing reads up to 2 bytes beyond allocated buffer boundaries. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10144 | Perfect Brands for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10144</link><description>The Perfect Brands for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the `brands` attribute of the `products` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47856 | In RSA Authentication Agent before 7.4.7, service paths and shortcut paths may be vulnerable to path interception if the path has one or mor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47856</link><description>In RSA Authentication Agent before 7.4.7, service paths and shortcut paths may be vulnerable to path interception if the path has one or more spaces and is not surrounded by quotation marks. An adversary can place an executable in a higher-level directory of the path, and Windows will resolve that executable instead of the intended executable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54338 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54338</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows an attacker to disclose user hashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54341 | A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There are Hard-coded configurati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54341</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There are Hard-coded configuration values.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54563 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54563</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows Incorrect Access Control, leading to Remote Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63674 | An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.1227.472.2926 allows local physical attackers to execute arbitrary code via overriding t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63674</link><description>An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.1227.472.2926 allows local physical attackers to execute arbitrary code via overriding the bootloader on the SD card.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54347 | A Directory Traversal vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54347</link><description>A Directory Traversal vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows an attacker to write arbitrary files under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29933 | Improper input validation within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to write out of bounds, potentially resulting in a crash or denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29933</link><description>Improper input validation within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to write out of bounds, potentially resulting in a crash or denial of service</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48511 | Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to write to an arbitrary physical address, potentially resulting in cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48511</link><description>Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to write to an arbitrary physical address, potentially resulting in crash or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48510 | Improper return value within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to bypass KSLR, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48510</link><description>Improper return value within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to bypass KSLR, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52538 | Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52538</link><description>Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25126 | TVT NVMS-9000 Hard-coded API Credentials &amp;amp; Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25126</link><description>Shenzhen TVT Digital Technology Co., Ltd. NVMS-9000 firmware (used by many white-labeled DVR/NVR/IPC products) contains hardcoded API credentials and an OS command injection flaw in its configuration services. The web/API interface accepts HTTP/XML requests authenticated with a fixed vendor credential string and passes user-controlled fields into shell execution contexts without proper argument sanitization. An unauthenticated remote attacker can leverage the hard-coded credential to access endpoints such as /editBlackAndWhiteList and inject shell metacharacters inside XML parameters, resulting in arbitrary command execution as root. The same vulnerable backend is also reachable in some models through a proprietary TCP service on port 4567 that accepts a magic GUID preface and base64-encoded XML, enabling the same command injection sink. Firmware releases from mid-February 2018 and later are reported to have addressed this issue. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-01-28 UTC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7330 | Ruijie Networks NBR Routers Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via fileupload.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7330</link><description>Ruijie NBR series routers contain an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability via /ddi/server/fileupload.php. The endpoint accepts attacker-supplied values in the name and uploadDir parameters and saves the provided multipart file content without adequate validation or sanitization of file type, path, or extension. A remote attacker can upload a crafted PHP file and then access it from the web root, resulting in arbitrary code execution in the context of the web service. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-01-14 UTC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14007 | TVT NVMS-9000 &amp;lt; 1.3.4 Unauthenticated Administrative Queries &amp;amp; Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14007</link><description>Shenzhen TVT Digital Technology Co., Ltd. NVMS-9000 firmware (used by many white-labeled DVR/NVR/IPC products) versions prior to 1.3.4 contain an authentication bypass in the NVMS-9000 control protocol. By sending a single crafted TCP payload to an exposed NVMS-9000 control port, an unauthenticated remote attacker can invoke privileged administrative query commands without valid credentials. Successful exploitation discloses sensitive information including administrator usernames and passwords in cleartext, network and service configuration, and other device details via commands such as queryBasicCfg, queryUserList, queryEmailCfg, queryPPPoECfg, and queryFTPCfg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0003 | Inadequate lock protection within Xilinx Run time may allow a local attacker to trigger a Use-After-Free condition potentially resulting in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0003</link><description>Inadequate lock protection within Xilinx Run time may allow a local attacker to trigger a Use-After-Free condition potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availability</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0007 | Insufficient validation within Xilinx Run Time framework could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges from user space to kernel space...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0007</link><description>Insufficient validation within Xilinx Run Time framework could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges from user space to kernel space, potentially compromising confidentiality, integrity, and/or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36150 | IBM Concert Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36150</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63498 | alinto SOGo 5.12.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "userName" parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63498</link><description>alinto SOGo 5.12.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "userName" parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56400 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the OAuth implementation of the Tuya SDK 6.5.0 for Android and iOS, affects the Tuya Smar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56400</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the OAuth implementation of the Tuya SDK 6.5.0 for Android and iOS, affects the Tuya Smart and Smartlife mobile applications, as well as other third-party applications that integrate the SDK, allows an attacker to link their own Amazon Alexa account to a victim's Tuya account. The applications fail to validate the OAuth state parameter during the account linking flow, enabling a cross-site request forgery (CSRF)-like attack. By tricking the victim into clicking a crafted authorization link, an attacker can complete the OAuth flow on the victim's behalf, resulting in unauthorized Alexa access to the victim's Tuya-connected devices. This affects users regardless of prior Alexa linkage and does not require the Tuya application to be active at the time. Successful exploitation may allow remote control of devices such as cameras, doorbells, door locks, or alarms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0005 | Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0005</link><description>Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting in crash or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64048 | YCCMS 3.4 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the article management functionality. The vulnerability exists in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64048</link><description>YCCMS 3.4 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the article management functionality. The vulnerability exists in the add() and getPost() functions within the ArticleAction.class.php file due to improper neutralization of user input in the article title field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52539 | A buffer overflow with Xilinx Run Time Environment may allow a local attacker to read or corrupt data from the advanced extensible interface...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52539</link><description>A buffer overflow with Xilinx Run Time Environment may allow a local attacker to read or corrupt data from the advanced extensible interface (AXI), potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality, integrity, and/or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64047 | OpenRapid RapidCMS 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /user/user-move.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64047</link><description>OpenRapid RapidCMS 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /user/user-move.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63914 | An issue was discovered in Cinnamon kotaemon 0.11.0. The _may_extract_zip function in the \libs\ktem\ktem\index\file\ui.py file does not che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63914</link><description>An issue was discovered in Cinnamon kotaemon 0.11.0. The _may_extract_zip function in the \libs\ktem\ktem\index\file\ui.py file does not check the contents of uploaded ZIP files. Although the contents are extracted into a temporary folder that is cleared before each extraction, successfully uploading a ZIP bomb could still cause the server to consume excessive resources during decompression. Moreover, if no further files are uploaded afterward, the extracted data could occupy disk space and potentially render the system unavailable. Anyone with permission to upload files can carry out this attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13466 | body-parser vulnerable to denial of service when url encoding is used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13466</link><description>body-parser 2.2.0 is vulnerable to denial of service due to inefficient handling of URL-encoded bodies with very large numbers of parameters. An attacker can send payloads containing thousands of parameters within the default 100KB request size limit, causing elevated CPU and memory usage. This can lead to service slowdown or partial outages under sustained malicious traffic.
This issue is addressed in version 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36112 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36112</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5 and 6.2.1.1 could reveal sensitive server IP configuration information to an unauthorized user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13609 | Keylime: keylime: registrar allows identity takeover via duplicate uuid registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13609</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in keylime where an attacker can exploit this flaw by registering a new agent using a different Trusted Platform Module (TPM) device but claiming an existing agent's unique identifier (UUID). This action overwrites the legitimate agent's identity, enabling the attacker to impersonate the compromised agent and potentially bypass security controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63434 | The update mechanism in Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is insecure. The application downloads and extracts up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63434</link><description>The update mechanism in Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is insecure. The application downloads and extracts update packages containing executable code without performing a cryptographic integrity or authenticity check on their contents. An attacker who can control the update metadata can serve a malicious package, which the application will accept, extract, and later execute, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63435 | Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 is Missing Authentication for Critical Function. The server-side endpoint responsible fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63435</link><description>Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 is Missing Authentication for Critical Function. The server-side endpoint responsible for serving update packages for the application does not require any authentication. This allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to freely download official update packages..</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63432 | Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is Missing SSL Certificate Validation. The application fails to properly valid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63432</link><description>Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is Missing SSL Certificate Validation. The application fails to properly validate the TLS certificate from its update server. An attacker on the same network can exploit this vulnerability by performing a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack to intercept, decrypt, and modify traffic between the application and the update server. This serves as the basis for further attacks, including Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63433 | Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior uses a hardcoded cryptographic key and IV to decrypt update metadata. The key ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63433</link><description>Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior uses a hardcoded cryptographic key and IV to decrypt update metadata. The key is stored as a static value within the application's code. An attacker with the ability to intercept network traffic can use this hardcoded key to decrypt, modify, and re-encrypt the update manifest, allowing them to direct the application to download a malicious update package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63958 | MILLENSYS Vision Tools Workspace 6.5.0.2585 exposes a sensitive configuration endpoint (/MILLENSYS/settings) that is accessible without auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63958</link><description>MILLENSYS Vision Tools Workspace 6.5.0.2585 exposes a sensitive configuration endpoint (/MILLENSYS/settings) that is accessible without authentication. This page leaks plaintext database credentials, file share paths, internal license server configuration, and software update parameters. An unauthenticated attacker can retrieve this information by accessing the endpoint directly, potentially leading to full system compromise. The vulnerability is due to missing access controls on a privileged administrative function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63952 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /mwapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63952</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /mwapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily create accounts via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63953 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /usapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63953</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /usapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily create accounts via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40213 | Bluetooth: MGMT: fix crash in set_mesh_sync and set_mesh_complete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40213</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: MGMT: fix crash in set_mesh_sync and set_mesh_complete

There is a BUG: KASAN: stack-out-of-bounds in set_mesh_sync due to
memcpy from badly declared on-stack flexible array.

Another crash is in set_mesh_complete() due to double list_del via
mgmt_pending_valid + mgmt_pending_remove.

Use DEFINE_FLEX to declare the flexible array right, and don't memcpy
outside bounds.

As mgmt_pending_valid removes the cmd from list, use mgmt_pending_free,
and also report status on error.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60638 | An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Nnssf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60638</link><description>An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Nnssf_NSSAIAvailability API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60632 | An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Npcf_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60632</link><description>An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Npcf_BDTPolicyControl API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60633 | An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via the Nudm_SubscriberDataManagement...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60633</link><description>An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via the Nudm_SubscriberDataManagement API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60917 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60917</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the color parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10554 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Requirements in ENOVIA Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10554</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Requirements in ENOVIA Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10555 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Service Items Management in DELMIA Service Process Engineer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10555</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Service Items Management in DELMIA Service Process Engineer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60915 | An issue in the size query parameter (/views/file.py) of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60915</link><description>An issue in the size query parameter (/views/file.py) of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to execute a path traversal via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60916 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60916</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the charge parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44018 | A firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in the OTA Update functionality of GL-Inet GL-AXT1800 4.7.0. A specially crafted .tar file can lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44018</link><description>A firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in the OTA Update functionality of GL-Inet GL-AXT1800 4.7.0. A specially crafted .tar file can lead to a firmware downgrade. An attacker can perform a man-in-the-middle attack to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56401 | ZIRA Group WBRM 7.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in referenceLookupsByTableNameAndColumnName.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56401</link><description>ZIRA Group WBRM 7.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in referenceLookupsByTableNameAndColumnName.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56423 | An issue in Austrian Academy of Sciences (AW) Austrian Archaeological Institute OpenAtlas v.8.12.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56423</link><description>An issue in Austrian Academy of Sciences (AW) Austrian Archaeological Institute OpenAtlas v.8.12.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the login error messages</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60914 | Incorrect access control in Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60914</link><description>Incorrect access control in Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via sending a crafted GET request to the /display_logo endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12969 | CVE-2025-12969</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12969</link><description>Fluent Bit in_forward input plugin does not properly enforce the security.users authentication mechanism under certain configuration conditions. This allows remote attackers with network access to the Fluent Bit instance exposing the forward input to send unauthenticated data. By bypassing authentication controls, attackers can inject forged log records, flood alerting systems, or manipulate routing decisions, compromising the authenticity and integrity of ingested logs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12970 | CVE-2025-12970</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12970</link><description>The extract_name function in Fluent Bit in_docker input plugin copies container names into a fixed size stack buffer without validating length. An attacker who can create containers or control container names, can supply a long name that overflows the buffer, leading to process crash or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12972 | CVE-2025-12972</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12972</link><description>Fluent Bit out_file plugin does not properly sanitize tag values when deriving output file names. When the File option is omitted, the plugin uses untrusted tag input to construct file paths. This allows attackers with network access to craft tags containing path traversal sequences that cause Fluent Bit to write files outside the intended output directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12977 | CVE-2025-12977</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12977</link><description>Fluent Bit in_http, in_splunk, and in_elasticsearch input plugins fail to sanitize tag_key inputs. An attacker with network access or the ability to write records into Splunk or Elasticsearch can supply tag_key values containing special characters such as newlines or ../ that are treated as valid tags. Because tags influence routing and some outputs derive filenames or contents from tags, this can allow newline injection, path traversal, forged record injection, or log misrouting, impacting data integrity and log routing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12978 | CVE-2025-12978</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12978</link><description>Fluent Bit in_http, in_splunk, and in_elasticsearch input plugins contain a flaw in the tag_key validation logic that fails to enforce exact key-length matching. This allows crafted inputs where a tag prefix is incorrectly treated as a full match. A remote attacker with authenticated or exposed access to these input endpoints can exploit this behavior to manipulate tags and redirect records to unintended destinations. This compromises the authenticity of ingested logs and can allow injection of forged data, alert flooding and routing manipulation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11921 | iStat Menus 7.10.4 - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11921</link><description>iStats contains an insecure XPC service that allows local, unprivileged users to escalate their privileges to root via command injection.This issue affects iStats: 7.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65493 | NULL pointer dereference in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65493</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS/TLS connection that triggers BIO_get_data() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65494 | NULL pointer dereference in get_san_or_cn_from_cert() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65494</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in get_san_or_cn_from_cert() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted X.509 certificate that causes sk_GENERAL_NAME_value() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65495 | Integer signedness error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65495</link><description>Integer signedness error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted TLS certificate that causes i2d_X509() to return -1 and be misused as a malloc() size parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65496 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65496</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65497 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65497</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65498 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65498</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65499 | Array index error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65499</link><description>Array index error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_ex_data_X509_STORE_CTX_idx() to return -1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65500 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65500</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65501 | Null pointer dereference in coap_dtls_info_callback() in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a DTLS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65501</link><description>Null pointer dereference in coap_dtls_info_callback() in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a DTLS handshake where SSL_get_app_data() returns NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65502 | Null pointer dereference in add_ca_certs() in Cesanta Mongoose before 7.2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via TLS initi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65502</link><description>Null pointer dereference in add_ca_certs() in Cesanta Mongoose before 7.2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via TLS initialization where SSL_CTX_get_cert_store() returns NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65503 | Use after free in endpoint destructors in Redboltz async_mqtt 10.2.5 allows local users to cause a denial of service via triggering SSL init...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65503</link><description>Use after free in endpoint destructors in Redboltz async_mqtt 10.2.5 allows local users to cause a denial of service via triggering SSL initialization failure that results in incorrect destruction order between io_context and endpoint objects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65998 | Apache Syncope: Default AES key used for internal password encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65998</link><description>Apache Syncope can be configured to store the user password values in the internal database with AES encryption, though this is not the default option.

When AES is configured, the default key value, hard-coded in the source code, is always used. This allows a malicious attacker, once obtained access to the internal database content, to reconstruct the original cleartext password values.
This is not affecting encrypted plain attributes, whose values are also stored using AES encryption.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.15 / 4.0.3, which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12628 | WP 2FA &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Second Factor Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12628</link><description>The WP 2FA WordPress plugin does not generate backup codes with enough entropy, which could allow attackers to bypass the second factor by brute forcing them</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40212 | nfsd: fix refcount leak in nfsd_set_fh_dentry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40212</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: fix refcount leak in nfsd_set_fh_dentry()

nfsd exports a "pseudo root filesystem" which is used by NFSv4 to find
the various exported filesystems using LOOKUP requests from a known root
filehandle.  NFSv3 uses the MOUNT protocol to find those exported
filesystems and so is not given access to the pseudo root filesystem.

If a v3 (or v2) client uses a filehandle from that filesystem,
nfsd_set_fh_dentry() will report an error, but still stores the export
in "struct svc_fh" even though it also drops the reference (exp_put()).
This means that when fh_put() is called an extra reference will be dropped
which can lead to use-after-free and possible denial of service.

Normal NFS usage will not provide a pseudo-root filehandle to a v3
client.  This bug can only be triggered by the client synthesising an
incorrect filehandle.

To fix this we move the assignments to the svc_fh later, after all
possible error cases have been detected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41016 | Multiple vulnerabilities in DFUSION by Davantis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41016</link><description>Inadequate access control vulnerability in Davantis DFUSION v6.177.7, which allows unauthorised actors to extract images and videos related to alarm events through access to “/alarms//”, where the “MEDIA” parameter can take the value of “snapshot” or “video.mp4”. These media files contain images recorded by security cameras in response to triggered alerts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41017 | Multiple vulnerabilities in DFUSION by Davantis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41017</link><description>Inadequate access control vulnerability in Davantis DDFUSION v6.177.7, which allows unauthorised actors to retrieve perspective parameters from security camera settings by accessing “/cameras//perspective”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12740 | Remote Command Execution in Looker via IBM DB2 JDBC drive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12740</link><description>A Looker user with a Developer role could create a database connection using IBM DB2 driver and, by manipulating LookML, cause Looker to execute a malicious command, due to inadequate filtering of the driver's parameters.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  25.0.93+
  *  25.6.84+

  *  25.12.42+
  *  25.14.50+
  *  25.16.44+</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12741 | Arbitrary File Write in Denodo dialect of Looker allows Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12741</link><description>A Looker user with Developer role could create a database connection using Denodo driver and, by manipulating LookML, cause Looker to execute a malicious command.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.108+
  *  24.18.200+
  *  25.0.78+
  *  25.6.65+
  *  25.8.47+
  *  25.12.10+
  *  25.14+</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41087 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) stored in Taclia&amp;#x27;s web application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41087</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability stored in tha Taclia web application, where the uploaded SVG images are not properly sanitized. This allows to the attackers to embed malicious scripts in SVG files such as image profiles, which are then stored on the server and executed in the context of any user who accesses the compromised resource.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41729 | DoS via Modbus Read Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41729</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can send a specially crafted Modbus read command to the device which leads to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12739 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Looker&amp;#x27;s Extension Loader leading to Admin Account Compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12739</link><description>An attacker with viewer permissions in Looker could craft a malicious URL that, when opened by a Looker admin, would execute an attacker-supplied script. Exploitation required at least one Looker extension installed on the instance.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :  *  24.18.201+
  *  25.0.79+
  *  25.6.66+
  *  25.12.7+
  *  25.16.0+
  *  25.18.0+
  *  25.20.0+</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 09:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13596 | Improper Error Handling Leading to Sensitive Information Disclosure in CIGES ≤ 2.15.6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13596</link><description>A sensitive information disclosure vulnerability exists in the error handling component of ATISoluciones CIGES Application version 2.15.6 and earlier. When certain unexpected conditions trigger unhandled exceptions, the application returns detailed error messages and stack traces to the client. This may expose internal filesystem paths, SQL queries, database connection details, or environment configuration data to remote unauthenticated attackers. This issue allows information gathering and reconnaissance but does not enable direct system compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13588 | lKinderBueno Streamity Xtream IPTV Player proxy.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13588</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lKinderBueno Streamity Xtream IPTV Player up to 2.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file public/proxy.php. Performing manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 2.8.1 is sufficient to resolve this issue. The patch is named c70bfb8d36b47bfd64c5ec73917e1d9ddb97af92. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13586 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System changepassword.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13586</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Admin/changepassword.php. This manipulation of the argument txtconfirm_password causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14015 | Studiocart &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14015</link><description>The WordPress eCommerce Plugin  WordPress plugin through 2.9.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12394 | Backup Migration &amp;lt; 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Backup Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12394</link><description>The Backup Migration WordPress plugin before 2.0.0 does not properly generate its backup path in certain server configurations, allowing unauthenticated users to fetch a log that discloses the backup filename. The backup archive is then downloadable without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12569 | WP Front User Submit &amp;lt; 5.0.0 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12569</link><description>The Guest posting / Frontend Posting / Front Editor  WordPress plugin before 5.0.0 does not validate a parameter before redirecting the user to its value, leading to an Open Redirect issue</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12629 | Broken Link Manager &amp;lt;= 0.6.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12629</link><description>The Broken Link Manager WordPress plugin through 0.6.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13585 | code-projects COVID Tracking System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13585</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects COVID Tracking System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument code results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13584 | Eigenfocus Description cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13584</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Eigenfocus up to 1.4.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Description Handler. The manipulation of the argument entry.description/time_entry.description leads to cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.4.1 is able to resolve this issue. The identifier of the patch is 7dec94c9d1f3e513e0ee38ba68caaba628e08582. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7402 | Ads Pro Plugin - Multi-Purpose WordPress Advertising Manager &amp;lt;= 4.95 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via site_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7402</link><description>The Ads Pro Plugin - Multi-Purpose WordPress Advertising Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘site_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.95 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:01:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13583 | code-projects Question Paper Generator POST Parameter signupscript.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13583</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Question Paper Generator 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /signupscript.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument Fname can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 04:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13582 | code-projects Jonnys Liquor GET Parameter detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13582</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Jonnys Liquor 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /detail.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument Product results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 04:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13581 | itsourcecode Student Information System schedule_edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13581</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Information System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /schedule_edit1.php. Such manipulation of the argument schedule_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13589 | Otsuka Information Technology｜FMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13589</link><description>FMS developed by Otsuka Information Technology has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13579 | code-projects Library System return.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /return.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13580 | code-projects Library System mail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13580</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Library System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /mail.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13578 | code-projects Library System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13578</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Library System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13577 | PHPGurukul Hostel Management System register-complaint.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13577</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Hostel Management System 2.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /register-complaint.php. Executing manipulation of the argument cdetails can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13576 | code-projects Blog Site admin.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13576</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Blog Site 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin.php. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13575 | code-projects Blog Site Category blog.php category_exists sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13575</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Blog Site 1.0. Impacted is the function category_exists of the file /resources/functions/blog.php of the component Category Handler. Such manipulation of the argument name/field leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13574 | code-projects Online Bidding System addcategory.php categoryadd unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13574</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Bidding System 1.0. This issue affects the function categoryadd of the file /administrator/addcategory.php. This manipulation of the argument catimage causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>