<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2071 | OS Command Injection Vulnerability in FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2071</link><description>A critical OS Command Injection vulnerability has been identified in the FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary operating system commands via specially crafted input. This vulnerability arises due to improper handling of untrusted input, which is passed directly to system-level commands without adequate sanitization or validation. Successful exploitation could allow attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system, potentially resulting in unauthorized access, data leakage, or full system compromise. Affected WebUI parameters are "hd" and "pi".</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2072 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2072</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been discovered in FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI, allowing attackers to inject malicious JavaScript code into web pages viewed by users. This issue arises when user-supplied input is improperly handled and reflected directly in the output of a web page without proper sanitization or encoding. Exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser, potentially leading to session hijacking, data theft, and other malicious actions. Affected WebUI parameters are "h", "hd", "p", "pi", "s", "t", "x", "y".</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2984 | code-projects Payroll Management System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2984</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Payroll Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /delete.php. The manipulation of the argument emp_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31406 | WordPress ELEX WooCommerce Request a Quote plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31406</link><description>Subscriber Broken Access Control in ELEX WooCommerce Request a Quote &lt;= 2.3.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31410 | WordPress WP Church Donation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31410</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ashish Ajani WP Church Donation allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WP Church Donation: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2983 | Legrand SMS PowerView os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2983</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2982 | Legrand SMS PowerView file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2982</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to file inclusion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 07:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2981 | Legrand SMS PowerView cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2981</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 07:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3019 | Cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in KNIME Business Hub web pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3019</link><description>KNIME Business Hub is affected by several cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in its web pages. If a user clicks on a malicious link or opens a malicious web page, arbitrary Java Script may be executed with this user's permissions. This can lead to information loss and/or modification of existing data.
The issues are caused by a  bug https://github.com/Baroshem/nuxt-security/issues/610  in the widely used nuxt-security module.





There are no viable workarounds therefore we strongly recommend to update to one of the following versions of KNIME Business Hub:





  *  1.13.3 or later






  *  1.12.4 or later</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2980 | Legrand SMS PowerView redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2980</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to open redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2402 | Hard-coded password for object store of KNIME Business Hub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2402</link><description>A hard-coded, non-random password for the object store (minio) of KNIME Business Hub in all versions except the ones listed below allows an unauthenticated remote attacker in possession of the password to read and manipulate swapped jobs or read and manipulate in- and output data of active jobs. It is also possible to cause a denial-of-service of most functionality of KNIME Business Hub by writing large amounts of data to the object store directly. 



There are no viable workarounds therefore we strongly recommend to update to one of the following versions of KNIME Business Hub: 



  *  1.13.2 or later 






  *  1.12.3 or later 






  *  1.11.3 or later 






  *  1.10.3 or later</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0613 | Photo Gallery &amp;lt; 1.8.34 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0613</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.34 does not sanitised and escaped comment added on images by unauthenticated users, leading to an Unauthenticated Stored-XSS attack when comments are displayed</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2979 | WCMS Registration setregister cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2979</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in WCMS 11. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?anonymous/setregister of the component Registration. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30835 | WordPress Accounting for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30835</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Bastien Ho Accounting for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Accounting for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30855 | WordPress Ads by WPQuads plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.87.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30855</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ads by WPQuads Ads by WPQuads allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ads by WPQuads: from n/a through 2.0.87.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30987 | WordPress JetBlocks For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetBlocks For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects JetBlocks For Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31016 | WordPress JetWooBuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.18 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31016</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound JetWooBuilder allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects JetWooBuilder: from n/a through 2.1.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31043 | WordPress JetSearch plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31043</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetSearch allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects JetSearch: from n/a through 3.5.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31387 | WordPress InstaWP Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.82 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31387</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in InstaWP InstaWP Connect allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects InstaWP Connect: from n/a through 0.1.0.82.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31412 | WordPress JetProductGallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31412</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetProductGallery allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects JetProductGallery: from n/a through 2.1.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31414 | WordPress Cost Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.65 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31414</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stylemix Cost Calculator Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Cost Calculator Builder: from n/a through 3.2.65.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31417 | WordPress WP Docs plugin &amp;lt; 2.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31417</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood WP Docs allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Docs: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2978 | WCMS Article Publishing Page CKEditor unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2978</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WCMS 11. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?articleadmin/upload/?&amp;amp;CKEditor=container&amp;amp;CKEditorFuncNum=1 of the component Article Publishing Page. The manipulation of the argument Upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2977 | GFI KerioConnect PDF File cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2977</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GFI KerioConnect 10.0.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component PDF File Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24517 | Use of client-side authentication issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24517</link><description>Use of client-side authentication issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain the product login password without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24852 | Storing passwords in a recoverable format issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24852</link><description>Storing passwords in a recoverable format issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, an attacker who can access the microSD card used on the product may obtain the product login password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25211 | Weak password requirements issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a brute-force attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25211</link><description>Weak password requirements issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a brute-force attack may allow an attacker unauthorized access and login.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26689 | Direct request ('Forced Browsing') issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If a remote attacker sends a specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26689</link><description>Direct request ('Forced Browsing') issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If a remote attacker sends a specially crafted HTTP request to the product, the product data may be obtained or deleted, and/or the product settings may be altered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31103 | Untrusted data deserialization vulnerability exists in a-blog cms. Processing a specially crafted request may store arbitrary files on the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31103</link><description>Untrusted data deserialization vulnerability exists in a-blog cms. Processing a specially crafted request may store arbitrary files on the server where the product is running. This can be leveraged to execute an arbitrary script on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2976 | GFI KerioConnect File Upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2976</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GFI KerioConnect 10.0.6. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component File Upload. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2975 | GFI KerioConnect Signature EditHtmlSource cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2975</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GFI KerioConnect 10.0.6 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file Settings/Email/Signature/EditHtmlSource of the component Signature Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3014 | Insecure direct object references (IDOR) in NightWolf Penetration Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3014</link><description>Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in access control in Tracking 2.1.4 on NightWolf Penetration Testing allows an attacker to access via manipulating request parameters or object references.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2974 | CodeCanyon Perfex CRM Contracts contract cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2974</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeCanyon Perfex CRM up to 3.2.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /contract of the component Contracts. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3011 | PiExtract SOOP-CLM - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3011</link><description>SOOP-CLM from PiExtract has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3013 | Insecure direct object references (IDOR) in NightWolf Penetration Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3013</link><description>Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in access control in Customer Portal before 2.1.4 on NightWolf Penetration Testing allows an attacker to access via manipulating request parameters or object references.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2973 | code-projects College Management System student.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2973</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/student.php. The manipulation of the argument profile_image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2972 | ConcreteCMS Page Attribute Display Block cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2972</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Page Attribute Display Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2970 | ConcreteCMS Switch Language Block cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected is an unknown function of the component Switch Language Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Label leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2971 | ConcreteCMS List Block cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2971</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component List Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name/Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1268 | Out-of-bounds vulnerability in EMF Recode processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1268</link><description>Out-of-bounds vulnerability in EMF Recode processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2969 | ConcreteCMS Feature Link Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2969</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function Save of the component Feature Link Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title/Body Source/Button Text leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2968 | ConcreteCMS Feature Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function Save of the component Feature Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Paragraph Source leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2967 | ConcreteCMS HTML Block save HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function Save of the component HTML Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument content leads to HTML injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2966 | ConcreteCMS Content Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function Save of the component Content Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Source leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2965 | ConcreteCMS Accordion Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Save of the component Accordion Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title/Body Source leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2964 | ConcreteCMS FAQ Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected is the function Save of the component FAQ Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Navigation/Title Text/Description Source leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 22:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2963 | ConcreteCMS Legacy Form Block addEditQuestion cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. This issue affects the function addEditQuestion of the component Legacy Form Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Question leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 22:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2961 | opensolon org.noear.solon.core.handle.RenderManager aa render_mav path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2961</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in opensolon up to 3.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function render_mav of the file /aa of the component org.noear.solon.core.handle.RenderManager. The manipulation of the argument template with the input ../org/example/HelloApp.class leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13804 | Vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise HPE Insight Cluster Management Utility (CMU).This issue affects HPE Insight Cluster Management U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13804</link><description>Vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise HPE Insight Cluster Management Utility (CMU).This issue affects HPE Insight Cluster Management Utility (CMU): 8.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2960 | TRENDnet TEW-637AP/TEW-638APB HTTP Request goahead sub_41DED0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2960</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in TRENDnet TEW-637AP and TEW-638APB 1.2.7/1.3.0.106. This affects the function sub_41DED0 of the file /bin/goahead of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2959 | TRENDnet TEW-410APB HTTP Request httpd sub_4019A0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-410APB 1.3.06b. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4019A0 of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2958 | TRENDnet TEW-818DRU HTTP Request httpd denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-818DRU 1.0.14.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2957 | TRENDnet TEW-411BRP+ HTTP Request httpd sub_401DB0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2957</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-411BRP+ 2.07. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function sub_401DB0 of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 19:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2956 | TRENDnet TI-G102i HTTP Request lighttpd plugins_call_handle_uri_raw null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2956</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TI-G102i 1.0.7.S0_ /1.0.8.S0_ and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function plugins_call_handle_uri_raw of the file /usr/sbin/lighttpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2955 | TOTOLINK A3000RU IBMS Configuration File ExportIbmsConfig.sh access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2955</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3000RU up to 5.9c.5185 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cgi-bin/ExportIbmsConfig.sh of the component IBMS Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2954 | mannaandpoem OpenManus File file_saver.py execute access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2954</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in mannaandpoem OpenManus up to 2025.3.13. This affects the function execute of the file app/tool/file_saver.py of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2953 | PyTorch torch.mkldnn_max_pool2d denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2953</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PyTorch 2.6.0+cu124. Affected by this issue is the function torch.mkldnn_max_pool2d. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2952 | Bluestar Micro Mall api.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2952</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Bluestar Micro Mall 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/api.php?mod=upload&amp;amp;type=1. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2951 | Bluestar Micro Mall data.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2951</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Bluestar Micro Mall 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/data.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1861 | Stream HTTP wrapper truncates redirect location to 1024 bytes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1861</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when parsing HTTP redirect in the response to an HTTP request, there is currently limit on the location value size caused by limited size of the location buffer to 1024. However as per RFC9110, the limit is recommended to be 8000. This may lead to incorrect URL truncation and redirecting to a wrong location.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 06:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1736 | Stream HTTP wrapper header check might omit basic auth header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1736</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when user-supplied headers are sent, the insufficient validation of the end-of-line characters may prevent certain headers from being sent or lead to certain headers be misinterpreted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1734 | Streams HTTP wrapper does not fail for headers with invalid name and no colon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1734</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when receiving headers from HTTP server, the headers missing a colon (:) are treated as valid headers even though they are not. This may confuse applications into accepting invalid headers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1219 | libxml streams use wrong content-type header when requesting a redirected resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1219</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when requesting a HTTP resource using the DOM or SimpleXML extensions, the wrong content-type header is used to determine the charset when the requested resource performs a redirect. This may cause the resulting document to be parsed incorrectly or bypass validations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55895 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55895</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 12:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11180 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11180</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Timer Widget ekit_countdown_timer_title parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13557 | Shortcodes by United Themes  &amp;lt;= 5.1.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13557</link><description>The Shortcodes by United Themes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2006 | Inline Image Upload for BBPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.19 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2006</link><description>The Inline Image Upload for BBPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the file uploading functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This may be exploitable by unauthenticated attackers when the "Allow guest users without accounts to create topics and replies" setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2249 | SoJ Soundslides &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2249</link><description>The SoJ SoundSlides plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the soj_soundslides_options_subpanel() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2266 | Checkout Mestres do WP for WooCommerce 8.6.5 - 8.7.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2266</link><description>The Checkout Mestres do WP for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the cwmpUpdateOptions() function in versions 8.6.5 to 8.7.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2803 | So-Called Air Quotes &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2803</link><description>The So-Called Air Quotes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2840 | DAP to Autoresponders Email Syncing &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2840</link><description>The DAP to Autoresponders Email Syncing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 through the publicly accessible phpinfo.php script. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1217 | Header parser of http stream wrapper does not handle folded headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1217</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when http request module parses HTTP response obtained from a server, folded headers are parsed incorrectly, which may lead to misinterpreting the response and using incorrect headers, MIME types, etc.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 05:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>