<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-9211 | FULL – Cliente &amp;lt;= 3.1.22 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9211</link><description>The FULL – Cliente plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.22. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9221 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 0.21.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9221</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 0.21.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9232 | Download Plugins and Themes in ZIP from Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9232</link><description>The Download Plugins and Themes in ZIP from Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9234 | GutenKit &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9234</link><description>The GutenKit – Page Builder Blocks, Patterns, and Templates for Gutenberg Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability check on the install_and_activate_plugin_from_external() function  (install-active-plugin REST API endpoint) in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate arbitrary plugins, or utilize the functionality to upload arbitrary files spoofed like plugins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9346 | Embed videos and respect privacy &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9346</link><description>The Embed videos and respect privacy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'v' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9436 | PublishPress Revisions: Duplicate Posts, Submit, Approve and Schedule Content Changes &amp;lt;= 3.5.14 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9436</link><description>The PublishPress Revisions: Duplicate Posts, Submit, Approve and Schedule Content Changes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9610 | Language Switcher &amp;lt;= 3.7.13 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9610</link><description>The Language Switcher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9611 | Increase upload file size &amp;amp; Maximum Execution Time limit &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9611</link><description>The Increase upload file size &amp; Maximum Execution Time limit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9616 | BlockMeister – Block Pattern Builder &amp;lt;= 3.1.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9616</link><description>The BlockMeister – Block Pattern Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9707 | Hunk Companion &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Installation/Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9707</link><description>The Hunk Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation/activation due to a missing capability check on the /wp-json/hc/v1/themehunk-import REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution if another vulnerable plugin is installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9543 | Powerpress &amp;lt;= 11.9.18 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via skipto Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9543</link><description>The PowerPress Podcasting plugin by Blubrry plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'skipto' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 11.9.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 05:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9586 | Linkz.ai &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9586</link><description>The Linkz.ai plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'check_auth' and 'check_logout' functions in versions up to, and including, 1.1.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 05:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9587 | Linkz.ai &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update via AJAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9587</link><description>The Linkz.ai plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_linkz' function in versions up to, and including, 1.1.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level privileges or above, to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 05:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21534 | Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.0.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21534</link><description>Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.0.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can execute aribitrary code on the system by exploiting the unsafe default usage of vm in Node.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;The unsafe behavior is still available after applying the fix but it is not turned on by default.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 05:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48987 | Snipe-IT before 7.0.10 allows remote code execution (associated with cookie serialization) when an attacker knows the APP_KEY. This is exace...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48987</link><description>Snipe-IT before 7.0.10 allows remote code execution (associated with cookie serialization) when an attacker knows the APP_KEY. This is exacerbated by .env files, available from the product's repository, that have default APP_KEY values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 04:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9822 | Pedalo Connector &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Authentication Bypass to Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9822</link><description>The Pedalo Connector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.0.5. This is due to insufficient restriction on the 'login_admin_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log to the first user, who is usually the administrator, or if it does not exist, then to the first administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 02:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9817 | code-projects Blood Bank System update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9817</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /update.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9818 | SourceCodester Online Veterinary Appointment System manage_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9818</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Veterinary Appointment System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/categories/manage_category.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47867 | Lack of integrity check on the downloaded FRP client in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47867</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability is a **lack of integrity check** on the downloaded FRP client, which could potentially allow attackers to introduce malicious code. If an attacker gains access to the remote URL from which the FRP client is downloaded, they could modify the binary without detection, as the Gradio server does not verify the file's checksum or signature.  Any users utilizing the Gradio server's sharing mechanism that downloads the FRP client could be affected by this vulnerability, especially those relying on the executable binary for secure data tunneling. There is no direct workaround for this issue without upgrading. However, users can manually validate the integrity of the downloaded FRP client by implementing checksum or signature verification in their own environment to ensure the binary hasn't been tampered with.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47868 | Several components’ post-process steps may allow arbitrary file leaks in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47868</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This is a **data validation vulnerability** affecting several Gradio components, which allows arbitrary file leaks through the post-processing step. Attackers can exploit these components by crafting requests that bypass expected input constraints. This issue could lead to sensitive files being exposed to unauthorized users, especially when combined with other vulnerabilities, such as issue TOB-GRADIO-15. The components most at risk are those that return or handle file data. Vulnerable Components: 1. **String to FileData:** DownloadButton, Audio, ImageEditor, Video, Model3D, File, UploadButton. 2. **Complex data to FileData:** Chatbot, MultimodalTextbox. 3. **Direct file read in preprocess:** Code. 4. **Dictionary converted to FileData:** ParamViewer, Dataset. Exploit Scenarios: 1. A developer creates a Dropdown list that passes values to a DownloadButton. An attacker bypasses the allowed inputs, sends an arbitrary file path (like `/etc/passwd`), and downloads sensitive files. 2. An attacker crafts a malicious payload in a ParamViewer component, leaking sensitive files from a server through the arbitrary file leak. This issue has been resolved in `gradio&gt;5.0`. Upgrading to the latest version will mitigate this vulnerability. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47869 | Non-constant-time comparison when comparing hashes in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47869</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability involves a **timing attack** in the way Gradio compares hashes for the `analytics_dashboard` function. Since the comparison is not done in constant time, an attacker could exploit this by measuring the response time of different requests to infer the correct hash byte-by-byte. This can lead to unauthorized access to the analytics dashboard, especially if the attacker can repeatedly query the system with different keys. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;4.44` to mitigate this issue. To mitigate the risk before applying the patch, developers can manually patch the `analytics_dashboard` dashboard to use a **constant-time comparison** function for comparing sensitive values, such as hashes. Alternatively, access to the analytics dashboard can be disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47870 | Race condition in update_root_in_config may redirect user traffic in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47870</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability involves a **race condition** in the `update_root_in_config` function, allowing an attacker to modify the `root` URL used by the Gradio frontend to communicate with the backend. By exploiting this flaw, an attacker can redirect user traffic to a malicious server. This could lead to the interception of sensitive data such as authentication credentials or uploaded files. This impacts all users who connect to a Gradio server, especially those exposed to the internet, where malicious actors could exploit this race condition. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=5` to address this issue. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47871 | Insecure communication between the FRP client and server in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47871</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability involves **insecure communication** between the FRP (Fast Reverse Proxy) client and server when Gradio's `share=True` option is used. HTTPS is not enforced on the connection, allowing attackers to intercept and read files uploaded to the Gradio server, as well as modify responses or data sent between the client and server. This impacts users who are sharing Gradio demos publicly over the internet using `share=True` without proper encryption, exposing sensitive data to potential eavesdroppers. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=5` to address this issue. As a workaround, users can avoid using `share=True` in production environments and instead host their Gradio applications on servers with HTTPS enabled to ensure secure communication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47872 | Cross-site Scripting on Gradio server via upload of HTML files, JS files, or SVG files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47872</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability involves **Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)** on any Gradio server that allows file uploads. Authenticated users can upload files such as HTML, JavaScript, or SVG files containing malicious scripts. When other users download or view these files, the scripts will execute in their browser, allowing attackers to perform unauthorized actions or steal sensitive information from their sessions. This impacts any Gradio server that allows file uploads, particularly those using components that process or display user-uploaded files. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=5` to address this issue. As a workaround, users can restrict the types of files that can be uploaded to the Gradio server by limiting uploads to non-executable file types such as images or text. Additionally, developers can implement server-side validation to sanitize uploaded files, ensuring that HTML, JavaScript, and SVG files are properly handled or rejected before being stored or displayed to users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9816 | Codezips Tourist Management System change-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9816</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Tourist Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/change-image.php. The manipulation of the argument packageimage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47084 | CORS origin validation is not performed when the request has a cookie in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47084</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability is related to **CORS origin validation**, where the Gradio server fails to validate the request origin when a cookie is present. This allows an attacker’s website to make unauthorized requests to a local Gradio server. Potentially, attackers can upload files, steal authentication tokens, and access user data if the victim visits a malicious website while logged into Gradio. This impacts users who have deployed Gradio locally and use basic authentication. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;4.44` to address this issue. As a workaround, users can manually enforce stricter CORS origin validation by modifying the `CustomCORSMiddleware` class in their local Gradio server code. Specifically, they can bypass the condition that skips CORS validation for requests containing cookies to prevent potential exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47164 | The `is_in_or_equal` function may be bypassed in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47164</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability relates to the **bypass of directory traversal checks** within the `is_in_or_equal` function. This function, intended to check if a file resides within a given directory, can be bypassed with certain payloads that manipulate file paths using `..` (parent directory) sequences. Attackers could potentially access restricted files if they are able to exploit this flaw, although the difficulty is high. This primarily impacts users relying on Gradio’s blocklist or directory access validation, particularly when handling file uploads. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=5.0` to address this issue. As a workaround, users can manually sanitize and normalize file paths in their Gradio deployment before passing them to the `is_in_or_equal` function. Ensuring that all file paths are properly resolved and absolute can help mitigate the bypass vulnerabilities caused by the improper handling of `..` sequences or malformed paths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47165 | CORS origin validation accepts the null origin in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47165</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability relates to **CORS origin validation accepting a null origin**. When a Gradio server is deployed locally, the `localhost_aliases` variable includes "null" as a valid origin. This allows attackers to make unauthorized requests from sandboxed iframes or other sources with a null origin, potentially leading to data theft, such as user authentication tokens or uploaded files. This impacts users running Gradio locally, especially those using basic authentication. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=5.0` to address this issue. As a workaround, users can manually modify the `localhost_aliases` list in their local Gradio deployment to exclude "null" as a valid origin. By removing this value, the Gradio server will no longer accept requests from sandboxed iframes or sources with a null origin, mitigating the potential for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47166 | One-level read path traversal in `/custom_component` in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47166</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability involves a **one-level read path traversal** in the `/custom_component` endpoint. Attackers can exploit this flaw to access and leak source code from custom Gradio components by manipulating the file path in the request. Although the traversal is limited to a single directory level, it could expose proprietary or sensitive code that developers intended to keep private. This impacts users who have developed custom Gradio components and are hosting them on publicly accessible servers. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=4.44` to address this issue. As a workaround, developers can sanitize the file paths and ensure that components are not stored in publicly accessible directories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47167 | SSRF in the path parameter of /queue/join in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47167</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability relates to **Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)** in the `/queue/join` endpoint. Gradio’s `async_save_url_to_cache` function allows attackers to force the Gradio server to send HTTP requests to user-controlled URLs. This could enable attackers to target internal servers or services within a local network and possibly exfiltrate data or cause unwanted internal requests. Additionally, the content from these URLs is stored locally, making it easier for attackers to upload potentially malicious files to the server. This impacts users deploying Gradio servers that use components like the Video component which involve URL fetching. Users are advised to upgrade to `gradio&gt;=5` to address this issue.  As a workaround, users can disable or heavily restrict URL-based inputs in their Gradio applications to trusted domains only. Additionally, implementing stricter URL validation (such as allowinglist-based validation) and ensuring that local or internal network addresses cannot be requested via the `/queue/join` endpoint can help mitigate the risk of SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47168 | The `enable_monitoring` flag set to `False` does not disable monitoring in Gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47168</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package designed for quick prototyping. This vulnerability involves data exposure due to the enable_monitoring flag not properly disabling monitoring when set to False. Even when monitoring is supposedly disabled, an attacker or unauthorized user can still access the monitoring dashboard by directly requesting the /monitoring endpoint. This means that sensitive application analytics may still be exposed, particularly in environments where monitoring is expected to be disabled. Users who set enable_monitoring=False to prevent unauthorized access to monitoring data are impacted. Users are advised to upgrade to gradio&gt;=4.44 to address this issue. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9814 | Codezips Pharmacy Management System update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9814</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Codezips Pharmacy Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file product/update.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9815 | Codezips Tourist Management System create-package.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9815</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Codezips Tourist Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/create-package.php. The manipulation of the argument packageimage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9487 | An Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed SAML SSO authentication to be bypassed when the encrypted assertions feature was enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9487</link><description>An improper verification of cryptographic signature vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed SAML SSO authentication to be bypassed resulting in unauthorized provisioning of users and access to the instance. Exploitation required the encrypted assertions feature to be enabled, and the attacker would require direct network access as well as a signed SAML response or metadata document. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.15 and was fixed in versions 3.11.16, 3.12.10, 3.13.5, and 3.14.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9812 | code-projects Crud Operation System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9812</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file delete.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9813 | Codezips Pharmacy Management System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9813</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Pharmacy Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file product/register.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9180 | Vault Operators in Root Namespace May Elevate Their Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9180</link><description>A privileged Vault operator with write permissions to the root namespace’s identity endpoint could escalate their privileges to Vault’s root policy. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.18.0 and Vault Enterprise 1.18.0, 1.17.7, 1.16.11, and 1.15.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9811 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System filter3.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9811</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file filter3.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 20:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9810 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort2_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file sort2_user.php. The manipulation of the argument qualification leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 20:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9808 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=products/view_product. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9809 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Master.php delete_product sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_product of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_product. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9807 | Craig Rodway Classroombookings Session Page sessions cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9807</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Craig Rodway Classroombookings 2.8.7 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /sessions of the component Session Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 2.8.8 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The project maintainer was contacted early about the disclosure. He responded very quickly, friendly, and professional.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9806 | Craig Rodway Classroombookings Room Page fields cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9806</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Craig Rodway Classroombookings up to 2.8.6 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /rooms/fields of the component Room Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.8.7 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The project maintainer was contacted early about the disclosure. He responded very quickly, friendly, and professional.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 18:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47354 | WordPress Simple Membership After Login Redirection plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47354</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in smp7, wp.Insider Simple Membership After Login Redirection.This issue affects Simple Membership After Login Redirection: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 18:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47648 | WordPress EventPrime plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.4.5 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47648</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in EventPrime Events EventPrime.This issue affects EventPrime: from n/a through 4.0.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 18:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47636 | WordPress WP JobSearch plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.9 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47636</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Eyecix JobSearch allows Object Injection.This issue affects JobSearch: from n/a through 2.5.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9805 | code-projects Blood Bank System campsdetails.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9805</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/campsdetails.php. The manipulation of the argument hospital/address/city/contact leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "hospital".</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9804 | code-projects Blood Bank System campsdetails.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9804</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/campsdetails.php. The manipulation of the argument hospital leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47962 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47962</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can manipulate an insider to visit a malicious page or file to leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47963 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47963</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can manipulate users to visit a malicious page or file to leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47964 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47964</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can manipulate users to visit a malicious page or file to leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47965 | Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47965</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can manipulate users to visit a malicious page or file to leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47966 | Use of Uninitialized Variable vulnerability in Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47966</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can manipulate users to visit a malicious page or file to leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9803 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System blooddetails.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9803</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file blooddetails.php. The manipulation of the argument Availibility leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9797 | code-projects Blood Bank System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9797</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file register.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9799 | SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9799</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file add.php. The manipulation of the argument email_address/address/company_name/job_title/jobDescriptionparameter leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9794 | Codezips Online Shopping Portal update-image1.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9794</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Online Shopping Portal 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /update-image1.php. The manipulation of the argument productimage1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25581 | Deserialization of untrusted data in InternalAttributeHandler in pac4j</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25581</link><description>pac4j is a security framework for Java. `pac4j-core` prior to version 4.0.0 is affected by a Java deserialization vulnerability. The vulnerability affects systems that store externally controlled values in attributes of the `UserProfile` class from pac4j-core. It can be exploited by providing an attribute that contains a serialized Java object with a special prefix `{#sb64}` and Base64 encoding. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the worst case. Although a `RestrictedObjectInputStream` is in place, that puts some restriction on what classes can be deserialized, it still allows a broad range of java packages and potentially exploitable with different gadget chains. pac4j versions 4.0.0 and greater are not affected by this issue. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9793 | Tenda AC1206 ate ate_ifconfig_set command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9793</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC1206 up to 15.03.06.23. This vulnerability affects the function ate_iwpriv_set/ate_ifconfig_set of the file /goform/ate. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9790 | LyLme_spage sou.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9790</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LyLme_spage 1.9.5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/sou.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9792 | D-Link DSL-2750U Port Forwarding Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9792</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in D-Link DSL-2750U R5B017. This affects an unknown part of the component Port Forwarding Page. The manipulation of the argument PortMappingDescription leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9788 | LyLme_spage tag.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9788</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in LyLme_spage 1.9.5 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/tag.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9789 | LyLme_spage apply.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9789</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LyLme_spage 1.9.5 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/apply.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9312 | Authd, through version 0.3.6, did not sufficiently randomize user IDs to prevent collisions. A local attacker who can register user names co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9312</link><description>Authd, through version 0.3.6, did not sufficiently randomize user IDs to prevent collisions. A local attacker who can register user names could spoof another user's ID and gain their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4658 | SQLi in TE Informatics&amp;#x27; Nova CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4658</link><description>SQL Injection: Hibernate vulnerability in TE Informatics Nova CMS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Nova CMS: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9787 | Contemporary Control System BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B UDP Packet denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9787</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Contemporary Control System BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B 2.7.2. This affects an unknown part of the component UDP Packet Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9785 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetDDNS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9785</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetDDNS of the file /goform/formSetDDNS. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9786 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formSetLog buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9786</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected by this issue is the function formSetLog of the file /goform/formSetLog. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35202 | Bitcoin Core before 25.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (blocktxn message-handling assertion and node exit) by includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35202</link><description>Bitcoin Core before 25.0 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (blocktxn message-handling assertion and node exit) by including transactions in a blocktxn message that are not committed to in a block's merkle root. FillBlock can be called twice for one PartiallyDownloadedBlock instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36051 | In btcd before 0.24.2, removeOpcodeByData mishandles the consensus rules for legacy signature verification. There can be a standard transact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36051</link><description>In btcd before 0.24.2, removeOpcodeByData mishandles the consensus rules for legacy signature verification. There can be a standard transaction that would be considered valid by Bitcoin Core but invalid by btcd.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6157 | An attacker who successfully exploited these vulnerabilities could cause the robot to stop.



A vulnerability exists in the PROFINET stack ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6157</link><description>An attacker who successfully exploited these vulnerabilities could cause the robot to stop.



A vulnerability exists in the PROFINET stack included in the RobotWare versions listed below. 

This vulnerability arises under specific condition when specially crafted message is processed by the system.

Below are reported vulnerabilities in the Robot Ware versions. 

* IRC5- RobotWare 6 &lt; 6.15.06 except 6.10.10, and 6.13.07</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6530 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6530</link><description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 17.1 prior 17.2.9, starting from 17.3 prior to 17.3.5, and starting from 17.4 prior to 17.4.2. When adding a authorizing an application, it can be made to render as HTML under specific circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9784 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formResetStatistic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9784</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected is the function formResetStatistic of the file /goform/formResetStatistic. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9782 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formEasySetupWWConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9782</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formEasySetupWWConfig of the file /goform/formEasySetupWWConfig. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 11:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9783 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formLogDnsquery buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9783</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formLogDnsquery of the file /goform/formLogDnsquery. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 11:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48902 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.46677 improper access control allowed users with project update permission to delete applications via AP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48902</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.46677 improper access control allowed users with project update permission to delete applications via API</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9201 | SQL injection vulnerability in SEUR plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9201</link><description>The SEUR plugin, in its versions prior to 2.5.11, is vulnerable to time-based SQL injection through the use of the ‘id_order’ parameter of the ‘/modules/seur/ajax/saveCodFee.php’ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8977 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8977</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.10 prior to 17.2.9, from 17.3 prior to 17.3.5, and from 17.4 prior to 17.4.2. Instances with Product Analytics Dashboard configured and enabled could be vulnerable to SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9596 | Inclusion of Sensitive Information in Source Code in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9596</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.6 prior to 17.2.9, from 17.3 prior to 17.3.5, and from 17.4 prior to 17.4.2. It was possible for an unauthenticated attacker to determine the GitLab version number for a GitLab instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45115 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Authentication (CWE-287)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45115</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authentication vulnerability that could result in privilege escalation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access or elevated privileges within the application. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45116 | Adobe Commerce | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45116</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited to execute arbitrary code. If an admin attacker can trick a user into clicking a specially crafted link or submitting a form, malicious scripts may be executed within the context of the victim's browser and have high impact on confidentiality and integrity. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45117 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45117</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. An admin attacker could exploit this vulnerability to read files from the system outside of the intended directories via PHP filter chain and also can have a low-availability impact on the service. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45118 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45118</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have high impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45119 | Adobe Commerce | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) (CWE-918)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45119</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. A low-privilege authenticated attacker can force the application to make arbitrary requests via injection of arbitrary URLs and have a low impact on both confidentiality and integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45120 | Adobe Commerce | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition (CWE-367)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45120</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability that could lead to a security feature bypass. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to alter a condition between the check and the use of a resource, having a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45121 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45121</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45122 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45122</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on confidentiality. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45123 | Adobe Commerce | Cross-site Scripting (Reflected XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45123</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If an attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45124 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45124</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45125 | Adobe Commerce | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45125</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could exploit this vulnerability to have a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45127 | Adobe Commerce | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45127</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an admin attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45128 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Authorization (CWE-285)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45128</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on integrity and availability. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45129 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45129</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in Privilege escalation. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45130 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45130</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45131 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Authorization (CWE-285)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45131</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on confidentiality and integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45132 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Authorization (CWE-285)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45132</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authorization vulnerability that could result in Privilege escalation. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and affect confidentiality. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45133 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45133</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Information Exposure vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. An admin attacker could leverage this vulnerability to have a low impact on confidentiality which may aid in further attacks. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45134 | Adobe Commerce | Information Exposure (CWE-200)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45134</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Information Exposure vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. An admin attacker could leverage this vulnerability to have a low impact on confidentiality which may aid in further attacks. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45135 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45135</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An admin attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on integrity. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45148 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Authentication (CWE-287)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45148</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authentication vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access without proper credentials. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45149 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45149</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.7-p2, 2.4.6-p7, 2.4.5-p9, 2.4.4-p10 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and have a low impact on confidentiality. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9623 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9623</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.16 prior to 17.2.9, starting from 17.3 prior to 17.3.5, and starting from 17.4 prior to 17.4.2, which allows deploy keys to push to an archived repository.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 09:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22068 | Weak Password Vulnerability in ZTE ZSR V2 Intelligent Multi Service Router</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22068</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE ZXR10 1800-2S series ,ZXR10 2800-4,ZXR10 3800-8,ZXR10 160 series on 64 bit allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects ZXR10 1800-2S series ,ZXR10 2800-4,ZXR10 3800-8,ZXR10 160 series: V4.00.10 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 09:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6747 | Information leak in mknotifyd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6747</link><description>Information leakage in mknotifyd in Checkmk before 2.3.0p18, 2.2.0p36, 2.1.0p49 and in 2.0.0p39 (EOL) allows attacker to get potentially sensitive data</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9802 | Conformance validation endpoint discloses detail about service to unauthenticated users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9802</link><description>The conformance validation endpoint is public so everybody can verify the conformance of onboarded services. The response could contain specific information about the service, including available endpoints, and swagger. It could advise about the running version of a service to an attacker. The attacker could also check if a service is running.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 07:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9796 | WP-Advanced-Search &amp;lt; 3.3.9.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9796</link><description>The WP-Advanced-Search WordPress plugin before 3.3.9.2 does not sanitize and escape the t parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing unauthenticated users to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 07:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9798 | Health endpoint offers list of onboarded services to unauthenticated users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9798</link><description>The health endpoint is public so everybody can see a list of all services. It is potentially valuable information for attackers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 07:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7049 | Exposure of Token in open-webui/open-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7049</link><description>In version v0.3.8 of open-webui/open-webui, a vulnerability exists where a token is returned when a user with a pending role logs in. This allows the user to perform actions without admin confirmation, bypassing the intended approval process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 07:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9780 | Missing Initialization of a Variable in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9780</link><description>ITS dissector crash in Wireshark 4.4.0 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 06:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9781 | Improper Handling of Missing Values in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9781</link><description>AppleTalk and RELOAD Framing dissector crash in Wireshark 4.4.0 and 4.2.0 to 4.2.7 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 06:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9156 | TI WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via lang parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9156</link><description>The TI WooCommerce Wishlist WordPress plugin through 2.8.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 06:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8477 | Newsletter, SMTP, Email marketing and Subscribe forms by Brevo (formely Sendinblue) &amp;lt;= 3.1.87 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8477</link><description>The Newsletter, SMTP, Email marketing and Subscribe forms by Brevo (formely Sendinblue) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the Init() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log out of a Brevo connection via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9022 | TS Poll – Survey, Versus Poll, Image Poll, Video Poll &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9022</link><description>The TS Poll – Survey, Versus Poll, Image Poll, Video Poll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9067 | Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp;amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary (Subscriber+) Attachment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9067</link><description>The Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_attachment' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary attachments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9074 | Advanced Blocks Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9074</link><description>The Advanced Blocks Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9520 | UserPlus &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9520</link><description>The UserPlus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above, to add, modify, or delete user meta and plugin options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8513 | QA Analytics &amp;lt;= 4.1.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8513</link><description>The QA Analytics – Web Analytics Tool with Heatmaps &amp; Session Replay Across All Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_save_plugin_config() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8729 | Easy Social Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8729</link><description>The Easy Social Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8987 | Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp;amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via youzify_media Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8987</link><description>The Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's youzify_media shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9057 | Curator.io: Show all your social media posts in a beautiful feed. &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via feed_id Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9057</link><description>The Curator.io: Show all your social media posts in a beautiful feed. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘feed_id’ attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9064 | Elementor Inline SVG &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9064</link><description>The Elementor Inline SVG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9065 | WP Helper Premium &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Missing Authorization in whp_smtp_send_mail_test</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9065</link><description>The WP Helper Premium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'whp_smtp_send_mail_test' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails containing any content and originating from the vulnerable WordPress instance to any recipient.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9066 | Marketing and SEO Booster &amp;lt;= 1.9.10 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9066</link><description>The Marketing and SEO Booster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9072 | GDPR-Extensions-com – Consent Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9072</link><description>The GDPR-Extensions-com – Consent Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9205 | Maximum Products per User for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9205</link><description>The Maximum Products per User for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9377 | Products, Order &amp;amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9377</link><description>The Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9457 | WP Builder &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9457</link><description>The WP Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9518 | UserPlus &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9518</link><description>The UserPlus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient restriction on the 'form_actions' and 'userplus_update_user_profile' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to specify their user role by supplying the 'role' parameter during a registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9519 | UserPlus &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) Registration Form Update to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9519</link><description>The UserPlus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an improper capability check on the 'save_metabox_form' function in versions up to, and including, 2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions or above, to update the registration form role to administrator, which leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9522 | WP Users Masquerade &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9522</link><description>The WP Users Masquerade plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to incorrect authentication and capability checking in the 'ajax_masq_login' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9581 | Shortcodes AnyWhere &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9581</link><description>The Shortcodes AnyWhere plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9685 | Notification for Telegram &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Send Telegram Test Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9685</link><description>The Notification for Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized test message sending due to a missing capability check on the 'nftb_test_action' function in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to send a test message via the Telegram Bot API to all users configured in the settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48957 | execute_filter_audio in archive_read_support_format_rar.c in libarchive before 3.7.5 allows out-of-bounds access via a crafted archive file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48957</link><description>execute_filter_audio in archive_read_support_format_rar.c in libarchive before 3.7.5 allows out-of-bounds access via a crafted archive file because src can move beyond dst.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48958 | execute_filter_delta in archive_read_support_format_rar.c in libarchive before 3.7.5 allows out-of-bounds access via a crafted archive file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48958</link><description>execute_filter_delta in archive_read_support_format_rar.c in libarchive before 3.7.5 allows out-of-bounds access via a crafted archive file because src can move beyond dst.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7048 | IDOR in open-webui/open-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7048</link><description>In version v0.3.8 of open-webui, an improper privilege management vulnerability exists in the API endpoints GET /api/v1/documents/ and POST /rag/api/v1/doc. This vulnerability allows a lower-privileged user to access and overwrite files managed by a higher-privileged admin. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can view metadata of files uploaded by an admin and overwrite these files, compromising the integrity and availability of the RAG models.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48949 | The verify function in lib/elliptic/eddsa/index.js in the Elliptic package before 6.5.6 for Node.js omits "sig.S().gte(sig.eddsa.curve.n) ||...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48949</link><description>The verify function in lib/elliptic/eddsa/index.js in the Elliptic package before 6.5.6 for Node.js omits "sig.S().gte(sig.eddsa.curve.n) || sig.S().isNeg()" validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48941 | The Syracom Secure Login (2FA) plugin for Jira, Confluence, and Bitbucket through 3.1.4.5 allows remote attackers to bypass 2FA by interacti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48941</link><description>The Syracom Secure Login (2FA) plugin for Jira, Confluence, and Bitbucket through 3.1.4.5 allows remote attackers to bypass 2FA by interacting with the /rest endpoint of Jira, Confluence, or Bitbucket. In the default configuration, /rest is allowlisted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48942 | The Syracom Secure Login (2FA) plugin for Jira, Confluence, and Bitbucket through 3.1.4.5 allows remote attackers to easily brute-force the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48942</link><description>The Syracom Secure Login (2FA) plugin for Jira, Confluence, and Bitbucket through 3.1.4.5 allows remote attackers to easily brute-force the 2FA PIN via the plugins/servlet/twofactor/public/pinvalidation endpoint. The last 30 and the next 30 tokens are valid.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8264 | Sensitive information in agent log file when detailed logging is enabled with Robot Schedule Enterprise prior to version 3.05</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8264</link><description>Fortra's Robot Schedule Enterprise Agent prior to version 3.05 writes FTP username and password information to the agent log file when detailed logging is enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48933 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.19.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48933</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.19.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML into the login page via a username if userControl has been set to a non-default value that allows special HTML characters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30118 | HCL Connections is susceptible to a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30118</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability which could allow a user to obtain sensitive information they are not entitled to because of improperly handling the request data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39515 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: With BGP traceoptions enabled, receipt of specifically malformed BGP update causes RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39515</link><description>An Improper Validation of Consistency within Input vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker sending a specifically malformed BGP packet to cause rpd to crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS). Continued receipt and processing of this packet will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

In some cases, rpd fails to restart requiring a manual restart via the 'restart routing' CLI command.

This issue only affects systems with BGP traceoptions enabled and 

requires a BGP session to be already established.  Systems without BGP traceoptions enabled are not affected by this issue.

This issue affects iBGP and eBGP, and both IPv4 and IPv6 are affected by this vulnerability.

This issue affects:

Junos OS: 

  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8, 
  *  22.2 before 22.2R3-S5, 
  *  22.3 before 22.3R3-S4, 
  *  22.4 before 22.4R3-S3, 
  *  23.2 before 23.2R2-S2, 
  *  23.4 before 23.4R2; 


Junos OS Evolved: 

  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-S2-EVO, 
  *  23.4-EVO before 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39516 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of a specifically malformed BGP packet causes RPD crash when segment routing is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39516</link><description>An Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability in

the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of 

 Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker sending a specifically malformed BGP packet to cause rpd to crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS). Continued receipt and processing of this packet will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue requires a BGP session to be already established.  Only systems with segment routing enabled are vulnerable to this issue.



This issue affects iBGP and eBGP with 

any address family

 configured.

This issue affects:

Junos OS: 



  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8,
  *  22.2 before 22.2R3-S5, 
  *  22.3 before 22.3R3-S4, 
  *  22.4 before 22.4R3-S3, 
  *  23.2 before 23.2R2-S2, 
  *  23.4 before 23.4R2; 




Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-S2-EVO, 
  *  23.4-EVO before 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39525 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: When BGP traceoptions is enabled, receipt of specially crafted BGP packet causes RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39525</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker sending a specific BGP packet to cause rpd to crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS). Continued receipt and processing of this packet will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue only affects systems with BGP traceoptions enabled and 

requires a BGP session to be already established.  Systems without BGP traceoptions enabled are not affected by this issue.

This issue affects iBGP and eBGP, and both IPv4 and IPv6 are affected by this vulnerability.

This issue affects:

Junos OS: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S8, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S4,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S3, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2; 




Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S4-EVO,
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-S1-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4-EVO before 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7041 | IDOR in open-webui/open-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7041</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in open-webui/open-webui version v0.3.8. The vulnerability occurs in the API endpoint `http://0.0.0.0:3000/api/v1/memories/{id}/update`, where the decentralization design is flawed, allowing attackers to edit other users' memories without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38815 | VMware NSX contains a content spoofing vulnerability. 

An unauthenticated malicious actor may be able to craft a URL and redirect a victim ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38815</link><description>VMware NSX contains a content spoofing vulnerability. 

An unauthenticated malicious actor may be able to craft a URL and redirect a victim to an attacker controlled domain leading to sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7037 | Arbitrary File Write/Delete Leading to RCE in open-webui/open-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7037</link><description>In version v0.3.8 of open-webui/open-webui, the endpoint /api/pipelines/upload is vulnerable to arbitrary file write and delete due to unsanitized file.filename concatenation with CACHE_DIR. This vulnerability allows attackers to overwrite and delete system files, potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38818 | VMware NSX contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. 

An authenticated malicious actor may exploit this vulnerability to obtain ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38818</link><description>VMware NSX contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. 

An authenticated malicious actor may exploit this vulnerability to obtain permissions from a separate group role than previously assigned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38817 | Mware NSX contains a command injection vulnerability. 

A malicious actor with access to the NSX Edge CLI terminal may be able to craft mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38817</link><description>Mware NSX contains a command injection vulnerability. 

A malicious actor with access to the NSX Edge CLI terminal may be able to craft malicious payloads to execute arbitrary commands on the operating system as root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3656 | Keycloak: unguarded admin rest api endpoints allows low privilege users to use administrative functionalities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3656</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. Certain endpoints in Keycloak's admin REST API allow low-privilege users to access administrative functionalities. This flaw allows users to perform actions reserved for administrators, potentially leading to data breaches or system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47828 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in ampache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47828</link><description>ampache is a web based audio/video streaming application and file manager. A CSRF attack can be performed in order to delete objects (Playlist, smartlist etc.). Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) is an attack that forces authenticated users to submit a request to a Web application against which they are currently authenticated. This vulnerability can be exploited by creating a malicious script with an arbitrary playlist ID belonging to another user. When the user submits the request, their playlist will be deleted. Any User with active sessions who are tricked into submitting a malicious request are impacted, as their playlists or other objects could be deleted without their consent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47832 | XML Signature Bypass via differential XML parsing in ssoready</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47832</link><description>ssoready is a single sign on provider implemented via docker. Affected versions are vulnerable to XML signature bypass attacks. An attacker can carry out signature bypass if you have access to certain IDP-signed messages. The underlying mechanism exploits differential behavior between XML parsers. Users of https://ssoready.com, the public hosted instance of SSOReady, are unaffected. We advise folks who self-host SSOReady to upgrade to 7f92a06 or later. Do so by updating your SSOReady Docker images from sha-... to sha-7f92a06. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47833 | Session Cookie without Secure and HTTPOnly flags in taipy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47833</link><description>Taipy is an open-source Python library for easy, end-to-end application development for data scientists and machine learning engineers. In affected versions session cookies are served without Secure and HTTPOnly flags. This issue has been addressed in release version 4.0.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7038 | Information Disclosure in open-webui/open-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7038</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in open-webui version 0.3.8. The vulnerability is related to the embedding model update feature under admin settings. When a user updates the model path, the system checks if the file exists and provides different error messages based on the existence and configuration of the file. This behavior allows an attacker to enumerate file names and traverse directories by observing the error messages, leading to potential exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47812 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) on Special:RequestImportQueue when displaying request date in ImportDump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47812</link><description>ImportDump is an extension for mediawiki designed to automate user import requests. Anyone who can edit the interface strings of a wiki (typically administrators and interface admins) can embed XSS payloads in the messages for dates, and thus XSS anyone who views Special:RequestImportQueue. This issue has been patched in commit `d054b95` and all users are advised to apply this commit to their branch. Users unable to upgrade may either Prevent access to Special:RequestImportQueue on all wikis, except for the global wiki; and If an interface administrator (or equivalent) level protection is available (which is not provided by default) on the global wiki, protect the affected messages up to that level. This causes the XSS to be virtually useless as users with those rights can already edit Javascript pages. Or Prevent access to Special:RequestImportQueue altogether.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47815 | Cross-site Scripting in IncidentReporting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47815</link><description>IncidentReporting is a MediaWiki extension for moving incident reports from wikitext to database tables. There are a variety of Cross-site Scripting issues, though all of them require elevated permissions. Some are available to anyone who has the `editincidents` right, some are available to those who can edit interface messages (typically administrators and interface admins), and one is available to those who can edit LocalSettings.php. These issues have been addressed in commit `43896a4` and all users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should prevent access to the Special:IncidentReports page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47816 | Users can impersonate import requesters if their actor IDs coincide in ImportDump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47816</link><description>ImportDump is a mediawiki extension designed to automate user import requests. A user's local actor ID is stored in the database to tell who made what requests. Therefore, if a user on another wiki happens to have the same actor ID as someone on the central wiki, the user on the other wiki can act as if they're the original wiki requester. This can be abused to create new comments, edit the request, and view the request if it's marked private. This issue has been addressed in commit `5c91dfc` and all users are advised to update. Users unable to update may disable the special page outside of their global wiki. See `miraheze/mw-config@e566499` for details on that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47763 | Wasmtime runtime crash when combining tail calls with trapping imports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47763</link><description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly. Wasmtime's implementation of WebAssembly tail calls combined with stack traces can result in a runtime crash in certain WebAssembly modules. The runtime crash may be undefined behavior if Wasmtime was compiled with Rust 1.80 or prior. The runtime crash is a deterministic process abort when Wasmtime is compiled with Rust 1.81 and later. WebAssembly tail calls are a proposal which relatively recently reached stage 4 in the standardization process. Wasmtime first enabled support for tail calls by default in Wasmtime 21.0.0, although that release contained a bug where it was only on-by-default for some configurations. In Wasmtime 22.0.0 tail calls were enabled by default for all configurations. The specific crash happens when an exported function in a WebAssembly module (or component) performs a `return_call` (or `return_call_indirect` or `return_call_ref`) to an imported host function which captures a stack trace (for example, the host function raises a trap). In this situation, the stack-walking code previously assumed there was always at least one WebAssembly frame on the stack but with tail calls that is no longer true. With the tail-call proposal it's possible to have an entry trampoline appear as if it directly called the exit trampoline. This situation triggers an internal assert in the stack-walking code which raises a Rust `panic!()`. When Wasmtime is compiled with Rust versions 1.80 and prior this means that an `extern "C"` function in Rust is raising a `panic!()`. This is technically undefined behavior and typically manifests as a process abort when the unwinder fails to unwind Cranelift-generated frames. When Wasmtime is compiled with Rust versions 1.81 and later this panic becomes a deterministic process abort. Overall the impact of this issue is that this is a denial-of-service vector where a malicious WebAssembly module or component can cause the host to crash. There is no other impact at this time other than availability of a service as the result of the crash is always a crash and no more. This issue was discovered by routine fuzzing performed by the Wasmtime project via Google's OSS-Fuzz infrastructure. We have no evidence that it has ever been exploited by an attacker in the wild. All versions of Wasmtime which have tail calls enabled by default have been patched: * 21.0.x - patched in 21.0.2 * 22.0.x - patched in 22.0.1 * 23.0.x - patched in 23.0.3  * 24.0.x - patched in 24.0.1 * 25.0.x - patched in 25.0.2. Wasmtime versions from 12.0.x (the first release with experimental tail call support) to 20.0.x (the last release with tail-calls off-by-default) have support for tail calls but the support is disabled by default. These versions are not affected in their default configurations, but users who explicitly enabled tail call support will need to either disable tail call support or upgrade to a patched version of Wasmtime. The main workaround for this issue is to disable tail support for tail calls in Wasmtime, for example with `Config::wasm_tail_call(false)`. Users are otherwise encouraged to upgrade to patched versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47813 | Wasmtime race condition could lead to WebAssembly control-flow integrity and type safety violations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47813</link><description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly. Under certain concurrent event orderings, a `wasmtime::Engine`'s internal type registry was susceptible to double-unregistration bugs due to a race condition, leading to panics and potentially type registry corruption. That registry corruption could, following an additional and particular sequence of concurrent events, lead to violations of WebAssembly's control-flow integrity (CFI) and type safety. Users that do not use `wasmtime::Engine` across multiple threads are not affected. Users that only create new modules across threads over time are additionally not affected. Reproducing this bug requires creating and dropping multiple type instances (such as `wasmtime::FuncType` or `wasmtime::ArrayType`) concurrently on multiple threads, where all types are associated with the same `wasmtime::Engine`. **Wasm guests cannot trigger this bug.** See the "References" section below for a list of Wasmtime types-related APIs that are affected. Wasmtime maintains an internal registry of types within a `wasmtime::Engine` and an engine is shareable across threads. Types can be created and referenced through creation of a `wasmtime::Module`, creation of `wasmtime::FuncType`, or a number of other APIs where the host creates a function (see "References" below). Each of these cases interacts with an engine to deduplicate type information and manage type indices that are used to implement type checks in WebAssembly's `call_indirect` function, for example. This bug is a race condition in this management where the internal type registry could be corrupted to trigger an assert or contain invalid state. Wasmtime's internal representation of a type has individual types (e.g. one-per-host-function) maintain a registration count of how many time it's been used. Types additionally have state within an engine behind a read-write lock such as lookup/deduplication information. The race here is a time-of-check versus time-of-use (TOCTOU) bug where one thread atomically decrements a type entry's registration count, observes zero registrations, and then acquires a lock in order to unregister that entry. However, between when this first thread observed the zero-registration count and when it acquires that lock, another thread could perform the following sequence of events: re-register another copy of the type, which deduplicates to that same entry, resurrecting it and incrementing its registration count; then drop the type and decrement its registration count; observe that the registration count is now zero; acquire the type registry lock; and finally unregister the type. Now, when the original thread finally acquires the lock and unregisters the entry, it is the second time this entry has been unregistered. This bug was originally introduced in Wasmtime 19's development of the WebAssembly GC proposal. This bug affects users who are not using the GC proposal, however, and affects Wasmtime in its default configuration even when the GC proposal is disabled. Wasmtime users using 19.0.0 and after are all affected by this issue. We have released the following Wasmtime versions, all of which have a fix for this bug: * 21.0.2 * 22.0.1 * 23.0.3 * 24.0.1 * 25.0.2. If your application creates and drops Wasmtime types on multiple threads concurrently, there are no known workarounds. Users are encouraged to upgrade to a patched release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9463 | Expedition: Unauthenticated OS Command Injection Vulnerability Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9463</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an unauthenticated attacker to run arbitrary OS commands as root in Expedition, resulting in disclosure of usernames, cleartext passwords, device configurations, and device API keys of PAN-OS firewalls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9464 | Expedition: Authenticated OS Command Injection Vulnerability Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9464</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an authenticated attacker to run arbitrary OS commands as root in Expedition, resulting in disclosure of usernames, cleartext passwords, device configurations, and device API keys of PAN-OS firewalls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9465 | Expedition: SQL Injection Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9465</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an unauthenticated attacker to reveal Expedition database contents, such as password hashes, usernames, device configurations, and device API keys. With this, attackers can also create and read arbitrary files on the Expedition system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9466 | Expedition: Cleartext Storage of Information Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9466</link><description>A cleartext storage of sensitive information vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an authenticated attacker to reveal firewall usernames, passwords, and API keys generated using those credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9467 | Expedition: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9467</link><description>A reflected XSS vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition enables execution of malicious JavaScript in the context of an authenticated Expedition user's browser if that user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to Expedition browser session theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9468 | PAN-OS: Firewall Denial of Service (DoS) via a Maliciously Crafted Packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9468</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software allows an unauthenticated attacker to crash PAN-OS due to a crafted packet through the data plane, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. Repeated attempts to trigger this condition will result in PAN-OS entering maintenance mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9469 | Cortex XDR Agent: Local Windows User Can Disable the Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9469</link><description>A problem with a detection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a user with Windows non-administrative privileges to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9470 | Cortex XSOAR: Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9470</link><description>A vulnerability in Cortex XSOAR allows the disclosure of incident data to users who do not have the privilege to view the data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9471 | PAN-OS: Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability in XML API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9471</link><description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the XML API of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated PAN-OS administrator with restricted privileges to use a compromised XML API key to perform actions as a higher privileged PAN-OS administrator. For example, an administrator with "Virtual system administrator (read-only)" access could use an XML API key of a "Virtual system administrator" to perform write operations on the virtual system configuration even though they should be limited to read-only operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9473 | GlobalProtect App: Local Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9473</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows allows a locally authenticated non-administrative Windows user to escalate their privileges to NT AUTHORITY/SYSTEM through the use of the repair functionality offered by the .msi file used to install GlobalProtect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43610 | Copilot Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43610</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45746 | An issue was discovered in Trusted Firmware-M through 2.1.0. User provided (and controlled) mailbox messages contain a pointer to a list of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45746</link><description>An issue was discovered in Trusted Firmware-M through 2.1.0. User provided (and controlled) mailbox messages contain a pointer to a list of input arguments (in_vec) and output arguments (out_vec). These list pointers are never validated. Each argument list contains a buffer pointer and a buffer length field. After a PSA call, the length of the output arguments behind the unchecked pointer is updated in mailbox_direct_reply, regardless of the call result. This allows an attacker to write anywhere in the secure firmware, which can be used to take over the control flow, leading to remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42988 | Lack of access control in ChallengeSolves (/api/v1/challenges/&lt;challenge id&gt;/solves) of CTFd v2.0.0 - v3.7.2 allows authenticated users to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42988</link><description>Lack of access control in ChallengeSolves (/api/v1/challenges//solves) of CTFd v2.0.0 - v3.7.2 allows authenticated users to retrieve a list of users who have solved the challenge, regardless of the Account Visibility settings. The issue is fixed in v3.7.3+.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46307 | A loop hole in the payment logic of Sparkshop v1.16 allows attackers to arbitrarily modify the number of products.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46307</link><description>A loop hole in the payment logic of Sparkshop v1.16 allows attackers to arbitrarily modify the number of products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46316 | DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sub_2C920 function at /cgi-bin/mainfunction.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46316</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sub_2C920 function at /cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying a crafted HTTP message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46292 | A buffer overflow in modsecurity v3.0.12 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input inserted into the name para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46292</link><description>A buffer overflow in modsecurity v3.0.12 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input inserted into the name parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46304 | A Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libcoap v4.3.5-rc2 and below allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the coap_handle_re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46304</link><description>A Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libcoap v4.3.5-rc2 and below allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the coap_handle_request_put_block function in src/coap_block.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25825 | FydeOS for PC 17.1 R114, FydeOS for VMware 17.0 R114, FydeOS for You 17.1 R114, and OpenFyde R114 were discovered to be configured with the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25825</link><description>FydeOS for PC 17.1 R114, FydeOS for VMware 17.0 R114, FydeOS for You 17.1 R114, and OpenFyde R114 were discovered to be configured with the root password saved as a wildcard. This allows attackers to gain root access without a password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47670 | ocfs2: add bounds checking to ocfs2_xattr_find_entry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47670</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: add bounds checking to ocfs2_xattr_find_entry()

Add a paranoia check to make sure it doesn't stray beyond valid memory
region containing ocfs2 xattr entries when scanning for a match.  It will
prevent out-of-bound access in case of crafted images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47671 | USB: usbtmc: prevent kernel-usb-infoleak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47671</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

USB: usbtmc: prevent kernel-usb-infoleak

The syzbot reported a kernel-usb-infoleak in usbtmc_write,
we need to clear the structure before filling fields.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47672 | wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: don&amp;#x27;t wait for tx queues if firmware is dead</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47672</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: don't wait for tx queues if firmware is dead

There is a WARNING in iwl_trans_wait_tx_queues_empty() (that was
recently converted from just a message), that can be hit if we
wait for TX queues to become empty after firmware died. Clearly,
we can't expect anything from the firmware after it's declared dead.

Don't call iwl_trans_wait_tx_queues_empty() in this case. While it could
be a good idea to stop the flow earlier, the flush functions do some
maintenance work that is not related to the firmware, so keep that part
of the code running even when the firmware is not running.

[edit commit message]</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47673 | wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: pause TCM when the firmware is stopped</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47673</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: pause TCM when the firmware is stopped

Not doing so will make us send a host command to the transport while the
firmware is not alive, which will trigger a WARNING.

bad state = 0
WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 17434 at drivers/net/wireless/intel/iwlwifi/iwl-trans.c:115 iwl_trans_send_cmd+0x1cb/0x1e0 [iwlwifi]
RIP: 0010:iwl_trans_send_cmd+0x1cb/0x1e0 [iwlwifi]
Call Trace:
 
 iwl_mvm_send_cmd+0x40/0xc0 [iwlmvm]
 iwl_mvm_config_scan+0x198/0x260 [iwlmvm]
 iwl_mvm_recalc_tcm+0x730/0x11d0 [iwlmvm]
 iwl_mvm_tcm_work+0x1d/0x30 [iwlmvm]
 process_one_work+0x29e/0x640
 worker_thread+0x2df/0x690
 ? rescuer_thread+0x540/0x540
 kthread+0x192/0x1e0
 ? set_kthread_struct+0x90/0x90
 ret_from_fork+0x22/0x30</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7292 | Account Controller allows high count of login attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7292</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.806), a credential stuffing attack is possible through improper restriction of excessive login attempts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8015 | Telerik Report Server Insecure Type Resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8015</link><description>In Progress Telerik Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.924), a remote code execution attack is possible through object injection via an insecure type resolution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7293 | Password policy for new users is not strong enough</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7293</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.806), a password brute forcing attack is possible through weak password requirements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7294 | Uncontrolled resource consumption of anonymous endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7294</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.806), an HTTP DoS attack is possible on anonymous endpoints without rate limiting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7840 | Improper neutralization special element in hyperlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7840</link><description>In Progress Telerik Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q3 (2024.3.924), a command injection attack is possible through improper neutralization of hyperlink elements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47421 | Adobe Framemaker | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47421</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47422 | Adobe Framemaker | Untrusted Search Path (CWE-426)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47422</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Untrusted Search Path vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting a malicious path into the search directories, which the application could unknowingly execute. This could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47423 | Adobe Framemaker | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type (CWE-434)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47423</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which can be automatically processed or executed by the system. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47424 | Adobe Framemaker | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47424</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47425 | Adobe Framemaker | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47425</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9671 | System: pdf invoices of the developer users can be seen if the url is known</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9671</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 3Scale. There is no auth mechanism to see a PDF invoice of a Developer user if the URL is known. Anyone can see the invoice if the URL is known or guessed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9675 | Buildah: buildah allows arbitrary directory mount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9675</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Buildah. Cache mounts do not properly validate that user-specified paths for the cache are within our cache directory, allowing a `RUN` instruction in a Container file to mount an arbitrary directory from the host (read/write) into the container as long as those files can be accessed by the user running Buildah.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45137 | InDesign Desktop | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type (CWE-434)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45137</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions 19.4, 18.5.3 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which, when executed, could run arbitrary code in the context of the server. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8014 | Telerik Reporting EntityDataSource Insecure Type Resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8014</link><description>In Progress Telerik Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q3 (18.2.24.924), a code execution attack is possible through object injection via an insecure type resolution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8048 | Telerik Reporting Insecure Expression Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8048</link><description>In Progress Telerik Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q3 (18.2.24.924), a code execution attack is possible using object injection via insecure expression evaluation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45136 | InCopy | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type (CWE-434)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45136</link><description>InCopy versions 19.4, 18.5.3 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution by an attacker. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which can then be executed on the server. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47661 | drm/amd/display: Avoid overflow from uint32_t to uint8_t</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47661</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Avoid overflow from uint32_t to uint8_t

[WHAT &amp; HOW]
dmub_rb_cmd's ramping_boundary has size of uint8_t and it is assigned
0xFFFF. Fix it by changing it to uint8_t with value of 0xFF.

This fixes 2 INTEGER_OVERFLOW issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47662 | drm/amd/display: Remove register from DCN35 DMCUB diagnostic collection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47662</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Remove register from DCN35 DMCUB diagnostic collection

[Why]
These registers should not be read from driver and triggering the
security violation when DMCUB work times out and diagnostics are
collected blocks Z8 entry.

[How]
Remove the register read from DCN35.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47663 | staging: iio: frequency: ad9834: Validate frequency parameter value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

staging: iio: frequency: ad9834: Validate frequency parameter value

In ad9834_write_frequency() clk_get_rate() can return 0. In such case
ad9834_calc_freqreg() call will lead to division by zero. Checking
'if (fout &gt; (clk_freq / 2))' doesn't protect in case of 'fout' is 0.
ad9834_write_frequency() is called from ad9834_write(), where fout is
taken from text buffer, which can contain any value.

Modify parameters checking.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47664 | spi: hisi-kunpeng: Add verification for the max_frequency provided by the firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: hisi-kunpeng: Add verification for the max_frequency provided by the firmware

If the value of max_speed_hz is 0, it may cause a division by zero
error in hisi_calc_effective_speed().
The value of max_speed_hz is provided by firmware.
Firmware is generally considered as a trusted domain. However, as
division by zero errors can cause system failure, for defense measure,
the value of max_speed is validated here. So 0 is regarded as invalid
and an error code is returned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47665 | i3c: mipi-i3c-hci: Error out instead on BUG_ON() in IBI DMA setup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47665</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i3c: mipi-i3c-hci: Error out instead on BUG_ON() in IBI DMA setup

Definitely condition dma_get_cache_alignment * defined value &gt; 256
during driver initialization is not reason to BUG_ON(). Turn that to
graceful error out with -EINVAL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47666 | scsi: pm80xx: Set phy-&amp;gt;enable_completion only when we wait for it</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47666</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: pm80xx: Set phy-&gt;enable_completion only when we wait for it

pm8001_phy_control() populates the enable_completion pointer with a stack
address, sends a PHY_LINK_RESET / PHY_HARD_RESET, waits 300 ms, and
returns. The problem arises when a phy control response comes late.  After
300 ms the pm8001_phy_control() function returns and the passed
enable_completion stack address is no longer valid. Late phy control
response invokes complete() on a dangling enable_completion pointer which
leads to a kernel crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47667 | PCI: keystone: Add workaround for Errata #i2037 (AM65x SR 1.0)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47667</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: keystone: Add workaround for Errata #i2037 (AM65x SR 1.0)

Errata #i2037 in AM65x/DRA80xM Processors Silicon Revision 1.0
(SPRZ452D_July 2018_Revised December 2019 [1]) mentions when an
inbound PCIe TLP spans more than two internal AXI 128-byte bursts,
the bus may corrupt the packet payload and the corrupt data may
cause associated applications or the processor to hang.

The workaround for Errata #i2037 is to limit the maximum read
request size and maximum payload size to 128 bytes. Add workaround
for Errata #i2037 here.

The errata and workaround is applicable only to AM65x SR 1.0 and
later versions of the silicon will have this fixed.

[1] -&gt; https://www.ti.com/lit/er/sprz452i/sprz452i.pdf</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47668 | lib/generic-radix-tree.c: Fix rare race in __genradix_ptr_alloc()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47668</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

lib/generic-radix-tree.c: Fix rare race in __genradix_ptr_alloc()

If we need to increase the tree depth, allocate a new node, and then
race with another thread that increased the tree depth before us, we'll
still have a preallocated node that might be used later.

If we then use that node for a new non-root node, it'll still have a
pointer to the old root instead of being zeroed - fix this by zeroing it
in the cmpxchg failure path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47669 | nilfs2: fix state management in error path of log writing function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47669</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix state management in error path of log writing function

After commit a694291a6211 ("nilfs2: separate wait function from
nilfs_segctor_write") was applied, the log writing function
nilfs_segctor_do_construct() was able to issue I/O requests continuously
even if user data blocks were split into multiple logs across segments,
but two potential flaws were introduced in its error handling.

First, if nilfs_segctor_begin_construction() fails while creating the
second or subsequent logs, the log writing function returns without
calling nilfs_segctor_abort_construction(), so the writeback flag set on
pages/folios will remain uncleared.  This causes page cache operations to
hang waiting for the writeback flag.  For example,
truncate_inode_pages_final(), which is called via nilfs_evict_inode() when
an inode is evicted from memory, will hang.

Second, the NILFS_I_COLLECTED flag set on normal inodes remain uncleared. 
As a result, if the next log write involves checkpoint creation, that's
fine, but if a partial log write is performed that does not, inodes with
NILFS_I_COLLECTED set are erroneously removed from the "sc_dirty_files"
list, and their data and b-tree blocks may not be written to the device,
corrupting the block mapping.

Fix these issues by uniformly calling nilfs_segctor_abort_construction()
on failure of each step in the loop in nilfs_segctor_do_construct(),
having it clean up logs and segment usages according to progress, and
correcting the conditions for calling nilfs_redirty_inodes() to ensure
that the NILFS_I_COLLECTED flag is cleared.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46870 | drm/amd/display: Disable DMCUB timeout for DCN35</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46870</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Disable DMCUB timeout for DCN35

[Why]
DMCUB can intermittently take longer than expected to process commands.

Old ASIC policy was to continue while logging a diagnostic error - which
works fine for ASIC without IPS, but with IPS this could lead to a race
condition where we attempt to access DCN state while it's inaccessible,
leading to a system hang when the NIU port is not disabled or register
accesses that timeout and the display configuration in an undefined
state.

[How]
We need to investigate why these accesses take longer than expected, but
for now we should disable the timeout on DCN35 to avoid this race
condition. Since the waits happen only at lower interrupt levels the
risk of taking too long at higher IRQ and causing a system watchdog
timeout are minimal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46871 | drm/amd/display: Correct the defined value for AMDGPU_DMUB_NOTIFICATION_MAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46871</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Correct the defined value for AMDGPU_DMUB_NOTIFICATION_MAX

[Why &amp; How]
It actually exposes '6' types in enum dmub_notification_type. Not 5. Using smaller
number to create array dmub_callback &amp; dmub_thread_offload has potential to access
item out of array bound. Fix it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47658 | crypto: stm32/cryp - call finalize with bh disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47658</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: stm32/cryp - call finalize with bh disabled

The finalize operation in interrupt mode produce a produces a spinlock
recursion warning. The reason is the fact that BH must be disabled
during this process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47659 | smack: tcp: ipv4, fix incorrect labeling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47659</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smack: tcp: ipv4, fix incorrect labeling

Currently, Smack mirrors the label of incoming tcp/ipv4 connections:
when a label 'foo' connects to a label 'bar' with tcp/ipv4,
'foo' always gets 'foo' in returned ipv4 packets. So,
1) returned packets are incorrectly labeled ('foo' instead of 'bar')
2) 'bar' can write to 'foo' without being authorized to write.

Here is a scenario how to see this:

* Take two machines, let's call them C and S,
   with active Smack in the default state
   (no settings, no rules, no labeled hosts, only builtin labels)

* At S, add Smack rule 'foo bar w'
   (labels 'foo' and 'bar' are instantiated at S at this moment)

* At S, at label 'bar', launch a program
   that listens for incoming tcp/ipv4 connections

* From C, at label 'foo', connect to the listener at S.
   (label 'foo' is instantiated at C at this moment)
   Connection succeedes and works.

* Send some data in both directions.
* Collect network traffic of this connection.

All packets in both directions are labeled with the CIPSO
of the label 'foo'. Hence, label 'bar' writes to 'foo' without
being authorized, and even without ever being known at C.

If anybody cares: exactly the same happens with DCCP.

This behavior 1st manifested in release 2.6.29.4 (see Fixes below)
and it looks unintentional. At least, no explanation was provided.

I changed returned packes label into the 'bar',
to bring it into line with the Smack documentation claims.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47660 | fsnotify: clear PARENT_WATCHED flags lazily</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47660</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fsnotify: clear PARENT_WATCHED flags lazily

In some setups directories can have many (usually negative) dentries.
Hence __fsnotify_update_child_dentry_flags() function can take a
significant amount of time. Since the bulk of this function happens
under inode-&gt;i_lock this causes a significant contention on the lock
when we remove the watch from the directory as the
__fsnotify_update_child_dentry_flags() call from fsnotify_recalc_mask()
races with __fsnotify_update_child_dentry_flags() calls from
__fsnotify_parent() happening on children. This can lead upto softlockup
reports reported by users.

Fix the problem by calling fsnotify_update_children_dentry_flags() to
set PARENT_WATCHED flags only when parent starts watching children.

When parent stops watching children, clear false positive PARENT_WATCHED
flags lazily in __fsnotify_parent() for each accessed child.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46237 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the patname, pataddress, and medhis parameters in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46237</link><description>PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the patname, pataddress, and medhis parameters in doctor/add-patient.php and doctor/edit-patient.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45138 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45138</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45139 | Substance3D - Stager | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45139</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45140 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45140</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45141 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45141</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45142 | Substance3D - Stager | Write-what-where Condition (CWE-123)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45142</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Write-what-where Condition vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write a controlled value to an arbitrary memory location, potentially leading to code execution. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45143 | Substance3D - Stager | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45143</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45144 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45144</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45152 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45152</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9286 | SQLi in TRtek Software&amp;#x27;s Distant Education Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection'), Improper Input Validation vulnerability in TRtek Software Distant Education Platform allows SQL Injection, Parameter Injection.This issue affects Distant Education Platform: before 3.2024.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9680 | An attacker was able to achieve code execution in the content process by exploiting a use-after-free in Animation timelines. We have had rep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9680</link><description>An attacker was able to achieve code execution in the content process by exploiting a use-after-free in Animation timelines. We have had reports of this vulnerability being exploited in the wild. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131.0.2, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3.1, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.16.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45720 | Apache Subversion: Command line argument injection on Windows platforms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45720</link><description>On Windows platforms, a "best fit" character encoding conversion of command line arguments to Subversion's executables (e.g., svn.exe, etc.) may lead to unexpected command line argument interpretation, including argument injection and execution of other programs, if a specially crafted command line argument string is processed.

All versions of Subversion up to and including Subversion 1.14.3 are affected on Windows platforms only. Users are recommended to upgrade to version Subversion 1.14.4, which fixes this issue.

Subversion is not affected on UNIX-like platforms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28168 | Apache XML Graphics FOP: XML External Entity (XXE) Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28168</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference ('XXE') vulnerability in Apache XML Graphics FOP.

This issue affects Apache XML Graphics FOP: 2.9.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 12:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47334 | WordPress Zoho Flow for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47334</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Zoho Flow Zoho Flow for WordPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Zoho Flow for WordPress: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 10:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45145 | Lightroom Desktop | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45145</link><description>Lightroom Desktop versions 7.4.1, 13.5, 12.5.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9575 | Local File Inclusion in pretix-widget WordPress plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9575</link><description>Local File Inclusion vulnerability in pretix Widget WordPress plugin pretix-widget on Windows allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects pretix Widget WordPress plugin: from 1.0.0 through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47410 | Animate | Stack-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-121)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47410</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47411 | Animate | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47411</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47412 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47412</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47413 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47413</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47414 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47414</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47415 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47415</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47416 | Animate | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47416</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47417 | Animate | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47417</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47418 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47418</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47419 | Animate | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47419</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47420 | Animate | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47420</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20787 | Substance3D - Painter | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20787</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 10.0.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45146 | Dimension | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45146</link><description>Dimension versions 4.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45150 | Dimension | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45150</link><description>Dimension versions 4.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9451 | Embed PDF Viewer &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via height and width Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9451</link><description>The Embed PDF Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'height' and 'width' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 07:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39586 | Dell AppSync Server, version 4.3 through 4.6, contains an XML External Entity Injection vulnerability. An adjacent high privileged attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39586</link><description>Dell AppSync Server, version 4.3 through 4.6, contains an XML External Entity Injection vulnerability. An adjacent high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39436 | In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39436</link><description>In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39437 | In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39437</link><description>In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39438 | In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39438</link><description>In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39439 | In DRM service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39439</link><description>In DRM service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39440 | In DRM service, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to local denial of service with System exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39440</link><description>In DRM service, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9449 | Auto iFrame &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via tag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9449</link><description>The Auto iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tag' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45872 | An issue was discovered in Qt before 6.2.11 and 6.3.x through 6.6.x before 6.6.1. When a QML image refers to an image whose content is not k...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45872</link><description>An issue was discovered in Qt before 6.2.11 and 6.3.x through 6.6.x before 6.6.1. When a QML image refers to an image whose content is not known yet, there is an assumption that it is an SVG document, leading to a denial of service (application crash) if it is not actually an SVG document.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46586 | cgi.c in weborf .0.17, 0.18, 0.19, and 0.20 (before 1.0) lacks '\0' termination of the path for CGI scripts because strncpy is misused.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46586</link><description>cgi.c in weborf .0.17, 0.18, 0.19, and 0.20 (before 1.0) lacks '\0' termination of the path for CGI scripts because strncpy is misused.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5968 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt;= 1.8.27 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5968</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.28 does not properly sanitise and escape some of its Gallery settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45359 | An issue was discovered in the Vector Skin component for MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. vector-toc-toggle-button-label is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45359</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Vector Skin component for MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. vector-toc-toggle-button-label is not escaped, but should be, because the line param can have markup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45361 | An issue was discovered in VectorComponentUserLinks.php in the Vector Skin component in MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45361</link><description>An issue was discovered in VectorComponentUserLinks.php in the Vector Skin component in MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. vector-intro-page MalformedTitleException is uncaught if it is not a valid title, leading to incorrect web pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37154 | check_by_ssh in Nagios nagios-plugins 2.4.5 allows arbitrary command execution via ProxyCommand, LocalCommand, and PermitLocalCommand with \...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37154</link><description>check_by_ssh in Nagios nagios-plugins 2.4.5 allows arbitrary command execution via ProxyCommand, LocalCommand, and PermitLocalCommand with \${IFS}. This has been categorized both as fixed in e8810de, and as intended behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36325 | i2p before 2.3.0 (Java) allows de-anonymizing the public IPv4 and IPv6 addresses of i2p hidden services (aka eepsites) via a correlation att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36325</link><description>i2p before 2.3.0 (Java) allows de-anonymizing the public IPv4 and IPv6 addresses of i2p hidden services (aka eepsites) via a correlation attack across the IPv4 and IPv6 addresses that occurs when a tunneled, replayed message has a behavior discrepancy (it may be dropped, or may result in a Wrong Destination response). An attack would take days to complete.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42934 | OpenIPMI before 2.0.36 has an out-of-bounds array access (for authentication type) in the ipmi_sim simulator, resulting in denial of service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42934</link><description>OpenIPMI before 2.0.36 has an out-of-bounds array access (for authentication type) in the ipmi_sim simulator, resulting in denial of service or (with very low probability) authentication bypass or code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45160 | Incorrect credential validation in LemonLDAP::NG 2.18.x and 2.19.x before 2.19.2 allows attackers to bypass OAuth2 client authentication via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45160</link><description>Incorrect credential validation in LemonLDAP::NG 2.18.x and 2.19.x before 2.19.2 allows attackers to bypass OAuth2 client authentication via an empty client_password parameter (client secret).</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47191 | pam_oath.so in oath-toolkit 2.6.7 through 2.6.11 before 2.6.12 allows root privilege escalation because, in the context of PAM code running ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47191</link><description>pam_oath.so in oath-toolkit 2.6.7 through 2.6.11 before 2.6.12 allows root privilege escalation because, in the context of PAM code running as root, it mishandles usersfile access, such as by calling fchown in the presence of a symlink.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32608 | HDF5 library through 1.14.3 has memory corruption in H5A__close resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32608</link><description>HDF5 library through 1.14.3 has memory corruption in H5A__close resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45179 | An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401 and 6.00PL01. Due to insufficient input validation, the C-MOR web int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45179</link><description>An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401 and 6.00PL01. Due to insufficient input validation, the C-MOR web interface is vulnerable to OS command injection attacks. It was found out that different functionality is vulnerable to OS command injection attacks, for example for generating new X.509 certificates, or setting the time zone. These OS command injection vulnerabilities in the script generatesslreq.pml can be exploited as a low-privileged authenticated user to execute commands in the context of the Linux user www-data via shell metacharacters in HTTP POST data (e.g., the city parameter). The OS command injection vulnerability in the script settimezone.pml or setdatetime.pml (e.g., via the year parameter) requires an administrative user for the C-MOR web interface. By also exploiting a privilege-escalation vulnerability, it is possible to execute commands on the C-MOR system with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35288 | Nitro PDF Pro before 13.70.8.82 and 14.x before 14.26.1.0 allows Local Privilege Escalation in the MSI Installer because custom actions occu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35288</link><description>Nitro PDF Pro before 13.70.8.82 and 14.x before 14.26.1.0 allows Local Privilege Escalation in the MSI Installer because custom actions occur unsafely in repair mode. CertUtil is run in a conhost.exe window, and there is a mechanism allowing CTRL+o to launch cmd.exe as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25284 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Method via the threeDsMethod.jsp threeDSMethodData parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25284</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Method via the threeDsMethod.jsp threeDSMethodData parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25285 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows form action hijacking via threeDsMethod.jsp?threeDSMethodData= or the threeDSMethodNotificationURL parameter. The destin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25285</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows form action hijacking via threeDsMethod.jsp?threeDSMethodData= or the threeDSMethodNotificationURL parameter. The destination web site for a form submission can be modified.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25286 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows CSRF in the Authorization Method via modified Origin and Referer HTTP headers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25286</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows CSRF in the Authorization Method via modified Origin and Referer HTTP headers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25282 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows XSS in its 3DSMethod Authentication via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redirect?action=ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25282</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows XSS in its 3DSMethod Authentication via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redirect?action=challenge&amp;amp;txn= substring.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25283 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Challenge via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25283</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Challenge via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redirect?action=challenge&amp;amp;txn= substring.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7963 | CMSMasters Content Composer &amp;lt;= 1.8.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7963</link><description>The CMSMasters Content Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's multiple shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 02:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>