<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:43:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-7731 | SECOM Dr.ID Access control  system - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7731</link><description>Dr.ID Access Control System from SECOM does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7588 | Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.87 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Accordion Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7588</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion block in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.87 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7729 | CAYIN Technology CMS - Sensitive File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7729</link><description>The CAYIN Technology CMS lacks proper access control, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to download arbitrary CGI files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7728 | CAYIN Technology CMS - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7728</link><description>The specific CGI of the CAYIN Technology CMS does not properly validate user input, allowing a remote attacker with administrator privileges to inject OS commands into the specific parameter and execute them on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20082 | In Modem, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20082</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01182594; Issue ID: MSV-1529.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20083 | In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20083</link><description>In venc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08810810 / ALPS08805789; Issue ID: MSV-1502.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36136 | An off-by-one error in WLInfoRailService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36136</link><description>An off-by-one error in WLInfoRailService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting in a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37373 | Improper input validation in the Central Filestore in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin rights to ach...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37373</link><description>Improper input validation in the Central Filestore in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin rights to achieve RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37399 | A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37399</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the service, resulting in a DoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38652 | Path traversal in the skin management component of Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38652</link><description>Path traversal in the skin management component of Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve denial of service via arbitrary file deletion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38653 | XXE in SmartDeviceServer in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38653</link><description>XXE in SmartDeviceServer in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.1 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7753 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System user_images direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user_images/. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7754 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System check_medicine_name.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7754</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax/check_medicine_name.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7752 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System update_medicine.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7752</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /update_medicine.php. The manipulation of the argument medicine_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38163 | Windows Update Stack Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38163</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7751 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System update_medicine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7751</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /update_medicine.php. The manipulation of the argument hidden_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7750 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System medicines.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7750</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /medicines.php. The manipulation of the argument medicine_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28986 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Java Deserialization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28986</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was susceptible to a Java Deserialization  Remote Code Execution that would allow access to run commands on the host machine.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7749 | SourceCodester Accounts Manager App add-account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7749</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Accounts Manager App 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/add-account.php. The manipulation of the argument account_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 22:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7748 | SourceCodester Accounts Manager App delete-account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7748</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Accounts Manager App 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-account.php. The manipulation of the argument account leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7742 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint multiDownload server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7742</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function multiDownload of the file /api/file/multiDownload of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument file leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7743 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint downloadUrl server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7743</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function downloadUrl of the file /api/file/downloadUrl of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument file leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7740 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint download server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7740</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function download of the file /api/test/download of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7741 | wanglongcn ltcms API Endpoint downloadfile downloadFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7741</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wanglongcn ltcms 1.0.20 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function downloadFile of the file /api/file/downloadfile of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42368 | open-telemetry has an Observable Timing Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42368</link><description>OpenTelemetry, also known as OTel, is a vendor-neutral open source Observability framework for instrumenting, generating, collecting, and exporting telemetry data such as traces, metrics, and logs. The bearertokenauth extension's server authenticator performs a simple, non-constant time string comparison of the received &amp; configured bearer tokens. This impacts anyone using the `bearertokenauth` server authenticator. Malicious clients with network access to the collector may perform a timing attack against a collector with this authenticator to guess the configured token, by iteratively sending tokens and comparing the response time. This would allow an attacker to introduce fabricated or bad data into the collector's telemetry pipeline. The observable timing vulnerability was fixed by using constant-time comparison in  0.107.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7738 | yzane vscode-markdown-pdf Markdown File pathname traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7738</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in yzane vscode-markdown-pdf 1.5.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Markdown File Handler. The manipulation leads to pathname traversal. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7739 | yzane vscode-markdown-pdf cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7739</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in yzane vscode-markdown-pdf 1.5.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7569 | An information disclosure vulnerability in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM versions 2023.4 and earlier allows an unauthenticated at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7569</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM versions 2023.4 and earlier allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the OIDC client secret via debug information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7570 | Improper certificate validation in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM Versions 2023.4 and earlier allows a remote attacker in a MITM p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7570</link><description>Improper certificate validation in Ivanti ITSM on-prem and Neurons for ITSM Versions 2023.4 and earlier allows a remote attacker in a MITM position to craft a token that would allow access to ITSM as any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7593 | Incorrect implementation of an authentication algorithm in Ivanti vTM other than versions 22.2R1 or 22.7R2 allows a remote unauthenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7593</link><description>Incorrect implementation of an authentication algorithm in Ivanti vTM other than versions 22.2R1 or 22.7R2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication of the admin panel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7733 | FastCMS New Article Category Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7733</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in FastCMS up to 0.1.5. Affected is an unknown function of the component New Article Category Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7567 | Rockwell Automation Micro850/870 Vulnerable to denial-of-service Vulnerability via CIP/Modbus Port</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7567</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists via the CIP/Modbus port in the Rockwell Automation Micro850/870 (2080 -L50E/2080 -L70E). If exploited, the CIP/Modbus communication may be disrupted for short duration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6079 | DLL Hijacking Vulnerability Exists in Rockwell Automation Emulate3D™</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6079</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Emulate3D™, which could be leveraged to execute a DLL Hijacking attack. The application loads shared libraries, which are readable and writable by any user. If exploited, a malicious user could leverage a malicious dll and perform a remote code execution attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29995 | Windows Kerberos Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29995</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37968 | Windows DNS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37968</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38063 | Windows TCP/IP Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38063</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38084 | Microsoft OfficePlus Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38084</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38098 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38098</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38106 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38106</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38107 | Windows Power Dependency Coordinator Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38107</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38108 | Azure Stack Hub Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38108</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38109 | Azure Health Bot Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38109</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38114 | Windows IP Routing Management Snapin Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38114</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38115 | Windows IP Routing Management Snapin Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38115</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38116 | Windows IP Routing Management Snapin Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38116</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38117 | NTFS Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38117</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38118 | Microsoft Local Security Authority (LSA) Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38118</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38120 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38120</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38121 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38121</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38122 | Microsoft Local Security Authority (LSA) Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38122</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38123 | Windows Bluetooth Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38123</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38125 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38125</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38126 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38126</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38127 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38127</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38128 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38128</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38130 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38130</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38131 | Clipboard Virtual Channel Extension Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38131</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38132 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38132</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38133 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38133</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38134 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38134</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38135 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38135</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38136 | Windows Resource Manager PSM Service Extension Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38136</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38137 | Windows Resource Manager PSM Service Extension Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38137</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38138 | Windows Deployment Services Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38138</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38140 | Windows Reliable Multicast Transport Driver (RMCAST) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38140</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38141 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38141</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38142 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38142</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38143 | Windows WLAN AutoConfig Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38143</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38144 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38144</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38145 | Windows Layer-2 Bridge Network Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38145</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38146 | Windows Layer-2 Bridge Network Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38146</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38147 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38147</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38148 | Windows Secure Channel Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38148</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38150 | Windows DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38150</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38151 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38151</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38152 | Windows OLE Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38152</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38153 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38153</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38154 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38154</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38155 | Security Center Broker Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38155</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38157 | Azure IoT SDK Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38157</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38158 | Azure IoT SDK Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38158</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38159 | Windows Network Virtualization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38159</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38160 | Windows Network Virtualization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38160</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38161 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38161</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38162 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38162</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38165 | Windows Compressed Folder Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38165</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38167 | .NET and Visual Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38167</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38168 | .NET and Visual Studio Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38168</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38169 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38169</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38170 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38170</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38171 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38171</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38172 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38172</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38173 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38173</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38177 | Windows App Installer Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38177</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38178 | Scripting Engine Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38178</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38180 | Windows SmartScreen Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38180</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38184 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38184</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38185 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38185</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38186 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38186</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38187 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38187</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38189 | Microsoft Project Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38189</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38191 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38191</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38193 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38193</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38195 | Azure CycleCloud Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38195</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38196 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38196</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38197 | Microsoft Teams for iOS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38197</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38198 | Windows Print Spooler Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38198</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38199 | Windows Line Printer Daemon (LPD) Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38199</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38201 | Azure Stack Hub Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38201</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38211 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38211</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38213 | Windows Mark of the Web Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38213</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38214 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38214</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38215 | Windows Cloud Files Mini Filter Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38215</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38223 | Windows Initial Machine Configuration Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37015 | An issue was discovered in Ada Web Server 20.0. When configured to use SSL (which is not the default setting), the SSL/TLS used to establish...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37015</link><description>An issue was discovered in Ada Web Server 20.0. When configured to use SSL (which is not the default setting), the SSL/TLS used to establish connections to external services is done without proper hostname validation. This is exploitable by man-in-the-middle attackers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31339 | Improper input validation in ARM® Trusted Firmware used in AMD’s Zynq™ UltraScale+™) MPSoC/RFSoC may allow a privileged attacker to perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31339</link><description>Improper input validation in ARM® Trusted Firmware used in AMD’s Zynq™ UltraScale+™) MPSoC/RFSoC may allow a privileged attacker to perform out of bound reads, potentially resulting in data leakage and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31341 | Insufficient
validation of the Input Output Control (IOCTL) input buffer in AMD μProf may
allow an authenticated attacker to cause an out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31341</link><description>Insufficient
validation of the Input Output Control (IOCTL) input buffer in AMD μProf may
allow an authenticated attacker to cause an out-of-bounds write, potentially
causing a Windows® OS crash, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31348 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31348</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31349 | Incorrect default permissions in the AMD μProf installation directory could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31349</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in the AMD μProf installation directory could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31366 | Improper input validation in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to perform a write to an invalid address, potentially resulting in denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31366</link><description>Improper input validation in AMD μProf could allow an attacker to perform a write to an invalid address, potentially resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21981 | Improper key usage control in AMD Secure Processor
(ASP) may allow an attacker with local access who has gained arbitrary code
execution pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21981</link><description>Improper key usage control in AMD Secure Processor
(ASP) may allow an attacker with local access who has gained arbitrary code
execution privilege in ASP to
extract ASP cryptographic keys, potentially resulting in loss of
confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41613 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Symphony CMS 2.7.10 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML by editing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41613</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Symphony CMS 2.7.10 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML by editing note.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41614 | symphonycms &lt;=2.7.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Comment component for articles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41614</link><description>symphonycms &lt;=2.7.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Comment component for articles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26344 | An out of bounds memory write when processing the AMD
PSP1 Configuration Block (APCB) could allow an attacker with access the ability
to mod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26344</link><description>An out of bounds memory write when processing the AMD
PSP1 Configuration Block (APCB) could allow an attacker with access the ability
to modify the BIOS image, and the ability to sign the resulting image, to
potentially modify the APCB block resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26367 | A malicious attacker in x86 can misconfigure the Trusted Memory Regions (TMRs), which may allow the attacker to set an arbitrary address ran...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26367</link><description>A malicious attacker in x86 can misconfigure the Trusted Memory Regions (TMRs), which may allow the attacker to set an arbitrary address range for the TMR, potentially leading to a loss of integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26387 | Insufficient access controls in ASP kernel may allow a
privileged attacker with access to AMD signing keys and the BIOS menu or UEFI
shell t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26387</link><description>Insufficient access controls in ASP kernel may allow a
privileged attacker with access to AMD signing keys and the BIOS menu or UEFI
shell to map DRAM regions in protected areas, potentially leading to a loss of platform integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46746 | Lack of stack protection exploit mechanisms in ASP Secure OS Trusted Execution Environment (TEE) may allow a privileged attacker with access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46746</link><description>Lack of stack protection exploit mechanisms in ASP Secure OS Trusted Execution Environment (TEE) may allow a privileged attacker with access to AMD signing
keys to c006Frrupt the return address, causing a
stack-based buffer overrun, potentially leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46772 | Insufficient input validation in the ABL may allow a privileged
attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell to tamper with the
struc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46772</link><description>Insufficient input validation in the ABL may allow a privileged
attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell to tamper with the
structure headers in SPI ROM causing an out of bounds memory read and write,
potentially resulting in memory corruption or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23815 | Improper bounds checking in APCB firmware may allow an attacker to perform an out of bounds write, corrupting the APCB entry, potentially le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23815</link><description>Improper bounds checking in APCB firmware may allow an attacker to perform an out of bounds write, corrupting the APCB entry, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23817 | Insufficient checking of memory buffer in ASP Secure OS may allow an attacker with a malicious TA to read/write to the ASP Secure OS kernel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23817</link><description>Insufficient checking of memory buffer in ASP Secure OS may allow an attacker with a malicious TA to read/write to the ASP Secure OS kernel virtual address space, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20509 | An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to perform a DMA read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20509</link><description>An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to perform a DMA read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, potentially resulting in loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20510 | An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, potentially re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20510</link><description>An insufficient DRAM address validation in PMFW may allow a privileged attacker to read from an invalid DRAM address to SRAM, potentially resulting in data corruption or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20512 | A hardcoded AES   key in PMFW may result in a privileged attacker gaining access to the key, potentially resulting in internal debug informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20512</link><description>A hardcoded AES   key in PMFW may result in a privileged attacker gaining access to the key, potentially resulting in internal debug information leakage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20513 | An insufficient bounds check in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker to utilize a malicious VF (virtualization function) t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20513</link><description>An insufficient bounds check in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker to utilize a malicious VF (virtualization function) to send a malformed message, potentially resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20518 | Incomplete cleanup in the ASP may expose the Master Encryption Key (MEK) to a privileged attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20518</link><description>Incomplete cleanup in the ASP may expose the Master Encryption Key (MEK) to a privileged attacker with access to the BIOS menu or UEFI shell and a memory exfiltration vulnerability, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20578 | A TOCTOU (Time-Of-Check-Time-Of-Use) in SMM may allow
an attacker with ring0 privileges and access to the
BIOS menu or UEFI shell to modify ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20578</link><description>A TOCTOU (Time-Of-Check-Time-Of-Use) in SMM may allow
an attacker with ring0 privileges and access to the
BIOS menu or UEFI shell to modify the communications buffer potentially
resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20584 | IOMMU improperly handles certain special address
ranges with invalid device table entries (DTEs), which may allow an attacker
with privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20584</link><description>IOMMU improperly handles certain special address
ranges with invalid device table entries (DTEs), which may allow an attacker
with privileges and a compromised Hypervisor to
induce DTE faults to bypass RMP checks in SEV-SNP, potentially leading to a
loss of guest integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20591 | Improper re-initialization of IOMMU during the DRTM event
may permit an untrusted platform configuration to persist, allowing an attacker
to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20591</link><description>Improper re-initialization of IOMMU during the DRTM event
may permit an untrusted platform configuration to persist, allowing an attacker
to read or modify hypervisor memory, potentially resulting in loss of
confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31304 | Improper input validation in SMU may allow an attacker with privileges and a compromised physical function (PF)      to modify the PCIe® lan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31304</link><description>Improper input validation in SMU may allow an attacker with privileges and a compromised physical function (PF)      to modify the PCIe® lane count and speed, potentially leading to a loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31305 | Generation of weak and predictable Initialization Vector (IV) in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker with privileges to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31305</link><description>Generation of weak and predictable Initialization Vector (IV) in PMFW (Power Management Firmware) may allow an attacker with privileges to reuse IV values to reverse-engineer debug data, potentially resulting in information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31307 | Improper validation of array index in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow a privileged attacker to cause an out-of-bounds memory read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31307</link><description>Improper validation of array index in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow a privileged attacker to cause an out-of-bounds memory read within PMFW, potentially leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31310 | Improper input validation in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow an attacker with privileges to send a malformed input for the "set t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31310</link><description>Improper input validation in Power Management Firmware (PMFW) may allow an attacker with privileges to send a malformed input for the "set temperature input selection" command, potentially resulting in a loss of integrity and/or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31356 | Incomplete system memory cleanup in SEV firmware could
allow a privileged attacker to corrupt guest private memory, potentially
resulting in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31356</link><description>Incomplete system memory cleanup in SEV firmware could
allow a privileged attacker to corrupt guest private memory, potentially
resulting in a loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41711 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41711</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (R6.4.0.136) could allow an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to the phone to conduct an argument injection attack, due to insufficient parameter sanitization. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6619 | Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource in Ocean Data Systems Dream Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6619</link><description>In Ocean Data Systems Dream Report, an incorrect permission vulnerability could allow a local unprivileged attacker to escalate their privileges and could cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36446 | The provisioning manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE through 7.6 SP1 could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct an authenticatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36446</link><description>The provisioning manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE through 7.6 SP1 could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct an authentication bypass attack due to improper access control. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to bypass the authorization schema.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6618 | Path Traversal in Ocean Data Systems Dream Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6618</link><description>In Ocean Data Systems Dream Report, a path traversal vulnerability could allow an attacker to perform remote code execution through the injection of a malicious dynamic-link library (DLL).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7113 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in AVEVA SuiteLink Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7113</link><description>If exploited, this vulnerability could cause a SuiteLink server to consume excessive system resources and slow down processing of Data I/O for the duration of the attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27486 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiDDoS version 5.5.0 through 5.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27486</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiDDoS version 5.5.0 through 5.5.1, 5.4.2 through 5.4.0, 5.3.0 through 5.3.1, 5.2.0, 5.1.0, 5.0.0, 4.7.0, 4.6.0 and 4.5.0 and FortiDDoS-F version 6.3.0 through 6.3.1, 6.2.0 through 6.2.2, 6.1.0 through 6.1.4 allows an authenticated attacker to execute shell code as `root` via `execute` CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45862 | An insufficient session expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] vulnerability in FortiOS 7.2.5 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45862</link><description>An insufficient session expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] vulnerability in FortiOS 7.2.5 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; FortiProxy 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions; FortiPAM 1.3 all versions, 1.2 all versions, 1.1 all versions, 1.0 all versions; FortiSwitchManager 7.2.1 and below, 7.0 all versions GUI may allow attackers to re-use websessions after GUI logout, should they manage to acquire the required credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26211 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('cross-site scripting') in Fortinet FortiSOAR 7.3.0 through 7.3.2 allows an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26211</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('cross-site scripting') in Fortinet FortiSOAR 7.3.0 through 7.3.2 allows an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the Communications module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21757 | A unverified password change in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, and versions 7.4.0 throug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21757</link><description>A unverified password change in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, and versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.1, as well as Fortinet FortiAnalyzer versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, and versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.1, allows an attacker to modify admin passwords via the device configuration backup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36505 | An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.5 through 7.2.7, 7.0.12 through 7.0.14 and 6.4.x may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36505</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.5 through 7.2.7, 7.0.12 through 7.0.14 and 6.4.x may allow an attacker who has already successfully obtained write access to the underlying system (via another hypothetical exploit) to bypass the file integrity checking system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7746 | Use of default credentials at Traccar fleet management solution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7746</link><description>Use of Default Credentials vulnerability in Tananaev Solutions Traccar Server on Administrator Panel modules allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects the privileged transactions implemented by the Traccar solution that should otherwise be protected by the authentication mechanism. 
These transactions could have an impact on any sensitive aspect of the platform, including Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6384 | Backup files may be downloaded by underprivileged users in MongoDB Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6384</link><description>"Hot" backup files may be downloaded by underprivileged users, if they are capable of acquiring a unique backup identifier. This issue affects MongoDB Enterprise Server v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.16, MongoDB Enterprise Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.11 and MongoDB Enterprise Server v7.3 versions prior to 7.3.3</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42736 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in addBlacklist. Au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42736</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in addBlacklist. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42737 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in delBlacklist. Au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42737</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in delBlacklist. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42738 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setDmzCfg. Authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42738</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setDmzCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42739 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setAccessDeviceC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42739</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setAccessDeviceCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42740 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setLedCfg. Authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42740</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setLedCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41623 | An issue in D3D Security D3D IP Camera (D8801) v.V9.1.17.1.4-20180428 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41623</link><description>An issue in D3D Security D3D IP Camera (D8801) v.V9.1.17.1.4-20180428 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6788 | Phoenix Contact: update feature from CHARX controller can be used to reset a low privilege user password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6788</link><description>A remote unauthenticated attacker can use the firmware update feature on the LAN interface of the device to reset the password for the predefined, low-privileged user “user-app” to the default password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38501 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Device Master ICDM-RX/* XSS vulnerability allows HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38501</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a HTML injection vulnerability with limited length to inject malicious HTML code and gain low-privileged access on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38502 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Device Master ICDM-RX/* XSS vulnerability allows stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38502</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use stored XSS vulnerability to obtain information from a user or reboot the affected device once.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3913 | Phoenix Contact: Start sequence allows attack during the boot process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3913</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use this vulnerability to change the device configuration due to a file writeable for short time after system startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5849 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Device Master ICDM-RX/* XSS vulnerability allows reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5849</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a reflected XSS vulnerability to obtain information from a user or reboot the affected device once.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43160 | WordPress BerqWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43160</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in BerqWP allows Code Injection.This issue affects BerqWP: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43165 | WordPress WPSection plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Contributor+ Limited Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43165</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Rashid87 WPSection allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WPSection: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37287 | Kibana arbitrary code execution via prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37287</link><description>A flaw allowing arbitrary code execution was discovered in Kibana. An attacker with access to ML and Alerting connector features, as well as write access to internal ML indices can trigger a prototype pollution vulnerability, ultimately leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43138 | WordPress Event Manager and Tickets Selling Plugin for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43138</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in MagePeople Team Event Manager for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Event Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43140 | WordPress  Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43140</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in G5Theme Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43141 | WordPress Participants Database plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.9.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43141</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Roland Barker, xnau webdesign Participants Database allows Object Injection.This issue affects Participants Database: from n/a through 2.5.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43153 | WordPress Woffice theme &amp;lt;= 5.4.10 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43153</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Woffice: from n/a through 5.4.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35124 | IBM OpenBMC authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35124</link><description>A vulnerability in the combination of the OpenBMC's FW1050.00 through FW1050.10, FW1030.00 through FW1030.50, and FW1020.00 through FW1020.60 default password and session management allow an attacker to gain administrative access to the BMC.  IBM X-Force ID:  290674.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40697 | IBM Common Licensing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40697</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  297895.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41774 | IBM Common Licensing cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41774</link><description>IBM Common Licensing 9.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  350348.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43131 | WordPress Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist) plugin &amp;lt; 1.7.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post/Page Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43131</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in WPWeb Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist) allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Docket (WooCommerce Collections / Wishlist / Watchlist): from n/a before 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43135 | WordPress WPCafe plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.28 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43135</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Themewinter WPCafe allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WPCafe: from n/a through 2.2.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39651 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Vouchers plugin &amp;lt; 4.9.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39651</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WPWeb WooCommerce PDF Vouchers allows File Manipulation.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Vouchers: from n/a before 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43121 | WordPress HUSKY plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43121</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in realmag777 HUSKY allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects HUSKY: from n/a through 1.3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43128 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Table Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43128</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WC Product Table WooCommerce Product Table Lite allows Code Injection.This issue affects WooCommerce Product Table Lite: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43129 | WordPress BetterDocs plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43129</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WPDeveloper BetterDocs allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects BetterDocs: from n/a through 3.5.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39642 | WordPress LearnPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.2 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39642</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects LearnPress: from n/a through 4.2.6.8.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38760 | WordPress Send Users Email plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38760</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in David Maucher Send Users Email allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Send Users Email: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38787 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26.8 - Sensitive Information via Imported File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38787</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Codection Import and export users and customers allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.26.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38747 | WordPress HitPay Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38747</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HitPay Payment Solutions Pte Ltd HitPay Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects HitPay Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38749 | WordPress Olive One Click Demo Import plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38749</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Olive Themes Olive One Click Demo Import allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Olive One Click Demo Import: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38752 | WordPress Zoho Campaigns plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zoho Campaigns allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Zoho Campaigns: from n/a through 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38756 | WordPress Coming Soon Page – Responsive Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38756</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Weblizar Coming Soon allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Coming Soon: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2259 | Reflected XXS Vulnerability in InstaRISPACS Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2259</link><description>This vulnerability exists in InstaRISPACS software due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the loginTo parameter in user login module of the web interface of the application. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted input to the vulnerable parameter to perform reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attacks on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38699 | WordPress Wallet System for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.13 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Exported File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38699</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Swings Wallet System for WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Wallet System for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.5.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38724 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Summary and Print plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38724</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Muhammad Rehman Contact Form 7 Summary and Print allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Summary and Print: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38742 | WordPress MBE eShip plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38742</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in MBE Worldwide S.P.A. MBE eShip allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects MBE eShip: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37935 | WordPress Woocommerce OpenPos plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.4 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37935</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in anhvnit Woocommerce OpenPos allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Woocommerce OpenPos: from n/a through 6.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38688 | WordPress Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Igor Benić Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes: from n/a through 8.2.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36398 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application executes a subset of its services as `NT AU...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36398</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application executes a subset of its services as `NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM`. This could allow a local attacker to execute operating system commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39922 | A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA1) (All version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39922</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCE (6ED1052-1FB08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCEo (6ED1052-2FB08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24CE (6ED1052-1CC08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24CEo (6ED1052-2CC08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCE (6ED1052-1HB08-0BA1) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCEo (6ED1052-2HB08-0BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCE (6AG1052-1MD08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6AG1052-2MD08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCE (6AG1052-1FB08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCEo (6AG1052-2FB08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CE (6AG1052-1CC08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CEo (6AG1052-2CC08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCE (6AG1052-1HB08-7BA1) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCEo (6AG1052-2HB08-7BA1) (All versions). Affected devices store user passwords in plaintext without proper protection. This could allow a physical attacker to retrieve them from the embedded storage ICs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41681 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). The web server of affected products is configured...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41681</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). The web server of affected products is configured to support weak ciphers  by default. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker in an on-path position to to read and modify any data passed over the connection between legitimate clients and the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41682 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce restric...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41682</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce restriction of  excessive authentication attempts. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to conduct brute force attacks against legitimate user passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41683 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce a stron...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41683</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence family (All versions &lt; V4.4). Affected products do not properly enforce a strong user password policy. This could facilitate a brute force attack against legitimate user passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41903 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application mounts th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41903</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application mounts the container's root filesystem with read and write privileges. This could allow an attacker to alter the container's filesystem leading to unauthorized modifications and data corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41904 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41904</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not properly enforce restriction of  excessive authentication attempts. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct brute force attacks against legitimate user credentials or keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41905 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41905</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application do not have access control for accessing the files. This could allow an authenticated attacker with low privilege's to get access to sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41906 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application does not ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41906</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application does not properly handle cacheable HTTP responses in the web service. This could allow an attacker to read and modify data stored in the local cache.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41907 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application is missin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41907</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC Traffic Analyzer (6GK8822-1BG01-0BA0) (All versions &lt; V2.0). The affected application is missing general HTTP security headers in the web server. This could allow an attacker to make the servers more prone to clickjacking attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41908 | A vulnerability has been identified in NX (All versions &lt; V2406.3000). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41908</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in NX (All versions &lt; V2406.3000). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PRT files. This could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41938 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The importCertificate function of the SINEC NMS Control web applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41938</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The importCertificate function of the SINEC NMS Control web application contains a path traversal vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated attacker it to delete arbitrary certificate files on the drive SINEC NMS is installed on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41939 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41939</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization checks. This could allow an authenticated attacker to bypass the checks and elevate their privileges on the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41940 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly validate user input to a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41940</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly validate user input to a privileged command queue. This could allow an authenticated attacker to execute OS commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41941 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41941</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V3.0). The affected application does not properly enforce authorization checks. This could allow an authenticated attacker to bypass the checks and modify settings in the application without authorization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41976 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41976</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1). Affected devices do not properly validate input in specific VPN configuration fields. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41977 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41977</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1). Affected devices do not properly enforce isolation between user sessions in their web server component. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to escalate their privileges on the devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41978 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41978</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.1). Affected devices insert sensitive information about the generation of 2FA tokens into log files. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to forge 2FA tokens of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7715 | D-Link DNS-1550-04 photocenter_mgr.cgi sprintf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6724 | Generate Images – Magic Post Thumbnail &amp;lt; 5.2.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6724</link><description>The Generate Images  WordPress plugin before 5.2.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6823 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.18 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via mla-inline-edit-upload-scripts AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6823</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation involving the mla-inline-edit-upload-scripts AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.18. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7247 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Gallery and Countdown Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7247</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Custom Gallery and Countdown widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39591 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Document Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39591</link><description>SAP Document Builder does not perform necessary authorization checks for one of the function modules resulting in escalation of privileges causing low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42373 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42373</link><description>SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM) fails to conduct proper authorization checks for authenticated users, leading to the potential escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation it could allow an attacker to delete non-sensitive report variants that are typically restricted, causing minimal impact on the integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 05:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7092 | Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 5.9.27 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via no_more_items_text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7092</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘no_more_items_text’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41734 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41734</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform, an authenticated attacker could call an underlying transaction, which leads to disclosure of user related information. There is no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28166 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28166</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
  Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
  network, that could be executed by the application. On successful
  exploitation, the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the
  application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41731 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41731</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
network, that could be executed by the application. On successful exploitation,
the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41736 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Permit to Work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41736</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP Permit to Work
allows an authenticated attacker to access information which would otherwise be
restricted causing low impact on the confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42375 | Multiple Unrestricted File Upload vulnerabilities in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42375</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
  Platform allows an authenticated attacker to upload malicious code over the
  network, that could be executed by the application. On successful exploitation,
  the attacker can cause a low impact on the Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41732 | Improper Access Control in SAP Netweaver Application Server ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41732</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP allows
  an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link that could bypass allowlist
  controls. Depending on the web applications provided by this server, the
  attacker might inject CSS code or links into the web application that could
  allow the attacker to read or modify information. There is no impact on
  availability of application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41737 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in SAP CRM ABAP (Insights Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41737</link><description>SAP CRM ABAP (Insights
Management) allows an authenticated attacker to enumerate HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 04:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33005 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP and Java),SAP Web Dispatcher and SAP Content Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33005</link><description>Due to the missing authorization checks in the
local systems, the admin users of SAP Web Dispatcher, SAP NetWeaver Application
Server (ABAP and Java), and SAP Content Server can impersonate other users and
may perform some unintended actions. This could lead to a low impact on
confidentiality and a high impact on the integrity and availability of the
applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41733 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41733</link><description>In SAP Commerce, valid user accounts can be
identified during the customer registration and login processes. This allows a
potential attacker to learn if a given e-mail is used for an account, but does
not grant access to any customer data beyond this knowledge. The attacker must
already know the e-mail that they wish to test for. The impact on
confidentiality therefore is low and no impact to integrity or availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41735 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Commerce Backoffice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41735</link><description>SAP Commerce Backoffice does not sufficiently
encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)
vulnerability causing low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42377 | Multiple Missing Authorization Check vulnerabilities in SAP Shared Service Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42377</link><description>SAP shared service framework allows an
authenticated non-administrative user to call a remote-enabled function, which
will allow them to insert value entries into a non-sensitive table, causing low
impact on integrity of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33003 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Commerce Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33003</link><description>Some OCC API endpoints in SAP Commerce Cloud
allows Personally Identifiable Information (PII) data, such as passwords, email
addresses, mobile numbers, coupon codes, and voucher codes, to be included in
the request URL as query or path parameters. On successful exploitation, this
could lead to a High impact on confidentiality and integrity of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41730 | Missing Authentication check in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41730</link><description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence
Platform, if Single Signed On is enabled on Enterprise authentication, an
unauthorized user can get a logon token using a REST endpoint. The attacker can
fully compromise the system resulting in High impact on confidentiality,
integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42374 | XML injection in SAP BEx Web Java Runtime Export Web Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42374</link><description>BEx Web Java Runtime Export Web Service does not
sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source. An
attacker can retrieve information from the SAP ADS system and exhaust the
number of XMLForm service which makes the SAP ADS rendering (PDF creation)
unavailable. This affects the confidentiality and availability of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42376 | Multiple Missing Authorization Check vulnerabilities in SAP Shared Service Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42376</link><description>SAP Shared Service Framework does not perform necessary
authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges. On successful exploitation, an attacker can cause a high impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7094 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Code Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7094</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection leading to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.6 via the 'storeTheme' function. This is due to a lack of sanitization on user-supplied values, which replace values in the style.php file, along with missing capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. This issue was partially patched in 2.8.6 when the code injection issue was resolved, and fully patched in 2.8.7 when the missing authorization and cross-site request forgery protection was added.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7388 | WP Bannerize Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7388</link><description>The WP Bannerize Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via banner alt data in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38382 | IBM Cloud Pak for Security session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38382</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security (CP4S) 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.23.0 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow another user to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  233672.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7709 | OcoMon URL require_access_recovery.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7709</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in OcoMon 4.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /includes/common/require_access_recovery.php of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.0.1 and 5.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7707 | Tenda FH1206 HTTP POST Request SafeEmailFilter formSafeEmailFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 02.03.01.35 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSafeEmailFilter of the file /goform/SafeEmailFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37924 | WordPress WP2Speed Faster – Optimize PageSpeed Insights Score 90-100 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37924</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Wp2speed WP2Speed Faster allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP2Speed Faster: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37930 | WordPress SmartMag theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37930</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeSphere SmartMag allows Excavation, Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects SmartMag: from n/a through 9.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35775 | WordPress Slider by Soliloquy plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35775</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting'), Improper Authentication vulnerability in Soliloquy Team Slider by Soliloquy allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Slider by Soliloquy: from n/a through 2.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43123 | WordPress Card Elements for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43123</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Techeshta Card Elements for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Card Elements for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43124 | WordPress Graphina plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Iqonic Design Graphina allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Graphina: from n/a through 1.8.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43125 | WordPress WP Table Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Table Builder WP Table Builder – WordPress Table Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Table Builder – WordPress Table Plugin: from n/a through 1.4.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43126 | WordPress Sender – Newsletter, SMS and Email Marketing Automation for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43126</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sender Sender – Newsletter, SMS and Email Marketing Automation for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Sender – Newsletter, SMS and Email Marketing Automation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.6.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43127 | WordPress  Products, Order &amp;amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43130 | WordPress Football Pool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43130</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Antoine Hurkmans Football Pool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Football Pool: from n/a through 2.11.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43133 | WordPress Themify Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themify Themify Shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themify Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43137 | WordPress WappPress Basic plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WappPress Team WappPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WappPress: from n/a through 6.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7705 | Fujian mwcms Image Upload uploadeditor.html uploadeditor unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function uploadeditor of the file /uploadeditor.html?action=uploadimage of the component Image Upload. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7706 | Fujian mwcms uploadfile.html uploadimage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function uploadimage of the file /uploadfile.html. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43139 | WordPress Football Pool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43139</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Antoine Hurkmans Football Pool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Football Pool: from n/a through 2.11.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43147 | WordPress Selection Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43147</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Merkulove Selection Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Selection Lite: from n/a through 1.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43148 | WordPress StreamCast  &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43148</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins StreamCast allows Stored XSS.This issue affects StreamCast: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43149 | WordPress CM Tooltip Glossary Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43149</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Tooltip Glossary allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CM Tooltip Glossary: from n/a through 4.3.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43150 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43150</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43151 | WordPress Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43151</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite: from n/a through 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43152 | WordPress 3D FlipBook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43152</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in iberezansky 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook Viewer, Flipbook Image Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects 3D FlipBook – PDF Flipbook Viewer, Flipbook Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.15.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43155 | WordPress ComboBlocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.86 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43155</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins ComboBlocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ComboBlocks: from n/a through 2.2.86.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43156 | WordPress Post Grid Master plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43156</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AddonMaster Post Grid Master allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Post Grid Master: from n/a through 3.4.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43161 | WordPress Slider &amp;amp; Popup Builder by Depicter plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43161</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Averta Depicter Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43163 | WordPress ParcelPanel plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43163</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Parcel Panel ParcelPanel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ParcelPanel: from n/a through 4.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43164 | WordPress Blockspare plugin  &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43164</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blockspare allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blockspare: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7066 | Siemens Teamcenter Visualization and JT2Go Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7066</link><description>The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of 
an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted PDF files. This 
could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current 
process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43210 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43210</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7590 | WordPress Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin&amp;lt;= 2.14.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Spectra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Spectra: from n/a through 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43213 | WordPress MultiVendorX Marketplace plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.17 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43213</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MultiVendorX WC Marketplace allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WC Marketplace: from n/a through 4.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43216 | WordPress Filr – Secure document library plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43216</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Patrick Posner Filr – Secure document library allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Filr – Secure document library: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43217 | WordPress Kodex Posts likes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43217</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pierre Lebedel Kodex Posts likes allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kodex Posts likes: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43218 | WordPress Mediavine Control Panel plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43218</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mediavine Mediavine Control Panel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediavine Control Panel: from n/a through 2.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43220 | WordPress Form Maker by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.26 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43220</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 10Web Form Builder Team Form Maker by 10Web allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Form Maker by 10Web: from n/a through 1.15.26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43224 | WordPress YaMaps for WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.27 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yuri Baranov YaMaps for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects YaMaps for WordPress: from n/a through 0.6.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43225 | WordPress Enter Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeLooks Enter Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Enter Addons: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43226 | WordPress WP Dashboard Notes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43226</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeroen Sormani WP Dashboard Notes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Dashboard Notes: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43227 | WordPress BetterDocs – Best Documentation, FAQ &amp;amp; Knowledge Base Plugin with AI Support &amp;amp; Instant Answer for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43227</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper BetterDocs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BetterDocs: from n/a through 3.5.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43231 | WordPress Tutor LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeum Tutor LMS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tutor LMS: from n/a through 2.7.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43233 | WordPress BSK Forms Blacklist plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BannerSky BSK Forms Blacklist allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BSK Forms Blacklist: from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43360 | ZoneMinder Time-based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43360</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. ZoneMinder is affected by a time-based SQL Injection vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34 and 1.37.61.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43358 | XSS vulnerability in filter view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43358</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. ZoneMinder has a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the filter view via the filter[Id]. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34 and 1.37.61.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43359 | XSS vulnerabilities in montagereview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43359</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. ZoneMinder has a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the montagereview via the displayinterval, speed, and scale parameters. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34 and 1.37.61.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7704 | Weaver e-cology Source Code ecology_dev.zip information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology 8. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cloudstore/ecode/setup/ecology_dev.zip of the component Source Code Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41884 | ZoneMinder Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (&amp;#x27;SQL Injection&amp;#x27;) in watch.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41884</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source Closed-circuit television software application. In WWW/AJAX/watch.php, Line: 51 takes a few parameter in sql query without sanitizing it which makes it vulnerable to sql injection. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.34.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42741 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setL2tpServerCfg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42741</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setL2tpServerCfg. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42742 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUrlFilterRule...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42742</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUrlFilterRules. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42743 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setSyslogCfg . A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42743</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setSyslogCfg . Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42744 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setModifyVpnUser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42744</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setModifyVpnUser. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42745 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUPnPCfg. Auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42745</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setUPnPCfg. Authenicated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42747 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWanIeCfg. Aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42747</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWanIeCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42748 | In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWiFiWpsCfg. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42748</link><description>In TOTOLINK X5000r v9.1.0cu.2350_b20230313, the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi contains an OS command injection vulnerability in setWiFiWpsCfg. Authenticated Attackers can send malicious packet to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48171 | An issue in OWASP DefectDojo before v.1.5.3.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the user permissions component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48171</link><description>An issue in OWASP DefectDojo before v.1.5.3.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the user permissions component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42546 | TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the password parameter in the loginauth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42546</link><description>TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the password parameter in the loginauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42547 | TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42547</link><description>TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41710 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41710</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit, through R6.4.0.HF1 (R6.4.0.136) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrative privilege to conduct an argument injection attack, due to insufficient parameter sanitization during the boot process. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the context of the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40893 | Firewalla BTLE Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40893</link><description>Multiple authenticated operating system (OS) command injection vulnerabilities exist in Firewalla Box Software 
versions before 1.979. A physically close 
attacker that is authenticated to the Bluetooth Low-Energy (BTLE) interface can use the network configuration service to inject commands in various configuration parameters including networkConfig.Interface.Phy.Eth0.Extra.PingTestIP, networkConfig.Interface.Phy.Eth0.Extra.DNSTestDomain, and networkConfig.Interface.Phy.Eth0.Gateway6. Additionally, because the configuration can be synced to the Firewalla cloud, the attacker may be able to persist access even after hardware resets and firmware re-flashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40892 | Firewalla BTLE Weak Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40892</link><description>A weak credential vulnerability exists in Firewalla Box Software versions before 1.979. This vulnerability allows a physically close attacker to use the license UUID for authentication and provision SSH credentials over the Bluetooth Low-Energy (BTLE) interface. Once an attacker gains access to the LAN, they could log into the SSH interface using the provisioned credentials. The license UUID can be acquired through plain-text Bluetooth sniffing, reading the QR code on the bottom of the device, or brute-forcing the UUID (though this is less likely).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6768 | Denial of Service in CLFS.sys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6768</link><description>A Denial of Service in CLFS.sys in Microsoft Windows 10, Windows 11, Windows Server 2016, Windows Server 2019, and Windows Server 2022 allows a malicious authenticated low-privilege user to cause a Blue Screen of Death via a forced call to the KeBugCheckEx function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42543 | TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42543</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the http_host parameter in the loginauth function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42545 | TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the ssid parameter in setWizardCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42545</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 has a buffer overflow vulnerability in the ssid parameter in setWizardCfg function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41651 | An issue in Prestashop v.8.1.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the module upgrade functionality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41651</link><description>An issue in Prestashop v.8.1.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the module upgrade functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42474 | Streamlit Path Traversal Security Vulnerability on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42474</link><description>Streamlit is a data oriented application development framework for python. Snowflake Streamlit open source addressed a security vulnerability via the static file sharing feature. Users of hosted Streamlit app(s) on Windows were vulnerable to a path traversal vulnerability when the static file sharing feature is enabled. An attacker could utilize the vulnerability to leak the password hash of the Windows user running Streamlit. The vulnerability was patched on Jul 25, 2024, as part of Streamlit open source version 1.37.0. The vulnerability only affects Windows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7700 | Foreman: command injection in &amp;quot;host init config&amp;quot; template via &amp;quot;install packages&amp;quot; field on foreman</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7700</link><description>A command injection flaw was found in the "Host Init Config" template in the Foreman application, via the "Install Packages" field on the "Register Host" page. This issue may allow an attacker with the necessary privileges to inject arbitrary commands into the configuration, potentially allowing unauthorized command execution during host registration. Although this issue requires user interaction to execute injected commands, it poses a significant risk if an unsuspecting user runs the generated registration script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40500 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Martin Kucej i-librarian v.5.11.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40500</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Martin Kucej i-librarian v.5.11.0 and before allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the search function in the import component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41475 | Gnuboard g6 6.0.7 is vulnerable to Session hijacking due to a CORS misconfiguration.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41475</link><description>Gnuboard g6 6.0.7 is vulnerable to Session hijacking due to a CORS misconfiguration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42623 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/delete/1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42623</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/delete/1</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42624 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/delete/10.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42624</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/delete/10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42625 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/add</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42625</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/add</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42626 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42626</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/add.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42627 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/delete/3.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42627</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/delete/3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7249 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Directory Services allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7249</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Directory Services allows Path Traversal.This issue affects OpenText Directory Services: from 16.4.2 before 24.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41909 | Apache MINA SSHD: integrity check bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41909</link><description>Like many other SSH implementations, Apache MINA SSHD suffered from the issue that is more widely known as CVE-2023-48795. An attacker that can intercept traffic between client and server could drop certain packets from the stream, potentially causing client and server to consequently end up with a connection for which 
some security features have been downgraded or disabled, aka a Terrapin 
attack

The mitigations to prevent this type of attack were implemented in Apache MINA SSHD 2.12.0, both client and server side. Users are recommended to upgrade to at least this version. Note that both the client and the server implementation must have mitigations applied against this issue, otherwise the connection may still be affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42489 | Pro Macros Remote Code Execution via Viewpdf and similar macros</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42489</link><description>Pro Macros provides XWiki rendering macros. Missing escaping in the Viewpdf macro allows any user with view right on the `CKEditor.HTMLConverter` page or edit or comment right on any page to perform remote code execution. Other macros like Viewppt are vulnerable to the same kind of attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42628 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/edit/3.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42628</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/snippet/edit/3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42629 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/edit/10.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42629</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/edit/10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42630 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/create_file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42630</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/plugin/file_manager/create_file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42631 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/edit/1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42631</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/layout/edit/1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42482 | fish-shop/syntax-check Improper Neutralization of Delimiters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42482</link><description>fish-shop/syntax-check is a GitHub action for syntax checking fish shell files. Improper neutralization of delimiters in the `pattern` input (specifically the command separator `;` and command substitution characters `(` and `)`) mean that arbitrary command injection is possible by modification of the input value used in a workflow. This has the potential for exposure or exfiltration of sensitive information from the workflow runner, such as might be achieved by sending environment variables to an external entity. It is recommended that users update to the patched version `v1.6.12` or the latest release version `v2.0.0`, however remediation may be possible through careful control of workflows and the `pattern` input value used by this action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42485 | Filament Excel Vulnerable to Path Traversal Attack on Export Download Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42485</link><description>Filament Excel enables excel export for Filament admin resources. The export download route `/filament-excel/{path}` allowed downloading any file without login when the webserver allows `../` in the URL.  Patched with Version v2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42632 | FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42632</link><description>FrogCMS v0.9.5 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/?/page/add.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39091 | An OS command injection vulnerability in the ccm_debug component of MIPC Camera firmware prior to v5.4.1.240424171021 allows attackers withi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39091</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the ccm_debug component of MIPC Camera firmware prior to v5.4.1.240424171021 allows attackers within the same network to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42481 | Complete crash of host system due to calculateDirectorySize in skyportd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42481</link><description>Skyport Daemon (skyportd) is the daemon for the Skyport Panel. By making thousands of folders &amp; files (easy due to skyport's lack of rate limiting on createFolder. createFile), skyportd in a lot of cases will cause 100% CPU usage and an OOM, probably crashing the system. This is fixed in 0.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36877 | Micro-Star International Z-series motherboards (Z590, Z490, and Z790) and B-series motherboards (B760, B560, B660, and B460) with firmware 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36877</link><description>Micro-Star International Z-series motherboards (Z590, Z490, and Z790) and B-series motherboards (B760, B560, B660, and B460) with firmware 7D25v14, 7D25v17 to 7D25v19, and 7D25v1A to 7D25v1H was discovered to contain a write-what-where condition in the in the SW handler for SMI 0xE3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42480 | Kamaji&amp;#x27;s RBAC Roles for `etcd` are not disjunct</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42480</link><description>Kamaji is the Hosted Control Plane Manager for Kubernetes. In versions 1.0.0 and earlier, Kamaji uses an "open at the top" range definition in RBAC for etcd roles leading to some TCPs API servers being able to read, write, and delete the data of other control planes. This vulnerability is fixed in edge-24.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27443 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the CalendarInvite ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27443</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the CalendarInvite feature of the Zimbra webmail classic user interface, because of improper input validation in the handling of the calendar header. An attacker can exploit this via an email message containing a crafted calendar header with an embedded XSS payload. When a victim views this message in the Zimbra webmail classic interface, the payload is executed in the context of the victim's session, potentially leading to execution of arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42478 | llama.cpp allows Arbitrary Address Read in rpc_server::get_tensor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42478</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. The unsafe `data` pointer member in the `rpc_tensor` structure can cause arbitrary address reading. This vulnerability is fixed in b3561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42479 | llama.cpp allows write-what-where in rpc_server::set_tensor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42479</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. The unsafe `data` pointer member in the `rpc_tensor` structure can cause arbitrary address writing. This vulnerability is fixed in b3561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21550 | SteVe is an open platform that implements different version of the OCPP protocol for Electric Vehicle charge points, acting as a central ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21550</link><description>SteVe is an open platform that implements different version of the OCPP protocol for Electric Vehicle charge points, acting as a central server for management of registered charge points. Attackers can inject arbitrary HTML and Javascript code via WebSockets leading to persistent Cross-Site Scripting in the SteVe management interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27442 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The zmmailboxdmgr binary, a component of ZCS, is intended to be executed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27442</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The zmmailboxdmgr binary, a component of ZCS, is intended to be executed by the zimbra user with root privileges for specific mailbox operations. However, an attacker can escalate privileges from the zimbra user to root, because of improper handling of input arguments. An attacker can execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges, leading to local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33533 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0, issue 1 of 2. A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33533</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0, issue 1 of 2. A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Zimbra webmail admin interface. This vulnerability occurs due to inadequate input validation of the packages parameter, allowing an authenticated attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of another user's browser session. By uploading a malicious JavaScript file and crafting a URL containing its location in the packages parameter, the attacker can exploit this vulnerability. Subsequently, when another user visits the crafted URL, the malicious JavaScript code is executed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33535 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability involves unauthenticated local file inclusion (LFI) in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33535</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability involves unauthenticated local file inclusion (LFI) in a web application, specifically impacting the handling of the packages parameter. Attackers can exploit this flaw to include arbitrary local files without authentication, potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is limited to files within a specific directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33536 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability occurs due to inadequate input validation of the res p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33536</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0. The vulnerability occurs due to inadequate input validation of the res parameter, allowing an authenticated attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of another user's browser session. By uploading a malicious JavaScript file, accessible externally, and crafting a URL containing its location in the res parameter, the attacker can exploit this vulnerability. Subsequently, when another user visits the crafted URL, the malicious JavaScript code is executed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42477 | llama.cpp global-buffer-overflow in ggml_type_size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42477</link><description>llama.cpp provides LLM inference in C/C++. The unsafe `type` member in the `rpc_tensor` structure can cause `global-buffer-overflow`. This vulnerability may lead to memory data leakage. The vulnerability is fixed in b3561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38530 | Open eClass Platform allows Arbitrary File Upload in &amp;quot;modules/h5p/save.php&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38530</link><description>The Open eClass platform (formerly known as GUnet eClass) is a complete Course Management System. An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the "save" functionality of the H5P module enables unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files on the server's filesystem. This may lead in unrestricted RCE on the backend server, since the upload location is accessible from the internet. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42520 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in /bin/boa via formParentControl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42520</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in /bin/boa via formParentControl.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6917 | RCE in Veribilim Software&amp;#x27;s Veribase Order Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6917</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Veribilim Software Veribase Order Management allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Veribase Order Management: before v4.010.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42258 | mm: huge_memory: use !CONFIG_64BIT to relax huge page alignment on 32 bit machines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42258</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: huge_memory: use !CONFIG_64BIT to relax huge page alignment on 32 bit machines

Yves-Alexis Perez reported commit 4ef9ad19e176 ("mm: huge_memory: don't
force huge page alignment on 32 bit") didn't work for x86_32 [1].  It is
because x86_32 uses CONFIG_X86_32 instead of CONFIG_32BIT.

!CONFIG_64BIT should cover all 32 bit machines.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/linux-mm/CAHbLzkr1LwH3pcTgM+aGQ31ip2bKqiqEQ8=FQB+t2c3dhNKNHA@mail.gmail.com/</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6639 | MDx &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mdx_list_item Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6639</link><description>The MDx theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mdx_list_item' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6684 | Authentication Bypass in GST Electronics&amp;#x27; inohom Nova Panel N7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6684</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in GST Electronics inohom Nova Panel N7 allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects inohom Nova Panel N7: through 1.9.9.6. NOTE: The vendor was contacted and it was learned that the product is not supported.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42167 | Command Injection in Organisationname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42167</link><description>The function "generate_app_certificates" in controllers/saml2/saml2.js of FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 does not neutralize special elements used in an OS Command properly. This allows an authenticated user with permissions to create applications to execute commands by creating an application with a malicious organisationname.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42165 | Arbitrary User Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42165</link><description>Insufficiently random values for generating activation token in FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 allow attackers to activate accounts of any user by predicting the token for the activation link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42166 | Command Injection in Applicationname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42166</link><description>The function "generate_app_certificates" in lib/app_certificates.js of FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 does not neutralize special elements used in an OS Command properly. This allows an authenticated user with permissions to create applications to execute commands by creating an application with a malicious name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42164 | Disabling MFA without Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42164</link><description>Insufficiently random values for generating password reset token in FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 allow attackers to disable two factor authorization of any user by predicting the token for the disable_2fa link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42163 | Password Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42163</link><description>Insufficiently random values for generating password reset token in FIWARE Keyrock &lt;= 8.4 allow attackers to take over the account of any user by predicting the token for the password reset link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6758 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Sprecher Automation SPRECON-E</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6758</link><description>Improper Privilege Management in Sprecher Automation SPRECON-E below version 8.71j allows a remote attacker with low privileges to save unauthorized protection assignments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7697 | Logical vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to user information leakage risks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7697</link><description>Logical vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to user information leakage risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 08:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36034 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36034</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8003 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in aggregate reports' search option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36035 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36035</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8003 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in user session recording.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36518 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36518</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8110 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in attack surface analyzer's dashboard.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5487 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5487</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8110 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in attack surface analyzer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5651 | Fence-agent: fence agent command line options leads to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5651</link><description>A flaw was found in fence agents that rely on SSH/Telnet. This vulnerability can allow a Remote Code Execution (RCE) primitive by supplying an arbitrary command to execute in the --ssh-path/--telnet-path arguments. A low-privilege user, for example, a user with developer access, can create a specially crafted FenceAgentsRemediation for a fence agent supporting  --ssh-path/--telnet-path arguments to execute arbitrary commands on the operator's pod. This RCE leads to a privilege escalation, first as the service account running the operator, then to another service account with cluster-admin privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 05:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5527 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5527</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8110 are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in file auditing configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7694 | TeamT5 ThreatSonar Anti-Ransomware - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7694</link><description>ThreatSonar Anti-Ransomware from TeamT5 does not properly validate the content of uploaded files. Remote attackers with  administrator privileges on the product platform can upload malicious files, which can be used to execute arbitrary system command on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 03:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7693 | Team Johnlong software Raiden MAILD Remote Management System -  Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7693</link><description>Raiden MAILD Remote Management System from Team Johnlong Software has a Relative Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary file on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7685 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System adds.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7685</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file adds.php. The manipulation of the argument name/dob/email/mobile/address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7686 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System register_case.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7686</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file register_case.php. The manipulation of the argument title/description/opposite_lawyer leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7683 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System addcase_stage.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7683</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file addcase_stage.php. The manipulation of the argument cname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7684 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System add_act.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7684</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file add_act.php. The manipulation of the argument aname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7682 | code-projects Job Portal rw_i_nat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7682</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Portal 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file rw_i_nat.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 01:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>