<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:31:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-27297 | Nix Corruption of fixed-output derivations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27297</link><description>Nix is a package manager for Linux and other Unix systems. A fixed-output derivations on Linux can send file descriptors to files in the Nix store to another program running on the host (or another fixed-output derivation) via Unix domain sockets in the abstract namespace. This allows to modify the output of the derivation, after Nix has registered the path as "valid" and immutable in the Nix database. In particular, this allows the output of fixed-output derivations to be modified from their expected content. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.3.18 2.18.2 2.19.4 and 2.20.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27938 | SMTP Smuggling in Postal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27938</link><description>Postal is an open source SMTP server. Postal versions less than 3.0.0 are vulnerable to SMTP Smuggling attacks which may allow incoming e-mails to be spoofed. This, in conjunction with a cooperative outgoing SMTP service, would allow for an incoming e-mail to be received by Postal addressed from a server that a user has 'authorised' to send mail on their behalf but were not the genuine author of the e-mail. Postal is not affected for sending outgoing e-mails as email is re-encoded with `&lt;CR&gt;&lt;LF&gt;` line endings when transmitted over SMTP. This issue has been addressed and users should upgrade to Postal v3.0.0 or higher. Once upgraded, Postal will only accept End of DATA sequences which are explicitly `&lt;CR&gt;&lt;LF&gt;.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;LF&gt;`. If a non-compliant sequence is detected it will be logged to the SMTP server log. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25854 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Insurance Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the Su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25854</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sourcecodester Insurance Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the Subject and Description fields when submitting a support ticket.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28120 | API key leak in codeium-chrome</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28120</link><description>codeium-chrome is an open source code completion plugin for the chrome web browser. The service worker of the codeium-chrome extension doesn't check the sender when receiving an external message. This allows an attacker to host a website that will steal the user's Codeium api-key, and thus impersonate the user on the backend autocomplete server. This issue has not been addressed. Users are advised to monitor the usage of their API key.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28187 | OS Command Injection Vulnerability in SOY CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28187</link><description>SOY CMS is an open source CMS (content management system) that allows you to build blogs and online shops. SOY CMS versions prior to 3.14.2 are vulnerable to an OS Command Injection vulnerability within the file upload feature when accessed by an administrator. The vulnerability enables the execution of arbitrary OS commands through specially crafted file names containing a semicolon, affecting the jpegoptim functionality. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.14.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28197 | Account Takeover via Session Fixation in Zitadel [Bypassing MFA]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28197</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management system. Zitadel uses a cookie to identify the user agent (browser) and its user sessions.  Although the cookie was handled according to best practices, it was accessible on subdomains of the ZITADEL instance. An attacker could take advantage of this and provide a malicious link hosted on the subdomain to the user to gain access to the victim’s account in certain scenarios. A possible victim would need to login through the malicious link for this exploit to work. If the possible victim already had the cookie present, the attack would not succeed. The attack would further only be possible if there was an initial vulnerability on the subdomain. This could either be the attacker being able to control DNS or a XSS vulnerability in an application hosted on a subdomain. Versions 2.46.0, 2.45.1, and 2.44.3 have been patched. Zitadel recommends upgrading to the latest versions available in due course. Note that applying the patch will invalidate the current cookie and thus users will need to start a new session and existing sessions (user selection) will be empty. For self-hosted environments unable to upgrade to a patched version, prevent setting the following cookie name on subdomains of your Zitadel instance (e.g. within your WAF): `__Secure-zitadel-useragent`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28198 | XML external entity (XXE) injection in OpenOLAT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28198</link><description>OpenOlat is an open source web-based e-learning platform for teaching, learning, assessment and communication. By manually manipulating http requests when using the draw.io integration it is possible to read arbitrary files as the configured system user and SSRF. The problem is fixed in version 18.1.6 and 18.2.2. It is advised to upgrade to the latest version of 18.1.x or 18.2.x. Users unable to upgrade may work around this issue by disabling the Draw.io module or the entire REST API which will secure the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2357 | IKEv2 misconfiguration can cause libreswan to abort and restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2357</link><description>The Libreswan Project was notified of an issue causing libreswan to restart under some IKEv2 retransmit scenarios when a connection is configured to use PreSharedKeys (authby=secret) and the connection cannot find a matching configured secret. When such a connection is automatically added on startup using the auto= keyword, it can cause repeated crashes leading to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22005 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible Authentication Bypass due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22005</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible Authentication Bypass due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22006 | Android kernel allows Information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22006</link><description>Android kernel allows Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22007 | In constraint_check of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22007</link><description>In constraint_check of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22008 | In config_gov_time_windows of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22008</link><description>In config_gov_time_windows of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22009 | In init_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22009</link><description>In init_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22010 | In dvfs_plugin_caller of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22010</link><description>In dvfs_plugin_caller of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22011 | In ss_ProcessRejectComponent of ss_MmConManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22011</link><description>In ss_ProcessRejectComponent of ss_MmConManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25984 | In dumpBatteryDefend of dump_power.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25984</link><description>In dumpBatteryDefend of dump_power.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25985 | In bigo_unlocked_ioctl of bigo.c, there is a possible UAF due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25985</link><description>In bigo_unlocked_ioctl of bigo.c, there is a possible UAF due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25986 | In ppmp_unprotect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible compromise of protected memory due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25986</link><description>In ppmp_unprotect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible compromise of protected memory due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege to TEE with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25987 | In pt_sysctl_command of pt.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25987</link><description>In pt_sysctl_command of pt.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25988 | In SAEMM_DiscloseGuti of SAEMM_RadioMessageCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25988</link><description>In SAEMM_DiscloseGuti of SAEMM_RadioMessageCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25989 | In gpu_slc_liveness_update of pixel_gpu_slc.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25989</link><description>In gpu_slc_liveness_update of pixel_gpu_slc.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25990 | In pktproc_perftest_gen_rx_packet_sktbuf_mode of link_rx_pktproc.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25990</link><description>In pktproc_perftest_gen_rx_packet_sktbuf_mode of link_rx_pktproc.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25991 | In acpm_tmu_ipc_handler of tmu_plugin.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25991</link><description>In acpm_tmu_ipc_handler of tmu_plugin.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25992 | In tmu_tz_control of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25992</link><description>In tmu_tz_control of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25993 | In tmu_reset_tmu_trip_counter of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25993</link><description>In tmu_reset_tmu_trip_counter of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27204 | In tmu_set_gov_active of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27204</link><description>In tmu_set_gov_active of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27205 | In tbd of tbd, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27205</link><description>In tbd of tbd, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27206 | In tbd of tbd, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27206</link><description>In tbd of tbd, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27207 | Android kernel allows Elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27207</link><description>Android kernel allows Elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27208 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27208</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27209 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27209</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27210 | In policy_check of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27210</link><description>In policy_check of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27211 | In AtiHandleAPOMsgType of ati_Main.c, there is a possible OOB write due to a missing null check. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27211</link><description>In AtiHandleAPOMsgType of ati_Main.c, there is a possible OOB write due to a missing null check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27212 | In init_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27212</link><description>In init_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27213 | In BroadcastSystemMessage of servicemgr.cpp, there is a possible Remote Code Execution due to a use after free. This could lead to local esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27213</link><description>In BroadcastSystemMessage of servicemgr.cpp, there is a possible Remote Code Execution due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27218 | In update_freq_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27218</link><description>In update_freq_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27219 | In tmu_set_pi of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27219</link><description>In tmu_set_pi of tmu.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27220 | In lpm_req_handler of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds memory access due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27220</link><description>In lpm_req_handler of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds memory access due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27221 | In update_policy_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27221</link><description>In update_policy_data of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27222 | In onSkipButtonClick of FaceEnrollFoldPage.java, there is a possible way to access the file the app cannot access  due to Intent Redirect GR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27222</link><description>In onSkipButtonClick of FaceEnrollFoldPage.java, there is a possible way to access the file the app cannot access  due to Intent Redirect GRANT_URI_PERMISSIONS Attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27223 | In EUTRAN_LCS_DecodeFacilityInformationElement of LPP_LcsManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27223</link><description>In EUTRAN_LCS_DecodeFacilityInformationElement of LPP_LcsManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure after authenticating the cell connection with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27224 | In strncpy of strncpy.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27224</link><description>In strncpy of strncpy.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27225 | In sendHciCommand of bluetooth_hci.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27225</link><description>In sendHciCommand of bluetooth_hci.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27226 | In tmu_config_gov_params of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27226</link><description>In tmu_config_gov_params of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27227 | Android kernel allows Remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27227</link><description>Android kernel allows Remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27228 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote code execution with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27228</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27229 | In ss_SendCallBarringPwdRequiredIndMsg of ss_CallBarring.c, there is a possible null pointer deref due to a missing null check. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27229</link><description>In ss_SendCallBarringPwdRequiredIndMsg of ss_CallBarring.c, there is a possible null pointer deref due to a missing null check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27230 | In ProtocolPsKeepAliveStatusAdapter::getCode() of protocolpsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds chec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27230</link><description>In ProtocolPsKeepAliveStatusAdapter::getCode() of protocolpsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27233 | In ppcfw_init_secpolicy of ppcfw.c, there is a possible permission bypass due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27233</link><description>In ppcfw_init_secpolicy of ppcfw.c, there is a possible permission bypass due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27234 | In fvp_set_target of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27234</link><description>In fvp_set_target of fvp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27235 | In plugin_extern_func of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27235</link><description>In plugin_extern_func of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27236 | In aoc_unlocked_ioctl of aoc.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27236</link><description>In aoc_unlocked_ioctl of aoc.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27237 | In wipe_ns_memory of nsmemwipe.c, there is a possible incorrect size calculation due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27237</link><description>In wipe_ns_memory of nsmemwipe.c, there is a possible incorrect size calculation due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6444 | Seriously Simple Podcasting &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Unauthenticated Administrator Email Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6444</link><description>The Seriously Simple Podcasting WordPress plugin before 3.0.0 discloses the Podcast owner's email address (which by default is the admin email address) via an unauthenticated crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7247 | Login as User or Customer &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7247</link><description>The Login as User or Customer WordPress plugin through 3.8 does not prevent users to log in as any other user on the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0559 | Enhanced Text Widget &amp;lt; 1.6.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0559</link><description>The Enhanced Text Widget WordPress plugin before 1.6.6 does not validate and escape some of its Widget options before outputting them back in attributes, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0561 | Ultimate Posts Widget &amp;lt; 2.3.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0561</link><description>The Ultimate Posts Widget WordPress plugin before 2.3.1 does not validate and escape some of its Widget options before outputting them back in attributes, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1068 | 404 Solution &amp;lt; 2.35.8 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1068</link><description>The 404 Solution WordPress plugin before 2.35.8 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by high privilege users such as admins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1273 | Starbox &amp;lt; 3.5.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1273</link><description>The Starbox WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1279 | Paid Memberships Pro &amp;lt; 2.12.9 - Contributor+ Arbitrary User Custom Field Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1279</link><description>The Paid Memberships Pro WordPress plugin before 2.12.9 does not prevent user with at least the contributor role from leaking other users' sensitive metadata.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1290 | Formidable Registration &amp;lt; 2.12 - Contributor+ Arbitrary User Password Reset To Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1290</link><description>The User Registration WordPress plugin before 2.12 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role from rendering sensitive shortcodes, allowing them to generate, and leak, valid password reset URLs, which they can use to take over any accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1487 | Photos and Files Contest Gallery &amp;lt;  21.3.1 - Author+ Stored Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1487</link><description>The Photos and Files Contest Gallery WordPress plugin before 21.3.1 does not sanitize and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as author to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1696 | Santesoft Sante FFT Imaging Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1696</link><description>In Santesoft Sante FFT Imaging versions 1.4.1 and prior once a user opens a malicious DCM file on affected FFT Imaging installations, a local attacker could perform an out-of-bounds write, which could allow for arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 17:03:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0039 | In attp_build_value_cmd of att_protocol.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0039</link><description>In attp_build_value_cmd of att_protocol.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0044 | In createSessionInternal of PackageInstallerService.java, there is a possible run-as any app due to improper input validation. This could le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0044</link><description>In createSessionInternal of PackageInstallerService.java, there is a possible run-as any app due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0045 | In smp_proc_sec_req of smp_act.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proxi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0045</link><description>In smp_proc_sec_req of smp_act.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0046 | In installExistingPackageAsUser of InstallPackageHelper.java, there is a possible carrier restriction bypass due to a logic error in the cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0046</link><description>In installExistingPackageAsUser of InstallPackageHelper.java, there is a possible carrier restriction bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0047 | In writeUserLP of UserManagerService.java, device policies are serialized with an incorrect tag due to a logic error in the code. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0047</link><description>In writeUserLP of UserManagerService.java, device policies are serialized with an incorrect tag due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service when policies are deserialized on reboot with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0048 | In Session of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible method to retain foreground service privileges due to incorrect handling of nu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0048</link><description>In Session of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible method to retain foreground service privileges due to incorrect handling of null responses. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0049 | In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0049</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User  interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0050 | In getConfig of SoftVideoDecoderOMXComponent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing validation check. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0050</link><description>In getConfig of SoftVideoDecoderOMXComponent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing validation check. This could lead to a local non-security issue with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0051 | In onQueueFilled of SoftMPEG4.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0051</link><description>In onQueueFilled of SoftMPEG4.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0052 | In multiple functions of healthconnect, there is a possible leakage of exercise route data due to a missing permission check. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0052</link><description>In multiple functions of healthconnect, there is a possible leakage of exercise route data due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0053 | In getCustomPrinterIcon of PrintManagerService.java, there is a possible way to view other user's images due to a confused deputy. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0053</link><description>In getCustomPrinterIcon of PrintManagerService.java, there is a possible way to view other user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23717 | In access_secure_service_from_temp_bond of btm_sec.cc, there is a possible way to achieve keystroke injection due to improper input validati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23717</link><description>In access_secure_service_from_temp_bond of btm_sec.cc, there is a possible way to achieve keystroke injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23609 | Improper Error Handling Issue in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23609</link><description>An improper error handling vulnerability in LabVIEW may result in remote code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23612 | Improper Error Handling Issue in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23612</link><description>An improper error handling vulnerability in LabVIEW may result in remote code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23608 | Out of Bounds Write Due to Missing Bounds Check in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23608</link><description>An out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check in LabVIEW may result in remote code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23610 | Out of Bounds Write Due to Missing Bounds Check in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23610</link><description>An out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check in LabVIEW may result in remote code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23611 | Out of Bounds Write Due to Missing Bounds Check in LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23611</link><description>An out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check in LabVIEW may result in remote code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to provide a user with a specially crafted VI. This vulnerability affects LabVIEW 2024 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0670 | Privilege escalation in windows agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0670</link><description>Privilege escalation in windows agent plugin in Checkmk before 2.2.0p23, 2.1.0p40 and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows local user to escalate privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1441 | Libvirt: off-by-one error in udevlistinterfacesbystatus()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1441</link><description>An off-by-one error flaw was found in the udevListInterfacesByStatus() function in libvirt when the number of interfaces exceeds the size of the `names` array. This issue can be reproduced by sending specially crafted data to the libvirt daemon, allowing an unprivileged client to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2370 | Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in ManageEngine Desktop Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2370</link><description>Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in ManageEngine Desktop Central affecting version 9, build 90055. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to upload a malicious file to the system without any credentials provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28823 | Amazon AWS aws-js-s3-explorer (aka AWS JavaScript S3 Explorer) 1.0.0 allows XSS via a crafted S3 bucket name to index.html.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28823</link><description>Amazon AWS aws-js-s3-explorer (aka AWS JavaScript S3 Explorer) 1.0.0 allows XSS via a crafted S3 bucket name to index.html.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 04:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28816 | Student Information Chatbot a0196ab allows SQL injection via the username to the login function in index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28816</link><description>Student Information Chatbot a0196ab allows SQL injection via the username to the login function in index.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2184 | Buffer overflow in identifier field of WSD probe request process of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2184</link><description>Buffer overflow in identifier field of WSD probe request process of Small Office Multifunction Printers and Laser Printers(*) which may allow an attacker on the network segment to trigger the affected product being unresponsive or to execute arbitrary code.*:Satera MF740C Series/Satera MF640C Series/Satera LBP660C Series/Satera LBP620C Series firmware v12.07 and earlier, and Satera MF750C Series/Satera LBP670C Series firmware v03.09 and earlier sold in Japan.Color imageCLASS MF740C Series/Color imageCLASS MF640C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1127C/Color imageCLASS LBP664Cdw/Color imageCLASS LBP622Cdw/Color imageCLASS X LBP1127C firmware v12.07 and earlier, and Color imageCLASS MF750C Series/Color imageCLASS X MF1333C/Color imageCLASS LBP674Cdw/Color imageCLASS X LBP1333C firmware v03.09 and earlier sold in US.i-SENSYS MF740C Series/i-SENSYS MF640C Series/C1127i Series/i-SENSYS LBP660C Series/i-SENSYS LBP620C Series/C1127P firmware v12.07 and earlier, and i-SENSYS MF750C Series/C1333i Series/i-SENSYS LBP673Cdw/C1333P firmware v03.09 and earlier sold in Europe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2365 | Musicshelf SHA-1 PinningTrustManager.java weak password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2365</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Musicshelf 1.0/1.1 on Android. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file io\fabric\sdk\android\services\network\PinningTrustManager.java of the component SHA-1 Handler. The manipulation leads to password hash with insufficient computational effort. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256321 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2364 | Musicshelf Backup androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2364</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Musicshelf 1.0/1.1 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256320.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2314 | If kernel headers need to be extracted, bcc will attempt to load them from a temporary directory. An unprivileged attacker could use this to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2314</link><description>If kernel headers need to be extracted, bcc will attempt to load them from a temporary directory. An unprivileged attacker could use this to force bcc to load compromised linux headers. Linux distributions which provide kernel headers by default are not affected by default.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2313 | If kernel headers need to be extracted, bpftrace will attempt to load them from a temporary directory. An unprivileged attacker could use th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2313</link><description>If kernel headers need to be extracted, bpftrace will attempt to load them from a temporary directory. An unprivileged attacker could use this to force bcc to load compromised linux headers. Linux distributions which provide kernel headers by default are not affected by default.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2363 | AOL AIM Triton Invite denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2363</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in AOL AIM Triton 1.0.4. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Invite Handler. The manipulation of the argument CSeq leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256318 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2355 | keerti1924 Secret-Coder-PHP-Project secret_coder.sql inclusion of sensitive information in source code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2355</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in keerti1924 Secret-Coder-PHP-Project 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /secret_coder.sql. The manipulation leads to inclusion of sensitive information in source code. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256315. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2354 | Dreamer CMS toEdit cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2354</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/menu/toEdit. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256314 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2353 | Totolink X6000R shttpd cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28757 | libexpat through 2.6.1 allows an XML Entity Expansion attack when there is isolated use of external parsers (created via XML_ExternalEntityP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28757</link><description>libexpat through 2.6.1 allows an XML Entity Expansion attack when there is isolated use of external parsers (created via XML_ExternalEntityParserCreate).</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 04:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2352 | 1Panel swap baseApi.UpdateDeviceSwap command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2352</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1Panel up to 1.10.1-lts. Affected by this issue is the function baseApi.UpdateDeviceSwap of the file /api/v1/toolbox/device/update/swap. The manipulation of the argument Path with the input 123123123\nopen -a Calculator leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256304.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2351 | CodeAstro Ecommerce Site Search action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2351</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CodeAstro Ecommerce Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file action.php of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument cat_id/brand_id/keyword leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256303.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 22:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2333 | CodeAstro Membership Management System add_members.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2333</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add_members.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256284.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2332 | SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store HTTP GET Request manage_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/maintenance/manage_category.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256283.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2331 | SourceCodester Tourist Reservation System System.cpp ad_writedata buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tourist Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function ad_writedata of the file System.cpp. The manipulation of the argument ad_code leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256282 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 10:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1870 | The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1870</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the callActivateLicenseEndpoint function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.260. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to update the license key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2330 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2330</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /protocol/index.php. The manipulation of the argument IPAddr leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256281 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2329 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2329</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/list_resource_icon.php?action=delete. The manipulation of the argument IconId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256280. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25501 | An issue WinMail v.7.1 and v.5.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the email parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25501</link><description>An issue WinMail v.7.1 and v.5.1 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the email parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1123 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a miss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1123</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_frontend_event_submission() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the title and content of arbitrary posts. This can also be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when the allow_submission_by_anonymous_user setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1124 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending due to a missing cap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1124</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending due to a missing capability check on the ep_send_attendees_email() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to send arbitrary emails with arbitrary content from the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1125 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1125</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the calendar_events_delete() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1320 | The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'offline_st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1320</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'offline_status' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1767 | The Blocksy theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1767</link><description>The Blocksy theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'className' and 'radius'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28089 | Hitron CODA-4582 2AHKM-CODA4589 7.2.4.5.1b8 devices allow a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity (who has access to the router admin panel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28089</link><description>Hitron CODA-4582 2AHKM-CODA4589 7.2.4.5.1b8 devices allow a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity (who has access to the router admin panel) to conduct a DOM-based stored XSS attack that can fetch remote resources. The payload is executed at index.html#advanced_location (aka the Device Location page). This can cause a denial of service or lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 06:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25951 | A command injection vulnerability exists in local RACADM. A malicious authenticated user could gain control of the underlying operating syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25951</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in local RACADM. A malicious authenticated user could gain control of the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 06:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46427 | An issue was discovered in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46427</link><description>An issue was discovered in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), and obtain sensitive information via null pointer deference in gf_dash_setup_period component in media_tools/dash_client.c.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46426 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46426</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in gpac version 2.3-DEV-rev588-g7edc40fee-master, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via gf_fwrite component in at utils/os_file.c.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50015 | An issue was discovered in Grandstream GXP14XX 1.0.8.9 and GXP16XX 1.0.7.13, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges via incorrect ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50015</link><description>An issue was discovered in Grandstream GXP14XX 1.0.8.9 and GXP16XX 1.0.7.13, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges via incorrect access control using an end-user session-identity token.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49340 | An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to escalate privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49340</link><description>An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and bypass authentication via incorrect access control in the web management portal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 04:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49341 | An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49341</link><description>An issue was discovered in Newland Nquire 1000 Interactive Kiosk version NQ1000-II_G_V1.00.011, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via cleartext credential storage in backup.htm component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 04:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28122 |  JWX vulnerable to a denial of service attack using compressed JWE message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28122</link><description>JWX is Go module implementing various JWx (JWA/JWE/JWK/JWS/JWT, otherwise known as JOSE) technologies. This vulnerability allows an attacker with a trusted public key to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition by crafting a malicious JSON Web Encryption (JWE) token with an exceptionally high compression ratio. This issue has been patched in versions 1.2.29 and 2.0.21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28176 | jose vulnerable to resource exhaustion via specifically crafted JWE with compressed plaintext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28176</link><description>jose is JavaScript module for JSON Object Signing and Encryption, providing support for JSON Web Tokens (JWT), JSON Web Signature (JWS), JSON Web Encryption (JWE), JSON Web Key (JWK), JSON Web Key Set (JWKS), and more. A vulnerability has 
 been identified in the JSON Web Encryption (JWE) decryption interfaces, specifically related to the support for decompressing plaintext after its decryption. Under certain conditions it is possible to have the user's environment consume unreasonable amount of CPU time or memory during JWE Decryption operations. This issue has been patched in versions 2.0.7 and 4.15.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28180 | Go JOSE vulnerable to Improper Handling of Highly Compressed Data (Data Amplification)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28180</link><description>Package jose aims to provide an implementation of the Javascript Object Signing and Encryption set of standards. An attacker could send a JWE containing compressed data that used large amounts of memory and CPU when decompressed by Decrypt or DecryptMulti. Those functions now return an error if the decompressed data would exceed 250kB or 10x the compressed size (whichever is larger). This vulnerability has been patched in versions 4.0.1, 3.0.3 and 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28184 | WeasyPrint allows the attachment of arbitrary files and URLs to a PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28184</link><description>WeasyPrint helps web developers to create PDF documents. Since version 61.0, there's a vulnerability which allows attaching content of arbitrary files and URLs to a generated PDF document, even if `url_fetcher` is configured to prevent access to files and URLs. This vulnerability has been patched in version 61.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 01:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>