<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 07:38:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10193 | WAVLINK WN530H4/WN530HG4/WN572HG3 internet.cgi ping_ddns command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10193</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WAVLINK WN530H4, WN530HG4 and WN572HG3 up to 20221028 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function ping_ddns of the file internet.cgi. The manipulation of the argument DDNS leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 07:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10192 | PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10192</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file search.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 07:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10191 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Booking Details Page book-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/book-details.php of the component Booking Details Page. The manipulation of the argument Official Remark leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 05:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10173 | didi DDMQ Console Module improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10173</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in didi DDMQ 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Console Module. The manipulation with the input /;login leads to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 05:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10171 | code-projects Blood Bank System massage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10171</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Blood Bank System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/massage.php. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 04:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10170 | code-projects Hospital Management System get_doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10170</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file get_doctor.php. The manipulation of the argument specilizationid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 04:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10169 | code-projects Hospital Management System change-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10169</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file change-password.php. The manipulation of the argument cpass leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 03:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10167 | Codezips Sales Management System deletecustind.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10167</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file deletecustind.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 03:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10166 | Codezips Sales Management System checkuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10166</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file checkuser.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10165 | Codezips Sales Management System deletecustcom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10165</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file deletecustcom.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10163 | SourceCodester Sentiment Based Movie Rating System movie_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10163</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Sentiment Based Movie Rating System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /msrps/movie_details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher disclosure mentions a slightly changed product name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10162 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Edit Subdomain Details Page edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10162</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-subadmin.php of the component Edit Subdomain Details Page. The manipulation of the argument sadminusername/fullname/emailid/mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "mobilenumber" to be affected. But it must be assumed that other parameters are affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10161 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Update Boat Image Page change-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10161</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file change-image.php of the component Update Boat Image Page. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 01:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10160 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System BW Dates Report Page bwdates-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10160</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bwdates-report-details.php of the component BW Dates Report Page. The manipulation of the argument fdate/tdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "fdate" to be affected. But it must be assumed "tdate" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10159 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System My Profile Page profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10159</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/profile.php of the component My Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument sadminusername/fullname/emailid/mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "mobilenumber" to be affected. But it must be assumed that other parameters are affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10158 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System session_start session fixiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10158</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. Affected is the function session_start. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10157 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Reset Your Password Page password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10157</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/password-recovery.php of the component Reset Your Password Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 22:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10156 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Sign In Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10156</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Sign In Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10155 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Book a Boat Page book-boat.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10155</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument phone_number leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 20:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10154 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Check Booking Status Page status.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10154</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file status.php of the component Check Booking Status Page. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10153 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System Book a Boat Page book-boat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10153</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument nopeople leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10142 | code-projects Blood Bank System viewrequest.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10142</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /viewrequest.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 17:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10141 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Session predictable state</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10141</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in jsbroks COCO Annotator 0.11.1. This affects an unknown part of the component Session Handler. The manipulation of the argument SECRET_KEY leads to predictable from observable state. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 15:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10140 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_supplier.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10140</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_supplier.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 14:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10139 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System add_new_supplier.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10139</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add_new_supplier.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 13:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10138 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System add_new_purchase.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10138</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add_new_purchase.php?action=is_supplier. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 13:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10137 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_medicine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10137</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /manage_medicine.php?action=delete. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10136 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10136</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument invoice_number leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 12:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10135 | ESAFENET CDG NetSecConfigService.java actionDelNetSecConfig sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10135</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function actionDelNetSecConfig of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/netSec/NetSecConfigService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10134 | ESAFENET CDG MultiServerAjax.java connectLogout sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10134</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function connectLogout of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/ajax/MultiServerAjax.java. The manipulation of the argument servername leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 10:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9897 | StreamWeasels Twitch Integration &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sw-twitch-embed Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9897</link><description>The StreamWeasels Twitch Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sw-twitch-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 09:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10133 | ESAFENET CDG NetSecPolicyAjax.java updateNetSecPolicyPriority sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10133</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function updateNetSecPolicyPriority of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/ajax/NetSecPolicyAjax.java. The manipulation of the argument id/frontId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 08:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6243 | EventON PRO - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via admin_test_email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6243</link><description>The EventON PRO - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the admin_test_email function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send test emails to arbitrary email addresses via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 06:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9889 | ElementInvader Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9889</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9 via the Page Loader widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to view private/draft/password protected posts, pages, and Elementor templates that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 06:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21536 | Versions of the package http-proxy-middleware before 2.0.7, from 3.0.0 and before 3.0.3 are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21536</link><description>Versions of the package http-proxy-middleware before 2.0.7, from 3.0.0 and before 3.0.3 are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to an UnhandledPromiseRejection error thrown by micromatch. An attacker could kill the Node.js process and crash the server by making requests to certain paths.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 05:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10131 | Remote Code Execution in infiniflow/ragflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10131</link><description>The `add_llm` function in `llm_app.py` in infiniflow/ragflow version 0.11.0 contains a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability. The function uses user-supplied input `req['llm_factory']` and `req['llm_name']` to dynamically instantiate classes from various model dictionaries. This approach allows an attacker to potentially execute arbitrary code due to the lack of comprehensive input validation or sanitization. An attacker could provide a malicious value for 'llm_factory' that, when used as an index to these model dictionaries, results in the execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 04:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25218 | Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp;amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25218</link><description>The Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 03:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9219 | WordPress Social Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.19 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9219</link><description>The WordPress Social Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29213 | Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29213</link><description>Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via unspecified attack vector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 23:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29821 | Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29821</link><description>Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via unspecified attack vector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 23:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37404 | Improper Input Validation in the admin portal of Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.1 and 9.1R18.9, or Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37404</link><description>Improper Input Validation in the admin portal of Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.1 and 9.1R18.9, or Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 23:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43577 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43577</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 22:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10129 | HFO4 shudong-share Share create_share.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10129</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in HFO4 shudong-share up to 2.4.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /includes/create_share.php of the component Share Handler. The manipulation of the argument fkey leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10130 | Tenda AC8 SetSysAutoRebbotCfg formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10130</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This vulnerability affects the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10128 | Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer td.js.gz risky encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10128</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer 2.01. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file td.js.gz. The manipulation leads to risky cryptographic algorithm. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 21:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10123 | Tenda AC8 saveParentControlInfo compare_parentcontrol_time stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10123</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function compare_parentcontrol_time of the file /goform/saveParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This is not the same issue like CVE-2023-33671. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10122 | Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer Operator Details Form InnerRepPlus.html missing password field masking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer 2.01. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /InnerRepPlus.html of the component Operator Details Form. The manipulation leads to missing password field masking. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49361 | Potential Vulnerability in ACON Library: Improper Input Validation Leading to Malicious Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49361</link><description>ACON is a widely-used library of tools for machine learning that focuses on adaptive correlation optimization. A potential vulnerability has been identified in the input validation process, which could lead to arbitrary code execution if exploited. This issue could allow an attacker to submit malicious input data, bypassing input validation, resulting in remote code execution in certain machine learning applications using the ACON library. All users utilizing ACON’s input-handling functions are potentially at risk. Specifically, machine learning models or applications that ingest user-generated data without proper sanitization are the most vulnerable. Users running ACON on production servers are at heightened risk, as the vulnerability could be exploited remotely. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10121 | wfh45678 Radar Interface authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10121</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wfh45678 Radar up to 1.0.8 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Interface Handler. The manipulation with the input /../ leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This appears not to be a path traversal weakness. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45944 | In J2eeFAST &lt;=2.7, the backend function has unsafe filtering, which allows an attacker to trigger certain sensitive functions resulting in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45944</link><description>In J2eeFAST &lt;=2.7, the backend function has unsafe filtering, which allows an attacker to trigger certain sensitive functions resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9593 | Time Clock &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 &amp;amp; Time Clock Pro &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated (Limited) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9593</link><description>The Time Clock plugin and Time Clock Pro plugin for WordPress are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 (for Time Clock) and 1.1.4 (for Time Clock Pro) via the 'etimeclockwp_load_function_callback' function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. The invoked function's parameters cannot be specified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10120 | wfh45678 Radar upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10120</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wfh45678 Radar up to 1.0.8 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /services/v1/common/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48016 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48016</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure. The attacker may be able to use exposed credentials to access the system with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47241 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains an Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability. A low pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47241</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains an Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access and modification of transmitted data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6080 | Privilege Escalation to SYSTEM in Lakeside Software Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6080</link><description>Lakeside Software’s SysTrack LsiAgent Installer version 10.7.8 for Windows contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability which allows attackers SYSTEM level access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42508 | This vulnerability could be exploited, leading to unauthorized disclosure of information to authenticated users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42508</link><description>This vulnerability could be exploited, leading to unauthorized disclosure of information to authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9537 | ScienceLogic SL1 unspecified vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9537</link><description>ScienceLogic SL1 (formerly EM7) is affected by an unspecified vulnerability involving an unspecified third-party component packaged with SL1. The vulnerability is addressed in SL1 versions 12.1.3+, 12.2.3+, and 12.3+.  Remediations have been made available for all SL1 versions back to version lines 10.1.x, 10.2.x, 11.1.x, 11.2.x, and 11.3.x.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 14:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47240 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.24 contains an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A local attacker with low privileges can acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47240</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.24 contains an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A local attacker with low privileges can access the file system and could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain write access to unauthorized data and cause a version update failure condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9674 | Debrandify · Remove or Replace WordPress Branding &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9674</link><description>The Debrandify · Remove or Replace WordPress Branding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43300 | WordPress Movie Database plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43300</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bert Kößler Movie Database allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Movie Database: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49224 | WordPress Mitm Bug Tracker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mahesh Patel Mitm Bug Tracker allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mitm Bug Tracker: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49225 | WordPress wpPricing Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Swebdeveloper wpPricing Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects wpPricing Builder: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49228 | WordPress bVerse Convert plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CrossedCode bVerse Convert allows Stored XSS.This issue affects bVerse Convert: from n/a through 1.3.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49230 | WordPress  Ajax Custom CSS/JS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49230</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Harpreet Singh Ajax Custom CSS/JS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ajax Custom CSS/JS: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49231 | WordPress WordPress Video plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Peter CyClop WordPress Video allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Video: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49232 | WordPress El mejor Cluster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49232</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Javier Loureiro El mejor Cluster allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects El mejor Cluster: from n/a through 1.1.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49233 | WordPress MAS Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MadrasThemes MAS Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects MAS Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49234 | WordPress Plexx Elementor Extension plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themeworm Plexx Elementor Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Plexx Elementor Extension: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49236 | WordPress Crazy Call To Action Box plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hafiz Uddin Ahmed Crazy Call To Action Box allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Crazy Call To Action Box: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49238 | WordPress ADIF Log Search Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0f - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49238</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M. Konieczny, DH9SB ADIF Log Search Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ADIF Log Search Widget: from n/a through 1.0f.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49239 | WordPress Add Categories Post Footer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nikhil Vaghela Add Categories Post Footer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Add Categories Post Footer: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49240 | WordPress AB Categories Search Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49240</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Agustin Berasategui AB Categories Search Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AB Categories Search Widget: from n/a through 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49241 | WordPress Tito plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tady Walsh Tito allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Tito: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49243 | WordPress Dynamic Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49243</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Jon Vincent Mendoza Dynamic Elementor Addons allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dynamic Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10057 | RSS Feed Widget &amp;lt;= 2.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via rfw-youtube-videos Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10057</link><description>The RSS Feed Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's rfw-youtube-videos shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9425 | Advanced Category and Custom Taxonomy Image &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ad_tax_image Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9425</link><description>The Advanced Category and Custom Taxonomy Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ad_tax_image shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47486 | There is an XSS vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could inject scripts into certain pages by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47486</link><description>There is an XSS vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could inject scripts into certain pages by building malicious data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47485 | There is a CSV injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could build malicious data to gene...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47485</link><description>There is a CSV injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could build malicious data to generate executable commands in the CSV file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47487 | There is a SQL injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47487</link><description>There is a SQL injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4740 | MXsecurity Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4740</link><description>MXsecurity software versions v1.1.0 and prior are vulnerable because of the use of hard-coded credentials. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to tamper with sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49570 | Insecure Trust of Basic Constraints certificate in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11210)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49570</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software trusts a certificate issued by an entity that isn't authorized to issue certificates. This occurs when the "Basic Constraints" extension in the certificate indicates that it is meant to be an "End Entity”. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4739 | MXsecurity License Generation Function Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4739</link><description>The lack of access restriction to a resource from unauthorized users makes MXsecurity software versions v1.1.0 and prior vulnerable. By acquiring a valid authenticator, an attacker can pose as an authorized user and successfully access the resource.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49567 | Insecure Trust of certificates using collision hash functions in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11239)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49567</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the product incorrectly checks the site's certificate, which allows an attacker to make MITM SSL connections to an arbitrary site. The product trusts certificates that are issued using the MD5 and SHA1 collision hash functions which allow attackers to create rogue certificates that appear legitimate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6058 | HTTPS Certificate Validation Issue in Bitdefender Safepay (VA-11167)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6058</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Safepay's handling of HTTPS connections. The issue arises when the product blocks a connection due to an untrusted server certificate but allows the user to add the site to exceptions, resulting in the product trusting the certificate for subsequent HTTPS scans. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack by using a self-signed certificate, which the product will trust after the site has been added to exceptions. This can lead to the interception and potential alteration of secure communications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6057 | Insecure Trust of DSA-Signed Certificates in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11166)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6057</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of certificates issued using the DSA signature algorithm. The product does not properly check the certificate chain, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites using a DSA-signed certificate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10055 | Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpsaio_snapchat Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10055</link><description>The Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpsaio_snapchat shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10078 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10078</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to add, modify, or delete plugin options and posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10079 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10079</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'text' parameter in the 'ajax_import_content' function. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10080 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10080</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via post meta in versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6056 | Insecure Trust of Self-Signed Certificates in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11164)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6056</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of self-signed certificates. The product is found to trust certificates signed with the RIPEMD-160 hashing algorithm without proper validation, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6055 | Improper Certificate Validation in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11158)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6055</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software fails to properly validate website certificates. Specifically, if a site certificate lacks the "Server Authentication" specification in the Extended Key Usage extension, the product does not verify the certificate's compliance with the site, deeming such certificates as valid. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9206 | MAS Companies For WP Job Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9206</link><description>The MAS Companies For WP Job Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9703 | Arconix Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9703</link><description>The Arconix Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46897 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. A logged-in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46897</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. A logged-in user with the permission of table management may obtain and/or alter the information of the unauthorized table.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47793 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. When accessing the edit screen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47793</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. When accessing the edit screen containing custom columns (column type: images or files), an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38820 | CVE-2024-38820: Spring Framework DataBinder Case Sensitive Match Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38820</link><description>The fix for CVE-2022-22968 made disallowedFields patterns in DataBinder case insensitive. However, String.toLowerCase() has some Locale dependent exceptions that could potentially result in fields not protected as expected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10014 | Flat UI Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via flatbtn Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10014</link><description>The Flat UI Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's flatbtn shortcode in version 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10040 | Infinite-Scroll &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10040</link><description>The Infinite-Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_ajax_edit and process_ajax_delete function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make changes to plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10049 | Edit WooCommerce Templates &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10049</link><description>The Edit WooCommerce Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8740 | GetResponse Forms by Optin Cat &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8740</link><description>The GetResponse Forms by Optin Cat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8790 | Social Share With Floating Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8790</link><description>The Social Share With Floating Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8916 | Suki Sites Import &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8916</link><description>The Suki Sites Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9350 | DPD Baltic Shipping &amp;lt;= 1.2.83 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9350</link><description>The DPD Baltic Shipping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search_value' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.83 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9361 | Bulk images optimizer: Resize, optimize, convert to webp, rename ... &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9361</link><description>The Bulk images optimizer: Resize, optimize, convert to webp, rename … plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_configuration' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9364 | SendGrid for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9364</link><description>The SendGrid for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_mailplus_clear_logs' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9366 | Easy Menu Manager | WPZest &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9366</link><description>The Easy Menu Manager | WPZest plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9373 | Elemenda &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9373</link><description>The Elemenda plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9382 | Gantry 4 Framework &amp;lt;= 4.1.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9382</link><description>The Gantry 4 Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'override_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9383 | Parcel Pro &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9383</link><description>The Parcel Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'action' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9452 | Branding &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9452</link><description>The Branding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9848 | Product Customizer Light &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9848</link><description>The Product Customizer Light plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9892 | Add Widget After Content &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9892</link><description>The Add Widget After Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10119 | SECOM WRTM326 - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10119</link><description>The wireless router WRTM326 from SECOM does not properly validate a specific parameter. An unauthenticated remote attacker could execute arbitrary system commands by sending crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10118 | SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10118</link><description>SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC does not properly filter user input in the specific functionality. Unauthenticated remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability to inject and execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9264 | Grafana SQL Expressions allow for remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9264</link><description>The SQL Expressions experimental feature of Grafana allows for the evaluation of `duckdb` queries containing user input. These queries are insufficiently sanitized before being passed to `duckdb`, leading to a command injection and local file inclusion vulnerability. Any user with the VIEWER or higher permission is capable of executing this attack.  The `duckdb` binary must be present in Grafana's $PATH for this attack to function; by default, this binary is not installed in Grafana distributions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 03:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>