<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:15:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-4177 | Host whitelist parser issue in GravityZone Console On-Premise (VA-11554)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4177</link><description>A host whitelist parser issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-2 that are running only on premise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5665 | Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) 2.7.1 - 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Options Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5665</link><description>The Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ‘export_settings’ function in versions 2.7.1 to 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read arbitrary options on affected sites.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3049 | Booth: specially crafted hash can lead to invalid hmac being accepted by booth server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3049</link><description>A flaw was found in Booth, a cluster ticket manager. If a specially-crafted hash is passed to gcry_md_get_algo_dlen(), it may allow an invalid HMAC to be accepted by the Booth server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5656 | Google CSE &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5656</link><description>The Google CSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0972 | BuddyPress Members Only &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Improper Access Control to Sensitive Information Exposure via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0972</link><description>The BuddyPress Members Only plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.5 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's "All Other Sections On Your Site Will be Opened to Guest" feature (when unset) and view restricted page and post content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1175 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.6 - Unauthenticated Payment Deletion via delete_payment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1175</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_payment' function in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary payments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5141 | Rotating Tweets (Twitter widget and shortcode) &amp;lt;= 1.9.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5141</link><description>The Rotating Tweets (Twitter widget and shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's' 'rotatingtweets' in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5152 | ElementsReady Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 6.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5152</link><description>The ElementsReady Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5153 | Startklar Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.7.15 - Unauthenticated Path Traversal to Arbitrary Directory Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5153</link><description>The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.15 via the 'dropzone_hash' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to copy the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information, and to delete arbitrary directories, including the root WordPress directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5161 | Magical Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.1.39 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5161</link><description>The Magical Addons For Elementor ( Header Footer Builder, Free Elementor Widgets, Elementor Templates Library ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.39 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5162 | WordPress prettyPhoto &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5162</link><description>The WordPress prettyPhoto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2922 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Widget Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2922</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via widget tags in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4212 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4212</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's TF Group Image, TF Nav Menu, TF Posts, TF Woo Product Grid, TF Accordion, and TF Image Box widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4364 | Qi Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4364</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4458 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4458</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in several widgets via URL parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4459 | Themesflat Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Widget Titles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4459</link><description>The Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget's titles in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4608 | SellKit – Funnel builder and checkout optimizer for WooCommerce to sell more, faster &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4608</link><description>The SellKit – Funnel builder and checkout optimizer for WooCommerce to sell more, faster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4707 | Materialis Companion &amp;lt;= 1.3.41 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Store Cross-Site Scripting via materialis_contact_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4707</link><description>The Materialis Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's materialis_contact_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.41 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5449 | WP Dark Mode – WordPress Dark Mode Plugin for Improved Accessibility, Dark Theme, Night Mode, and Social Sharing &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5449</link><description>The WP Dark Mode – WordPress Dark Mode Plugin for Improved Accessibility, Dark Theme, Night Mode, and Social Sharing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wpdm_social_share_save_options function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5615 | Open Graph &amp;lt;= 1.11.2 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5615</link><description>The Open Graph plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.2 via the 'opengraph_default_description' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including partial content of password-protected blog posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2017 | Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp;amp; Clock &amp;lt;= 2.7.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2017</link><description>The Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp; Clock plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the conditionsRow and switchCountdown functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject PHP Objects and modify the status of countdowns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6956 | EasyAzon – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via easyazon-cloaking-locale</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6956</link><description>The EasyAzon – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘easyazon-cloaking-locale’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6966 | The Moneytizer &amp;lt;= 9.5.20 - Missing Authorization via multiple AJAX actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6966</link><description>The The Moneytizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX functions in the /core/core_ajax.php file in all versions up to, and including, 9.5.20. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to update and retrieve billing and bank details, update and reset the plugin's settings, and update languages as well as other lower-severity actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6968 | The Moneytizer &amp;lt;= 9.5.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via multiple AJAX actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6968</link><description>The The Moneytizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 9.5.20. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple AJAX functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to to update and retrieve billing and bank details, update and reset the plugin's settings, and update languages as well as other lower-severity actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0910 | Restrict for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0910</link><description>The Restrict for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to improper restrictions on hidden data that make it accessible through the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive data from post content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2350 | Clever Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple CAFE Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2350</link><description>The Clever Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the CAFE Icon, CAFE Team Member, and CAFE Slider widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4194 | Album and Image Gallery plus Lightbox &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4194</link><description>The The Album and Image Gallery plus Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4705 | Testimonials Widget &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via testimonials Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4705</link><description>The Testimonials Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's testimonials shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4788 | Boostify Header Footer Builder for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Page/Post Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4788</link><description>The Boostify Header Footer Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the create_bhf_post function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create pages or posts with arbitrary content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4942 | Custom Dash &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4942</link><description>The Custom Dash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5001 | Image Hover Effects for Elementor with Lightbox and Flipbox &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via _id, oxi_addons_f_title_tag, and content_description_tag Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5001</link><description>The Image Hover Effects for Elementor with Lightbox and Flipbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the '_id', 'oxi_addons_f_title_tag', and 'content_description_tag' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5179 | Cowidgets – Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5179</link><description>The Cowidgets – Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 via the 'item_style' and 'style' parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5224 | Easy Social Like Box – Popup – Sidebar Widget &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5224</link><description>The Easy Social Like Box – Popup – Sidebar Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cardoza_facebook_like_box' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5324 | Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) 2.7.1 - 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5324</link><description>The Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'import_settings' function in versions 2.7.1 to 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary options on affected sites. This can be used to enable new user registration and set the default role for new users to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5342 | Simple Image Popup Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5342</link><description>The Simple Image Popup Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sips_popup' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0912 | CCURE passwords exposed to administrators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0912</link><description>Under certain circumstances the Microsoft® Internet Information Server (IIS) used to host the C•CURE 9000 Web Server will log Microsoft Windows credential details within logs. There is no impact to non-web service interfaces C•CURE 9000 or prior versions</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 23:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5653 | Chanjet Smooth T+system keyEdit.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5653</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Chanjet Smooth T+system 3.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /tplus/UFAQD/keyEdit.aspx. The manipulation of the argument KeyID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-267185 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5171 | heap buffer overflow in libaom</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5171</link><description>Integer overflow in libaom internal function img_alloc_helper can lead to heap buffer overflow. This function can be reached via 3 callers:


  *  Calling aom_img_alloc() with a large value of the d_w, d_h, or align parameter may result in integer overflows in the calculations of buffer sizes and offsets and some fields of the returned aom_image_t struct may be invalid.
  *  Calling aom_img_wrap() with a large value of the d_w, d_h, or align parameter may result in integer overflows in the calculations of buffer sizes and offsets and some fields of the returned aom_image_t struct may be invalid.
  *  Calling aom_img_alloc_with_border() with a large value of the d_w, d_h, align, size_align, or border parameter may result in integer overflows in the calculations of buffer sizes and offsets and some fields of the returned aom_image_t struct may be invalid.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36667 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/idcProType_deal.php?mudi=add&amp;nohrefStr=c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36667</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/idcProType_deal.php?mudi=add&amp;amp;nohrefStr=close</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36668 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component admin/type_deal.php?mudi=del</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36668</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component admin/type_deal.php?mudi=del</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50804 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 128...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50804</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 1280, 1380, 1330, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Auto T5123. The baseband software does not properly check format types specified by the NAS (Non-Access-Stratum) module. This can lead to bypass of authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36669 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component admin/type_deal.php?mudi=add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36669</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component admin/type_deal.php?mudi=add.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36670 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component admin/vpsClass_deal.php?mudi=del</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36670</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component admin/vpsClass_deal.php?mudi=del</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49927 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49927</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 1280, 1380, 1330, 9110, W920, Exynos Modem 5123, Exynos Modem 5300, and Exynos Auto T5123. The baseband software does not properly check format types specified by the RRC. This can lead to a lack of encryption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49928 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49928</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 1280, 1380, 1330, 9110, W920, Exynos Modem 5123, Exynos Modem 5300, and Exynos Auto T5123. The baseband software does not properly check states specified by the RRC. This can lead to disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50803 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 128...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50803</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 1280, 1380, 1330, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Auto T5123. The baseband software does not properly check replay protection specified by the NAS (Non-Access-Stratum) module. This can lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27370 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27370</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_config_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on hal_req-&gt;num_config_discovery_attr coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27371 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27371</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_followup_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on hal_req-&gt;service_specific_info_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27372 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27372</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_config_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on disc_attr-&gt;infrastructure_ssid_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27373 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27373</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_config_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on disc_attr-&gt;mesh_id_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27374 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27374</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_publish_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on hal_req-&gt;service_specific_info_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27375 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27375</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_followup_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on hal_req-&gt;sdea_service_specific_info_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27377 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27377</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_get_security_info_nl(), there is no input validation check on sec_info-&gt;key_info.body.pmk_info.pmk_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27381 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27381</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_send_action_frame_ut(), there is no input validation check on len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap over-read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27376 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27376</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_subscribe_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on hal_req-&gt;rx_match_filter_len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27378 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27378</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_send_action_frame_cert(), there is no input validation check on len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap over-read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27379 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27379</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_nan_subscribe_get_nl_params(), there is no input validation check on hal_req-&gt;num_intf_addr_present coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap overwrite.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27380 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27380</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_set_delayed_wakeup_type(), there is no input validation check on a length of ioctl_args-&gt;args[i] coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap over-read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27382 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27382</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 980, Exynos 850, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, and Exynos 1330. In the function slsi_send_action_frame(), there is no input validation check on len coming from userspace, which can lead to a heap over-read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28818 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28818</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 2200, 1280, 1380, 1330, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Auto T5123. The baseband software does not properly check states specified by the RRC (Radio Resource Control) module. This can lead to disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5037 | Openshift/telemeter: iss check during jwt authentication can be bypassed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5037</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift's Telemeter. If certain conditions are in place, an attacker can use a forged token to bypass the issue ("iss") check during JSON web token (JWT) authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5184 | Prompt Injection in EmailGPT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5184</link><description>The EmailGPT service contains a prompt injection vulnerability. The service uses an API service that allows a malicious user to inject a direct prompt and take over the service logic. Attackers can exploit the issue by forcing the AI service to leak the standard hard-coded system prompts and/or execute unwanted prompts. When engaging with EmailGPT by submitting a malicious prompt that requests harmful information, the system will respond by providing the requested data. This vulnerability can be exploited by any individual with access to the service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36129 | OpenTelemetry Collector has a Denial of Service via Zip/Decompression Bomb sent over HTTP or gRPC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36129</link><description>The OpenTelemetry Collector offers a vendor-agnostic implementation on how to receive, process and export telemetry data. An unsafe decompression vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to crash the collector via excessive memory consumption. OTel Collector version 0.102.1 fixes this issue.  It is also fixed in the confighttp module version 0.102.0 and configgrpc module version 0.102.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4008 | FDSK Leak in KNX Secure Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4008</link><description>FDSK Leak in ABB, Busch-Jaeger, FTS Display (version 1.00) and BCU (version 1.3.0.33) allows attacker to take control via access to local KNX Bus-System</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4009 | Replay Attack in KNX Secure Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4009</link><description>Replay Attack

in ABB, Busch-Jaeger, FTS Display (version 1.00) and BCU (version 1.3.0.33) allows attacker to capture/replay KNX telegram to local KNX Bus-System</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20404 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an SSRF at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20404</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an SSRF attack on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for specific HTTP requests that are sent to an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain limited sensitive information for services that are associated to the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20405 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored X...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20405</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored XSS attack by exploiting an RFI vulnerability. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for specific HTTP requests that are sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive information on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35674 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.109 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35674</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates).This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.109.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24789 | Mishandling of corrupt central directory record in archive/zip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24789</link><description>The archive/zip package's handling of certain types of invalid zip files differs from the behavior of most zip implementations. This misalignment could be exploited to create an zip file with contents that vary depending on the implementation reading the file. The archive/zip package now rejects files containing these errors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24790 | Unexpected behavior from Is methods for IPv4-mapped IPv6 addresses in net/netip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24790</link><description>The various Is methods (IsPrivate, IsLoopback, etc) did not work as expected for IPv4-mapped IPv6 addresses, returning false for addresses which would return true in their traditional IPv4 forms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3716 | Foreman-installer: candlepin database password being leaked to local users via the process list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3716</link><description>A flaw was found in foreman-installer when puppet-candlepin is invoked cpdb with the --password parameter. This issue leaks the password in the process list and allows an attacker to take advantage and obtain the password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4812 | Katello: potential cross-site scripting exploit in ui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4812</link><description>A flaw was found in the Katello plugin for Foreman, where it is possible to store malicious JavaScript code in the "Description" field of a user. This code can be executed when opening certain pages, for example, Host Collections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36837 | SQL Injection vulnerability in CRMEB v.5.2.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the getProductList function in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36837</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in CRMEB v.5.2.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the getProductList function in the ProductController.php file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5629 | Out-of-bounds read in bson module of PyMongo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5629</link><description>An out-of-bounds read in the 'bson' module of PyMongo 4.6.2 or earlier allows deserialization of malformed BSON provided by a Server to raise an exception which may contain arbitrary application memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35673 | WordPress Pure Chat plugin &amp;lt;= 2.22 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35673</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pure Chat by Ruby Pure Chat.This issue affects Pure Chat: from n/a through 2.22.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3469 | GP Premium &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3469</link><description>The GP Premium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the message parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5459 | Restaurant Menu and Food Ordering &amp;lt;= 2.4.16 - Missing Authorization to Menu Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5459</link><description>The Restaurant Menu and Food Ordering plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized creation of data due to a missing capability check on 'add_section', 'add_menu', 'add_menu_item', and 'add_menu_page' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create menu sections, menus, food items, and new menu pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1662 | Information Disclosure in Porty&amp;#x27;s PowerBank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1662</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in PORTY Smart Tech Technology Joint Stock Company PowerBank Application allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects PowerBank Application: before 2.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5526 | Grafana OnCall is an easy-to-use on-call management tool that will help reduce toil in on-call management through simpler workflows and inte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5526</link><description>Grafana OnCall is an easy-to-use on-call management tool that will help reduce toil in on-call management through simpler workflows and interfaces that are tailored specifically for engineers.

Grafana OnCall, from version 1.1.37 before 1.5.2 are vulnerable to a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the webhook functionallity. 

This issue was fixed in version 1.5.2</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4001 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.2.93 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpdm_modal_login_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4001</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpdm_modal_login_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.93 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5536 | GamiPress – Link &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5536</link><description>The GamiPress – Link plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's gamipress_link shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 09:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1272 | Information Disclosure to Source Code in TNB Mobile Solutions&amp;#x27; Cockpit Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1272</link><description>Inclusion of Sensitive Information in Source Code vulnerability in TNB Mobile Solutions Cockpit Software allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Cockpit Software: before v0.251.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4743 | LifterLMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for eLearning &amp;lt;= 7.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4743</link><description>The LifterLMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for eLearning plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the orderBy attribute of the lifterlms_favorites shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4821 | WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via su_lightbox Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4821</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_lightbox shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5571 | EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp;amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp;amp; Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 -  Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via EmbedPress PDF Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5571</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute within the plugin's EmbedPress PDF widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23669 | An improper authorization in Fortinet FortiWebManager version 7.2.0 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.4 and 6.3.0 and 6.2.3 through 6.2.4 and 6.0.2 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23669</link><description>An improper authorization in Fortinet FortiWebManager version 7.2.0 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.4 and 6.3.0 and 6.2.3 through 6.2.4 and 6.0.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via HTTP requests or CLI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4939 | Weaver Xtreme Theme Support &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via div Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4939</link><description>The Weaver Xtreme Theme Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's div shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5006 | Boostify Header Footer Builder for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via size Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5006</link><description>The Boostify Header Footer Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘size’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5439 | Blocksy &amp;lt;= 2.0.50 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5439</link><description>The Blocksy theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the custom_url parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.50 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5453 | ProfileGrid &amp;lt;= 5.8.6 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5453</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pm_dismissible_notice and pm_wizard_update_group_icon functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary options to the value '1' or change group icons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1164 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4.43 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Form Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1164</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's contact form widget error message and redirect URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.43 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied error messages. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2368 | Mollie Forms &amp;lt;= 2.6.13 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Post Duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2368</link><description>The Mollie Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the duplicateForm() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to duplicate forms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4088 | Gutenberg Blocks and Page Layouts – Attire Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4088</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks and Page Layouts – Attire Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the disable_fe_assets function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or above, to change the plugin's settings. Additionally, no nonce check is performed resulting in a CSRF vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5222 | Responsive Addons – Starter Templates, Advanced Features and Customizer Settings for Responsive Theme. &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5222</link><description>The Responsive Addons – Starter Templates, Advanced Features and Customizer Settings for Responsive Theme. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file uploader in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4886 | BuddyBoss Platform &amp;lt; 2.6.0 - Subscriber+ Comment on Private Post via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4886</link><description>The  contains an IDOR vulnerability that allows a user to comment on a private post by manipulating the ID included in the request</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1161 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4.43 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1161</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Custom Attributes for blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.43 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 05:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1940 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4.41 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1940</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via post content in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.41 due to insufficient input sanitization performed only on the client side and insufficient output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 05:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2087 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4.43 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2087</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form name values in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.43 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 05:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3667 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4.43 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Store Cross-Site Scripting via Widget Link To URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3667</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Link To' field of multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.43 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 05:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4295 | Email Subscribers by Icegram Express &amp;lt;= 5.7.20 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4295</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘hash’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.20 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 05:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5149 | BuddyForms &amp;lt;= 2.8.9 - Email Verification Bypass due to Insufficient Randomness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5149</link><description>The BuddyForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Email Verification Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.9 via the use of an insufficiently random activation code. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the email verification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 04:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34055 | Cyrus IMAP before 3.8.3 and 3.10.x before 3.10.0-rc1 allows authenticated attackers to cause unbounded memory allocation by sending many LIT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34055</link><description>Cyrus IMAP before 3.8.3 and 3.10.x before 3.10.0-rc1 allows authenticated attackers to cause unbounded memory allocation by sending many LITERALs in a single command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 04:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5262 | ProjectDiscovery Interactsh - Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5262</link><description>Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in smb server in ProjectDiscovery Interactsh allows remote attackers to read/write any files in the directory and subdirectories of where the victim runs interactsh-server via anonymous login.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 04:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5483 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8 - Basic Information Disclosure via JSON API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5483</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8 due to incorrect implementation of get_items_permissions_check function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract basic information about website users, including their emails</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5317 | Newsletter &amp;lt;= 8.3.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via np1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5317</link><description>The Newsletter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'np1' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5636 | itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5636</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file report/index.php. The manipulation of the argument procduct leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267092.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4084 | SSRF vulnerability in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4084</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the latest version of mintplex-labs/anything-llm, allowing attackers to bypass the official fix intended to restrict access to intranet IP addresses and protocols. Despite efforts to filter out intranet IP addresses starting with 192, 172, 10, and 127 through regular expressions and limit access protocols to HTTP and HTTPS, attackers can still bypass these restrictions using alternative representations of IP addresses and accessing other ports running on localhost. This vulnerability enables attackers to access any asset on the internal network, attack web services on the internal network, scan hosts on the internal network, and potentially access AWS metadata endpoints. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs, which can be exploited to perform SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28657 | Apport does not disable python crash handler before entering chroot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28657</link><description>Apport does not disable python crash handler before entering chroot</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28658 | Apport argument parsing mishandles filename splitting on older kernels resulting in argument spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28658</link><description>Apport argument parsing mishandles filename splitting on older kernels resulting in argument spoofing</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5635 | itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5635</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument txtsearch leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267091.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28654 | is_closing_session() allows users to fill up apport.log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28654</link><description>is_closing_session() allows users to fill up apport.log</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28655 | is_closing_session() allows users to create arbitrary tcp dbus connections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28655</link><description>is_closing_session() allows users to create arbitrary tcp dbus connections</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28656 | is_closing_session() allows users to consume RAM in the Apport process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28656</link><description>is_closing_session() allows users to consume RAM in the Apport process</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28652 | ~/.config/apport/settings parsing is vulnerable to "billion laughs" attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28652</link><description>~/.config/apport/settings parsing is vulnerable to "billion laughs" attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30889 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in audimex audimexEE v.15.1.2 and fixed in 15.1.3.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30889</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in audimex audimexEE v.15.1.2 and fixed in 15.1.3.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the service, method, widget_type, request_id, payload parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36675 | LyLme_spage v1.9.5 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the get_head function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36675</link><description>LyLme_spage v1.9.5 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the get_head function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36121 |  netty-incubator-codec-ohttp&amp;#x27;s BoringSSLAEADContext Repeats Nonces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36121</link><description>netty-incubator-codec-ohttp is the OHTTP implementation for netty. BoringSSLAEADContext keeps track of how many OHTTP responses have been sent and uses this sequence number to calculate the appropriate nonce to use with the encryption algorithm. Unfortunately, two separate errors combine which would allow an attacker to cause the sequence number to overflow and thus the nonce to repeat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32974 | Envoy affected by a crash in EnvoyQuicServerStream::OnInitialHeadersComplete()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32974</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. A crash was observed in `EnvoyQuicServerStream::OnInitialHeadersComplete()` with following call stack. It is a use-after-free caused by QUICHE continuing push request headers after `StopReading()` being called on the stream. As after `StopReading()`, the HCM's `ActiveStream` might have already be destroyed and any up calls from QUICHE could potentially cause use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32975 | Envoy crashes in QuicheDataReader::PeekVarInt62Length()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32975</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. There is a crash at `QuicheDataReader::PeekVarInt62Length()`. It is caused by integer underflow in the `QuicStreamSequencerBuffer::PeekRegion()` implementation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32976 | Envoy can enter an endless loop while decompressing Brotli data with extra input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32976</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Envoyproxy with a Brotli filter can get into an endless loop during decompression of Brotli data with extra input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34362 | Envoy affected by a crash (use-after-free) in EnvoyQuicServerStream</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34362</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. There is a use-after-free in `HttpConnectionManager` (HCM) with `EnvoyQuicServerStream` that can crash Envoy. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a request without `FIN`, then a `RESET_STREAM` frame, and then after receiving the response, closing the connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34363 | Envoy can crash due to uncaught nlohmann JSON exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34363</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Due to how Envoy invoked the nlohmann JSON library, the library could throw an uncaught exception from downstream data if incomplete UTF-8 strings were serialized. The uncaught exception would cause Envoy to crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34364 | Envoy OOM vector from HTTP async client with unbounded response buffer for mirror response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34364</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Envoy exposed an out-of-memory (OOM) vector from the mirror response, since async HTTP client will buffer the response with an unbounded buffer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23326 | Envoy incorrectly accepts HTTP 200 response for entering upgrade mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23326</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. A theoretical request smuggling vulnerability exists through Envoy if a server can be tricked into adding an upgrade header into a response. Per RFC https://www.rfc-editor.org/rfc/rfc7230#section-6.7 a server sends 101 when switching protocols. Envoy incorrectly accepts a 200 response from a server when requesting a protocol upgrade, but 200 does not indicate protocol switch. This opens up the possibility of request smuggling through Envoy if the server can be tricked into adding the upgrade header to the response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 20:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4219 | SSRF In BeyondInsight</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4219</link><description>Prior to 23.2, it is possible to perform arbitrary Server-Side requests via HTTP-based connectors within BeyondInsight, resulting in a server-side request forgery vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 20:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4220 | Information Disclosure in BeyondInsight</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4220</link><description>Prior to 23.1, an information disclosure vulnerability exists within BeyondInsight which can allow an attacker to enumerate usernames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 20:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28103 | Action Pack is missing security headers on non-HTML responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28103</link><description>Action Pack is a framework for handling and responding to web requests. Since 6.1.0, the application configurable Permissions-Policy is only served on responses with an HTML related Content-Type. This vulnerability is fixed in  6.1.7.8, 7.0.8.2, and 7.1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 20:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32464 | ActionText ContentAttachment can Contain Unsanitized HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32464</link><description>Action Text brings rich text content and editing to Rails. Instances of ActionText::Attachable::ContentAttachment included within a rich_text_area tag could potentially contain unsanitized HTML. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.1.3.4 and 7.2.0.beta2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 20:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4520 | Improper Access Control in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4520</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in the gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt application, specifically in version 20240410. This vulnerability allows any user on the server to access the chat history of any other user without requiring any form of interaction between the users. Exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to data breaches, including the exposure of sensitive personal details, financial data, or confidential conversations. Additionally, it could facilitate identity theft and manipulation or fraud through the unauthorized access to users' chat histories. This issue is due to insufficient access control mechanisms in the application's handling of chat history data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 20:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30525 | WordPress Move Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30525</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in moveaddons Move Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Move Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30528 | WordPress Spiffy Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30528</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins Spiffy Calendar.This issue affects Spiffy Calendar: from n/a through 4.9.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25095 | WordPress Easy Forms for Mailchimp plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25095</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Code Parrots Easy Forms for Mailchimp.This issue affects Easy Forms for Mailchimp: from n/a through 6.9.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30484 | WordPress RT Easy Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30484</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RT Easy Builder – Advanced addons for Elementor.This issue affects RT Easy Builder – Advanced addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34759 | WordPress Picture Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34759</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VideoWhisper Picture Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Picture Gallery: from n/a through 1.5.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35670 | WordPress Integrate Google Drive plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.93 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35670</link><description>Broken Authentication vulnerability in SoftLab Integrate Google Drive.This issue affects Integrate Google Drive: from n/a through 1.3.93.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35672 | WordPress Netgsm plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35672</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Netgsm.This issue affects Netgsm: from n/a through 2.9.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36857 | Jan v0.4.12 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the /v1/app/readFileSync interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36857</link><description>Jan v0.4.12 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the /v1/app/readFileSync interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36858 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /v1/app/writeFileSync interface of Jan v0.4.12 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36858</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /v1/app/writeFileSync interface of Jan v0.4.12 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37273 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /v1/app/appendFileSync interface of Jan v0.4.12 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37273</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /v1/app/appendFileSync interface of Jan v0.4.12 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29004 | SolarWinds Platform Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29004</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was determined to be affected by a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability affecting the web console. A high-privileged user and user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28996 | SolarWinds Platform SWQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28996</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was determined to be affected by a SWQL Injection Vulnerability. Attack complexity is high for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28999 | SolarWinds Platform Race Condition Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28999</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was determined to be affected by a Race Condition Vulnerability affecting the web console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36549 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/vpsCompany_deal.php?mudi=rev&amp;nohrefStr=close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36549</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/vpsCompany_deal.php?mudi=rev&amp;amp;nohrefStr=close</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36550 | idccms V1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/vpsCompany_deal.php?mudi=add&amp;nohrefStr=close</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36550</link><description>idccms V1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/vpsCompany_deal.php?mudi=add&amp;amp;nohrefStr=close</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32871 | Pimcore Vulnerable to Flooding Server with Thumbnail files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32871</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. The Pimcore thumbnail generation can be used to flood the server with large files. By changing the file extension or scaling factor of the requested thumbnail, attackers can create files that are much larger in file size than the original. This vulnerability is fixed in 11.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36547 | idccms V1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component http://127.0.0.1:80/admin/vpsClass_deal.php?mud...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36547</link><description>idccms V1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component http://127.0.0.1:80/admin/vpsClass_deal.php?mudi=add</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36548 | idccms V1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via admin/vpsCompany_deal.php?mudi=del</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36548</link><description>idccms V1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via admin/vpsCompany_deal.php?mudi=del</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0756 | Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.3000000023 - Iframe Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0756</link><description>The Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress plugin through 4.3000000023 lacks validation of URLs when adding iframes, allowing attackers to inject an iFrame in the page and thus load arbitrary content from any page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35649 | WordPress Save as PDF Plugin by Pdfcrowd plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35649</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pdfcrowd Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd: from n/a through 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35651 | WordPress WP Flow Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins WP Flow Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Flow Plus: from n/a through 5.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35652 | WordPress Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35652</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saso Nikolov Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35653 | WordPress Visual Composer Website Builder, Landing Page Builder, Custom Theme Builder, Maintenance Mode &amp;amp; Coming Soon Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 45.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in visualcomposer.Com Visual Composer Website Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Visual Composer Website Builder: from n/a through 45.8.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36400 | nano-id is unable to generate the correct character set</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36400</link><description>nano-id is a unique string ID generator for Rust. Affected versions of the nano-id crate incorrectly generated IDs using a reduced character set in the `nano_id::base62` and `nano_id::base58` functions. Specifically, the `base62` function used a character set of 32 symbols instead of the intended 62 symbols, and the `base58` function used a character set of 16 symbols instead of the intended 58 symbols. Additionally, the `nano_id::gen` macro is also affected when a custom character set that is not a power of 2 in size is specified. It should be noted that `nano_id::base64` is not affected by this vulnerability. This can result in a significant reduction in entropy, making the generated IDs predictable and vulnerable to brute-force attacks when the IDs are used in security-sensitive contexts such as session tokens or unique identifiers. The vulnerability is fixed in 0.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35654 | WordPress Responsive theme &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35654</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CyberChimps Responsive allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive: from n/a through 5.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35655 | WordPress Brave – Interactive Content plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brave Brave Popup Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Brave Popup Builder: from n/a through 0.6.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35664 | WordPress WPvivid Backup for MainWP plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.32 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPvivid Team WPvivid Backup for MainWP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WPvivid Backup for MainWP: from n/a through 0.9.32.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35666 | WordPress Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesflat Themesflat Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themesflat Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35668 | WordPress Newsletter, SMTP, Email marketing and Subscribe forms by Brevo plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.77 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35668</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brevo Newsletter, SMTP, Email marketing and Subscribe forms by Sendinblue allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Newsletter, SMTP, Email marketing and Subscribe forms by Sendinblue: from n/a through 3.1.77.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35782 | WordPress Cowidgets – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35782</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codeless Cowidgets – Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cowidgets – Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35634 | Woocommerce – Recent Purchases plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 -  File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35634</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Wow-Company Woocommerce – Recent Purchases allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Woocommerce – Recent Purchases: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35700 | WordPress UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.8 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35700</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in DeluxeThemes Userpro allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Userpro: from n/a through 5.1.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35629 | WordPress Easy Digital Downloads – Recent Purchases plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Remote File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35629</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Wow-Company Easy Digital Downloads – Recent Purchases allows PHP Remote File Inclusion.This issue affects Easy Digital Downloads – Recent Purchases: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34552 | WordPress Stockholm theme &amp;lt;= 9.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34552</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Select-Themes Stockholm allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Stockholm: from n/a through 9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34554 | WordPress Stockholm Core plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34554</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Select-Themes Stockholm Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Stockholm Core: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34792 | WordPress Dextaz Ping plugin &amp;lt;= 0.65 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34792</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in dexta Dextaz Ping allows Command Injection.This issue affects Dextaz Ping: from n/a through 0.65.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33568 | WordPress Element Pack Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7.4 - Arbitrary File Read and Phar Deserialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33568</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal'), Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Pro allows Path Traversal, Object Injection.This issue affects Element Pack Pro: from n/a through 7.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33628 | WordPress XforWooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33628</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in XforWooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects XforWooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34384 | WordPress Sina Extension for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34384</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in SinaExtra Sina Extension for Elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Sina Extension for Elementor: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34551 | WordPress Stockholm theme &amp;lt;= 9.6 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34551</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Select-Themes Stockholm allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Stockholm: from n/a through 9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33541 | WordPress Better Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33541</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in BetterAddons Better Elementor Addons allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Better Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33557 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33557</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through 5.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33560 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.8 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33560</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in 8theme XStore allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25600 | WordPress Bricks Theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25600</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Codeer Limited Bricks Builder allows Code Injection.This issue affects Bricks Builder: from n/a through 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52176 | WordPress Malware Scanner plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - IP Restriction Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52176</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in miniorange Malware Scanner allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Malware Scanner: from n/a through 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36800 | A SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ID parameter in Download.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36800</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ID parameter in Download.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:03:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36801 | A SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lgid parameter in Download.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36801</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lgid parameter in Download.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51542 | WordPress Branda plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.14 - IP Restriction Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51542</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in WPMU DEV Branda allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Branda: from n/a through 3.4.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51543 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.5.0 -  IP Limit Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51543</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51544 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.5.0 - Form Submission Limit Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51544</link><description>Improper Control of Interaction Frequency vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51667 | WordPress Rate my Post – WP Rating System plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51667</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in FeedbackWP Rate my Post – WP Rating System allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Rate my Post – WP Rating System: from n/a through 3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52147 | WordPress All-In-One Security (AIOS) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Secret Login Page Location Disclosure on Multisites vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52147</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in All In One WP Security &amp; Firewall Team All In One WP Security &amp; Firewall allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects All In One WP Security &amp; Firewall: from n/a through 5.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51511 | WordPress Booster Elite for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt; 7.1.3 - Authenticated Production Creation/Modification Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51511</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Pluggabl LLC Booster Elite for WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Booster Elite for WooCommerce: from n/a before 7.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29170 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.x through 9.8.0.x contain a use of hard coded credentials vulnerability. An adjacent network unauthentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29170</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.x through 9.8.0.x contain a use of hard coded credentials vulnerability. An adjacent network unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure of network traffic and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37055 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.24.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37055</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.24.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded pmdarima model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37056 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.23.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37056</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.23.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded LightGBM scikit-learn model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37057 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 2.0.0rc0 or newer, enabling a maliciously upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37057</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 2.0.0rc0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded Tensorflow model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37058 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 2.5.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously upload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37058</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 2.5.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded Langchain AgentExecutor model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37059 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 0.5.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously upload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37059</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 0.5.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded PyTorch model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37060 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.27.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37060</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.27.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously crafted Recipe to execute arbitrary code on an end user’s system when run.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37061 | Remote Code Execution can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.11.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously crafted MLproject...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37061</link><description>Remote Code Execution can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.11.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously crafted MLproject to execute arbitrary code on an end user’s system when run.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37062 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 3.7.0 or newer of Ydata's ydata-profiling open-source library, enabling a malicously...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37062</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 3.7.0 or newer of Ydata's ydata-profiling open-source library, enabling a malicously crafted report to run arbitrary code on an end user's system when loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37063 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in versions 3.7.0 or newer of Ydata's ydata-profiling open-source library allows for payloads to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37063</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in versions 3.7.0 or newer of Ydata's ydata-profiling open-source library allows for payloads to be run when a maliocusly crafted report is viewed in the browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37064 | Deseriliazation of untrusted data can occur in versions 3.7.0 or newer of Ydata's ydata-profiling open-source library, enabling a maliciousl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37064</link><description>Deseriliazation of untrusted data can occur in versions 3.7.0 or newer of Ydata's ydata-profiling open-source library, enabling a maliciously crafted dataset to run arbitrary code on an end user's system when loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37065 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 0.6 or newer of the skops python library, enabling a maliciously crafted model to ru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37065</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 0.6 or newer of the skops python library, enabling a maliciously crafted model to run arbitrary code on an end user's system when loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4254 | Secrets Exfiltration in gradio-app/gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4254</link><description>The 'deploy-website.yml' workflow in the gradio-app/gradio repository, specifically in the 'main' branch, is vulnerable to secrets exfiltration due to improper authorization. The vulnerability arises from the workflow's explicit checkout and execution of code from a fork, which is unsafe as it allows the running of untrusted code in an environment with access to push to the base repository and access secrets. This flaw could lead to the exfiltration of sensitive secrets such as GITHUB_TOKEN, HF_TOKEN, VERCEL_ORG_ID, VERCEL_PROJECT_ID, COMMENT_TOKEN, AWSACCESSKEYID, AWSSECRETKEY, and VERCEL_TOKEN. The vulnerability is present in the workflow file located at https://github.com/gradio-app/gradio/blob/72f4ca88ab569aae47941b3fb0609e57f2e13a27/.github/workflows/deploy-website.yml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49852 | WordPress Responsive Slick Slider WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49852</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Vsourz Digital Responsive Slick Slider WordPress allows Code Injection.This issue affects Responsive Slick Slider WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37052 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.1.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously upload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37052</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.1.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded scikit-learn model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37053 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.1.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously upload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37053</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 1.1.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded scikit-learn model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37054 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 0.9.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously upload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37054</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the MLflow platform running version 0.9.0 or newer, enabling a maliciously uploaded PyFunc model to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49774 | WordPress WP Photo Album Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.02.005 - IP Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49774</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in J.N. Breetvelt a.K.A. OpaJaap WP Photo Album Plus allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Photo Album Plus: from n/a through 8.5.02.005.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49822 | WordPress Ultimate Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.10 - Secret Login Page Location Disclosure on Multisites vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49822</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in David Vongries Ultimate Dashboard allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Ultimate Dashboard: from n/a through 3.7.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49748 | WordPress WPS Hide Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Secret Login Page Location Disclosure on Multisites vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49748</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in WPServeur, NicolasKulka, wpformation WPS Hide Login allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WPS Hide Login: from n/a through 1.9.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48747 | WordPress Booster for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.2 - Authenticated Production Creation/Modification Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48747</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Pluggabl LLC Booster for WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Booster for WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48753 | WordPress Restricted Site Access plugin &amp;lt;= 7.4.1 - IP Restriction Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48753</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in 10up Restricted Site Access allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Restricted Site Access: from n/a through 7.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49741 | WordPress Coming soon and Maintenance mode plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - IP Filtering Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49741</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in wpdevart Coming soon and Maintenance mode allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Coming soon and Maintenance mode: from n/a through 3.7.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48335 | WordPress Hide login page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Secret Login Page Location Disclosure on Multisites vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48335</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Webcraftic Hide login page allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Hide login page: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48745 | WordPress Captcha Code plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48745</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in WebFactory Ltd Captcha Code allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Captcha Code: from n/a through 2.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48285 | WordPress Accept Stripe Payments plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.79 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48285</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Tips and Tricks HQ Stripe Payments allows Code Injection.This issue affects Stripe Payments: from n/a through 2.0.79.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48290 | WordPress Form Maker by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15.20 - Captcha Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48290</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in 10Web Form Builder Team Form Maker by 10Web allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Form Maker by 10Web: from n/a through 1.15.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48318 | WordPress Contact Form Email plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.41 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48318</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in CodePeople Contact Form Email allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Contact Form Email: from n/a through 1.3.41.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48271 | WordPress Maspik – Spam Blacklist plugin &amp;lt;= 0.10.3 - IP Filtering Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48271</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in yonifre Maspik – Spam blacklist allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Maspik – Spam blacklist: from n/a through 0.10.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48276 | WordPress WP Forms Puzzle Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48276</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Nitin Rathod WP Forms Puzzle Captcha allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects WP Forms Puzzle Captcha: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47769 | WordPress WP Maintenance plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.3 - IP Filtering Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47769</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in WP Maintenance allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Maintenance: from n/a through 6.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47818 | WordPress LWS Hide Login plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Secret Login Page Location Disclosure on Multisites vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47818</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in LWS LWS Hide Login allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects LWS Hide Login: from n/a through 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47837 | WordPress ARMember plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.10 - Membership Plan Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47837</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Repute Infosystems ARMember allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects ARMember: from n/a through 4.0.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47513 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47513</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz allows Code Injection.This issue affects ARI Stream Quiz: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47663 | WordPress Foyer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Menno Luitjes Foyer allows Code Injection.This issue affects Foyer: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47189 | WordPress Defender Security plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.0 - Masked Login Area View Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47189</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in WPMU DEV Defender Security allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Defender Security: from n/a through 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4637 | Slider Revolution &amp;lt;= 6.7.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Elementor wrapperid and zindex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4637</link><description>The Slider Revolution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied Elementor 'wrapperid' and 'zindex' display attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5463 | A vulnerability regarding buffer copy without checking the size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') has been found in the login component. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5463</link><description>A vulnerability regarding buffer copy without checking the size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') has been found in the login component. This allows remote attackers to conduct denial-of-service attacks via unspecified vectors. This attack only affects the login service which will automatically restart. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.1.1-0383 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46630 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Password Protected View Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46630</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in wpase Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE): from n/a through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45053 | WordPress WP Content Pilot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - HTML Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in pluginever WP Content Pilot – Autoblogging &amp; Affiliate Marketing Plugin allows Code Injection.This issue affects WP Content Pilot – Autoblogging &amp; Affiliate Marketing Plugin: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45635 | WordPress Responsive Tabs plugin &amp;lt; 4.0.6 - HTML Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45635</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in WP Darko Responsive Tabs allows Code Injection.This issue affects Responsive Tabs: from n/a before 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46310 | WordPress wpDiscuz plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.10 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46310</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in gVectors Team wpDiscuz allows Code Injection.This issue affects wpDiscuz: from n/a through 7.6.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45009 | WordPress Captcha for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.3 - Capcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45009</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Forge12 Interactive GmbH Captcha/Honeypot for Contact Form 7 allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Captcha/Honeypot for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.11.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5751 | CODESYS: Development system prone to DoS through exposure of resource to wrong sphere</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5751</link><description>A local attacker with low privileges can read and modify any users files and cause a DoS in the working directory of the affected products due to exposure of resource to wrong sphere.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5000 | CODESYS: Incorrect calculation of buffer size can cause DoS on CODESYS OPC UA products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5000</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use a malicious OPC UA client to send a crafted request to affected CODESYS products which can cause a DoS due to incorrect calculation of buffer size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4581 | Slider Revolution &amp;lt;= 6.7.11 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Add Layer class, id, and title Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4581</link><description>The Slider Revolution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Add Layer widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied 'class', 'id', and 'title' attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires an Administrator to give Slider Creation privileges to Author-level users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5422 | Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5422</link><description>An uncontrolled resource consumption of file descriptors in SEH Computertechnik utnserver Pro, SEH Computertechnik utnserver ProMAX, SEH Computertechnik INU-100 allows DoS via HTTP.This issue affects utnserver Pro, utnserver ProMAX, INU-100 version 20.1.22 and below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5421 | Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5421</link><description>Missing input validation and OS command integration of the input in the utnserver Pro, utnserver ProMAX, INU-100 web-interface allows authenticated command injection.This issue affects utnserver Pro, utnserver ProMAX, INU-100 version 20.1.22 and below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5420 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in SEH Computertechnik utnserver Pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5420</link><description>Missing input validation in the SEH Computertechnik utnserver Pro, SEH Computertechnik utnserver ProMAX, SEH Computertechnik INU-100 web-interface allows stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)..This issue affects utnserver Pro, utnserver ProMAX, INU-100 version 20.1.22 and below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44235 | WordPress WP Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44235</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Devnath verma WP Captcha allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects WP Captcha: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4253 | Command Injection in gradio-app/gradio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4253</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the gradio-app/gradio repository, specifically within the 'test-functional.yml' workflow. The vulnerability arises due to improper neutralization of special elements used in a command, allowing for unauthorized modification of the base repository or secrets exfiltration. The issue affects versions up to and including '@gradio/video@0.6.12'. The flaw is present in the workflow's handling of GitHub context information, where it echoes the full name of the head repository, the head branch, and the workflow reference without adequate sanitization. This could potentially lead to the exfiltration of sensitive secrets such as 'GITHUB_TOKEN', 'COMMENT_TOKEN', and 'CHROMATIC_PROJECT_TOKEN'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41134 | WordPress Antispam Bee plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.3 - Country IP Restriction Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41134</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in pluginkollektiv Antispam Bee allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Antispam Bee: from n/a through 2.11.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36104 | Apache OFBiz: Path traversal leading to a RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36104</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Apache OFBiz. This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.14.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.14, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38520 | WordPress Pinpoint Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.3.4 - Parameter Tampering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38520</link><description>External Control of Assumed-Immutable Web Parameter vulnerability in PINPOINT.WORLD Pinpoint Booking System allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Pinpoint Booking System: from n/a through 2.9.9.3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39161 | WordPress Discussion Board plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39161</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in WP Discussion Board Discussion Board allows Content Spoofing, Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Discussion Board: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40332 | WordPress WP-PostRatings plugin &amp;lt;= 1.91 - Rating limit Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40332</link><description>Improper Control of Interaction Frequency vulnerability in Lester ‘GaMerZ’ Chan WP-PostRatings allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects WP-PostRatings: from n/a through 1.91.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40557 | WordPress Tabs &amp;amp; Accordion plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.10 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in PickPlugins Tabs &amp; Accordion allows Code Injection.This issue affects Tabs &amp; Accordion: from n/a through 1.3.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40673 | WordPress Cartpauj Register Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.02 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40673</link><description>: Improper Control of Interaction Frequency vulnerability in cartpauj Cartpauj Register Captcha allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Cartpauj Register Captcha: from n/a through 1.0.02.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28494 | WordPress Contact Form Email plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.31 - Missing Authorization Leading To Feedback Submission Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28494</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodePeople Contact Form Email allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Contact Form Email: from n/a through 1.3.31.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33930 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.66 - Unrestricted Zip Extraction vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33930</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) allows Code Injection.This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.66.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34001 | WordPress Hide My WP Ghost – Security Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.25 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34001</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in WPPlugins – WordPress Security Plugins Hide My WP Ghost allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Hide My WP Ghost: from n/a through 5.0.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37865 | WordPress IP2Location Country Blocker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.29.1 - IP Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37865</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in IP2Location Download IP2Location Country Blocker allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Download IP2Location Country Blocker: from n/a through 2.29.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20873 | Improper input validation vulnerability in caminfo driver prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20873</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in caminfo driver prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20874 | Improper access control vulnerability in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20874</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20875 | Improper caller verification vulnerability in SemClipboard prior to SMR June-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access arbitrary files...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20875</link><description>Improper caller verification vulnerability in SemClipboard prior to SMR June-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20876 | Improper input validation in libsheifdecadapter.so prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to lead to memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20876</link><description>Improper input validation in libsheifdecadapter.so prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20877 | Heap out-of-bound write vulnerability in parsing grid image header in libsavscmn.so prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20877</link><description>Heap out-of-bound write vulnerability in parsing grid image header in libsavscmn.so prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20878 | Heap out-of-bound write vulnerability in parsing grid image in libsavscmn.so prior to SMR June-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20878</link><description>Heap out-of-bound write vulnerability in parsing grid image in libsavscmn.so prior to SMR June-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20879 | Improper input validation vulnerability in libsavscmn.so prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20879</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in libsavscmn.so prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20880 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to overwrite memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20880</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to overwrite memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20881 | Improper input validation vulnerability in chnactiv TA prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers lead to potential a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20881</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in chnactiv TA prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers lead to potential arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20882 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR June-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to arbitrary data access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20882</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR June-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to arbitrary data access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20883 | Incorrect use of privileged API vulnerability in registerBatteryStatsCallback in BatteryStatsService prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20883</link><description>Incorrect use of privileged API vulnerability in registerBatteryStatsCallback in BatteryStatsService prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to use privileged API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20884 | Incorrect use of privileged API vulnerability in getSemBatteryUsageStats in BatteryStatsService prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20884</link><description>Incorrect use of privileged API vulnerability in getSemBatteryUsageStats in BatteryStatsService prior to SMR Jun-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to use privileged API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20885 | Improper component protection vulnerability in Samsung Dialer prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to make a call without ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20885</link><description>Improper component protection vulnerability in Samsung Dialer prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to make a call without proper permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20886 | Arbitrary directory creation in Samsung Live Wallpaper PC prior to version 3.3.8.0 allows attacker to create arbitrary directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20886</link><description>Arbitrary directory creation in Samsung Live Wallpaper PC prior to version 3.3.8.0 allows attacker to create arbitrary directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20887 | Arbitrary directory creation in GalaxyBudsManager PC prior to version 2.1.240315.51 allows attacker to create arbitrary directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20887</link><description>Arbitrary directory creation in GalaxyBudsManager PC prior to version 2.1.240315.51 allows attacker to create arbitrary directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5485 | SureTriggers – Connect All Your Plugins, Apps, Tools &amp;amp; Automate Everything! &amp;lt;= 1.0.46 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Trigger Link Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5485</link><description>The SureTriggers – Connect All Your Plugins, Apps, Tools &amp; Automate Everything! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Trigger Link shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.47 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0757 | Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.3000000023 - Author+ Upload to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0757</link><description>The Insert or Embed Articulate Content into WordPress plugin through 4.3000000023 is not properly filtering which file extensions are allowed to be imported on the server, allowing the uploading of malicious code within zip files</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2470 | Simple Ajax Chat &amp;lt; 20240412 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2470</link><description>The Simple Ajax Chat  WordPress plugin before 20240412 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4057 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt; 3.2.37 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4057</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP  WordPress plugin before 3.2.37 does not validate and escape some of its block attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4180 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 6.4.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4180</link><description>The Events Calendar WordPress plugin before 6.4.0.1 does not properly sanitize user-submitted content when rendering some views via AJAX.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4749 | WP eMember &amp;lt; 10.3.9 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4749</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before 10.3.9 does not sanitize and escape the "fieldId" parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4750 | BuddyBoss Platform &amp;lt; 2.6.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference on Like Comment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4750</link><description>The buddyboss-platform WordPress plugin before 2.6.0 contains an IDOR vulnerability that allows a user to like a private post by manipulating the ID included in the request</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4856 | FS Product Inquiry &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4856</link><description>The FS Product Inquiry WordPress plugin through 1.1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or unauthenticated users</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4857 | FS Product Inquiry &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4857</link><description>The FS Product Inquiry WordPress plugin through 1.1.1 does not sanitise and escape some form submissions, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1717 | Admin Notices Manager &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Email Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1717</link><description>The Admin Notices Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_ajax_call() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve a list of registered user emails.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1718 | Claudio Sanches – Checkout Cielo for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity to Order Payment Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1718</link><description>The Claudio Sanches – Checkout Cielo for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to insufficient payment validation in the update_order_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the status of orders to paid bypassing payment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2019 | WP-DB-Table-Editor &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated(Contributor+) Database Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2019</link><description>The WP-DB-Table-Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, and loss of data due to lack of a default capability requirement on the 'dbte_render' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to modify database tables that the theme has been configured to use the plugin to edit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2382 | Authorize.net Payment Gateway For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 8.0 - Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity to Unauthenticated Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2382</link><description>The Authorize.net Payment Gateway For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 8.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying the authenticity of the request that updates a orders payment status. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update order payment statuses to paid bypassing any payment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3031 | Fluid Notification Bar &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3031</link><description>The Fluid Notification Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3230 | Download Attachments &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3230</link><description>The Download Attachments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'download-attachments' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3555 | Social Link Pages: link-in-bio landing pages for your social media profiles &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Page Creation and Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3555</link><description>The Social Link Pages: link-in-bio landing pages for your social media profiles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the import_link_pages() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary pages and malicious web scripts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4273 | Essential Real Estate &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4273</link><description>The Essential Real Estate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ere_property_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4274 | Essential Real Estate &amp;lt;= 4.4.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Attachment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4274</link><description>The Essential Real Estate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to insufficient validation on the remove_property_attachment_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary attachments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4462 | Nafeza Prayer Time &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4462</link><description>The Nafeza Prayer Time plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4697 | Cowidgets – Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via heading_tag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4697</link><description>The Cowidgets – Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘heading_tag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4997 | WPUpper Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 3.43 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4997</link><description>The WPUpper Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data when preparing sharing links for posts and pages in all versions up to, and including, 3.43. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain the contents of password protected posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3888 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3888</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: The vulnerable code in this plugin is specifically tied to the tagDiv Newspaper theme. If another theme is installed (e.g., NewsMag), this code may not be present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29976 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the command “show_allsessions” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29976</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the command “show_allsessions” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to obtain a logged-in administrator’s session information containing cookies on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4552 | Social Login Lite For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4552</link><description>The Social Login Lite For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.6.0. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the social login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4870 | Frontend Registration – Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 5.1 - Authenticated (Editor+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4870</link><description>The Frontend Registration – Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 5.1 due to insufficient restriction on the '_cf7frr_' post meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access and above, to modify the default user role in the registration form settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29972 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the CGI program "remote_help-cgi" in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29972</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the CGI program "remote_help-cgi" in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29973 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29973</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29974 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The remote code execution vulnerability in the CGI program “file_upload-cgi” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29974</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The remote code execution vulnerability in the CGI program “file_upload-cgi” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code by uploading a crafted configuration file to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29975 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the SUID executable binary in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29975</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the SUID executable binary in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to execute some system commands as the “root” user on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>