<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-0300 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform HTTP POST Request userattestation.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0300</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform up to 20240101. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /useratte/userattestation.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument web_img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249866 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0299 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249865 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0298 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0298</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249864. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0297 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi UploadFirmwareFile os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function UploadFirmwareFile of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249863. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0296 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi NTPSyncWithHost os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0296</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249862 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0295 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setWanCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0295</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. This affects the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249861 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 03:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0294 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setUssd os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0294</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected by this issue is the function setUssd of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ussd leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249860. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 03:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0293 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setUploadSetting os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0293</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249859. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47140 | IBM CICS Transaction Gateway improper access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47140</link><description>IBM CICS Transaction Gateway 9.3 could allow a user to transfer or view files due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  270259.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50948 | IBM Storage Fusion HCI information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50948</link><description>IBM Storage Fusion HCI 2.1.0 through 2.6.1 contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.  IBM X-Force ID:  275671.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0292 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0292</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7215 | Chanzhaoyu chatgpt-web cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7215</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Chanzhaoyu chatgpt-web 2.11.1. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input &lt;image src onerror=prompt(document.domain)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249779.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0291 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi UploadFirmwareFile command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0291</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadFirmwareFile of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249857 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0290 | Kashipara Food Management System stock_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0290</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file stock_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument item_type leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249851.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0289 | Kashipara Food Management System stock_entry_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0289</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file stock_entry_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument itemype leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249850 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0288 | Kashipara Food Management System rawstock_used_damaged_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0288</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file rawstock_used_damaged_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249849 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 23:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0287 | Kashipara Food Management System itemBillPdf.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0287</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file itemBillPdf.php. The manipulation of the argument printid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249848.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 23:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7214 | Totolink N350RT HTTP POST Request main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7214</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this issue is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v8 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249770 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 20:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47145 | IBM Db2 for Windows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47145</link><description>IBM Db2 for Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges to the SYSTEM user using the MSI repair functionality.  IBM X-Force ID:  270402.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 19:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7213 | Totolink N350RT HTTP POST Request main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7213</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=1 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v33 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249769 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 19:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0286 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System Contact Form index.php#contact_us cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0286</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php#contact_us of the component Contact Form. The manipulation of the argument Name/Email/Message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249843.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0284 | Kashipara Food Management System party_submit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0284</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file party_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument party_address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249839.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7212 | DeDeCMS Backend file_class.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7212</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in DeDeCMS up to 5.7.112. Affected is an unknown function of the file file_class.php of the component Backend. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249768. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0283 | Kashipara Food Management System party_details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0283</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_details.php. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249838 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0282 | Kashipara Food Management System addmaterialsubmit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0282</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file addmaterialsubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument tin leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249837 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0281 | Kashipara Food Management System loginCheck.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0281</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file loginCheck.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249836.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0280 | Kashipara Food Management System item_type_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0280</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file item_type_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument type_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249835.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0279 | Kashipara Food Management System item_list_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0279</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file item_list_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249834 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0278 | Kashipara Food Management System partylist_edit_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0278</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file partylist_edit_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249833 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 13:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0277 | Kashipara Food Management System party_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0277</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249832.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0276 | Kashipara Food Management System rawstock_used_damaged_smt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0276</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file rawstock_used_damaged_smt.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249831.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0275 | Kashipara Food Management System item_edit_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0275</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file item_edit_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249830 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0274 | Kashipara Food Management System billAjax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0274</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file billAjax.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249829 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 11:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0273 | Kashipara Food Management System addwaste_entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0273</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file addwaste_entry.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249828.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 11:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0272 | Kashipara Food Management System addmaterialsubmit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0272</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file addmaterialsubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument material_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249827.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 10:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7211 | Uniway Router Administrative Web Interface reliance on ip address for authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Uniway Router 2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Administrative Web Interface. The manipulation leads to reliance on ip address for authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249766 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 10:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7210 | OneNav API improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7210</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OneNav up to 0.9.33. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?c=api of the component API. The manipulation of the argument X-Token leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249765 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 09:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7209 | Uniway Router Device Reset device_reset.cgi denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7209</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Uniway Router up to 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boaform/device_reset.cgi of the component Device Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249758 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0271 | Kashipara Food Management System addmaterial_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0271</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file addmaterial_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249826 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0270 | Kashipara Food Management System item_list_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0270</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file item_list_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249825 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 08:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0268 | Kashipara Hospital Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file registration.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email/pass/gender/age/city leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249824.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 07:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7208 | Totolink X2000R_V2 boa formTmultiAP buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7208</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink X2000R_V2 2.0.0-B20230727.10434. This vulnerability affects the function formTmultiAP of the file /bin/boa. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. VDB-249742 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 07:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0267 | Kashipara Hospital Management System Parameter login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0267</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249823.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0266 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System User Registration cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0266</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component User Registration. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249822 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 05:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0265 | SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System GET Parameter index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0265</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249821 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 05:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0264 | SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System LoginRegistration.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0264</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /LoginRegistration.php. The manipulation of the argument formToken leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249820.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 04:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0263 | ACME Ultra Mini HTTPd HTTP GET Request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0263</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ACME Ultra Mini HTTPd 1.21. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249819.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0262 | Online Job Portal Create News Page News.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0262</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Online Job Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/News.php of the component Create News Page. The manipulation of the argument News with the input &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(0x00C57D)&lt;/scRipt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249818 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0261 | Sentex FTPDMIN RNFR Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0261</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sentex FTPDMIN 0.96 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component RNFR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249817 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0260 | SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal Password Change change_password_teacher.php session expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0260</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file change_password_teacher.php of the component Password Change. The manipulation leads to session expiration. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249816.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:02:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51441 | Apache Axis 1.x (EOL) may allow SSRF when untrusted input is passed to the service admin HTTP API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51441</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Axis allowed users with access to the admin service to perform possible SSRF
This issue affects Apache Axis: through 1.3.

As Axis 1 has been EOL we recommend you migrate to a different SOAP engine, such as Apache Axis 2/Java. Alternatively you could use a build of Axis with the patch from  https://github.com/apache/axis-axis1-java/commit/685c309febc64aa393b2d64a05f90e7eb9f73e06  applied. The Apache Axis project does not expect to create an Axis 1.x release 
fixing this problem, though contributors that would like to work towards
 this are welcome.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 12:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6798 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6798</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized settings update due to a missing capability check when updating settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access or above to change the plugin's settings including proxy settings, which are also exposed to authors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6801 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Store...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6801</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50121 | Autel EVO NANO drone flight control firmware version 1.6.5 is vulnerable to denial of service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50121</link><description>Autel EVO NANO drone flight control firmware version 1.6.5 is vulnerable to denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46953 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS v.5.9.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the d parameter in the Documents modul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46953</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS v.5.9.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the d parameter in the Documents module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39853 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Dzzoffice version 2.01, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doobj and doevent par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39853</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Dzzoffice version 2.01, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doobj and doevent parameters in the Network Disk backend module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50609 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AVA teaching video application service platform version 3.1, allows remote attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50609</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AVA teaching video application service platform version 3.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to ajax.aspx.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 03:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50612 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in fit2cloud Cloud Explorer Lite version 1.4.1, allow local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50612</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in fit2cloud Cloud Explorer Lite version 1.4.1, allow local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the cloud accounts parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 02:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>