<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-13873 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Photo Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13873</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.8 via the deleteUserPhoto() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to remove profile photos from users accounts. Please note that this does not officially delete the file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13899 | Mambo Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13899</link><description>The Mambo Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input via the $data parameter in the fImportMenu function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1509 | Show Me The Cookies &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1509</link><description>The The Show Me The Cookies plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1510 | Custom Post Type Date Archives &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1510</link><description>The The Custom Post Type Date Archives plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22341 | IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22341</link><description>IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.0 through 4.0.9, 4.5.0 through 4.5.3, 4.6.0 through 4.6.6, 4.7.0 through 4.7.4, and 4.8.0 through 4.8.7 could allow unauthorized data access from a remote data source object due to improper privilege management.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:05:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45674 | IBM Security Verify Bridge information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45674</link><description>IBM Security Verify Bridge Directory Sync 1.0.1 through 1.0.12, IBM Security Verify Gateway for Windows Login 1.0.1 through 1.0.10, and IBM Security Verify Gateway for Radius 1.0.1 through 1.0.11 

stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26622 | sqrt doesn&amp;#x27;t define rounding behavior in Vyper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26622</link><description>vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. Vyper `sqrt()` builtin uses the babylonian method to calculate square roots of decimals. Unfortunately, improper handling of the oscillating final states may lead to sqrt incorrectly returning rounded up results. This issue is being addressed and a fix is expected in version 0.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as the patched release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27104 | double eval in For List Iter in Vyper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27104</link><description>vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. Multiple evaluation of a single expression is possible in the iterator target of a for loop. While the iterator expression cannot produce multiple writes, it can consume side effects produced in the loop body (e.g. read a storage variable updated in the loop body) and thus lead to unexpected program behavior. Specifically, reads in iterators which contain an ifexp (e.g. `for s: uint256 in ([read(), read()] if True else [])`) may interleave reads with writes in the loop body. Vyper for loops allow two kinds of iterator targets, namely the `range()` builtin and an iterable type, like SArray and DArray. During codegen, iterable lists are required to not produce any side-effects (in the following code, `range_scope` forces `iter_list` to be parsed in a constant context, which is checked against `is_constant`). However, this does not prevent the iterator from consuming side effects provided by the body of the loop. For SArrays on the other hand, `iter_list` is instantiated in the body of a `repeat` ir, so it can be evaluated several times. This issue is being addressed and is expected to be available in version 0.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as the patched release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27105 | AugAssign evaluation order causing OOB write within the object in Vyper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27105</link><description>vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. Vyper handles AugAssign statements by first caching the target location to avoid double evaluation. However, in the case when target is an access to a DynArray and the rhs modifies the array, the cached target will evaluate first, and the bounds check will not be re-evaluated during the write portion of the statement. This issue has been addressed in version 0.4.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27106 | Code injection in binance-trading-bot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27106</link><description>binance-trading-bot is an automated Binance trading bot with trailing buy/sell strategy. Authenticated users of binance-trading-bot can achieve Remote Code Execution on the host system due to a command injection vulnerability in the `/restore` endpoint. The restore endpoint of binance-trading-bot is vulnerable to command injection via the `/restore` endpoint. The name of the uploaded file is passed to shell.exec without sanitization other than path normalization, resulting in Remote Code Execution. This may allow any authorized user to execute code in the context of the host machine. This issue has been addressed in version 0.0.100 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-8900 | A vulnerability in the SecureROM of some Apple devices can be exploited by an unauthenticated local attacker to execute arbitrary code upon ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8900</link><description>A vulnerability in the SecureROM of some Apple devices can be exploited by an unauthenticated local attacker to execute arbitrary code upon booting those devices. This vulnerability allows arbitrary code to be executed on the device. Exploiting the vulnerability requires physical access to the device: the device must be plugged in to a computer upon booting, and it must be put into Device Firmware Update (DFU) mode. The exploit is not persistent; rebooting the device overrides any changes to the device's software that were made during an exploited session on the device. Additionally, unless an attacker has access to the device's unlock PIN or fingerprint, an attacker cannot gain access to information protected by Apple's Secure Enclave or Touch ID features.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27108 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability due to improper use of string.replace in dom-expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27108</link><description>dom-expressions is a Fine-Grained Runtime for Performant DOM Rendering. In affected versions the use of javascript's `.replace()` opens up to potential Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities with the special replacement patterns beginning with `$`. Particularly, when the attributes of `Meta` tag from solid-meta are user-defined, attackers can utilise the special replacement patterns, either `$'` or `$\`` to achieve XSS. The solid-meta package has this issue since it uses `useAffect` and context providers, which injects the used assets in the html header. "dom-expressions" uses `.replace()` to insert the assets, which is vulnerable to the special replacement patterns listed above.  This effectively means that if the attributes of an asset tag contained user-controlled data, it would be vulnerable to XSS. For instance, there might be meta tags for the open graph protocol in a user profile page, but if attackers set the user query to some payload abusing `.replace()`, then they could execute arbitrary javascript in the victim's web browser. Moreover, it could be stored and cause more problems. This issue has been addressed in version 0.39.5 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27109 | Lack of Escaping of HTML in JSX Fragments allows for Cross-site Scripting in solid-js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27109</link><description>solid-js is a declarative, efficient, and flexible JavaScript library for building user interfaces. In affected versions Inserts/JSX expressions inside illegal inlined JSX fragments lacked escaping, allowing user input to be rendered as HTML when put directly inside JSX fragments. This issue has been addressed in version 1.9.4 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25282 | Potential Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in ragflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25282</link><description>RAGFlow is an open-source RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) engine based on deep document understanding. An authenticated user can exploit the Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability that may lead to unauthorized cross-tenant access (list tenant user accounts, add user account into other tenant). Unauthorized cross-tenant access: list user from other tenant (e.g., via GET //user/list), add user account to other tenant (POST //user). This issue has not yet been patched. Users are advised to reach out to the project maintainers to coordinate a fix.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1555 | hzmanyun Education and Training System saveImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1555</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in hzmanyun Education and Training System 3.1.1. This vulnerability affects the function saveImage. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25604 | Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the vif_disable function in mtkwifi.lua.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25604</link><description>Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the vif_disable function in mtkwifi.lua.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25605 | Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the apcli_wps_gen_pincode function in mtkwifi.lua.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25605</link><description>Totolink X5000R V9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 is vulnerable to command injection via the apcli_wps_gen_pincode function in mtkwifi.lua.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-19248 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PbootCMS 1.4.1 in parsing if statements in templates, resulting in a malicious user's ability to contaminate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-19248</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PbootCMS 1.4.1 in parsing if statements in templates, resulting in a malicious user's ability to contaminate template content by searching for page contamination URLs, thus triggering vulnerabilities when the program uses eval statements to parse templates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25767 | A vertical privilege escalation vulnerability in the component /controller/UserController.java of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to arbitrari...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25767</link><description>A vertical privilege escalation vulnerability in the component /controller/UserController.java of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to arbitrarily delete users via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25768 | MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the component \servlet\DispatcherServlet.jav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25768</link><description>MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the component \servlet\DispatcherServlet.java. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25769 | Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /controller/UserController.java.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25769</link><description>Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /controller/UserController.java.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25770 | Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /agency/AgencyUserController.java.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25770</link><description>Wangmarket v4.10 to v5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /agency/AgencyUserController.java.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25772 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /back/UserController.java of Jspxcms v9.0 to v9.5 allows attackers to arbitrarily add A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25772</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /back/UserController.java of Jspxcms v9.0 to v9.5 allows attackers to arbitrarily add Administrator accounts via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55156 | An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the deserializeArgs() method of Java SDK for CloudEvents v4.0.1 allows attackers to access sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55156</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the deserializeArgs() method of Java SDK for CloudEvents v4.0.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via supplying a crafted XML-formatted event message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55159 | GFast between v2 to v3.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the SortName parameter at /system/loginLog/list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55159</link><description>GFast between v2 to v3.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the SortName parameter at /system/loginLog/list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25765 | MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file write vulnerability via the component /file/save.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25765</link><description>MRCMS v3.1.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file write vulnerability via the component /file/save.do.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25766 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /file/savefile.do of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25766</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /file/savefile.do of MRCMS v3.1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted .jsp file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25877 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin.php. The atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25877</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25878 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /del.php. The attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25878</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /del.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57176 | An issue in the shiroFilter function of White-Jotter project v0.2.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal and access sensitive e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57176</link><description>An issue in the shiroFilter function of White-Jotter project v0.2.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal and access sensitive endpoints via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25876 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /delete.php. The att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25876</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /delete.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25875 | A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /message.php. The at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25875</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ITSourcecode Simple ChatBox up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /message.php. The attack can use SQL injection to obtain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1548 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1548</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/archives/edit. The manipulation of the argument editorValue/answer/content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25505 | Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the sub_452A4 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25505</link><description>Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the sub_452A4 function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25507 | There is a RCE vulnerability in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi. In the formexeCommand function, the parameter cmdinput will cause remote comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25507</link><description>There is a RCE vulnerability in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16_multi. In the formexeCommand function, the parameter cmdinput will cause remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25510 | Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the get_parentControl_list_Info function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25510</link><description>Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the get_parentControl_list_Info function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1403 | Qiskit SDK denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1403</link><description>Qiskit SDK 0.45.0 through 1.2.4 could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service using a maliciously crafted QPY file containing a malformed symengine serialization stream which can cause a segfault within the symengine library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45673 | IBM Security Verify Bridge information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45673</link><description>IBM Security Verify Bridge Directory Sync 1.0.1 through 1.0.12, IBM Security Verify Gateway for Windows Login 1.0.1 through 1.0.10, and IBM Security Verify Gateway for Radius 1.0.1 through 1.0.11 stores user credentials in configuration files which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1546 | BDCOM Behavior Management and Auditing System operate.mds log_operate_clear os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1546</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in BDCOM Behavior Management and Auditing System up to 20250210 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function log_operate_clear of the file /webui/modules/log/operate.mds. The manipulation of the argument start_code leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26014 | A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the path parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26014</link><description>A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26013 | An issue in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the read.py component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26013</link><description>An issue in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the read.py component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1543 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS ueditor-1.4.3.3 path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1543</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /resource/js/ueditor-1.4.3.3. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1544 | dingfanzu CMS loadShopInfo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1544</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in dingfanzu CMS up to 20250210. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ajax/loadShopInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument shopId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1538 | D-Link DAP-1320 api set_ws_action heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1538</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DAP-1320 1.00. Affected by this vulnerability is the function set_ws_action of the file /dws/api/. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1539 | D-Link DAP-1320 storagein.pd-XXXXXX replace_special_char stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1539</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAP-1320 1.00. Affected by this issue is the function replace_special_char of the file /storagein.pd-XXXXXX. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1536 | Raisecom Multi-Service Intelligent Gateway Request Parameter vpn_template_style.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1536</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom Multi-Service Intelligent Gateway up to 20250208. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /vpn/vpn_template_style.php of the component Request Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1537 | Harpia DiagSystem atualatendimento_jpeg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1537</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Harpia DiagSystem 12. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /diagsystem/PACS/atualatendimento_jpeg.php. The manipulation of the argument codexame leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0838 | Heap Buffer overflow in Abseil</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0838</link><description>There exists a heap buffer overflow vulnerable in Abseil-cpp. The sized constructors, reserve(), and rehash() methods of absl::{flat,node}hash{set,map} did not impose an upper bound on their size argument. As a result, it was possible for a caller to pass a very large size that would cause an integer overflow when computing the size of the container's backing store, and a subsequent out-of-bounds memory write. Subsequent accesses to the container might also access out-of-bounds memory. We recommend upgrading past commit 5a0e2cb5e3958dd90bb8569a2766622cb74d90c1</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10222 | SVG Support &amp;lt;= 2.5.10 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10222</link><description>The SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. By default, this can only be exploited by administrators, but the ability to upload SVG files can be extended to authors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-6158 | Opera Mini for Android before version 52.2 is vulnerable to an address bar spoofing attack. The vulnerability allows a malicious page to tri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6158</link><description>Opera Mini for Android before version 52.2 is vulnerable to an address bar spoofing attack. The vulnerability allows a malicious page to trick the browser into showing an address of a different page. This may allow the malicious page to impersonate another page and trick a user into providing sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26794 | Exim 4.98 before 4.98.1, when SQLite hints and ETRN serialization are used, allows remote SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26794</link><description>Exim 4.98 before 4.98.1, when SQLite hints and ETRN serialization are used, allows remote SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1535 | Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System admin.ticket.close.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1535</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System 8.142.100.161. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /wuser/admin.ticket.close.php. The manipulation of the argument ticket_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9150 | Code Injection in Wyn Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9150</link><description>Report generation functionality in Wyn Enterprise allows for code inclusion, but not sufficiently limits what code might be included. An attacker is able use a low privileges account in order to abuse this functionality and execute malicious code, load DLL libraries and executing OS commands on a host system with applications high privileges.
This issue has been fixed in version 8.0.00204.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13455 | igumbi Online Booking &amp;lt;= 1.40 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13455</link><description>The igumbi Online Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'igumbi_calendar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13713 | WPExperts Square For GiveWP &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13713</link><description>The WPExperts Square For GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13846 | Indeed Ultimate Learning Pro &amp;lt;= 3.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via post_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13846</link><description>The Indeed Ultimate Learning Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘post_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13900 | Head, Footer and Post Injections &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Code Injection in Multisite Environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13900</link><description>The Head, Footer and Post Injections plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject PHP Code in multisite environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1402 | Event Tickets and Registration &amp;lt;= 5.19.1.1 - Missing Authorization to Ticket Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1402</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_ticket_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.19.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary Attendee tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1489 | WP-Appbox &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via appbox Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1489</link><description>The WP-Appbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's appbox shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1470 | Eclipse OMR: Null pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1470</link><description>In Eclipse OMR, from the initial contribution to version 0.4.0, some OMR internal port library and utilities consumers of z/OS atoe functions do not check their return values for NULL memory pointers or for memory allocation failures.  This can lead to NULL pointer dereference crashes.  Beginning in version 0.5.0, internal OMR consumers of atoe functions handle NULL return values and memory allocation failures correctly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1471 | Eclipse OMR: Buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1471</link><description>In Eclipse OMR versions 0.2.0 to 0.4.0, some of the z/OS atoe print functions use a constant length buffer for string conversion. If the input format string and arguments are larger than the buffer size then buffer overflow occurs.  Beginning in version 0.5.0, the conversion buffers are sized correctly and checked appropriately to prevent buffer overflows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12276 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12276</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to second-order SQL Injection via filenames in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with  access to upload files and manage filenames through a third-party plugin like a File Manager, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. The risk of this vulnerability is very minimal as it requires a user to be able to manipulate filenames in order to successfully exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12452 | Ziggeo &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12452</link><description>The Ziggeo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ziggeo_event' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13353 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13353</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 via several widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13461 | Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13461</link><description>The Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'autoship-create-scheduled-order-action' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13648 | Maps for WP &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13648</link><description>The Maps for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'MapOnePoint' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0727 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0727</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length in one packet smaller than the data 
request size of the other packet. A possible workaround is to disable 
HTTP PUT support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0728 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0728</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length smaller than the data request size. A
 possible workaround is to disable HTTP PUT support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1410 | Events Calendar Made Simple – Pie Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via piecal Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1410</link><description>The Events Calendar Made Simple – Pie Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's piecal shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0726 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0726</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service by specially 
crafted packets. The core issue is missing closing of a file in case of 
an error condition, resulting in the 404 error for each further file 
request. Users can work-around the issue by disabling the PUT request 
support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13314 | Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel &amp;lt; 2.7.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13314</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel  WordPress plugin before 2.7.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13585 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt; 4.12.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13585</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite  WordPress plugin before 4.12.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11260 | Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! &amp;lt;= 6.6.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via Event Status Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11260</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the active_status parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 05:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13235 | Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13235</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'language' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13379 | C9 Admin Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13379</link><description>The C9 Admin Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13388 | TCBD Tooltip &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13388</link><description>The TCBD Tooltip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcbdtooltip_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13537 | C9 Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13537</link><description>The C9 Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.7. This is due the plugin containing a publicly accessible composer-setup.php file with error display enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13672 | Mini Course Generator | Embed mini-courses and interactive content &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13672</link><description>The Mini Course Generator | Embed mini-courses and interactive content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mcg' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13751 | 3D Photo Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13751</link><description>The 3D Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'des[]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13818 | Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.9 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Log Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13818</link><description>The Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3.9 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information about users contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13883 | WPUpper Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 3.51 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom CSS Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13883</link><description>The WPUpper Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.51. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_custom_css_request' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject custom CSS to modify a site via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1406 | Newpost Catch &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via npc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1406</link><description>The Newpost Catch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's npc shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1407 | AMO Team Showcase &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via amoteam_skills Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1407</link><description>The AMO Team Showcase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's amoteam_skills shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38657 | External control of a file name in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.4 and Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.3 allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38657</link><description>External control of a file name in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.4 and Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1001 | Medixant RadiAnt DICOM Viewer Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1001</link><description>Medixant RadiAnt DICOM Viewer is vulnerable due to failure of the update mechanism to verify the update server's certificate which could allow an attacker to alter network traffic and carry out a machine-in-the-middle attack (MITM). An attacker could modify the server's response and deliver a malicious update to the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27100 | An authenticated user can crash lakeFS by exhausting server memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27100</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms your object storage into a Git-like repository. In affected versions an authenticated user can crash lakeFS by exhausting server memory.  This is an authenticated denial-of-service issue. This problem has been patched in version 1.50.0. Users on versions 1.49.1 and below are affected. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should either set the environment variable `LAKEFS_BLOCKSTORE_S3_DISABLE_PRE_SIGNED_MULTIPART` to `true` or configure the `disable_pre_signed_multipart` key to true in their config yaml.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54756 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the ZScript function of ZDoom Team GZDoom v4.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54756</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the ZScript function of ZDoom Team GZDoom v4.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted PK3 file containing a malicious ZScript source file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27088 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in template implementation in oxyno-zeta/s3-proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27088</link><description>oxyno-zeta/s3-proxy is an aws s3 proxy written in go. In affected versions a Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability enables attackers to create malicious URLs that, when visited, inject scripts into the web application. This can lead to session hijacking or phishing attacks on a trusted domain, posing a moderate risk to all users. It's possible to inject html elements, including scripts through the folder-list template. The affected template allows users to interact with the URL path provided by the `Request.URL.Path` variable, which is then rendered directly into the HTML without proper sanitization or escaping. This can be abused by attackers who craft a malicious URL containing injected HTML or JavaScript. When users visit such a URL, the malicious script will be executed in the user's context. This issue has been addressed in version 4.18.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25663 | A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06. Affected is the function SUB_0046AC38 of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25663</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06. Affected is the function SUB_0046AC38 of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25664 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_49E098 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25664</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_49E098 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25667 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25667</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25668 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_47D878 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25668</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_47D878 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25678 | Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the funcpara1 parameter in the formSetCfm function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25678</link><description>Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the funcpara1 parameter in the formSetCfm function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25679 | Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the index parameter in the formWifiMacFilterSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25679</link><description>Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the index parameter in the formWifiMacFilterSet function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22973 | An issue in QiboSoft QiboCMS X1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the http_curl() function in the '/application...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22973</link><description>An issue in QiboSoft QiboCMS X1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the http_curl() function in the '/application/common. php' file that directly retrieves the URL request response content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25662 | Tenda O4 V3.0 V1.0.0.10(2936) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function SafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterList via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25662</link><description>Tenda O4 V3.0 V1.0.0.10(2936) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function SafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterList via the argument remark/type/time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25674 | Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in form_fast_setting_wifi_set via the parameter ssid.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25674</link><description>Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in form_fast_setting_wifi_set via the parameter ssid.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25675 | Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 has a command injection vulnerablility located in the formexeCommand function. The str variable receives the cm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25675</link><description>Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 has a command injection vulnerablility located in the formexeCommand function. The str variable receives the cmdinput parameter from a POST request and is later assigned to the cmd_buf variable, which is directly used in the doSystemCmd function, causing an arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25676 | Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the list parameter in the formwrlSSIDset function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25676</link><description>Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the list parameter in the formwrlSSIDset function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25957 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in Xunruicms v.4.6.3 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25957</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in Xunruicms v.4.6.3 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25958 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25958</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25960 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the menu interface of the member ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25960</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the menu interface of the member center of the background administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27097 | Cache variables with the operations when transforms exist on the root level even if variables change in the further requests with the same operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27097</link><description>GraphQL Mesh is a GraphQL Federation framework and gateway for both GraphQL Federation and non-GraphQL Federation subgraphs, non-GraphQL services, such as REST and gRPC, and also databases such as MongoDB, MySQL, and PostgreSQL. When a user transforms on the root level or single source with transforms, and the client sends the same query with different variables, the initial variables are used in all following requests until the cache evicts DocumentNode. If a token is sent via variables, the following requests will act like the same token is sent even if the following requests have different tokens. This can cause a short memory leak but it won't grow per each request but per different operation until the cache evicts DocumentNode by LRU mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27098 | Unwanted access to the entire file system vulnerability due to a missing check in `staticFiles` HTTP handler in graphql-mesh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27098</link><description>GraphQL Mesh is a GraphQL Federation framework and gateway for both GraphQL Federation and non-GraphQL Federation subgraphs, non-GraphQL services, such as REST and gRPC, and also databases such as MongoDB, MySQL, and PostgreSQL. Missing check vulnerability in the static file handler allows any client to access the files in the server's file system. When `staticFiles` is set in the `serve` settings in the configuration file, the following handler doesn't check if `absolutePath` is still under the directory provided as `staticFiles`. Users have two options to fix vulnerability; 1. Update `@graphql-mesh/cli` to a version higher than `0.82.21`, and if you use `@graphql-mesh/http`, update it to a version higher than `0.3.18` 2. Remove `staticFiles` option from the configuration, and use other solutions to serve static files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24893 | Remote code execution as guest via SolrSearchMacros request in xwiki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24893</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any guest can perform arbitrary remote code execution through a request to `SolrSearch`. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. To reproduce on an instance, without being logged in, go to `/xwiki/bin/get/Main/SolrSearch?media=rss&amp;amp;text=%7D%7D%7D%7B%7Basync%20async%3Dfalse%7D%7D%7B%7Bgroovy%7D%7Dprintln%28"Hello%20from"%20%2B%20"%20search%20text%3A"%20%2B%20%2823%20%2B%2019%29%29%7B%7B%2Fgroovy%7D%7D%7B%7B%2Fasync%7D%7D%20`. If there is an output, and the title of the RSS feed contains `Hello from search text:42`, then the instance is vulnerable. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.10.11, 16.4.1 and 16.5.0RC1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may edit `Main.SolrSearchMacros` in `SolrSearchMacros.xml` on line 955 to match the `rawResponse` macro in `macros.vm#L2824` with a content type of `application/xml`, instead of simply outputting the content of the feed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25299 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) in the real-time collaboration package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25299</link><description>CKEditor 5 is a modern JavaScript rich-text editor with an MVC architecture. During a recent internal audit, a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the CKEditor 5 real-time collaboration package. This vulnerability affects user markers, which represent users' positions within the document. It can lead to unauthorized JavaScript code execution, which might happen with a very specific editor and token endpoint configuration. This vulnerability affects only installations with Real-time collaborative editing enabled. The problem has been recognized and patched. The fix is available in version 44.2.1 (and above). Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0352 | Rapid Response Monitoring My Security Account App Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0352</link><description>Rapid Response Monitoring My Security Account App utilizes an API that could be exploited by an attacker to modify request data, potentially causing the API to return information about other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1265 | Elseta Vinci Protocol Analyzer OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1265</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Vinci Protocol Analyzer that could allow an attacker to escalate privileges and perform code execution on affected system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26618 | SSH SFTP packet size not verified properly in Erlang OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26618</link><description>Erlang is a programming language and runtime system for building massively scalable soft real-time systems with requirements on high availability. OTP is a set of Erlang libraries, which consists of the Erlang runtime system, a number of ready-to-use components mainly written in Erlang. Packet size is not verified properly for SFTP packets. As a result when multiple SSH packets (conforming to max SSH packet size) are received by ssh, they might be combined into an SFTP packet which will exceed the max allowed packet size and potentially cause large amount of memory to be allocated. Note that situation described above can only happen for successfully authenticated users after completing the SSH handshake. This issue has been patched in OTP versions 27.2.4, 26.2.5.9, and 25.3.2.18. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27096 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;html/personalizacao_upload.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_campo&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27096</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, personalizacao_upload.php endpoint. This vulnerability allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.14 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51338 | PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters of&amp;n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51338</link><description>PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters of&amp;nbsp;index.php&amp;nbsp;page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51339 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51339</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7141 | CSRF in Gliffy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7141</link><description>Versions of Gliffy Online prior to versions 4.14.0-7 contains a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) flaw.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51336 | PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51336</link><description>PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51337 | PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in "lid" parameter in index.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51337</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in "lid" parameter in index.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54958 | Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is susceptible to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Tools page. This flaw allows an attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54958</link><description>Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is susceptible to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Tools page. This flaw allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the Tools interface, which are then stored and executed in the context of other users accessing the page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54960 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute SQL injection via a crafted payload in the History...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54960</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute SQL injection via a crafted payload in the History Tab component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54961 | Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 has an Information Disclosure vulnerability, which allows unauthenticated users to access multiple pages displaying the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54961</link><description>Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 has an Information Disclosure vulnerability, which allows unauthenticated users to access multiple pages displaying the usernames and email addresses of all current users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54959 | Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack through the Favorites component, enabling POST-based Cross-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54959</link><description>Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack through the Favorites component, enabling POST-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27091 | OpenH264 Decoding Functions Heap Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27091</link><description>OpenH264 is a free license codec library which supports H.264 encoding and decoding. A vulnerability in the decoding functions of OpenH264 codec library could allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trigger a heap overflow. This vulnerability is due to a race condition between a Sequence Parameter Set (SPS) memory allocation and a subsequent non Instantaneous Decoder Refresh (non-IDR) Network Abstraction Layer (NAL) unit memory usage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious bitstream and tricking a victim user into processing an arbitrary video containing the malicious bistream. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected crash in the victim's user decoding client and, possibly, perform arbitrary commands on the victim's host by abusing the heap overflow. This vulnerability affects OpenH264 2.5.0 and earlier releases. Both Scalable Video Coding (SVC) mode and Advanced Video Coding (AVC) mode are affected by this vulnerability. OpenH264 software releases 2.6.0 and later contained the fix for this vulnerability. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

### For more information

If you have any questions or comments about this advisory:
* [Open an issue in cisco/openh264](https://github.com/cisco/openh264/issues)
* Email Cisco Open Source Security ([oss-security@cisco.com](mailto:oss-security@cisco.com)) and Cisco PSIRT ([psirt@cisco.com](mailto:psirt@cisco.com))

### Credits:

* **Research:** Octavian Guzu and Andrew Calvano of Meta
* **Fix ideation:** Philipp Hancke and Shyam Sadhwani of Meta
* **Fix implementation:** Benzheng Zhang (@BenzhengZhang)
* **Release engineering:** Benzheng Zhang (@BenzhengZhang)</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55457 | MasterSAM Star Gate 11 is vulnerable to directory traversal via /adama/adama/downloadService. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55457</link><description>MasterSAM Star Gate 11 is vulnerable to directory traversal via /adama/adama/downloadService. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the file parameter to access arbitrary files on the server, potentially exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46933 | An issue was discovered in Atos Eviden BullSequana XH2140 BMC before C4EM-125: OMF_C4E 101.05.0014. Some BullSequana XH products were shippe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46933</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Eviden BullSequana XH2140 BMC before C4EM-125: OMF_C4E 101.05.0014. Some BullSequana XH products were shipped without proper hardware programming, leading to a potential denial-of-service with privileged access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25968 | DDSN Interactive cm3 Acora CMS version 10.1.1 contains an improper access control vulnerability. An editor-privileged user can access sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25968</link><description>DDSN Interactive cm3 Acora CMS version 10.1.1 contains an improper access control vulnerability. An editor-privileged user can access sensitive information, such as system administrator credentials, by force browsing the endpoint and exploiting the 'file' parameter. By referencing specific files (e.g., cm3.xml), attackers can bypass access controls, leading to account takeover and potential privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51333 | PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51333</link><description>PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51334 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51334</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51335 | PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51335</link><description>PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25973 | A stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the "related recommendations" feature in Ppress v.0.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25973</link><description>A stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the "related recommendations" feature in Ppress v.0.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the article.title, article.category, and article.tags parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26308 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_FILTERLIST function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26308</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_FILTERLIST function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26311 | Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the clip actions parsing functions (parseSWF_CLIPACTIONS and parseSWF_CLIPACTIONRECORD) in uti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26311</link><description>Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the clip actions parsing functions (parseSWF_CLIPACTIONS and parseSWF_CLIPACTIONRECORD) in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allow attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26306 | A memory leak has been identified in the readSizedString function in util/read.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26306</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the readSizedString function in util/read.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26307 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_IMPORTASSETS2 function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26307</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_IMPORTASSETS2 function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26310 | Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the ABC file parsing functions (parseABC_CONSTANT_POOL and `parseABC_FILE) in util/parser.c of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26310</link><description>Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the ABC file parsing functions (parseABC_CONSTANT_POOL and `parseABC_FILE) in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allow attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted ABC file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26304 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_EXPORTASSETS function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26304</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_EXPORTASSETS function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26305 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_SOUNDINFO function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26305</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_SOUNDINFO function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26309 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_DEFINESCENEANDFRAMEDATA function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26309</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_DEFINESCENEANDFRAMEDATA function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57716 | An issue in trenoncourt AutoQueryable v.1.7.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Unselectable function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57716</link><description>An issue in trenoncourt AutoQueryable v.1.7.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Unselectable function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51331 | PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51331</link><description>PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51332 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51332</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0161 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0161</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.0.9 and 11.0.0.0 could allow a local user to execute arbitrary code due to improper restrictions on code generation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51330 | PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Now Showing menu "date" parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51330</link><description>PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Now Showing menu "date" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51327 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51327</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51326 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51326</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51323 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51323</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51324 | PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51324</link><description>PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51325 | PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51325</link><description>PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51317 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51317</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51318 | PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51318</link><description>PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51319 | PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51319</link><description>PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51320 | PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51320</link><description>PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51321 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51321</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51316 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 allows attackers to send an excessive amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51316</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51312 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Reservations menu, Schedule section date ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51312</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Reservations menu, Schedule section date parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51313 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51313</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51314 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51314</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51315 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "seat_name, plugin_sms_api_key,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51315</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "seat_name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57401 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Uniclare Student portal v.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Forgot Pass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57401</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Uniclare Student portal v.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Forgot Password function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51310 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51310</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51311 | PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51311</link><description>PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51306 | PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, title" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51306</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51308 | PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51308</link><description>PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51309 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51309</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20059 | PingAM Java Policy Agent path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20059</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Ping Identity PingAM Java Policy Agent allows Parameter Injection.This issue affects PingAM Java Policy Agent: through 5.10.3, through 2023.11.1, through 2024.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1039 | Lenix Elementor Leads addon &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URL Form Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1039</link><description>The Lenix Elementor Leads addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a URL form field in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49337 | IBM OpenPages HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49337</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages 





is vulnerable to HTML injection, caused by improper validation of user-supplied input of text fields used to construct workflow email notifications. A remote authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability using HTML tags in a text field of an object to inject malicious script into an email which would be executed in a victim's mail client within the security context of the OpenPages mail message. An attacker could use this for phishing or identity theft attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49344 | IBM OpenPages session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49344</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages 



with Watson Assistant chat feature enabled the application establishes a session when a user logs in and uses chat, but the chat session is still left active after logout.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49779 | IBM OpenPages cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49779</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages 

could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions, caused by improper validation and management of authentication cookies. By modifying the CSRF token and Session Id cookie parameters using the cookies of another user, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass security restrictions and gain unauthorized access to the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49781 | IBM OpenPages XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49781</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21105 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a command execution vulnerability. A Low privileged malicious user with local access c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21105</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a command execution vulnerability. A Low privileged malicious user with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability by running the specific binary and perform any administrative action permitted by it resulting in shutting down the server, modifying the configuration leading to gain access to unauthorized data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21106 | Dell Recover Point for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a Weak file system permission vulnerability. A low privileged Local attacker could po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21106</link><description>Dell Recover Point for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a Weak file system permission vulnerability. A low privileged Local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to impacting only non-sensitive resources in the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0868 | Remote Code Execution in DocsGPT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0868</link><description>A vulnerability, that could result in Remote Code Execution (RCE), has been found in DocsGPT. Due to improper parsing of JSON data using eval() an unauthorized attacker could send arbitrary Python code to be executed via /api/remote endpoint.

This issue affects DocsGPT: from 0.8.1 through 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1043 | Embed Any Document – Embed PDF, Word, PowerPoint and Excel Files &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via embeddoc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1043</link><description>The Embed Any Document – Embed PDF, Word, PowerPoint and Excel Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 via the 'embeddoc' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13476 | LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13476</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'engtz_wd_save_dropship' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.11 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13520 | Gift Cards (Gift Vouchers and Packages) (WooCommerce Supported) &amp;lt;= 4.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Price, Date, and Note Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13520</link><description>The Gift Cards (Gift Vouchers and Packages) (WooCommerce Supported) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data|loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_voucher_price', 'update_voucher_date', 'update_voucher_note' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the value, expiration date, and user note for any gift voucher.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13748 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt;= 1.4 Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13748</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Title parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13753 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13753</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the update_profile function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify victim's email via a forged request, which might lead to account takeover, granted they can trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13789 | Ravpage &amp;lt;= 2.31 - PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13789</link><description>The ravpage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.31 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'paramsv2' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13792 | WooCommerce Food - Restaurant Menu &amp;amp; Food ordering &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via ids</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13792</link><description>The WooCommerce Food - Restaurant Menu &amp; Food ordering plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13802 | Bandsintown Events &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13802</link><description>The Bandsintown Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bandsintown_events' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13849 | Cookie Notice Bar &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13849</link><description>The Cookie Notice Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13855 | Prime Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via pae_global_block Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13855</link><description>The Prime Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 via the pae_global_block shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract information from posts that are not public, including drafts, private, password protected, and restricted posts. This applies to posts created with Elementor only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6432 | Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via content Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6432</link><description>The Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter within the plugin's shortcode Content Block in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0866 | Legoeso PDF Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection via checkedVals Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0866</link><description>The Legoeso PDF Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘checkedVals’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1328 | Typed JS: A typewriter style animation &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via typespeed Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1328</link><description>The Typed JS: A typewriter style animation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘typespeed’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1483 | LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition &amp;lt;= 2.3.12 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1483</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the engtz_wd_save_dropship AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the drop shipping settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13888 | WPMobile.App &amp;lt;= 11.56 - Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;redirect&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13888</link><description>The WPMobile.App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 11.56. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect URL supplied via the 'redirect' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0897 | Modal Window &amp;lt;= 6.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via iframeBox Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0897</link><description>The Modal Window – create popup modal window plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'iframeBox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1064 | Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) &amp;lt;= 2.8.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via xoo_el_action Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1064</link><description>The Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's xoo_el_action shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13155 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.140 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Transparent Split Hero Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13155</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Transparent Split Hero widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.140 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note: Since the widget code isn't part of the code base, to apply the patch, the affected widget: Transparent Split Hero must be deleted and reinstalled manually.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 07:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26856 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26856</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. If an attacker logs in to the affected product with an administrative account and manipulates requests for a certain screen operation, an arbitrary OS command may be executed. This vulnerability was reported on a different screen operation from CVE-2025-20617.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 05:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13445 | Elementor Website Builder – More Than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.27.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13445</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More Than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the border, margin and gap parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.27.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 04:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27218 | Sitecore Experience Manager (XM) and Experience Platform (XP) 10.4 before KB1002844 allow remote code execution through insecure deserializa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27218</link><description>Sitecore Experience Manager (XM) and Experience Platform (XP) 10.4 before KB1002844 allow remote code execution through insecure deserialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 04:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49780 | IBM OpenPages path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49780</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 

IBM OpenPages could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker with privileges to perform Import Configuration could send a specially crafted http request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) in the file name parameter used in Import Configuration to write files to arbitrary locations outside of the specified directory and possibly overwrite arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49782 | IBM OpenPages improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49782</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 



could allow a remote attacker to spoof mail server identity when using SSL/TLS security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to sensitive information disclosed through email notifications generated by OpenPages or disrupt notification delivery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43196 | IBM OpenPages data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43196</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 

application could allow an authenticated user to manipulate data in the Questionnaires application allowing the user to spoof other users' responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49355 | IBM OpenPages log manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49355</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 may write improperly neutralized data to server log files when the tracing is enabled per the System Tracing feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24947 | A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) in LSQUIC (aka LiteSpeed QUIC) before 4.2.0 allows remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24947</link><description>A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) in LSQUIC (aka LiteSpeed QUIC) before 4.2.0 allows remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs). This is caused by XXH32 usage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23020 | An issue was discovered in Kwik before 0.10.1. A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) allows remote a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23020</link><description>An issue was discovered in Kwik before 0.10.1. A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) allows remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs).</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24946 | The hash table used to manage connections in picoquic before b80fd3f uses a weak hash function, allowing remote attackers to cause a conside...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24946</link><description>The hash table used to manage connections in picoquic before b80fd3f uses a weak hash function, allowing remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs).</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1492 | Uncontrolled Recursion in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1492</link><description>Bundle Protocol and CBOR dissector crashes in Wireshark 4.4.0 to 4.4.3 and 4.2.0 to 4.2.10 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1222 | An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1222</link><description>An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data in Citrix Secure Access Client for Mac</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1223 | An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1223</link><description>An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data in Citrix Secure Access Client for Mac</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1293 | HashiCorp Hermes Improperly Validates AWS ALB JWTs, which May Lead to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1293</link><description>Hermes versions up to 0.4.0 improperly validated the JWT provided when using the AWS ALB authentication mode, potentially allowing for authentication bypass. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-1293, was fixed in Hermes 0.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>