<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-49620 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Authenticated users could delete UDFs in resource center they were not authorized for</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49620</link><description>Before DolphinScheduler version 3.1.0, the login user could delete UDF function in the resource center unauthorized (which almost used in sql task), with unauthorized access vulnerability (IDOR), but after version 3.1.0 we fixed this issue. We mark this cve as moderate level because it still requires user login to operate, please upgrade to version 3.1.0 to avoid this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45135 | Apache Cocoon: SQL injection in DatabaseCookieAuthenticatorAction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Cocoon.This issue affects Apache Cocoon: from 2.2.0 before 2.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49701 | Out-of-bounds access a buffer in SIM management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49701</link><description>Memory Corruption in SIM management while USIMPhase2init</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49077 | mailcow-dockerized XSS Vulnerability in Quarantine UI Allows Unauthorized Access and Data Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49077</link><description>Mailcow: dockerized is an open source groupware/email suite based on docker. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified within the Quarantine UI of the system. This vulnerability poses a significant threat to administrators who utilize the Quarantine feature. An attacker can send a carefully crafted email containing malicious JavaScript code. This issue has been patched in version 2023-11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49095 | nexkey allows arbitrary users to impersonate any remote user due to missing signature validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49095</link><description>nexkey is a microblogging platform. Insufficient validation of ActivityPub requests received in inbox could allow any user to impersonate another user in certain circumstances. This issue has been patched in version 12.122.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49700 | Buffer Copy Without Checking size of input in IMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49700</link><description>Security best practices violations, a string operation in Streamingmedia will write past the end of fixed-size destination buffer if the source buffer is too large.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49699 | Out-of-bounds access a buffer in IMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49699</link><description>Memory Corruption in IMS while calling VoLTE Streamingmedia Interface</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49081 | aiohttp&amp;#x27;s ClientSession is vulnerable to CRLF injection via version</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49081</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Improper validation made it possible for an attacker to modify the HTTP request (e.g. to insert a new header) or create a new HTTP request if the attacker controls the HTTP version. The vulnerability only occurs if the attacker can control the HTTP version of the request. This issue has been patched in version 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49052 | File Upload vulnerability in Microweber v.2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the file upload f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49052</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Microweber v.2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the file upload function in the created forms component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49076 | Pimcore missing token/header to prevent CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49076</link><description>Customer-data-framework allows management of customer data within Pimcore. There are no tokens or headers to prevent CSRF attacks from occurring, therefore an attacker could abuse this vulnerability to create new customers. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49087 | Validation of SignedInfo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49087</link><description>xml-security is a library that implements XML signatures and encryption. Validation of an XML signature requires verification that the hash value of the related XML-document matches a specific DigestValue-value, but also that the cryptographic signature on the SignedInfo-tree (the one that contains the DigestValue) verifies and matches a trusted public key. If an attacker somehow (i.e. by exploiting a bug in PHP's canonicalization function) manages to manipulate the canonicalized version's DigestValue, it would be possible to forge the signature. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.12 and 5.0.0-alpha.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47418 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in o2oa version 8.1.2 and before, allows attackers to create a new interface in the service manage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47418</link><description>Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in o2oa version 8.1.2 and before, allows attackers to create a new interface in the service management function to execute JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49094 | Symbolicator Server Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49094</link><description>Symbolicator is a symbolication service for native stacktraces and minidumps with symbol server support. An attacker could make Symbolicator send arbitrary GET HTTP requests to internal IP addresses by using a specially crafted HTTP endpoint. The response could be reflected to the attacker if they have an account on Sentry instance. The issue has been fixed in the release 23.11.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49097 | ZITADEL vulnerable account takeover via malicious host header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49097</link><description>ZITADEL is an identity infrastructure system. ZITADEL uses the notification triggering requests Forwarded or X-Forwarded-Host header to build the button link sent in emails for confirming a password reset with the emailed code. If this header is overwritten and a user clicks the link to a malicious site in the email, the secret code can be retrieved and used to reset the users password and take over his account. Accounts with MFA or Passwordless enabled can not be taken over by this attack. This issue has been patched in versions 2.41.6, 2.40.10 and 2.39.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47463 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47463</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the gl_nas_sys authentication function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47464 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47464</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 version 4.0.0 before 4.5.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the upload API function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5247 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability due to External Control of File Name or Path in multiple Mitsubishi Electric FA Engineering Software ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5247</link><description>Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability due to External Control of File Name or Path in multiple Mitsubishi Electric FA Engineering Software Products allows a malicious attacker to execute a malicious code by having legitimate users open a specially crafted project file, which could result in information disclosure, tampering and deletion, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5772 | The Debug Log Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5772</link><description>The Debug Log Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the clear_log() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear the debug log via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35137 | An improper authentication vulnerability in the authentication module of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35137</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability in the authentication module of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain system information by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35138 | A command injection vulnerability in the “show_zysync_server_contents” function of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35138</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the “show_zysync_server_contents” function of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37927 | The improper neutralization of special elements in the CGI program of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37927</link><description>The improper neutralization of special elements in the CGI program of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37928 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37928</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4473 | A command injection vulnerability in the web server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4473</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the web server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4474 | The improper neutralization of special elements in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4474</link><description>The improper neutralization of special elements in the WSGI server of the Zyxel NAS326 firmware version V5.21(AAZF.14)C0 and NAS542 firmware version V5.21(ABAG.11)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted URL to a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3741 | An OS Command injection vulnerability in NEC Platforms DT900 and DT900S Series all versions allows an attacker to execute any command on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3741</link><description>An OS Command injection vulnerability in NEC Platforms DT900 and DT900S Series all versions allows an attacker to execute any command on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40458 | AceManager DOS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40458</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Sierra Wireless, Inc ALEOS could potentially allow a remote attacker to trigger a 
Denial of Service (DoS) condition for ACEManager without impairing 
other router functions. This condition is cleared by restarting the 
device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49694 | NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Privilege Escalation Via MySQL Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49694</link><description>A low-privileged OS user with access to a Windows host where NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System is installed can create arbitrary JSP files in a Tomcat web application directory. The user can then execute the JSP files under the security context of SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49693 | NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System RCE via Unprotected Access to Java Debug Wire Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49693</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System has Java Debug Wire Protocol (JDWP) listening on port 11611 and it is remotely accessible by unauthenticated users, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42536 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42536</link><description>Remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42537 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42537</link><description>Remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42538 | Elevation of privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42538</link><description>Elevation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42539 | Information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42539</link><description>Information disclosure</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42540 | Elevation of privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42540</link><description>Elevation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42541 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42541</link><description>Remote code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48945 | A stack overflow in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted SQL statements.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48945</link><description>A stack overflow in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted SQL statements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48946 | An issue in the box_mpy function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48946</link><description>An issue in the box_mpy function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48947 | An issue in the cha_cmp function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48947</link><description>An issue in the cha_cmp function of openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48948 | An issue in the box_div function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48948</link><description>An issue in the box_div function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48949 | An issue in the box_add function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48949</link><description>An issue in the box_add function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48950 | An issue in the box_col_len function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after runni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48950</link><description>An issue in the box_col_len function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48951 | An issue in the box_equal function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48951</link><description>An issue in the box_equal function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48952 | An issue in the box_deserialize_reusing function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48952</link><description>An issue in the box_deserialize_reusing function in openlink virtuoso-opensource v7.2.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) after running a SELECT statement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49082 | aiohttp&amp;#x27;s ClientSession is vulnerable to CRLF injection via method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49082</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Improper validation makes it possible for an attacker to modify the HTTP request (e.g. insert a new header) or even create a new HTTP request if the attacker controls the HTTP method. The vulnerability occurs only if the attacker can control the HTTP method (GET, POST etc.) of the request. If the attacker can control the HTTP version of the request it will be able to modify the request (request smuggling). This issue has been patched in version 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44383 | October CMS stored XSS by authenticated backend user with improper configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44383</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform to assist with development workflow. A user with access to the media manager that stores SVG files could create a stored XSS attack against themselves and any other user with access to the media manager when SVG files are supported. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49091 | Jwttoken in Cosmos server never expires after password changed and logging out</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49091</link><description>Cosmos provides users the ability self-host a home server by acting as a secure gateway to your application, as well as a server manager. Cosmos-server is vulnerable due to to the authorization header used for user login remaining valid and not expiring after log out. This vulnerability allows an attacker to use the token to gain unauthorized access to the application/system even after the user has logged out. This issue has been patched in version 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 19:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49079 | Misskey&amp;#x27;s missing signature validation allows arbitrary users to impersonate any remote user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49079</link><description>Misskey is an open source, decentralized social media platform. Misskey's missing signature validation allows arbitrary users to impersonate any remote user. This issue has been patched in version 2023.11.1-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49083 | cryptography vulnerable to NULL-dereference when loading PKCS7 certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49083</link><description>cryptography is a package designed to expose cryptographic primitives and recipes to Python developers. Calling `load_pem_pkcs7_certificates` or `load_der_pkcs7_certificates` could lead to a NULL-pointer dereference and segfault. Exploitation of this vulnerability poses a serious risk of Denial of Service (DoS) for any application attempting to deserialize a PKCS7 blob/certificate. The consequences extend to potential disruptions in system availability and stability. This vulnerability has been patched in version 41.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6217 | MOVEit Transfer XSS via MOVEit Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6217</link><description>In Progress MOVEit Transfer versions released before 2022.0.9 (14.0.9), 2022.1.10 (14.1.10), 2023.0.7 (15.0.7), a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified when MOVEit Gateway is used in conjunction with MOVEit Transfer.  

An attacker could craft a malicious payload targeting the system which comprises a MOVEit Gateway and MOVEit Transfer deployment.  If a MOVEit user interacts with the crafted payload, the attacker would be able to execute malicious JavaScript within the context of the victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6218 | MOVEit Transfer Group Admin Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6218</link><description>In Progress MOVEit Transfer versions released before 2022.0.9 (14.0.9), 2022.1.10 (14.1.10), 2023.0.7 (15.0.7), a privilege escalation path associated with group administrators has been identified.  It is possible for a group administrator to elevate a group members permissions to the role of an organization administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48880 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48880</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Menu Name field at /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=Index&amp;a=changeTableVal&amp;_ajax=1&amp;lang=cn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48881 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48881</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Field Title field at /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=Field&amp;a=arctype_add&amp;_ajax=1&amp;lang=cn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48882 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48882</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EyouCMS v1.6.4-UTF8-SP1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Document Properties field at /login.php m=admin&amp;c=Index&amp;a=changeTableVal&amp;_ajax=1&amp;lang=cn.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49090 | CarrierWave has a content-type allowlist bypass vulnerability, possibly leading to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49090</link><description>CarrierWave is a solution for file uploads for Rails, Sinatra and other Ruby web frameworks. CarrierWave has a Content-Type allowlist bypass vulnerability, possibly leading to XSS. The validation in `allowlisted_content_type?` determines Content-Type permissions by performing a partial match. If the `content_type` argument of `allowlisted_content_type?` is passed a value crafted by the attacker, Content-Types not included in the `content_type_allowlist` will be allowed. This issue has been patched in versions 2.2.5 and 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 14:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49652 | Incorrect permission checks in Jenkins Google Compute Engine Plugin 4.550.vb_327fca_3db_11 and earlier allow attackers with global Item/Conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49652</link><description>Incorrect permission checks in Jenkins Google Compute Engine Plugin 4.550.vb_327fca_3db_11 and earlier allow attackers with global Item/Configure permission (while lacking Item/Configure permission on any particular job) to enumerate system-scoped credentials IDs of credentials stored in Jenkins and to connect to Google Cloud Platform using attacker-specified credentials IDs obtained through another method, to obtain information about existing projects. This fix has been backported to 4.3.17.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49653 | Jenkins Jira Plugin 3.11 and earlier does not set the appropriate context for credentials lookup, allowing attackers with Item/Configure per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49653</link><description>Jenkins Jira Plugin 3.11 and earlier does not set the appropriate context for credentials lookup, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to access and capture credentials they are not entitled to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49654 | Missing permission checks in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allow attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML file from the Jenkins con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49654</link><description>Missing permission checks in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allow attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML file from the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49655 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allows attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49655</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier allows attackers to have Jenkins parse an XML file from the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49656 | Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier does not configure its XML parser to prevent XML external entity (XXE) attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49656</link><description>Jenkins MATLAB Plugin 2.11.0 and earlier does not configure its XML parser to prevent XML external entity (XXE) attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49673 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49673</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers to connect to an attacker-specified hostname and port using attacker-specified username and password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49674 | A missing permission check in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49674</link><description>A missing permission check in Jenkins NeuVector Vulnerability Scanner Plugin 1.22 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to connect to an attacker-specified hostname and port using attacker-specified username and password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40626 | [20231101] - Core - Exposure of environment variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40626</link><description>The language file parsing process could be manipulated to expose environment variables. Environment variables might contain sensible information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6345 | Integer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6345</link><description>Integer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6346 | Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6346</link><description>Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6347 | Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6347</link><description>Use after free in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6348 | Type Confusion in Spellcheck in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6348</link><description>Type Confusion in Spellcheck in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6350 | Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6350</link><description>Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted avif file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6351 | Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6351</link><description>Use after free in libavif in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.199 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted avif file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6378 | Logback &amp;quot;receiver&amp;quot; DOS vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6378</link><description>A serialization vulnerability in logback receiver component part of 
logback version 1.4.11 allows an attacker to mount a Denial-Of-Service 
attack by sending poisoned data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6070 | A server-side request forgery vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.8 allows a low privileged authenticated user to upload arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6070</link><description>A server-side request forgery vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.8 allows a low privileged authenticated user to upload arbitrary content, potentially altering configuration. This is possible through the certificate validation functionality where the API accepts uploaded content and doesn't parse for invalid data</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45479 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter in the function sub_49E09...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45479</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the list parameter in the function sub_49E098.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45480 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the src parameter in the function sub_47D878...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45480</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the src parameter in the function sub_47D878.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45481 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the firewallEn parameter in the function Set...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45481</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the firewallEn parameter in the function SetFirewallCfg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45482 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_paren...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45482</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45483 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the function compare_p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45483</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the function compare_parentcontrol_time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45484 | Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the function fro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45484</link><description>Tenda AC10 version US_AC10V4.0si_V16.03.10.13_cn was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the function fromSetWifiGuestBasic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46886 | Dreamer CMS before version 4.0.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. Background template management allows arbitrary modification of the t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46886</link><description>Dreamer CMS before version 4.0.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. Background template management allows arbitrary modification of the template file, allowing system sensitive files to be read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46887 | In Dreamer CMS before 4.0.1, the backend attachment management office has an Arbitrary File Download vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46887</link><description>In Dreamer CMS before 4.0.1, the backend attachment management office has an Arbitrary File Download vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47462 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 v.3.215 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file shar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47462</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in GL.iNet AX1800 v.3.215 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file sharing function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 04:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23324 | Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials for the Administrator account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23324</link><description>Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials for the Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23325 | Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the NetHostname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23325</link><description>Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard 3.74 - Firmware 3.80 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the NetHostname parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24294 | Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard v3.74 - Firmware v3.80 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component NetlinkWeb::Information::S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24294</link><description>Zumtobel Netlink CCD Onboard v3.74 - Firmware v3.80 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the component NetlinkWeb::Information::SetDeviceIdentification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46944 | An issue in GitKraken GitLens before v.14.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the Visual Studio Codes wor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46944</link><description>An issue in GitKraken GitLens before v.14.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file to the Visual Studio Codes workspace trust component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49092 | RustCrypto/RSA vulnerable to a Marvin Attack via key recovery through timing sidechannels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49092</link><description>RustCrypto/RSA is a portable RSA implementation in pure Rust. Due to a non-constant-time implementation, information about the private key is leaked through timing information which is observable over the network. An attacker may be able to use that information to recover the key. There is currently no fix available. As a workaround, avoid using the RSA crate in settings where attackers are able to observe timing information, e.g. local use on a non-compromised computer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 21:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29061 | Lack of Adequate BIOS Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29061</link><description>There is no BIOS password on the FACSChorus workstation. A threat actor with physical access to the workstation can potentially exploit this vulnerability to access the BIOS configuration and modify the drive boot order and BIOS pre-boot authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29062 | Unsecure Identity Verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29062</link><description>The Operating System hosting the FACSChorus application is configured to allow transmission of hashed user credentials upon user action without adequately validating the identity of the requested resource. This is possible through the use of LLMNR, MBT-NS, or MDNS and will result in NTLMv2 hashes being sent to a malicious entity position on the local network. These hashes can subsequently be attacked through brute force and cracked if a weak password is used. This attack would only apply to domain joined systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29063 | Lack of DMA Access Protections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29063</link><description>The FACSChorus workstation does not prevent physical access to its PCI express (PCIe) slots, which could allow a threat actor to insert a PCI card designed for memory capture. A threat actor can then isolate sensitive information such as a BitLocker encryption key from a dump of the workstation RAM during startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29064 | Hardcoded Secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29064</link><description>The FACSChorus software contains sensitive information stored in plaintext. A threat actor could gain hardcoded secrets used by the application, which include tokens and passwords for administrative accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29065 | Overly Permissive Access Policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29065</link><description>The FACSChorus software database can be accessed directly with the privileges of the currently logged-in user. A threat actor with physical access could potentially gain credentials, which could be used to alter or destroy data stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29066 | Incorrect User Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29066</link><description>The FACSChorus software does not properly assign data access privileges for operating system user accounts. A non-administrative OS account can modify information stored in the local application data folders.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48193 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in JumpServer GPLv3 v.3.8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via bypassing the command ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48193</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in JumpServer GPLv3 v.3.8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via bypassing the command filtering function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29060 | Lack of USB Whitelisting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29060</link><description>The FACSChorus workstation operating system does not restrict what devices can interact with its USB ports. If exploited, a threat actor with physical access to the workstation could gain access to system information and potentially exfiltrate data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45539 | HAProxy before 2.8.2 accepts # as part of the URI component, which might allow remote attackers to obtain sensitive information or have unsp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45539</link><description>HAProxy before 2.8.2 accepts # as part of the URI component, which might allow remote attackers to obtain sensitive information or have unspecified other impact upon misinterpretation of a path_end rule, such as routing index.html#.png to a static server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30588 | When an invalid public key is used to create an x509 certificate using the crypto.X509Certificate() API a non-expect termination occurs maki...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30588</link><description>When an invalid public key is used to create an x509 certificate using the crypto.X509Certificate() API a non-expect termination occurs making it susceptible to DoS attacks when the attacker could force interruptions of application processing, as the process terminates when accessing public key info of provided certificates from user code. The current context of the users will be gone, and that will cause a DoS scenario. This vulnerability affects all active Node.js versions v16, v18, and, v20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30590 | The generateKeys() API function returned from crypto.createDiffieHellman() only generates missing (or outdated) keys, that is, it only gener...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30590</link><description>The generateKeys() API function returned from crypto.createDiffieHellman() only generates missing (or outdated) keys, that is, it only generates a private key if none has been set yet, but the function is also needed to compute the corresponding public key after calling setPrivateKey(). However, the documentation says this API call: "Generates private and public Diffie-Hellman key values".

The documented behavior is very different from the actual behavior, and this difference could easily lead to security issues in applications that use these APIs as the DiffieHellman may be used as the basis for application-level security, implications are consequently broad.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48121 | An authentication bypass vulnerability in the Direct Connection Module in Ezviz CS-C6N-xxx prior to v5.3.x build 20230401, Ezviz CS-CV310-xx...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48121</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in the Direct Connection Module in Ezviz CS-C6N-xxx prior to v5.3.x build 20230401, Ezviz CS-CV310-xxx prior to v5.3.x build 20230401, Ezviz CS-C6CN-xxx prior to v5.3.x build 20230401, Ezviz CS-C3N-xxx prior to v5.3.x build 20230401 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information by sending crafted messages to the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49078 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in raptor-web 0.4.4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49078</link><description>raptor-web is a CMS for game server communities that can be used to host information and keep track of players. In version 0.4.4 of raptor-web, it is possible to craft a malicious URL that will result in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A user controlled URL parameter is loaded into an internal template that has autoescape disabled. This is a cross-site scripting vulnerability that affects all deployments of `raptor-web` on version `0.4.4`. Any victim who clicks on a malicious crafted link will be affected. This issue has been patched 0.4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42504 | Apache Superset: Lack of rate limiting allows for possible denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42504</link><description>An authenticated malicious user could initiate multiple concurrent requests, each requesting multiple dashboard exports, leading to a possible denial of service.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40056 | SolarWinds Platform SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40056</link><description>SQL Injection Remote Code Vulnerability was found in the SolarWinds
Platform. This vulnerability can be exploited with a low privileged account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41264 | Netwrix Usercube before 6.0.215, in certain misconfigured on-premises installations, allows authentication bypass on deployment endpoints, l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41264</link><description>Netwrix Usercube before 6.0.215, in certain misconfigured on-premises installations, allows authentication bypass on deployment endpoints, leading to privilege escalation. This only occurs if the configuration omits the required restSettings.AuthorizedClientId and restSettings.AuthorizedSecret fields (for the POST /api/Deployment/ExportConfiguration and POST /api/Deployment endpoints).</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48848 | An arbitrary file read vulnerability in ureport v2.2.9 allows a remote attacker to arbitrarily read files on the server by inserting a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48848</link><description>An arbitrary file read vulnerability in ureport v2.2.9 allows a remote attacker to arbitrarily read files on the server by inserting a crafted path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45286 | HTTP request body disclosure in github.com/go-resty/resty/v2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45286</link><description>A race condition in go-resty can result in HTTP request body disclosure across requests. This condition can be triggered by calling sync.Pool.Put with the same *bytes.Buffer more than once, when request retries are enabled and a retry occurs. The call to sync.Pool.Get will then return a bytes.Buffer that hasn't had bytes.Buffer.Reset called on it. This dirty buffer will contain the HTTP request body from an unrelated request, and go-resty will append the current HTTP request body to it, sending two bodies in one request. The sync.Pool in question is defined at package level scope, so a completely unrelated server could receive the request body.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 16:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42502 | Apache Superset: Open Redirect Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42502</link><description>An authenticated attacker with update datasets permission could change a dataset link to an untrusted site by spoofing the HTTP Host header, users could be redirected to this site when clicking on that specific dataset. This issue affects Apache Superset versions before 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42505 | Apache Superset: Sensitive information disclosure on db connection details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42505</link><description>An authenticated user with read permissions on database connections metadata could potentially access sensitive information such as the connection's username.

This issue affects Apache Superset before 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49062 | Katran could disclose non-initialized kernel memory as part of an IP header. The issue was present for IPv4 encapsulation and ICMP (v4) Too ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49062</link><description>Katran could disclose non-initialized kernel memory as part of an IP header. The issue was present for IPv4 encapsulation and ICMP (v4) Too Big packet generation. After a bpf_xdp_adjust_head call, Katran code didn’t initialize the Identification field for the IPv4 header, resulting in writing content of kernel memory in that field of IP header. The issue affected all Katran versions prior to commit 6a03106ac1eab39d0303662963589ecb2374c97f</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46589 | Apache Tomcat: HTTP request smuggling via malformed trailer headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46589</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.Tomcat from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M10, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.15, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.82 and from 8.5.0 through 8.5.95 did not correctly parse HTTP trailer headers. A trailer header that exceeded the header size limit could cause Tomcat to treat a single 
request as multiple requests leading to the possibility of request 
smuggling when behind a reverse proxy.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M11 onwards, 10.1.16 onwards, 9.0.83 onwards or 8.5.96 onwards, which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41678 | Apache ActiveMQ: Deserialization vulnerability on Jolokia that allows authenticated users to perform RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41678</link><description>Once an user is authenticated on Jolokia, he can potentially trigger arbitrary code execution. 

In details, in ActiveMQ configurations, jetty allows
org.jolokia.http.AgentServlet to handler request to /api/jolokia

org.jolokia.http.HttpRequestHandler#handlePostRequest is able to
create JmxRequest through JSONObject. And calls to
org.jolokia.http.HttpRequestHandler#executeRequest.

Into deeper calling stacks,
org.jolokia.handler.ExecHandler#doHandleRequest is able to invoke
through refection.

And then, RCE is able to be achieved via
jdk.management.jfr.FlightRecorderMXBeanImpl which exists on Java version above 11.

1 Call newRecording.

2 Call setConfiguration. And a webshell data hides in it.

3 Call startRecording.

4 Call copyTo method. The webshell will be written to a .jsp file.

The mitigation is to restrict (by default) the actions authorized on Jolokia, or disable Jolokia.
A more restrictive Jolokia configuration has been defined in default ActiveMQ distribution. We encourage users to upgrade to ActiveMQ distributions version including updated Jolokia configuration: 5.16.6, 5.17.4, 5.18.0, 6.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49313 | A dylib injection vulnerability in XMachOViewer 0.04 allows attackers to compromise integrity. By exploiting this, unauthorized code can be ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49313</link><description>A dylib injection vulnerability in XMachOViewer 0.04 allows attackers to compromise integrity. By exploiting this, unauthorized code can be injected into the product's processes, potentially leading to remote control and unauthorized access to sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49314 | Asana Desktop 2.1.0 on macOS allows code injection because of specific Electron Fuses. There is inadequate protection against code injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49314</link><description>Asana Desktop 2.1.0 on macOS allows code injection because of specific Electron Fuses. There is inadequate protection against code injection through settings such as RunAsNode and EnableNodeCliInspectArguments, and thus r3ggi/electroniz3r can be used to perform an attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6239 | Incorrect calculation of effective permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6239</link><description>Under rare conditions, the effective permissions of an object might be incorrectly calculated if the object has a specific configuration of metadata-driven permissions in M-Files Server versions 23.9 and 23.10 and 23.11 before 23.11.13168.7 allowing user to access object with incorrectly calculated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48042 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Search filters in Prestashop Amazzing filter version up to version 3.2.5, allows remote attackers to inject ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48042</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Search filters in Prestashop Amazzing filter version up to version 3.2.5, allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6359 | Cross-Site Scripting in Alumne LMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6359</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been found in Alumne LMS affecting version 4.0.0.1.08. An attacker could exploit the 'localidad' parameter to inject a custom JavaScript payload and partially take over another user's browser session, due to the lack of proper sanitisation of the 'localidad' field on the /users/editmy page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5981 | Gnutls: timing side-channel in the rsa-psk authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5981</link><description>A vulnerability was found that the response times to malformed ciphertexts in RSA-PSK ClientKeyExchange differ from response times of ciphertexts with correct PKCS#1 v1.5 padding.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6201 | Command Injection in Univera Panorama Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6201</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Univera Computer System Panorama allows Command Injection.This issue affects Panorama: before 8.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42004 | IBM Security Guardium CSV injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42004</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 11.3, 11.4, and 11.5 is potentially vulnerable to CSV injection.  A remote attacker could execute malicious commands due to improper validation of csv file contents.  IBM X-Force ID:  265262.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 10:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6151 | Information Disclosure in Eskom E-municipality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6151</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ESKOM Computer e-municipality module allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects e-municipality module: before v.105.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 09:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6150 | Information Disclosure in Eskom E-municipality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6150</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ESKOM Computer e-municipality module allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects e-municipality module: before v.105.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34055 | Spring Boot server Web Observations DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34055</link><description>In Spring Boot versions 2.7.0 - 2.7.17, 3.0.0-3.0.12 and 3.1.0-3.1.5, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when all of the following are true:

  *  the application uses Spring MVC or Spring WebFlux
  *  org.springframework.boot:spring-boot-actuator is on the classpath</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34053 | Spring Framework server Web Observations DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34053</link><description>In Spring Framework versions 6.0.0 - 6.0.13, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable when all of the following are true:

  *  the application uses Spring MVC or Spring WebFlux
  *  io.micrometer:micrometer-core is on the classpath
  *  an ObservationRegistry is configured in the application to record observations


Typically, Spring Boot applications need the org.springframework.boot:spring-boot-actuator dependency to meet all conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34054 | Reactor Netty HTTP Server Metrics DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34054</link><description>In Reactor Netty HTTP Server, versions 1.1.x prior to 1.1.13 and versions 1.0.x prior to 1.0.39, it is possible for a user to provide specially crafted HTTP requests that may cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable if Reactor Netty HTTP Server built-in integration with Micrometer is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4667 | Stored Cross Site Scripting in webserver administration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4667</link><description>The web interface of the PAC Device allows the device administrator user profile to store malicious scripts in some fields. The stored malicious script is then executed when the GUI is opened by any users of the webserver administration interface. 



The root cause of the vulnerability is inadequate input validation and output encoding in the web administration interface component of the firmware.

This could lead to  unauthorized access and data leakage</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48022 | Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the job submission API. NOTE: the vendor's position is t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48022</link><description>Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the job submission API. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this report is irrelevant because Ray, as stated in its documentation, is not intended for use outside of a strictly controlled network environment</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48023 | Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows /log_proxy SSRF. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this report is irrelevant because Ray, as stated in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48023</link><description>Anyscale Ray 2.6.3 and 2.8.0 allows /log_proxy SSRF. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this report is irrelevant because Ray, as stated in its documentation, is not intended for use outside of a strictly controlled network environment</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4224 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4224</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/dropbox.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4225 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4225</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/exercise.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4226 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4226</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/work.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4220 | Chamilo LMS Unauthenticated Big Upload File Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4220</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in big file upload functionality in `/main/inc/lib/javascript/bigupload/inc/bigUpload.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows unauthenticated attackers to perform stored cross-site scripting attacks and obtain remote code execution via uploading of web shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4221 | Chamilo LMS Learning Path PPT2LP Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4221</link><description>Command injection in `main/lp/openoffice_presentation.class.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows users permitted to upload Learning Paths to obtain remote code execution via improper neutralisation of special characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4222 | Chamilo LMS Learning Path PPT2LP Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4222</link><description>Command injection in `main/lp/openoffice_text_document.class.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows users permitted to upload Learning Paths to obtain remote code execution via improper neutralisation of special characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4223 | Chamilo LMS File Upload Functionality Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4223</link><description>Unrestricted file upload in `/main/inc/ajax/document.ajax.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.24 allows authenticated attackers with learner role to obtain remote code execution via uploading of PHP files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3368 | Chamilo LMS Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3368</link><description>Command injection in `/main/webservices/additional_webservices.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.20 allows unauthenticated attackers to obtain remote code execution via improper neutralisation of special characters. This is a bypass of CVE-2023-34960.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3533 | Chamilo LMS Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3533</link><description>Path traversal in file upload functionality in `/main/webservices/additional_webservices.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.20 allows unauthenticated attackers to perform stored cross-site scripting attacks and obtain remote code execution via arbitrary file write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3545 | Chamilo LMS Htaccess File Upload Security Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3545</link><description>Improper sanitisation in `main/inc/lib/fileUpload.lib.php` in Chamilo LMS &lt;= v1.11.20 on Windows and Apache installations allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass file upload security protections and obtain remote code execution via uploading of `.htaccess` file. This vulnerability may be exploited by privileged attackers or chained with unauthenticated arbitrary file write vulnerabilities, such as CVE-2023-3533, to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24023 | Bluetooth BR/EDR devices with Secure Simple Pairing and Secure Connections pairing in Bluetooth Core Specification 4.2 through 5.4 allow cer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24023</link><description>Bluetooth BR/EDR devices with Secure Simple Pairing and Secure Connections pairing in Bluetooth Core Specification 4.2 through 5.4 allow certain man-in-the-middle attacks that force a short key length, and might lead to discovery of the encryption key and live injection, aka BLUFFS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49075 | Pimcore Admin UI has Two Factor Authentication disabled for non admin security firewalls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49075</link><description>The Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. `AdminBundle\Security\PimcoreUserTwoFactorCondition` introduced in v11 disable the two factor authentication for all non-admin security firewalls. An authenticated user can access the system without having to provide the two factor credentials. This issue has been patched in version 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6225 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_meta sh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6225</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's su_meta shortcode combined with post meta data in all versions up to, and including, 5.13.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied meta values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6226 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6226</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.13.3 via the su_meta shortcode due to missing validation on the user controlled keys 'key' and 'post_id'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to retrieve arbitrary post meta values which may contain sensitive information when combined with another plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48713 | Knative Serving vulnerable to attacker-controlled pod causing denial of service of autoscaler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48713</link><description>Knative Serving builds on Kubernetes to support deploying and serving of applications and functions as serverless containers. An attacker who controls a pod to a degree where they can control the responses from the /metrics endpoint can cause Denial-of-Service of the autoscaler from an unbound memory allocation bug. This is a DoS vulnerability, where a non-privileged Knative user can cause a DoS for the cluster. This issue has been patched in version 0.39.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32064 | OroCommerce Customer Portal Incorrect Customer and Customer Group Frontend Menus pages visibility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32064</link><description>OroCommerce package with customer portal and non authenticated visitor website base features. Back-office users can access information about Customer and Customer User menus, bypassing ACL security restrictions due to insufficient security checks. This issue has been patched in version 5.0.11 and 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32065 | OroCommerce get-totals-for-checkout API endpoint returns unwanted data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32065</link><description>OroCommerce is an open-source Business to Business Commerce application built with flexibility in mind. Detailed Order totals information may be received by Order ID. This issue is patched in version 5.0.11 and 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32063 | OroCRMCallBundle has incorrect call view page visibility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32063</link><description>OroCalendarBundle enables a Calendar feature and related functionality in Oro applications. Back-office users can access information from any call event, bypassing ACL security restrictions due to insufficient security checks. This issue has been patched in version 5.0.4 and 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6219 | The BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'bookingpress_proce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6219</link><description>The BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'bookingpress_process_upload' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.76. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5797 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5797</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, NWA50AX firmware version 6.29(ABYW.2), WAC500 firmware version 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware version 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware version 6.65(ACGG.1), could allow an authenticated local attacker to access the administrator’s logs on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5960 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the hotspot feature of the Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37 and V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5960</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the hotspot feature of the Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37 and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37 could allow an authenticated local attacker to access the system files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37926 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37926</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command to dump system logs on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47503 | An issue in jflyfox jfinalCMS v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.jsp component in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47503</link><description>An issue in jflyfox jfinalCMS v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.jsp component in the template management module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4397 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4397</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware version 5.37, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware version 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command with crafted strings on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4398 | An integer overflow vulnerability in the source code of the QuickSec IPSec toolkit used in the VPN feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4398</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the source code of the QuickSec IPSec toolkit used in the VPN feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions on an affected device by sending a crafted IKE packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5650 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the ZySH of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5650</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the ZySH of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to modify the URL of the registration page in the web GUI of an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30585 | A vulnerability has been identified in the Node.js (.msi version) installation process, specifically affecting Windows users who install Nod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30585</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Node.js (.msi version) installation process, specifically affecting Windows users who install Node.js using the .msi installer. This vulnerability emerges during the repair operation, where the "msiexec.exe" process, running under the NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM context, attempts to read the %USERPROFILE% environment variable from the current user's registry.

The issue arises when the path referenced by the %USERPROFILE% environment variable does not exist. In such cases, the "msiexec.exe" process attempts to create the specified path in an unsafe manner, potentially leading to the creation of arbitrary folders in arbitrary locations.

The severity of this vulnerability is heightened by the fact that the %USERPROFILE% environment variable in the Windows registry can be modified by standard (or "non-privileged") users. Consequently, unprivileged actors, including malicious entities or trojans, can manipulate the environment variable key to deceive the privileged "msiexec.exe" process. This manipulation can result in the creation of folders in unintended and potentially malicious locations.

It is important to note that this vulnerability is specific to Windows users who install Node.js using the .msi installer. Users who opt for other installation methods are not affected by this particular issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35136 | An improper input validation vulnerability in the “Quagga” package of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35136</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability in the “Quagga” package of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to access configuration files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35139 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG FLEX series f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35139</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.37, could allow an unauthenticated LAN-based attacker to store malicious scripts in a vulnerable device. A successful XSS attack could then result in the stored malicious scripts being executed to steal cookies when the user visits the specific CGI used for dumping ZTP logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37925 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37925</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, NWA50AX firmware version 6.29(ABYW.2), WAC500 firmware version 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware version 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware version 6.65(ACGG.1), could allow an authenticated local attacker to access system files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>