<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:43:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-35203 | Mahara before 22.10.6, 23.04.6, and 24.04.1 allows cross-site scripting (XSS) via a file, with JavaScript code as part of its name, that is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35203</link><description>Mahara before 22.10.6, 23.04.6, and 24.04.1 allows cross-site scripting (XSS) via a file, with JavaScript code as part of its name, that is uploaded via the Mahara filebrowser system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47192 | An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. The use of a malicious export download URL can allow an attacker to download files th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47192</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. The use of a malicious export download URL can allow an attacker to download files that they do not have permission to download.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52353 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Badaso CMS 2.9.11. The Media Manager allows authenticated users to upload files containing embe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52353</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Badaso CMS 2.9.11. The Media Manager allows authenticated users to upload files containing embedded PHP code via the file-upload endpoint, bypassing content-type validation. When such a file is accessed via its URL, the server executes the PHP payload, enabling an attacker to run arbitrary system commands and achieve full compromise of the underlying host. This has been demonstrated by embedding a backdoor within a PDF and renaming it with a .php extension.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55443 | Telpo MDM 1.4.6 thru 1.4.9 for Android contains sensitive administrator credentials and MQTT server connection details (IP/port) that are st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55443</link><description>Telpo MDM 1.4.6 thru 1.4.9 for Android contains sensitive administrator credentials and MQTT server connection details (IP/port) that are stored in plaintext within log files on the device's external storage. This allows attackers with access to these logs to: 1. Authenticate to the MDM web platform to execute administrative operations (device shutdown/factory reset/software installation); 2. Connect to the MQTT server to intercept/publish device data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50971 | Directory traversal vulnerability in AbanteCart version 1.4.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to gain access to sensitive system files via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50971</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in AbanteCart version 1.4.2 allows unauthenticated attackers to gain access to sensitive system files via the template parameter to index.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50975 | IPFire 2.29 web-based firewall interface (firewall.cgi) fails to sanitize several rule parameters such as PROT, SRC_PORT, TGT_PORT, dnatport...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50975</link><description>IPFire 2.29 web-based firewall interface (firewall.cgi) fails to sanitize several rule parameters such as PROT, SRC_PORT, TGT_PORT, dnatport, key, ruleremark, src_addr, std_net_tgt, and tgt_addr, allowing an authenticated administrator to inject persistent JavaScript. This stored XSS payload is executed whenever another admin views the firewall rules page, enabling session hijacking, unauthorized actions within the interface, or further internal pivoting. Exploitation requires only high-privilege GUI access, and the complexity of the attack is low.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9478 | Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.154 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9478</link><description>Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 139.0.7258.154 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23307 | NVIDIA NeMo Curator for all platforms contains a vulnerability where a malicious file created by an attacker could allow code injection. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23307</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Curator for all platforms contains a vulnerability where a malicious file created by an attacker could allow code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23312 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the retrieval services component, where malicious data created by an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23312</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the retrieval services component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23313 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23313</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23314 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23314</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the NLP component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23315 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the export and deploy component, where malicious data created by an atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23315</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the export and deploy component, where malicious data created by an attacker could cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57818 | Firecrawl SSRF Vulnerability via malicious webhook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57818</link><description>Firecrawl turns entire websites into LLM-ready markdown or structured data. Prior to version 2.0.1, a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability was discovered in Firecrawl's webhook functionality. Authenticated users could configure a webhook to an internal URL and send POST requests with arbitrary headers, which may have allowed access to internal systems. This has been fixed in version 2.0.1. If upgrading is not possible, it is recommend to isolate Firecrawl from any sensitive internal systems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50976 | IPFire 2.29 DNS management interface (dns.cgi) fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the NAMESERVER, REMARK, and TLS_HOSTNAME qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50976</link><description>IPFire 2.29 DNS management interface (dns.cgi) fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the NAMESERVER, REMARK, and TLS_HOSTNAME query parameters, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55298 | ImageMagick Format String Bug in InterpretImageFilename leads to arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55298</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to ImageMagick versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2, a format string bug vulnerability exists in InterpretImageFilename function where user input is directly passed to FormatLocaleString without proper sanitization. An attacker can overwrite arbitrary memory regions, enabling a wide range of attacks from heap overflow to remote code execution. This issue has been patched in versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57803 | ImageMagick (WriteBMPImage): 32-bit integer overflow when writing BMP scanline stride → heap buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57803</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2 for ImageMagick's 32-bit build, a 32-bit integer overflow in the BMP encoder’s scanline-stride computation collapses bytes_per_line (stride) to a tiny value while the per-row writer still emits 3 × width bytes for 24-bpp images. The row base pointer advances using the (overflowed) stride, so the first row immediately writes past its slot and into adjacent heap memory with attacker-controlled bytes. This is a classic, powerful primitive for heap corruption in common auto-convert pipelines. This issue has been patched in versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50974 | The Calamaris log exporter CGI (/cgi-bin/logs.cgi/calamaris.dat) in IPFire 2.29 does not properly sanitize user-supplied input before incorp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50974</link><description>The Calamaris log exporter CGI (/cgi-bin/logs.cgi/calamaris.dat) in IPFire 2.29 does not properly sanitize user-supplied input before incorporating parameter values into a shell command. An unauthenticated remote attacker can inject arbitrary OS commands by embedding shell metacharacters in any of the following parameters BYTE_UNIT, DAY_BEGIN, DAY_END, HIST_LEVEL, MONTH_BEGIN, MONTH_END, NUM_CONTENT, NUM_DOMAINS, NUM_HOSTS, NUM_URLS, PERF_INTERVAL, YEAR_BEGIN, YEAR_END.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1494 | IBM Cognos Command Center clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1494</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1994 | IBM Cognos Command Center code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1994</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 



could allow a local user to execute arbitrary code on the system due to the use of unsafe use of the BinaryFormatter function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2697 | IBM Cognos Command Center HTTP Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2697</link><description>IBM Cognos Command Center 10.2.4.1 and 10.2.5 

could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52184 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Helpy.io v.2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the New Topic Ticket funtion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52184</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Helpy.io v.2.8.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the New Topic Ticket funtion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55212 | ImageMagick affected by divide-by-zero in ThumbnailImage via montage -geometry &amp;quot;:&amp;quot; leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55212</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2, passing a geometry string containing only a colon (":") to montage -geometry leads GetGeometry() to set width/height to 0. Later, ThumbnailImage() divides by these zero dimensions, triggering a crash (SIGFPE/abort), resulting in a denial of service. This issue has been patched in versions 6.9.13-28 and 7.1.2-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36729 | RACOM M!DGE2 Privilege Escalation via SDK Testing Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36729</link><description>A non-primary administrator user with admin rights to the web interface but without shell access permissions can display configuration of the device including the master admin password. This vulnerability also allows the user to give themselves shell access with the root gid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9491 | Microsoft Windows LNK File UI Misrepresentation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9491</link><description>Microsoft Windows LNK File UI Misrepresentation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of .LNK files. Crafted data in an .LNK file can cause hazardous content in the file to be invisible to a user who inspects the file via the Windows-provided user interface. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-25373.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57425 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 allows an authenticated attacker to inject mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57425</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious JavaScript into the 'question' and 'answer' fields via the update-faq.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57813 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in github.com/traPtitech/traQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57813</link><description>traQ is a messenger application built for Digital Creators Club traP. Prior to version 3.25.0, a vulnerability exists where sensitive information, such as OAuth tokens, are recorded in log files when an error occurs during the execution of an SQL query. An attacker could intentionally trigger an SQL error by methods such as placing a high load on the database. This could allow an attacker who has the authority to view the log files to illicitly acquire the recorded sensitive information. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.25.0. If upgrading is not possible, a temporary workaround involves reviewing access permissions for SQL error logs and strictly limiting access to prevent unauthorized users from viewing them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57810 | jsPDF Parsing of Corrupt PNGs Leads to Potential Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57810</link><description>jsPDF is a library to generate PDFs in JavaScript. Prior to 3.0.2, user control of the first argument of the addImage method results in CPU utilization and denial of service. If given the possibility to pass unsanitized image data or URLs to the addImage method, a user can provide a harmful PNG file that results in high CPU utilization and denial of service. The vulnerability was fixed in jsPDF 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56432 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Nagios XI 2024R2. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56432</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Nagios XI 2024R2. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a logged-in user's session via a specially crafted URL. The issue resides in a web component responsible for rendering performance-related data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25732 | Incorrect access control in the EEPROM component of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25732</link><description>Incorrect access control in the EEPROM component of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 allows attackers to replace password hashes stored in the EEPROM with hashes of their own, leading to the escalation of privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25733 | Incorrect access control in the SPI Flash Chip of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25733</link><description>Incorrect access control in the SPI Flash Chip of Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 allows physically proximate attackers to arbitrarily modify SPI flash regions, leading to a degradation of the security posture of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25734 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 was discovered to contain an u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25734</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 was discovered to contain an unauthenticated EFI shell which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or escalate privileges during the boot process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25735 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack SPI Pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25735</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack SPI Protected Range Registers (PRRs), allowing attackers with software running on the system to modify SPI flash in real-time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25736 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9260 RSU LEO v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to contain Android Debug Bridge (ADB) p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25736</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9260 RSU LEO v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to contain Android Debug Bridge (ADB) pre-installed (/mnt/c3platpersistent/opt/platform-tools/adb) and enabled by default, allowing unauthenticated root shell access to the cellular modem via the default 'kapsch' user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25737 | Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack secure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25737</link><description>Kapsch TrafficCom RIS-9160 &amp; RIS-9260 Roadside Units (RSUs) v3.2.0.829.23, v3.8.0.1119.42, and v4.6.0.1211.28 were discovered to lack secure password requirements for its BIOS Supervisor and User accounts, allowing attackers to bypass authentication via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52037 | A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=sites. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52037</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=sites. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions leads to a stored XSS vulnerability. The issue was confirmed to be present in the source code as of commit 7d821a0f028b0778b245b99ab3d3bff1ac10e2d3 (dated 2024-05-08), and was fixed in commit 95322c5121dbd7070f3bd54f2848079654a0a8ea (dated 2025-03-31). The attack can be launched remotely. CWE Definition of the Vulnerability: CWE-79.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52035 | A vulnerability in NotesCMS and specifically in the page /index.php?route=notes. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52035</link><description>A vulnerability in NotesCMS and specifically in the page /index.php?route=notes. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions leads to a stored XSS vulnerability. The issue was confirmed to be present in the source code as of commit 7d821a0f028b0778b245b99ab3d3bff1ac10e2d3 (dated 2024-05-08) and was fixed in commit 95322c5121dbd7070f3bd54f2848079654a0a8ea (dated 2025-03-31). The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52036 | A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=categories....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52036</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in NotesCMS and classified as medium. Affected by this vulnerability is the page /index.php?route=categories. The manipulation of the title of the service descriptions leads to a stored XSS vulnerability. The issue was confirmed to be present in the source code as of commit 7d821a0f028b0778b245b99ab3d3bff1ac10e2d3 (dated 2024-05-08), and was fixed in commit 95322c5121dbd7070f3bd54f2848079654a0a8ea (dated 2025-03-31). The attack can be launched remotely. CWE Definition of the Vulnerability: CWE-79.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6366 | Event List &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6366</link><description>The Event List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's capabilities prior to updating their profile in the el_update_profile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change their capabilities to those of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39335 | Supported versions of Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.1 and 23.04 before 23.04.6 are vulnerable to information being disclosed to an institution a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39335</link><description>Supported versions of Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.1 and 23.04 before 23.04.6 are vulnerable to information being disclosed to an institution administrator under certain conditions via the 'Current submissions' page: Administration -&gt; Groups -&gt; Submissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52217 | SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to HTML Injection. Legacy UI fields improperly handle user-supplied inp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52217</link><description>SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to HTML Injection. Legacy UI fields improperly handle user-supplied input, allowing injection of arbitrary HTML.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52218 | SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to Content Spoofing / Text Injection. Improper sanitization of unspecif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52218</link><description>SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 is vulnerable to Content Spoofing / Text Injection. Improper sanitization of unspecified parameters allows attackers to inject arbitrary text or limited HTML into the login page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52219 | SelectZero SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 contains an Open Redirect vulnerability. Legacy UI fields can be used to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52219</link><description>SelectZero SelectZero Data Observability Platform before 2025.5.2 contains an Open Redirect vulnerability. Legacy UI fields can be used to create arbitrary external links via HTML Injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29992 | Mahara before 24.04.9 exposes database connection information if the database becomes unreachable, e.g., due to the database server being te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29992</link><description>Mahara before 24.04.9 exposes database connection information if the database becomes unreachable, e.g., due to the database server being temporarily down or too busy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45753 | In Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4, the external RSS feed block can cause XSS if the external feed XML has a malicious value for the link attribu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45753</link><description>In Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4, the external RSS feed block can cause XSS if the external feed XML has a malicious value for the link attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47853 | An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. Attackers may utilize escalation of privileges in certain cases when logging into Mah...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47853</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mahara 23.04.8 and 24.04.4. Attackers may utilize escalation of privileges in certain cases when logging into Mahara with Learning Tools Interoperability (LTI).</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9483 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 singlePortForwardAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9483</link><description>A flaw has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. Affected is the function singlePortForwardAdd of the file /goform/singlePortForwardAdd. This manipulation of the argument ruleName/schedule/inboundFilter causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55526 | n8n-workflows Main Commit ee25413 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via the download_workflow function within api_server.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55526</link><description>n8n-workflows Main Commit ee25413 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via the download_workflow function within api_server.py</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50753 | Mitrastar GPT-2741GNAC-N2 devices are provided with access through ssh into a restricted default shell.The command "deviceinfo show file" is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50753</link><description>Mitrastar GPT-2741GNAC-N2 devices are provided with access through ssh into a restricted default shell.The command "deviceinfo show file" is supposed to be used from restricted shell to show files and directories. By providing " /bin/sh" (quotes included) to the argument of this command will drop a root shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9481 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setIpv6 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9481</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function setIpv6 of the file /goform/setIpv6. The manipulation of the argument tunrd_Prefix leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9482 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 portRangeForwardAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9482</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This impacts the function portRangeForwardAdd of the file /goform/portRangeForwardAdd. The manipulation of the argument ruleName/schedule/inboundFilter/TCPPorts/UDPPorts results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8424 | Improper access control on the NetScaler Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8424</link><description>Improper access control on the NetScaler Management Interface in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when an attacker can get access to the appliance NSIP, Cluster Management IP or local GSLB Site IP or SNIP with Management Access</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38676 | iommu/amd: Avoid stack buffer overflow from kernel cmdline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38676</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iommu/amd: Avoid stack buffer overflow from kernel cmdline

While the kernel command line is considered trusted in most environments,
avoid writing 1 byte past the end of "acpiid" if the "str" argument is
maximum length.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7775 | Memory overflow vulnerability leading to Remote Code Execution and/or Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7775</link><description>Memory overflow vulnerability leading to Remote Code Execution and/or Denial of Service in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when NetScaler is configured as Gateway (VPN virtual server, ICA Proxy, CVPN, RDP Proxy) or AAA virtual server

(OR)

NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway 13.1, 14.1, 13.1-FIPS and NDcPP: LB virtual servers of type (HTTP, SSL or HTTP_QUIC) bound with IPv6 services or servicegroups bound with IPv6 servers 

(OR)

NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway 13.1, 14.1, 13.1-FIPS and NDcPP: LB virtual servers of type (HTTP, SSL or HTTP_QUIC) bound with DBS IPv6 services or servicegroups bound with IPv6 DBS servers

(OR)

CR virtual server with type HDX</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7776 | Memory overflow vulnerability leading to unpredictable or erroneous behavior and Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7776</link><description>Memory overflow vulnerability leading to unpredictable or erroneous behavior and Denial of Service in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when NetScaler is configured as a Gateway (VPN virtual server, ICA Proxy, CVPN, RDP Proxy) with PCoIP Profile bounded to it</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53811 | TCC Bypass via misconfigured Node fuses in Mosh-Pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53811</link><description>The configuration of Mosh-Pro on macOS, specifically the "RunAsNode" fuse enabled, allows a local attacker with unprivileged access to execute arbitrary code that inherits Mosh-Pro TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions. 
Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Accessing other resources beyond previously granted TCC permissions will prompt the user for approval in the name of Mosh-Pro, potentially disguising attacker's malicious intent. 

This issue was detected in 1.3.2 version of Mosh-Pro. Since authors did not respond to messages from CNA, patching status is unknown.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53813 | TCC Bypass via misconfigured Node fuses in Nozbe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53813</link><description>The configuration of Nozbe on macOS, specifically the "RunAsNode" fuse enabled, allows a local attacker with unprivileged access to execute arbitrary code that inherits Nozbe TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions. 
Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

This issue was fixed in version 2025.11 of Nozbe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8597 | Privilege Escalation via get-task-allow entitlement in MacVim.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8597</link><description>MacVim's configuration on macOS, specifically the presence of entitlement "com.apple.security.get-task-allow", allows local attackers with unprivileged access (e.g. via a malicious application) to attach a debugger, read or modify the process memory, inject code in the application's context despite being signed with Hardened Runtime and bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

According to Apple documentation, when a non-root user runs an app with the debugging tool entitlement, the system presents an authorization dialog asking for a system administrator's credentials. Since there is no prompt when the target process has "get-task-allow" entitlement, the presence of this entitlement was decided to be treated as a vulnerability because it removes one step needed to perform an attack.


This issue was fixed in build r181.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8700 | Privilege Escalation via get-task-allow entitlement in Invoice Ninja</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8700</link><description>Invoice Ninja's configuration on macOS, specifically the presence of entitlement "com.apple.security.get-task-allow", allows local attackers with unprivileged access (e.g. via a malicious application) to attach a debugger, read or modify the process memory, inject code in the application's context despite being signed with Hardened Runtime and bypass Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

According to Apple documentation, when a non-root user runs an app with the debugging tool entitlement, the system presents an authorization dialog asking for a system administrator's credentials. Since there is no prompt when the target process has "get-task-allow" entitlement, the presence of this entitlement was decided to be treated as a vulnerability because it removes one step needed to perform an attack.


This issue was fixed in version 5.0.175</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9190 | TCC Bypass via misconfigured Node fuses in Cursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9190</link><description>The configuration of Cursor on macOS, specifically the "RunAsNode" fuse enabled, allows a local attacker with unprivileged access to execute arbitrary code that inherits Cursor TCC (Transparency, Consent, and Control) permissions. 
Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Accessing other resources beyond previously granted TCC permissions will prompt the user for approval in the name of Cursor, potentially disguising attacker's malicious intent. 

This issue was detected in 15.4.1 version of Cursor. Project maintainers decided not to fix this issue, because a scenario including a local attacker falls outside their defined threat model.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44002 | Arbitrary File Creation via Symbolic Link leading to Denial-of-Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44002</link><description>Race Condition in the Directory Validation Logic in the TeamViewer Full Client and Host prior version 15.69 on Windows allows a local non-admin user to create arbitrary files with SYSTEM privileges, potentially leading to a denial-of-service condition, via symbolic link manipulation during directory verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1501 | Incorrect authorization for traces request/download in CMC before 25.1.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1501</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in the Request Trace and Download Trace functionalities of CMC before 25.1.0 due to a specific access restriction not being properly enforced for users with limited privileges. An authenticated user with limited privileges can request and download trace files due to improper access restrictions, potentially exposing unauthorized network data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48108 | WordPress School Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 93.2.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48108</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mojoomla School Management allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 93.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29901 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29901</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4933 and later</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6247 | WordPress Automatic Plugin - AI content generator and auto poster plugin &amp;lt;= 3.118.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6247</link><description>The WordPress Automatic Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.118.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on one of its functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update campaigns and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8860 | Tourfic &amp;lt;= 2.14.5 - Missing Authorization in Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8860</link><description>The Tourfic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the tf_order_status_email_resend_function,  tf_visitor_details_edit_function, tf_checkinout_details_edit_function, tf_order_status_edit_function, tf_order_bulk_action_edit_function, tf_remove_room_order_ids, and tf_delete_old_review_fields functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.5. This makes it possible for authenticated  attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to resend order status emails, update visitor/order details, edit check-in/out details, edit order status, perform bulk order status updates, remove room order IDs, and delete old review fields, respectively.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53419 | COMMGR Code Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53419</link><description>Delta Electronics COMMGR has Code Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53418 | COMMGR Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53418</link><description>Delta Electronics COMMGR has Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57704 | EIP Builder XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57704</link><description>Delta Electronics EIP Builder version 1.11 is vulnerable to a File Parsing XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41702 | egOS WebGUI Hard-Coded JWT Secret Enables Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41702</link><description>The JWT secret key is embedded in the egOS WebGUI backend and is readable to the default user. An unauthenticated remote attacker can generate valid HS256 tokens and bypass authentication/authorization due to the use of hard-coded cryptographic key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9476 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System editemployee_process.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9476</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Superadmin_Dashboard/process/editemployee_process.php. Such manipulation of the argument employee_file201 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9475 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System editemployee_process.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9475</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Admin_Dashboard/process/editemployee_process.php. This manipulation of the argument employee_file201 causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5931 | Dokan Pro &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Authenticated (Vendor+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5931</link><description>The Dokan Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.5. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password during a staff password reset. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with vendor-level access and above, to elevate their privilege to the level of a staff member and then change arbitrary user passwords, including those of administrators in order to gain access to their accounts. By default, the plugin allows customers to become vendors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9473 | SourceCodester Online Bank Management System feedback.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9473</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Online Bank Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /feedback.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9474 | Mihomo Party Socket sysproxy.ts enableSysProxy temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9474</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Mihomo Party up to 1.8.1 on macOS. Affected is the function enableSysProxy of the file src/main/sys/sysproxy.ts of the component Socket Handler. The manipulation results in creation of temporary file with insecure permissions. The attack requires a local approach. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9472 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_owner_utility.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9472</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /owner_utility/add_owner_utility.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9470 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_m_committee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9470</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /management/add_m_committee.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9471 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_maintenance_cost.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9471</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /maintenance/add_maintenance_cost.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9172 | Vibes &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via `resource` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9172</link><description>The Vibes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘resource’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9468 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9468</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /bill/add_bill.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9469 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System add_fund.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9469</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /fund/add_fund.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9444 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System delete_group_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9444</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/controller/delete_group_student.php. The manipulation of the argument batch_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9461 | diyhi bbs File Compression FilePackageManageAction.java information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9461</link><description>A weakness has been identified in diyhi bbs up to 6.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/cms/web/action/filePackage/FilePackageManageAction.java of the component File Compression Handler. This manipulation of the argument idGroup causes information disclosure. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9443 | Tenda CH22 editUserName formeditUserName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9443</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formeditUserName of the file /goform/editUserName. Executing manipulation of the argument new_account can lead to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8447 | Incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read-only access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8447</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed users with access to any repository to retrieve limited code content from another repository by creating a diff between the repositories. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker needed to know the name of a private repository along with its branches, tags, or commit SHAs that they could use to trigger compare/diff functionality and retrieve limited code without proper authorization. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.18, and was fixed in versions 3.14.17, 3.15.12, 3.16.8 and 3.17.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9438 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System add_student.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9438</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add_student.php. The manipulation of the argument address results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9439 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System edit_faculty.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9439</link><description>A weakness has been identified in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /rse/admin/edit_faculty.php?id=2. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9440 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System add_title.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9440</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_title.php. Such manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9433 | mtons mblog Admin Panel list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/user/list of the component Admin Panel. Performing manipulation of the argument Name results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9434 | 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System edit_title.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9434</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in 1000projects Online Project Report Submission and Evaluation System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_title.php?id=1. Executing manipulation of the argument desc can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9432 | mtons mblog Admin Panel list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9432</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/post/list of the component Admin Panel. Such manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9430 | mtons mblog update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9430</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/options/update. The manipulation of the argument input results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9431 | mtons mblog search cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9431</link><description>A flaw has been found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /search. This manipulation of the argument kw causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9429 | mtons mblog Post submit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9429</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /post/submit of the component Post Handler. The manipulation of the argument content/title/ leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9425 | itsourcecode Online Tour and Travel Management System enquiry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9425</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Online Tour and Travel Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /enquiry.php. Performing manipulation of the argument pid results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9426 | itsourcecode Online Tour and Travel Management System package.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9426</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Online Tour and Travel Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /package.php. Executing manipulation of the argument subcatid can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9423 | Campcodes Online Water Billing System editecex.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9423</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Water Billing System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /editecex.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9424 | Ruijie WS7204-A branch_import.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9424</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Ruijie WS7204-A 2017.06.15. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /itbox_pi/branch_import.php?a=branch_list. Such manipulation of the argument province leads to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9421 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addcomplain.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9421</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /complain/addcomplain.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9422 | oitcode samarium Team Image team cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9422</link><description>A vulnerability was found in oitcode samarium up to 0.9.6. This impacts an unknown function of the file /dashboard/team of the component Team Image Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57814 | request-filtering-agent SSRF Bypass via HTTPS Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57814</link><description>request-filtering-agent is an http(s).Agent implementation that blocks requests to Private/Reserved IP addresses. Versions 1.x.x and earlier contain a vulnerability where HTTPS requests to 127.0.0.1 bypass IP address filtering, while HTTP requests are correctly blocked. This allows attackers to potentially access internal HTTPS services running on localhost, bypassing the library's SSRF protection. The vulnerability is particularly dangerous when the application accepts user-controlled URLs and internal services are only protected by network-level restrictions. This vulnerability has been fixed in request-filtering-agent version 2.0.0. Users should upgrade to version 2.0.0 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9420 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addfloor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9420</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /floor/addfloor.php. Executing manipulation of the argument hdnid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57809 | XGrammar affected by Denial of Service by infinite recursion grammars</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57809</link><description>XGrammar is an open-source library for efficient, flexible, and portable structured generation. Prior to version 0.1.21, XGrammar has an infinite recursion issue in the grammar. This issue has been resolved in version 0.1.21.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57805 | The Scratch Channel&amp;#x27;s Publish Articles POST Request Can Upload Articles Without Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57805</link><description>The Scratch Channel is a news website. In versions 1 and 1.1, a POST request to the endpoint used to publish articles, can be used to post an article in any category with any date, regardless of who's logged in. This issue has been patched in version 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8627 | Unauthenticated Protocol Commands on TP-Link KP303</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8627</link><description>The TP-Link KP303 Smartplug can be issued unauthenticated protocol commands that may cause unintended power-off condition and potential information leak.

This issue affects TP-Link KP303 (US) Smartplug: before 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57804 | h2 allows HTTP Request Smuggling due to illegal characters in headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57804</link><description>h2 is a pure-Python implementation of a HTTP/2 protocol stack. Prior to version 4.3.0, an HTTP/2 request splitting vulnerability allows attackers to perform request smuggling attacks by injecting CRLF characters into headers. This occurs when servers downgrade HTTP/2 requests to HTTP/1.1 without properly validating header names/values, enabling attackers to manipulate request boundaries and bypass security controls. This issue has been patched in version 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9419 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addunit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9419</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /unit/addunit.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 21:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9418 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addowner.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9418</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /owner/addowner.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6188 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS, maliciously formed UDP packets with source port 3503 may be accepted by EOS. UDP Port 3503 is associated with LspPing Echo Reply. This can result in unexpected behaviors, especially for UDP based services that do n</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6188</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS, maliciously formed UDP packets with source port 3503 may be accepted by EOS. UDP Port 3503 is associated with LspPing Echo Reply. This can result in unexpected behaviors, especially for UDP based services that do not perform some form of authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3456 | On affected platforms running Arista EOS, the global common encryption key configuration may be logged in clear text, in local or remote accounting logs. Knowledge of both the encryption key and protocol specific encrypted secrets from the device running-c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3456</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista EOS, the global common encryption key configuration may be logged in clear text, in local or remote accounting logs. Knowledge of both the encryption key and protocol specific encrypted secrets from the device running-config could then be used to obtain protocol specific passwords in cases where symmetric passwords are required between devices with neighbor protocol relationships.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9417 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System addemployee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9417</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /employee/addemployee.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52130 | File upload vulnerability in WebErpMesv2 1.17 in the app/Http/Controllers/FactoryController.php controller. This flaw allows an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52130</link><description>File upload vulnerability in WebErpMesv2 1.17 in the app/Http/Controllers/FactoryController.php controller. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, including PHP scripts, which can be accessed via direct GET requests, potentially resulting in remote code execution (RCE) on the web server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9416 | oitcode samarium Pages Image webpage cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9416</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in oitcode samarium up to 0.9.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cms/webpage/ of the component Pages Image Handler. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9415 | GreenCMS index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9415</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in GreenCMS up to 2.3.0603. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?m=admin&amp;amp;c=media&amp;amp;a=fileconnect. The manipulation of the argument upload[] leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9414 | kalcaddle kodbox Download from Link serverDownload server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9414</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle kodbox 1.61. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /?explorer/upload/serverDownload of the component Download from Link Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument url results in server-side request forgery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9413 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go system_router.go SelectListByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9413</link><description>A flaw has been found in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. This impacts the function SelectListByPage of the file modules/system/system_router.go. This manipulation of the argument orderByColumn/isAsc causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57811 | Craft Potential Remote Code Execution via Twig SSTI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57811</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. From versions 4.0.0-RC1 to 4.16.5 and 5.0.0-RC1 to 5.8.6, there is a potential remote code execution vulnerability via Twig SSTI (Server-Side Template Injection). This is a follow-up to CVE-2024-52293. This vulnerability has been patched in versions 4.16.6 and 5.8.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50383 | alextselegidis Easy!Appointments v1.5.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the order_by parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50383</link><description>alextselegidis Easy!Appointments v1.5.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the order_by parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57802 | Airlink&amp;#x27;s Daemon Symlink Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57802</link><description>Airlink's Daemon interfaces with Docker and the Panel to provide secure access for controlling instances via the Panel. In version 1.0.0, an attacker with access to the affected container can create symbolic links inside the mounted directory (/app/data). Because the container bind-mounts an arbitrary host path, these symlinks can point to sensitive locations on the host filesystem. When the application or other processes follow these symlinks, the attacker can gain unauthorized read access to host files outside the container. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9412 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go DictDataDao.go SelectListByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9412</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. This affects the function SelectListByPage of the file modules/system/dao/DictDataDao.go. The manipulation of the argument orderByColumn/isAsc results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9411 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go LoginInforService.go SelectPageList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9411</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. The impacted element is the function SelectPageList of the file modules/system/service/LoginInforService.go. The manipulation of the argument isAsc leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57772 | Dataease H2 JDBC RCE Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57772</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.12, there is a H2 JDBC RCE bypass in DataEase. If the JDBC URL meets criteria, the getJdbcUrl method is returned, which acts as the getter for the JdbcUrl parameter provided. This bypasses H2's filtering logic and returns the H2 JDBC URL, allowing the "driver":"org.h2.Driver" to specify the H2 driver for the JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 2.10.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50722 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in sparkshop v.1.1.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Common.php component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50722</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in sparkshop v.1.1.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Common.php component</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29420 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a directory traversal vulnerability in the getThemeFilesByName function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29420</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has a directory traversal vulnerability in the getThemeFilesByName function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29421 | PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the getThemeFileContent function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29421</link><description>PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the getThemeFileContent function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57773 | Dataease DB2 Aspectweaver Deserialization Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57773</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.12, because DB2 parameters are not filtered, a JNDI injection attack can be directly launched. JNDI triggers an AspectJWeaver deserialization attack, writing to various files. This vulnerability requires commons-collections 4.x and aspectjweaver-1.9.22.jar. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 2.10.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9410 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go GenTableDao.go SelectListByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9410</link><description>A weakness has been identified in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. The affected element is the function SelectListByPage of the file modules/system/dao/GenTableDao.go. Executing manipulation of the argument isAsc/orderByColumn can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53120 | Securden Unified PAM Path Traversal In File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53120</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in unauthenticated upload functionality allows a malicious actor to upload binaries and scripts to the server’s configuration and web root directories, achieving remote code execution on the Unified PAM server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57760 | Langflow Vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via CLI Superuser Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57760</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Langflow containers where an authenticated user with RCE access can invoke the internal CLI command langflow superuser to create a new administrative user. This results in full superuser access, even if the user initially registered through the UI as a regular (non-admin) account. A patched version has not been made public at this time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6737 | Securden Unified PAM Shared SSH Key and Cloud Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6737</link><description>Securden’s Unified PAM Remote Vendor Gateway access portal shares infrastructure and access tokens across multiple tenants. A malicious actor can obtain authentication material and access the gateway server with low-privilege permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53118 | Securden Unified PAM Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53118</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists which allows an unauthenticated attacker to control administrator backup functions, leading to compromise of passwords, secrets, and application session tokens stored by the Unified PAM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53119 | Securden Unified PAM Unauthenticated Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53119</link><description>An unauthenticated unrestricted file upload vulnerability allows an attacker to upload malicious binaries and scripts to the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9409 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go CommonController.go DownloadUpload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9409</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in lostvip-com ruoyi-go up to 2.1. Impacted is the function DownloadTmp/DownloadUpload of the file modules/system/controller/CommonController.go. Performing manipulation of the argument fileName results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3478 | OpenText Enterprise Security Manager Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3478</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in OpenText Enterprise Security Manager. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55574 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in docmost v.0.21.0 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55574</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in docmost v.0.21.0 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55301 | The Scratch Channel Allows Username Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55301</link><description>The Scratch Channel is a news website. In version 1, it is possible to go to application in devtools and click local storage to edit the account's username locally. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55575 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SMM Panel 3.1 allowing remote attackers to gain sensitive information via a crafted HTTP request with action=...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55575</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in SMM Panel 3.1 allowing remote attackers to gain sensitive information via a crafted HTTP request with action=service_detail.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29523 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping6 function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29523</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping6 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55409 | FoxCMS 1.2.6, there is a Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in /index.php/article. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55409</link><description>FoxCMS 1.2.6, there is a Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in /index.php/article. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50900 | An issue was discovered in getrebuild/rebuild 4.0.4. The affected source code class is com.rebuild.web.RebuildWebInterceptor, and the affect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50900</link><description>An issue was discovered in getrebuild/rebuild 4.0.4. The affected source code class is com.rebuild.web.RebuildWebInterceptor, and the affected function is preHandle In the filter code, use CodecUtils.urlDecode(request.getRequestURI()) to obtain the URL-decoded request path, and then determine whether the path endsWith /error. If so, execute return true to skip this Interceptor. Else, redirect to /user/login api. Allowing unauthenticated attackers to gain sensitive information or escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56212 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in add-doctor.php via the docname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56212</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in add-doctor.php via the docname parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56214 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in index.php via the username parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56214</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in index.php via the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5302 | Denial of Service (DOS) in JSONReader in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5302</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the JSONReader component of the run-llama/llama_index repository, specifically in version v0.12.37. The vulnerability is caused by uncontrolled recursion when parsing deeply nested JSON files, which can lead to Python hitting its maximum recursion depth limit. This results in high resource consumption and potential crashes of the Python process. The issue is resolved in version 0.12.38.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56215 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in contact.php via the pagetitle parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56215</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in contact.php via the pagetitle parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56216 | phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in about-us.php via the pagetitle parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56216</link><description>phpgurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in about-us.php via the pagetitle parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46412 | Incorrect access control in the prehandle function of Rebuild v3.7.7 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46412</link><description>Incorrect access control in the prehandle function of Rebuild v3.7.7 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted GET request sent to /commons/ip-location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44179 | Hitron CGNF-TWN 3.1.1.43-TWN-pre3 contains a command injection vulnerability in the telnet service. The issue arises due to improper input v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44179</link><description>Hitron CGNF-TWN 3.1.1.43-TWN-pre3 contains a command injection vulnerability in the telnet service. The issue arises due to improper input validation within the telnet command handling mechanism. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands through the telnet interface when prompted for inputs or commands. Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution (RCE) under the privileges of the telnet user, potentially allowing unauthorized access to system settings and sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46413 | Rebuild v3.7.7 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the type parameter in the com.rebuild.web.admin.rbstore.RB...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46413</link><description>Rebuild v3.7.7 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the type parameter in the com.rebuild.web.admin.rbstore.RBStoreController#loadDataIndex method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29520 | Incorrect access control in the Maintenance module of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29520</link><description>Incorrect access control in the Maintenance module of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily change the high-privileged account passwords and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29521 | Insecure default credentials for the Adminsitrator account of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29521</link><description>Insecure default credentials for the Adminsitrator account of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to escalate privileges via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29522 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29522</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ping function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29524 | Incorrect access control in the component /cgi-bin/system_diagnostic_main.asp of DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 allows attackers to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29524</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /cgi-bin/system_diagnostic_main.asp of DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 allows attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29525 | DASAN GPON ONU H660WM OS version H660WMR210825 Hardware version DS-E5-583-A1 was discovered to contain insecure default credentials in the m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29525</link><description>DASAN GPON ONU H660WM OS version H660WMR210825 Hardware version DS-E5-583-A1 was discovered to contain insecure default credentials in the modem's control panel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44178 | DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 is susceptible to improper access control under its default settings. Attackers can exploit this vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44178</link><description>DASAN GPON ONU H660WM H660WMR210825 is susceptible to improper access control under its default settings. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information and modify its configuration via the UPnP protocol WAN sides without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51281 | D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the en`, `val and id parameters in the qj_asp function. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51281</link><description>D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the en`, `val and id parameters in the qj_asp function. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by sending crafted GET requests with overly long values for these parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29519 | A command injection vulnerability in the EXE parameter of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29519</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the EXE parameter of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32468 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32468</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .bmp file, an integer overflow can be made to occur when calculating the stride for decoding. Afterwards, this will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when decoding the image which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35984 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35984</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding the image data from a specially crafted .pcx file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46407 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Palette Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46407</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 Palette Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .bmp file, an integer overflow can be made to occur which will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when reading the palette from the image. These conditions can allow for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50129 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50129</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decoding the image data from a specially crafted .tga file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52456 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the WebP Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52456</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the WebP Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .webp animation an integer overflow can be made to occur when calculating the stride for decoding. Afterwards, this will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when decoding the image which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52930 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52930</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the BMPv3 RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressing the image data from a specially crafted .bmp file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53085 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53085</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD RLE Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When decompressing the image data from a specially crafted .psd file, a heap-based buffer overflow can occur which allows for remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53510 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53510</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PSD Image Decoding functionality of the SAIL Image Decoding Library v0.9.8. When loading a specially crafted .psd file, an integer overflow can be made to occur when calculating the stride for decoding. Afterwards, this will cause a heap-based buffer to overflow when decoding the image which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker will need to convince the library to read a file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26467 | Apache Cassandra: User with MODIFY permission on ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser via unsafe actions (4.0.16 only)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26467</link><description>Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions vulnerability in Apache Cassandra. An user with MODIFY permission ON ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser within a targeted Cassandra cluster via unsafe actions to a system resource. Operators granting data MODIFY permission on all keyspaces on affected versions should review data access rules for potential breaches.



This issue affects Apache Cassandra 3.0.30, 3.11.17, 4.0.16, 4.1.7, 5.0.2, but this advisory is only for 4.0.16 because the fix to CVE-2025-23015 was incorrectly applied to 4.0.16, so that version is still affected.

Users in the 4.0 series are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.17 which fixes the issue. Users from 3.0, 3.11, 4.1 and 5.0 series should follow recommendation from CVE-2025-23015.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29514 | Incorrect access control in the config.xgi function of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to downloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29514</link><description>Incorrect access control in the config.xgi function of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to download the configuration file via providing a crafted web request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29515 | Incorrect access control in the DELT_file.xgi endpoint of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to modi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29515</link><description>Incorrect access control in the DELT_file.xgi endpoint of D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 allows attackers to modify arbitrary settings within the device's XML database, including the administrator’s password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29516 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the backup functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29516</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the backup function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29517 | D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the traceroute6 fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29517</link><description>D-Link DSL-7740C with firmware DSL7740C.V6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the traceroute6 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54370 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to SSRF when reading and displaying a processed HTML document in the browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54370</link><description>PhpOffice/PhpSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Prior to versions 1.30.0, 2.1.12, 2.4.0, 3.10.0, and 5.0.0, SSRF can occur when a processed HTML document is read and displayed in the browser. The vulnerability lies in the setPath method of the PhpOffice\PhpSpreadsheet\Worksheet\Drawing class, where a crafted string from the user is passed to the HTML reader. This issue has been patched in versions 1.30.0, 2.1.12, 2.4.0, 3.10.0, and 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46411 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46411</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48005 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the RHS2000 parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Bran...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48005</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the RHS2000 parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted RHS2000 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52461 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52461</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted .nex file can lead to an information leak. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52581 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the GDF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52581</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the GDF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted GDF file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53511 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53511</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53518 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the ABF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53518</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the ABF parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted ABF file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53557 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53557</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53853 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ISHNE parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53853</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ISHNE parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted ISHNE ECG annotations file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54462 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54462</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Nex parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted .nex file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54480 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54480</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8719 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 0:

				if (tag==0) {
					if (len!=1) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag0 incorrect length %i!=1\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);
				}</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54481 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54481</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8744 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 3:

				else if (tag==3) {
					// character code
					char v[17];		// [1]
					if (len&gt;16) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag2 incorrect length %i&gt;16\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;v,1,len,hdr);
					v[len]  = 0;

In this case, the overflowed buffer is the newly-declared `v` \[1\] instead of `buf`. Since `v` is only 17 bytes large, much smaller values of `len` (even those encoded using a single octet) can trigger an overflow in this code path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54482 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54482</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8751 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 4:

				else if (tag==4) {
					// SPR
					if (len&gt;4) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag4 incorrect length %i&gt;4\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54483 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54483</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8759 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 5:

				else if (tag==5)     //0x05: number of channels
				{
					uint16_t oldNS=hdr-&gt;NS;
					if (len&gt;4) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag5 incorrect length %i&gt;4\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54484 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54484</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8779 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 6:

				else if (tag==6) 	// 0x06 "number of sequences"
				{
					// NRec
					if (len&gt;4) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag6 incorrect length %i&gt;4\n",len);
					curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54485 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54485</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8785 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 8:

                else if (tag==8) {
                    if (len&gt;2) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag8 incorrect length %i&gt;2\n",len);
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54486 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54486</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8824 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 11:

                else if (tag==11)    //0x0B
                {
                    // Fs
                    if (len&gt;6) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag11 incorrect length %i&gt;6\n",len);
                    double  fval;
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54487 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54487</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8842 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 12:

                else if (tag==12)    //0x0C
                {
                    // sampling resolution
                    if (len&gt;6) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag12 incorrect length %i&gt;6\n",len);
                    val32   = 0;
                    int8_t  v8;
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;UnitCode,1,1,hdr);
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;v8,1,1,hdr);
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len-2,hdr);

In addition to values of `len` greater than 130 triggering a buffer overflow, a value of `len` smaller than 2 will also trigger a buffer overflow due to an integer underflow when computing `len-2` in this code path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54488 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54488</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8850 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 13:

                else if (tag==13) {
                    if (len&gt;8) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag13 incorrect length %i&gt;8\n",len);
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54489 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54489</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 8970 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 63:

                else if (tag==63) {
                    uint8_t tag2=255, len2=255;

                    count = 0;
                    while ((count&lt;len) &amp;&amp; !(FlagInfiniteLength &amp;&amp; len2==0 &amp;&amp; tag2==0)){
                        curPos += ifread(&amp;tag2,1,1,hdr);
                        curPos += ifread(&amp;len2,1,1,hdr);
                        if (VERBOSE_LEVEL==9)
                            fprintf(stdout,"MFER: tag=%3i chan=%2i len=%-4i tag2=%3i len2=%3i curPos=%i %li count=%4i\n",tag,chan,len,tag2,len2,curPos,iftell(hdr),(int)count);

                        if (FlagInfiniteLength &amp;&amp; len2==0 &amp;&amp; tag2==0) break;

                        count  += (2+len2);
                        curPos += ifread(&amp;buf,1,len2,hdr);

Here, the number of bytes read is not the Data Length decoded from the current frame in the file (`len`) but rather is a new length contained in a single octet read from the same input file (`len2`). Despite this, a stack-based buffer overflow condition can still occur, as the destination buffer is still `buf`, which has a size of only 128 bytes, while `len2` can be as large as 255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54490 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54490</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9090 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 64:

                else if (tag==64)     //0x40
                {
                    // preamble
                    char tmp[256];  // [1]
                    curPos += ifread(tmp,1,len,hdr);

In this case, the overflowed buffer is the newly-declared `tmp` \[1\] instead of `buf`. While `tmp` is larger than `buf`, having a size of 256 bytes, a stack overflow can still occur in cases where `len` is encoded using multiple octets and is greater than 256.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54491 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54491</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9191 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 65:

                else if (tag==65)     //0x41: patient event
                {
                    // event table

                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54492 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54492</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9141 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 67:

                else if (tag==67)     //0x43: Sample skew
                {
                    int skew=0;     // [1]
                    curPos += ifread(&amp;amp;skew, 1, len,hdr);

In this case, the address of the newly-defined integer `skew` \[1\] is overflowed instead of `buf`. This means a stack overflow can occur using much smaller values of `len` in this code path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54493 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54493</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9184 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 131:

                else if (tag==131)    //0x83
                {
                    // Patient Age
                    if (len!=7) fprintf(stderr,"Warning MFER tag131 incorrect length %i!=7\n",len);
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54494 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54494</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MFER parsing functionality of The Biosig Project libbiosig 3.9.0 and Master Branch (35a819fa). A specially crafted MFER file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.This vulnerability manifests on line 9205 of biosig.c on the current master branch (35a819fa), when the Tag is 133:

                else if (tag==133)    //0x85
                {
                    curPos += ifread(buf,1,len,hdr);</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45968 | An issue in System PDV v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the hash parameter in a URL. The application contai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45968</link><description>An issue in System PDV v1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the hash parameter in a URL. The application contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability, which occurs due to a lack of proper authorization checks when accessing objects referenced by this parameter. This allows direct access to other users' data or internal resources without proper permission. Successful exploitation of this flaw may result in the exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47799 | Mahara before 22.10.4 and 23.x before 23.04.4 allows information disclosure if the experimental HTML bulk export is used via the administrat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47799</link><description>Mahara before 22.10.4 and 23.x before 23.04.4 allows information disclosure if the experimental HTML bulk export is used via the administration interface or via the CLI, and the resulting export files are given to the account holders. They may contain images of other account holders because the cache is not cleared after the files of one account are exported.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39923 | An issue was discovered in Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.2 and 23.04 before 23.04.7. The About, Contact, and Help footer links can be set up to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39923</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mahara 24.04 before 24.04.2 and 23.04 before 23.04.7. The About, Contact, and Help footer links can be set up to be vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to not sanitising the values. These links can only be set up by an admin but are clickable by any logged-in person.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43960 | Adminer 4.8.1, when using Monolog for logging, allows a Denial of Service (memory consumption) via a crafted serialized payload (e.g., using...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43960</link><description>Adminer 4.8.1, when using Monolog for logging, allows a Denial of Service (memory consumption) via a crafted serialized payload (e.g., using s:1000000000), leading to a PHP Object Injection issue. Remote, unauthenticated attackers can trigger this by sending a malicious serialized object, which forces excessive memory usage, rendering Adminer’s interface unresponsive and causing a server-level DoS. While the server may recover after several minutes, multiple simultaneous requests can cause a complete crash requiring manual intervention.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9407 | mtons mblog profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9407</link><description>A flaw has been found in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /settings/profile. Executing manipulation of the argument signature can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48303 | WordPress Post Type Converter plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48303</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kevin Langley Jr. Post Type Converter allows Cross-Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Post Type Converter: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 10:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8562 | Custom Query Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Path Traversal via lens Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8562</link><description>The Custom Query Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.0 via the 'lens' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 09:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7426 | MINOVA TTA Information Disclosure and Credential Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7426</link><description>Information disclosure and exposure of authentication FTP credentials over the debug port 1604 in the MINOVA TTA service. This allows unauthenticated remote access to an active FTP account containing sensitive internal data and import structures. In environments where this FTP server is part of automated business processes (e.g. EDI or data integration), this could lead to data manipulation, extraction, or abuse.  Debug ports 1602, 1603 and 1636 also expose service architecture information and system activity logs</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5191 | Unquoted Search Path Vulnerability in the Utility for Industrial Computers (Windows)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5191</link><description>An Unquoted Search Path vulnerability has been identified in the utility for Moxa’s industrial computers (Windows). Due to the unquoted path configuration in the SerialInterfaceService.exe utility, a local attacker with limited privileges could place a malicious executable in a higher-priority directory within the search path. When the Serial Interface service starts, the malicious executable could be run with SYSTEM privileges. Successful exploitation could allow privilege escalation or enable an attacker to maintain persistence on the affected system. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality, integrity, or availability within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 08:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9118 | Dataform Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9118</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in the NPM package installation process of Google Cloud Dataform allows a remote attacker to read and write files in other customers' repositories via a maliciously crafted package.json file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54300 | Extension - norrnext.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54300</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla was discovered. The SVG upload feature does not sanitize uploads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54301 | Extension - norrnext.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54301</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in Quantum Manager component 1.0.0-3.2.0 for Joomla was discovered. File names are not properly escaped.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8997 | OpenText Enterprise Security Manager Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8997</link><description>An Information Exposure vulnerability has been identified in OpenText Enterprise Security Manager. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5514 | Denial-of-Service(DoS) Vulnerability in Web server function on MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5514</link><description>Improper Handling of Length Parameter Inconsistency vulnerability in web server function on Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to delay the processing of the web server function and prevent legitimate users from utilizing the web server function, by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9406 | xuhuisheng lemon CmsArticleController.java uploadImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9406</link><description>A weakness has been identified in xuhuisheng lemon up to 1.13.0. This affects the function uploadImage of the file CmsArticleController.java of the component com.mossle.cms.web.CmsArticleController.uploadImage. This manipulation of the argument Upload causes unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9405 | Open5GS gmm-sm.c gmm_state_exception assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9405</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. The impacted element is the function gmm_state_exception of the file src/amf/gmm-sm.c. The manipulation results in reachable assertion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The patch is identified as 8e5fed16114f2f5e40bee1b161914b592b2b7b8f. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9404 | Scada-LTS Folder pointHierarchySLTS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9404</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pointHierarchySLTS of the component Folder Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9403 | jqlang jq JSON jq_test.c run_jq_tests assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9403</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jqlang jq up to 1.6. Impacted is the function run_jq_tests of the file jq_test.c of the component JSON Parser. Executing manipulation can lead to reachable assertion. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Other versions might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9402 | HuangDou UTCMS Config update.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9402</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HuangDou UTCMS 9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file app/modules/ut-frame/admin/update.php of the component Config Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument UPDATEURL results in server-side request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9401 | HuangDou UTCMS Login login.php comparison</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9401</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HuangDou UTCMS 9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file app/modules/ut-frame/admin/login.php of the component Login. Such manipulation of the argument code leads to incorrect comparison. The attack can be executed remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9400 | YiFang CMS P_file.php mergeMultipartUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9400</link><description>A flaw has been found in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. This affects the function mergeMultipartUpload of the file app/utils/base/plugin/P_file.php. This manipulation of the argument File causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9399 | YiFang CMS L_tool.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9399</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file app/logic/L_tool.php. The manipulation of the argument new_url results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9398 | YiFang CMS Migrate.php exportInstallTable information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9398</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function exportInstallTable of the file app/utils/base/database/Migrate.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 23:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9397 | givanz Vvveb media.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9397</link><description>A weakness has been identified in givanz Vvveb up to 1.0.7.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/traits/media.php. Executing manipulation of the argument files[] can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue. The code maintainer explains, that "[he] fixed the code to remove this vulnerability and will make a new release".</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 23:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9396 | ckolivas lrzip strtol_l.c __GI_____strtol_l_internal null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9396</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in ckolivas lrzip up to 0.651. This impacts the function __GI_____strtol_l_internal of the file strtol_l.c. Performing manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 22:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9395 | wangsongyan wblog backup.go RestorePost server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9395</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in wangsongyan wblog 0.0.1. This affects the function RestorePost of the file backup.go. Such manipulation of the argument fileName leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 22:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9394 | PoDoFo PDF Dictionary PdfTokenizer.cpp DetermineDataType use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9394</link><description>A flaw has been found in PoDoFo 1.1.0-dev. This issue affects the function PdfTokenizer::DetermineDataType of the file src/podofo/main/PdfTokenizer.cpp of the component PDF Dictionary Parser. Executing manipulation can lead to use after free. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called 22d16cb142f293bf956f66a4d399cdd65576d36c. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9393 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 addStaProfile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9393</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This vulnerability affects the function addStaProfile of the file /goform/addStaProfile. Performing manipulation of the argument profile_name/Ssid/wep_key_1/wep_key_2/wep_key_3/wep_key_4/wep_key_length/wep_default_key/cipher/passphrase results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9392 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 qosClassifier stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9392</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function qosClassifier of the file /goform/qosClassifier. Such manipulation of the argument dir/sFromPort/sToPort/dFromPort/dToPort/protocol/layer7/dscp/remark_dscp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 15:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9391 | Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP com.artery.workflow.ServiceImpl getFieldValue sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9391</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP up to 11.0. Affected by this issue is the function getFieldValue of the component com.artery.workflow.ServiceImpl. This manipulation of the argument sql causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9390 | vim xxd xxd.c main buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9390</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in vim up to 9.1.1615. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file src/xxd/xxd.c of the component xxd. The manipulation results in buffer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Upgrading to version 9.1.1616 addresses this issue. The patch is identified as eeef7c77436a78cd27047b0f5fa6925d56de3cb0. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9389 | vim memmove-vec-unaligned-erms.S __memmove_avx_unaligned_erms memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9389</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in vim 9.1.0000. Affected is the function __memmove_avx_unaligned_erms of the file memmove-vec-unaligned-erms.S. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Some users are not able to reproduce this. One of the users mentions that this appears not to be working, "when coloring is turned on".</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9388 | Scada-LTS watch_list.shtm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9388</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file watch_list.shtm. Executing manipulation of the argument Name can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9387 | DCN DCME-720 Web Management Backend ip_block.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9387</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DCN DCME-720 9.1.5.11. This affects an unknown function of the file /usr/local/www/function/audit/newstatistics/ip_block.php of the component Web Management Backend. Performing manipulation of the argument ip results in os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Other products might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9386 | appneta tcpreplay tcprewrite get.c get_l2len_protocol use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9386</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in appneta tcpreplay up to 4.5.1. The impacted element is the function get_l2len_protocol of the file get.c of the component tcprewrite. Such manipulation leads to use after free. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.2-beta3 is sufficient to resolve this issue. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 11:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9385 | appneta tcpreplay tcprewrite edit_packet.c fix_ipv6_checksums use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9385</link><description>A flaw has been found in appneta tcpreplay up to 4.5.1. The affected element is the function fix_ipv6_checksums of the file edit_packet.c of the component tcprewrite. This manipulation causes use after free. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.2-beta3 is sufficient to fix this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9384 | appneta tcpreplay parse_args.c tcpedit_post_args null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9384</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in appneta tcpreplay up to 4.5.1. Impacted is the function tcpedit_post_args of the file /src/tcpedit/parse_args.c. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.2-beta2 is recommended to address this issue. Upgrading the affected component is advised. The vendor explains, that he was "[a]ble to reproduce in 6fcbf03 but not in 4.5.2-beta2".</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9383 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera passwd crypt weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9383</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. This issue affects the function crypt of the file /etc/passwd. The manipulation leads to use of weak hash. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 09:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9382 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera Telnet Sevice s1_rf_test_config backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9382</link><description>A weakness has been identified in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file s1_rf_test_config of the component Telnet Sevice. Executing manipulation can lead to backdoor. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. This attack is characterized by high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9381 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera wpa_supplicant.conf information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9381</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. This affects an unknown part of the file /tmp/wpa_supplicant.conf. Performing manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be carried out on the physical device. The attack's complexity is rated as high. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9380 | FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera Firmware passwd hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9380</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in FNKvision Y215 CCTV Camera 10.194.120.40. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /etc/passwd of the component Firmware. Such manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9379 | Belkin AX1800 Firmware Update data authenticity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9379</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Belkin AX1800 1.1.00.016. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Firmware Update Handler. This manipulation causes insufficient verification of data authenticity. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8208 | Spexo Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8208</link><description>The Spexo Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36157 | IBM Jazz Foundation incorrect authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36157</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2 to 7.0.2 iFix035, 7.0.3 to 7.0.3 iFix018, and 7.1.0 to 7.1.0 iFix004 could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to update server property files that would allow them to perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36174 | IBM Integrated Analytics System file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36174</link><description>IBM Integrated Analytics System 1.0.0.0 through 1.0.30.0 could allow an authenticated user to upload a file with dangerous types that could be executed by another user if opened.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>