<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:45:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-1375 | Event post &amp;lt;= 5.9.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1375</link><description>The Event post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized bulk metadata update due to a missing nonce check on the save_bulkdatas function in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update post_meta_data via a forged request, granted they can trick a logged-in user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6677 | Privilege escalation in uberAgent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6677</link><description>Privilege escalation in uberAgent</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6396 | Arbitrary File Overwrite and Data Exfiltration in aimhubio/aim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6396</link><description>Path Traversal: '\..\filename' in aimhubio/aim</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6392 | Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv &amp;lt;= 7.2.7 - Authenticated(Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6392</link><description>The Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings modification due to missing capability checks on the plugin functions in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the connected Sirv account to an attacker-controlled one.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6468 | Vault Vulnerable to Denial of Service When Setting a Proxy Protocol Behavior</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6468</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise did not properly handle requests originating from unauthorized IP addresses when the TCP listener option, proxy_protocol_behavior, was set to deny_unauthorized. When receiving a request from a source IP address that was not listed in proxy_protocol_authorized_addrs, the Vault API server would shut down and no longer respond to any HTTP requests, potentially resulting in denial of service.

While this bug also affected versions of Vault up to 1.17.1 and 1.16.5, a separate regression in those release series did not allow Vault operators to configure the deny_unauthorized option, thus not allowing the conditions for the denial of service to occur.

Fixed in Vault and Vault Enterprise 1.17.2, 1.16.6, and 1.15.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-29946 | NATS.io NATS Server before 2.8.2 and Streaming Server before 0.24.6 could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions, caused by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29946</link><description>NATS.io NATS Server before 2.8.2 and Streaming Server before 0.24.6 could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions, caused by the failure to enforce negative user permissions in one scenario. By using a queue subscription on the wildcard, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to allow denied subjects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36435 | An issue was discovered on Supermicro BMC firmware in select X11, X12, H12, B12, X13, H13, and B13 motherboards (and CMM6 modules). An unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36435</link><description>An issue was discovered on Supermicro BMC firmware in select X11, X12, H12, B12, X13, H13, and B13 motherboards (and CMM6 modules). An unauthenticated user can post crafted data to the interface that triggers a stack buffer overflow, and may lead to arbitrary remote code execution on a BMC.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6531 | XSS in Bootstrap carousel component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6531</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bootstrap that exposes users to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. The issue is present in the carousel component, where the data-slide and data-slide-to attributes can be exploited through the href attribute of an &lt;a&gt; tag due to inadequate sanitization. This vulnerability could potentially enable attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript within the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6484 | XSS in Bootstrap carousel component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6484</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bootstrap that exposes users to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. The issue is present in the carousel component, where the data-slide and data-slide-to attributes can be exploited through the href attribute of an &lt;a&gt; tag due to inadequate sanitization. This vulnerability could potentially enable attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript within the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6485 | XSS in Bootstrap button component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6485</link><description>A security vulnerability has been discovered in bootstrap that could enable Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. The vulnerability is associated with the data-loading-text attribute within the button plugin. This vulnerability can be exploited by injecting malicious JavaScript code into the attribute, which would then be executed when the button's loading state is triggered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39550 | Junos OS: MX Series with SPC3 line card: Port flaps causes rtlogd memory leak leading to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39550</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the rtlogd process of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series with SPC3 allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger internal events cause ( which can be done by repeated port flaps) to cause a slow memory leak, ultimately leading to a Denial of Service (DoS). 

Memory can only be recovered by manually restarting rtlogd process. 
The memory usage can be monitored using the below command.

    user@host&gt; show system processes extensive | match rtlog 



This issue affects Junos OS on MX Series with SPC3 line card: 



  *  from 21.2R3 before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4R2 before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S1, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39551 | Junos OS: SRX Series and MX Series with SPC3 and MS-MPC/MIC: Receipt of specific packets in H.323 ALG causes traffic drop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39551</link><description>An Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in the H.323 ALG (Application Layer Gateway) of  Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series and MX Series with SPC3 and MS-MPC/MIC, allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker to send specific packets causing traffic loss leading to Denial of Service (DoS). 

Continued receipt and processing of these specific packets will sustain the Denial of Service condition.

The memory usage can be monitored using the below command.

  user@host&gt; show usp memory segment sha data objcache jsf 
This issue affects SRX Series and MX Series with SPC3 and MS-MPC/MIC: 

  *   20.4 before 20.4R3-S10, 
  *   21.2 before 21.2R3-S6, 
  *   21.3 before 21.3R3-S5, 
  *   21.4 before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *   22.1 before 22.1R3-S4, 
  *   22.2 before 22.2R3-S2, 
  *   22.3 before 22.3R3-S1, 
  *   22.4 before 22.4R3, 
  *   23.2 before 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39552 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Malformed BGP UPDATE causes RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39552</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (RPD) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a network based, unauthenticated attacker to cause the RPD process to crash leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

When a malformed BGP UPDATE packet is received over an established BGP session, RPD crashes and restarts.

Continuous receipt of the malformed BGP UPDATE messages will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition for impacted devices.

This issue affects eBGP and iBGP, in both IPv4 and IPv6 implementations.  This issue requires a remote attacker to have at least one established BGP session.

This issue affects:
 
Juniper Networks Junos OS:
  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S6;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R2.



Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved:
  *  All versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3-EVO versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4-EVO versions earlier than 21.4R3-S8;
  *  22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3-EVO versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
  *  22.4-EVO versions earlier than 22.4R3;
  *  23.2-EVO versions earlier than 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39553 | Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of arbitrary data when sampling service is enabled, leads to partial Denial of Service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39553</link><description>An Exposure of Resource to Wrong Sphere vulnerability in the sampling service of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker to send arbitrary data to the device, which leads msvcsd process to crash with limited availability impacting Denial of Service (DoS) and allows unauthorized network access to the device, potentially impacting system integrity.

This issue only happens when inline jflow is configured.

This does not impact any forwarding traffic. The impacted services MSVCS-DB app crashes momentarily and recovers by itself. 

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved: 
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S7-EVO; 
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3-EVO;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2-EVO;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3-EVO;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6681 | witmy my-springsecurity-plus dept sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6681</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in witmy my-springsecurity-plus up to 2024-07-04. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/dept. The manipulation of the argument params.dataScope leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39541 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Inconsistent information in the TE database can lead to an rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39541</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

When conflicting information (IP or ISO addresses) about a node is added to the Traffic Engineering (TE) database and then a subsequent operation attempts to process these, rpd will crash and restart.

This issue affects:

Junos OS:



  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3-S1,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2, 
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R1-S1, 23.4R2, 




This issue does not affect Junos OS versions earlier than 22.4R1.

Junos OS Evolved:



  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R3-S2-EVO,
  *  23.2-EVO versions before 23.2R2-EVO,
  *  23.4-EVO versions before 23.4R1-S1-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO,






This issue does not affect Junos OS Evolved versions earlier than 

before 22.4R1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39542 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A malformed CFM packet or specific transit traffic leads to FPC crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39542</link><description>An Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series with MPC10/11 or LC9600, MX304, and Junos OS Evolved on ACX Series and PTX Series allows an unauthenticated, network based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

This issue can occur in two scenarios:

1. If a device, which is configured with SFLOW and ECMP, receives specific valid transit traffic, which is subject to sampling, the packetio process crashes, which in turn leads to an evo-aftman crash and causes the FPC to stop working until it is restarted. (This scenario is only applicable to PTX but not to ACX or MX.)

2. If a device receives a malformed CFM packet on an interface configured with CFM, the packetio process crashes, which in turn leads to an evo-aftman crash and causes the FPC to stop working until it is restarted. Please note that the CVSS score is for the formally more severe issue 1.

The CVSS score for scenario 2. is: 6.5 (CVSS:3.1/AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H)




This issue affects Junos OS:



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S4,
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R2,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S2; 




Junos OS Evolved:




  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39543 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of a large RPKI-RTR PDU packet can cause rpd to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39543</link><description>A Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to send specific RPKI-RTR packets resulting in a crash, creating a Denial of Service (DoS) condition. Continued receipt and processing of this packet will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue affects 

Junos OS: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S8,
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S2, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2.



Junos OS Evolved:  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3-EVO,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1-EVO,
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39545 | Junos OS: SRX Series, MX Series with SPC3 and NFX350: When VPN tunnels parameters are not configured in specific way the iked process will crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39545</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the the IKE daemon (iked) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series, MX Series with SPC3 and NFX350 allows allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker sending specific mismatching parameters as part of the IPsec negotiation to trigger an iked crash leading to Denial of Service (DoS).

This issue is applicable to all platforms that run iked. This issue affects Junos OS on SRX Series, MX Series with SPC3 and NFX350: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S7, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S2, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S1, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R2-S1, 22.3R3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R1-S2, 22.4R2, 22.4R3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39546 | Junos OS Evolved: Local low-privilege user can gain root permissions leading to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39546</link><description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability in the Socket Intercept (SI) command file interface of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an authenticated, low-privilege local attacker to modify certain files, allowing the attacker to cause any command to execute with root privileges leading to privilege escalation ultimately compromising the system. 

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions prior to 21.2R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  21.4 versions prior to  21.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  22.1 versions prior to 22.1R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  22.2 versions prior to 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  22.3 versions prior to 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  22.4 versions prior to 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  23.2 versions prior to 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39548 | Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of specific packets in the aftmand process will lead to a memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39548</link><description>An Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in the aftmand process of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to consume memory resources, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS) condition. The processes do not recover on their own and must be manually restarted.

This issue affects both IPv4 and IPv6. 

Changes in memory usage can be monitored using the following CLI command:
user@device&gt; show system memory node  | grep evo-aftmann
This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  21.3 versions before 21.3R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S4-EVO,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S3-EVO,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R2-S2-EVO, 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R1-S1-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39549 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of malformed BGP path attributes leads to a memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39549</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the routing process daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an attacker to send a malformed BGP Path attribute update which allocates memory used to log the bad path attribute. This memory is not properly freed in all circumstances, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

Consumed memory can be freed by manually restarting Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd).

Memory utilization could be monitored by: 
user@host&gt; show system memory or show system monitor memory status

This issue affects:

Junos OS:   *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S8,

  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S3,
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S2, 23.4R2,
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-EVO.


Junos OS Evolved:
  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S8-EVO,
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S3-EVO,

  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S2, 23.4R2,
  *  from 24.2 before 24.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39531 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX 7000 Series: Protocol specific DDoS configuration affects other protocols</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39531</link><description>An Improper Handling of Values vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX 7000 Series allows a network-based, unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

If a value is configured for DDoS bandwidth or burst parameters for any protocol in
a queue, all protocols which share the same queue will have
their bandwidth or burst value changed to the new value. If, for example, OSPF was configured with a certain bandwidth value, ISIS would also be limited to this value. So inadvertently either the control plane is open for a high level of specific traffic which was supposed to be limited to a lower value, or the limit for a certain protocol is so low that chances to succeed with a volumetric DoS attack are significantly increased. 




This issue affects Junos OS Evolved on ACX 7000 Series:



  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3-EVO,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3-S2-EVO,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-EVO,
  *  23.4 

versions 

before 23.4R1-S1-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39532 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Confidential information in logs can be accessed by another user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39532</link><description>An Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a local, authenticated attacker with high privileges to access sensitive information.

When another user performs a specific operation, sensitive information is stored as plain text in a specific log file, so that a high-privileged attacker has access to this information.
This issue affects:

Junos OS:



  *  All versions before 22.1R2-S2,
  *  22.1R3 and later versions,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R2-S1, 22.2R3,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R1-S2, 22.3R2;




Junos OS Evolved:



  *  All versions before before 22.1R3-EVO,
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R2-S1-EVO, 22.2R3-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R1-S1-EVO, 22.3R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39533 | Junos OS: QFX5000 Series and EX4600 Series: Output firewall filter is not applied if certain match criteria are used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39533</link><description>An Unimplemented or Unsupported Feature in the UI vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS on QFX5000 Series and EX4600 Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a minor integrity impact to downstream networks.If one or more of the following match conditions

ip-source-address
ip-destination-address
arp-type

which are not supported for this type of filter, are used in an ethernet switching filter, and then this filter is applied as an output filter, the configuration can be committed but the filter will not be in effect.




This issue affects Junos OS on QFX5000 Series and EX4600 Series:

  *  All version before 21.2R3-S7, 
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S6,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S5,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S2, 
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2.



Please note that the implemented fix ensures these unsupported match conditions cannot be committed anymore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39535 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX 7000 Series: When specific traffic is received in a VPLS scenario evo-pfemand crashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39535</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX 7000 Series allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

When a device has a Layer 3 or an IRB interface configured in a VPLS instance and specific traffic is received, the evo-pfemand processes crashes which causes a service outage for the respective FPC until the system is recovered manually.

This issue only affects Junos OS Evolved 22.4R2-S1 and 22.4R2-S2 releases and is fixed in 22.4R3. No other releases are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39536 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Flaps of BFD sessions with authentication cause a ppmd memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39536</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the Periodic Packet Management Daemon (ppmd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to cause a 

Denial-of-Service (DoS).


When a BFD session configured with authentication flaps, ppmd memory can leak. Whether the leak happens depends on a race condition which is outside the attackers control. This issue only affects BFD operating in distributed aka delegated (which is the default behavior) or inline mode.



Whether the leak occurs can be monitored with the following CLI command:

&gt; show ppm request-queue


FPC     Pending-request
fpc0                   2
request-total-pending: 2


where a continuously increasing number of pending requests is indicative of the leak. 




This issue affects:

Junos OS:


  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8,
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S7,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S4,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3,
  *  23.1 versions before 23.1R2.



Junos OS Evolved:
  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-S4-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R3-EVO,
  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R3-EVO,
  *  23.2-EVO versions before 23.2R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39537 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX7000 Series: Ports which have been inadvertently exposed can be reached over the network</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39537</link><description>An Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX 7000 Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a limited information disclosure and availability impact to the device.



Due to a wrong initialization, specific processes which should only be able to communicate internally within the device can be reached over the network via open ports.




This issue affects Junos OS Evolved on ACX 7000 Series:



  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  22.2-EVO 

versions 

before 22.2R3-S4-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R3-S3-EVO,
  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R3-S2-EVO,
  *  23.2-EVO versions before 23.2R2-EVO,
  *  23.4-EVO versions before 23.4R1-S1-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39538 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX7000 Series: When multicast traffic with a specific (S,G) is received evo-pfemand crashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39538</link><description>A Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input vulnerability in the PFE management daemon (evo-pfemand) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX7000 Series allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a 

Denial-of-Service (DoS).When multicast traffic with a specific, valid (S,G) is received, evo-pfemand crashes which leads to an outage of the affected FPC until it is manually recovered.


This issue affects Junos OS Evolved on ACX7000 Series:


  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-S4-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  23.2-EVO versions before 23.2R2-EVO, 
  *  23.4-EVO versions before 23.4R1-S2-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39539 | Junos OS: MX Series: Continuous subscriber logins will lead to a memory leak and eventually an FPC crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39539</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series allows an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

In a subscriber management scenario continuous subscriber logins will trigger a memory leak and eventually lead to an FPC crash and restart.

This issue affects Junos OS on MX Series:



  *  All version before 21.2R3-S6,
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S6,
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S5,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3, 
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S2,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39540 | Junos OS: SRX Series, and MX Series with SPC3: Specific valid TCP traffic can cause a pfe crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39540</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (pfe) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series, and MX Series with SPC3 allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).

When an affected device receives specific valid TCP traffic, the pfe crashes and restarts leading to a momentary but complete service outage.

This issue affects Junos OS:

21.2 releases from 21.2R3-S5 before 21.2R3-S6.

This issue does not affect earlier or later releases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39520 | Junos OS Evolved: CLI parameter processing issue allows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39520</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved commands allows a local, authenticated attacker with low privileges to escalate their privileges to 'root' leading to a full compromise of the system.

The Junos OS Evolved CLI doesn't properly handle command options in some cases, allowing users which execute specific CLI commands with a crafted set of parameters to escalate their privileges to root on shell level.

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved:

  *  All version before 20.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  21.2-EVO versions before 21.2R3-S4-EVO,
  *  21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R2-S1-EVO, 22.2R3-EVO, 
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39521 | Junos OS Evolved: CLI parameter processing issue allows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39521</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved commands allows a local, authenticated attacker with low privileges to escalate their privileges to 'root' leading to a full compromise of the system.

The Junos OS Evolved CLI doesn't properly handle command options in some cases, allowing users which execute specific CLI commands with a crafted set of parameters to escalate their privileges to root on shell level.


This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  21.1-EVO versions 21.1R1-EVO and later before 21.2R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  22.1-EVO versions before 22.1R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39522 | Junos OS Evolved: CLI parameter processing issue allows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39522</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved commands allows a local, authenticated attacker with low privileges to escalate their privileges to 'root' leading to a full compromise of the system.

The Junos OS Evolved CLI doesn't properly handle command options in some cases, allowing users which execute specific CLI commands with a crafted set of parameters to escalate their privileges to root on shell level.


This issue affects Junos OS Evolved:



  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R2-EVO,
  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R1-S1-EVO, 22.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39523 | Junos OS Evolved: CLI parameter processing issue allows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39523</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved commands allows a local, authenticated attacker with low privileges to escalate their privileges to 'root' leading to a full compromise of the system.

The Junos OS Evolved CLI doesn't properly handle command options in some cases, allowing users which execute specific CLI commands with a crafted set of parameters to escalate their privileges to root on shell level.

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 

  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  21.2-EVO versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO,
  *  22.1-EVO versions before 22.1R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-EVO,
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R2-EVO,
  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39524 | Junos OS Evolved: CLI parameter processing issue allows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39524</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved commands allows a local, authenticated attacker with low privileges to escalate their privileges to 'root' leading to a full compromise of the system.

The Junos OS Evolved CLI doesn't properly handle command options in some cases, allowing users which execute specific CLI commands with a crafted set of parameters to escalate their privileges to root on shell level.

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved:

All versions before 20.4R3-S7-EVO,

21.2-EVO versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,

21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO, 

22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-EVO,

22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R2-EVO,

22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39528 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Concurrent deletion of a routing-instance and receipt of an SNMP request cause an RPD crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39528</link><description>A Use After Free vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an authenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).On all Junos OS and Junos Evolved platforms, if a routing-instance deactivation is triggered, and at the same time a specific SNMP request is received, a segmentation fault occurs which causes rpd to crash and restart.




This issue affects:

   Junos OS:



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S5,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S2,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2.




   Junos OS Evolved:



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO,
  *  21.4-EVO versions before 21.4R3-S5-EVO,
  *  22.2-EVO versions before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  22.3-EVO versions before 22.3R3-S2-EVO,
  *  22.4-EVO versions before 22.4R3-EVO,
  *  23.2-EVO versions before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39529 | Junos OS: SRX Series: If DNS traceoptions are configured in a DGA or tunnel detection scenario specific DNS traffic leads to a PFE crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39529</link><description>A Use of Externally-Controlled Format String vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS).



If DNS Domain Generation Algorithm (DGA) detection or tunnel detection, and DNS-filtering traceoptions are configured, and specific valid transit DNS traffic is received this causes a PFE crash and restart, leading to a Denial of Service.

This issue affects Junos OS: 
  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S6,
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3,
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S3,
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3,
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39530 | Junos OS: Attempting to access specific sensors on platforms not supporting these will lead to a chassisd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39530</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the chassis management daemon (chassisd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a 

Denial-of-Service (DoS).

If an attempt is made to access specific sensors on platforms not supporting these sensors, either via GRPC or netconf, chassisd will crash and restart leading to a restart of all FPCs and thereby a complete outage.

This issue affects Junos OS:



  *  21.4 versions from 21.4R3 before 21.4R3-S5,
  *  22.1 versions from 22.1R3 before 22.1R3-S4,
  *  22.2 versions from 22.2R2 before 22.2R3,
  *  22.3 versions from 22.3R1 before 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3,
  *  22.4 versions from 22.4R1 before 22.4R2.


This issue does not affect Junos OS versions earlier than 21.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6680 | witmy my-springsecurity-plus build sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6680</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in witmy my-springsecurity-plus up to 2024-07-04. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/dept/build. The manipulation of the argument params.dataScope leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271153 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39519 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX 7000 Series: Multicast traffic is looped in a multihoming EVPN MPLS scenario</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39519</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX7000 Series allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a 

Denial-of-Service (DoS).

On all ACX 7000 Series platforms running 

Junos OS Evolved, and configured with IRBs, if a Customer Edge device (CE) device is dual homed to two Provider Edge devices (PE) a traffic loop will occur when the CE sends multicast packets. This issue can be triggered by IPv4 and IPv6 traffic.


This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 

All versions from 22.2R1-EVO and later versions before 22.4R2-EVO,

This issue does not affect Junos OS Evolved versions before 22.1R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39905 | Red-DiscordBot vulnerable to Incorrect Authorization in commands API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39905</link><description>Red is a fully modular Discord bot. Due to a bug in Red's Core API, 3rd-party cogs using the `@commands.can_manage_channel()` command permission check without additional permission controls may authorize a user to run a command even when that user doesn't have permissions to manage a channel. None of the core commands or core cogs are affected. The maintainers of the project are not aware of any _public_ 3rd-party cog utilizing this API at the time of writing this advisory. The problem was patched and released in version 3.5.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39904 | Code Execution Vulnerability via Local File Path Traversal in Vnote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39904</link><description>VNote is a note-taking platform. Prior to 3.18.1, a code execution vulnerability existed in VNote, which allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary programs on the victim's system. A crafted URI can be used in a note to perform this attack using file:/// as a link. For example, file:///C:/WINDOWS/system32/cmd.exe. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary programs by embedding a reference to a local executable file such as file:///C:/WINDOWS/system32/cmd.exe and file:///C:/WINDOWS/system32/calc.exe. This vulnerability can be exploited by creating and sharing specially crafted notes. An attacker could send a crafted note file and perform further attacks. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.18.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32753 | TYCO Illustra Pro Gen 4 - JQuery version</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32753</link><description>Under certain circumstances the camera may be susceptible to known vulnerabilities associated with the JQuery versions prior to 3.5.0 third-party component</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39317 | Wagtail regular expression denial-of-service via search query parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39317</link><description>Wagtail is an open source content management system built on Django. A bug in Wagtail's `parse_query_string` would result in it taking a long time to process suitably crafted inputs. When used to parse sufficiently long strings of characters without a space, `parse_query_string` would take an unexpectedly large amount of time to process, resulting in a denial of service. In an initial Wagtail installation, the vulnerability can be exploited by any Wagtail admin user. It cannot be exploited by end users. If your Wagtail site has a custom search implementation which uses `parse_query_string`, it may be exploitable by other users (e.g. unauthenticated users). Patched versions have been released as Wagtail 5.2.6, 6.0.6 and 6.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6679 | witmy my-springsecurity-plus role sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6679</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in witmy my-springsecurity-plus up to 2024-07-04. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/role. The manipulation of the argument params.dataScope leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271152.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28872 | Incorrect TLS certificate validation can lead to escalated privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28872</link><description>The TLS certificate validation code is flawed. An attacker can obtain a TLS certificate from the Stork server and use it to connect to the Stork agent. Once this connection is established with the valid certificate, the attacker can send malicious commands to a monitored service (Kea or BIND 9), possibly resulting in confidential data loss and/or denial of service. It should be noted that this vulnerability is not related to BIND 9 or Kea directly, and only customers using the Stork management tool are potentially affected.
This issue affects Stork versions 0.15.0 through 1.15.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38535 | Suricata http2: oom from duplicate headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38535</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Suricata can run out of memory when parsing crafted HTTP/2 traffic. Upgrade to 6.0.20 or 7.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38536 | Suricata http/range: NULL-ptr deref when http.memcap is reached</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38536</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. A memory allocation failure due to `http.memcap` being reached leads to a NULL-ptr reference leading to a crash. Upgrade to 7.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38534 | Suricata modbus: txs without responses are never freed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38534</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Crafted modbus traffic can lead to unlimited resource accumulation within a flow. Upgrade to 7.0.6. Set a limited stream.reassembly.depth to reduce the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37151 | Suricata defrag: IP ID reuse can lead to policy bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37151</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. 
Mishandling of multiple fragmented packets using the same IP ID value can lead to packet reassembly failure, which can lead to policy bypass. Upgrade to 7.0.6 or 6.0.20. When using af-packet, enable `defrag` to reduce the scope of the problem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6035 | Stored XSS in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6035</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240410. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into the chat history file. When a victim uploads this file, the malicious script is executed in the victim's browser. This can lead to user data theft, session hijacking, malware distribution, and phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 10:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6407 | CWE-200: Information Exposure vulnerability exists that could cause disclosure of
credentials when a specially crafted message is sent to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6407</link><description>CWE-200: Information Exposure vulnerability exists that could cause disclosure of
credentials when a specially crafted message is sent to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 09:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6528 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site
Scripting') vulnerability exists that could cause a vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6528</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site
Scripting') vulnerability exists that could cause a vulnerability leading to a cross-site scripting
condition where attackers can have a victim’s browser run arbitrary JavaScript when they visit a
page containing the injected payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 09:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2602 | CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path
Traversal') vulnerability exists that could result in remote code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2602</link><description>CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path
Traversal') vulnerability exists that could result in remote code execution when an authenticated
user executes a saved project file that has been tampered by a malicious actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5680 | CWE-129: Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability exists that could cause local denial-of-service when a malicious actor with local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5680</link><description>CWE-129: Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability exists that could cause local denial-of-service when a malicious actor with local user access crafts a script/program using an IOCTL
call in the Foxboro.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5681 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause local denial-of-service,
privilege escalation, and potentially kerne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5681</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause local denial-of-service,
privilege escalation, and potentially kernel execution when a malicious actor with local user
access crafts a script/program using an IOCTL call in the Foxboro.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5679 | CWE-787: Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability exists that could cause local denial-of-service, or
kernel memory leak when a malicious actor wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5679</link><description>CWE-787: Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability exists that could cause local denial-of-service, or
kernel memory leak when a malicious actor with local user access crafts a script/program using
an IOCTL call in the Foxboro.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38433 | Nuvoton - CWE-305: Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38433</link><description>Nuvoton - CWE-305: Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness

An attacker with write access to the SPI-Flash on an NPCM7xx BMC subsystem that uses the Nuvoton BootBlock

reference code can modify the u-boot image header on flash parsed by the BootBlock which could lead to arbitrary code

execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2880 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5257 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5470 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6385 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6256 | Feeds for YouTube (YouTube video, channel, and gallery plugin) &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6256</link><description>The Feeds for YouTube (YouTube video, channel, and gallery plugin) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'youtube-feed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6624 | JSON API User &amp;lt;= 3.9.3 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6624</link><description>The JSON API User plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.3. This is due to improper controls on custom user meta fields. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as administrators on the site. The plugin requires the JSON API plugin to also be installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6666 | WP ERP &amp;lt;= 1.13.0 - Authenticated (Accounting Manager+) SQL Injection via vendor_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6666</link><description>The WP ERP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘vendor_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Accounting Manager access (erp_ac_view_sales_summary capability) and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1845 | VikRentCar Car Rental Management System &amp;lt; 1.3.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1845</link><description>The VikRentCar Car Rental Management System WordPress plugin before 1.3.2 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4655 | Ultimate Blocks &amp;lt; 3.1.9 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4655</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.1.9 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5444 | Bible Text &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5444</link><description>The Bible Text WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6025 | Quiz and Survey Master &amp;lt; 9.0.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6025</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.0.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its Quiz settings, which could allow contributors and higher to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6026 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.56 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6026</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.56 does not sanitise and escape some of its Slide options, which could allow authenticated users with access to the Sliders (by default Administrator, however this can be changed via the Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.56's options) and the ability to add images (Editor+) to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6138 | Secure Copy Content Protection &amp;lt; 4.0.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6138</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking WordPress plugin before 4.0.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22280 | VMSA-2024-0017: VMware Aria Automation updates address SQL-injection vulnerability (CVE-2024-22280)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22280</link><description>VMware Aria Automation does not apply correct input validation which allows for SQL-injection in the product. An authenticated malicious user could enter specially crafted SQL queries and perform unauthorised read/write operations in the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 04:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0619 | Payflex Payment Gateway &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Missing Authorization to Order Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0619</link><description>The Payflex Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the payment_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the status of orders, which can potentially lead to revenue loss.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6397 | InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.44 - Authentication Bypass to Admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6397</link><description>The InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.0.44. This is due to insufficient verification of the API key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username, and to perform a variety of other administrative tasks. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in 0.1.0.44, but was still exploitable via Cross-Site Request Forgery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6554 | Branda – White Label WordPress, Custom Login Page Customizer &amp;lt;= 3.4.18 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6554</link><description>The Branda – White Label WordPress, Custom Login Page Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.18. This is due the plugin utilizing composer without preventing direct access to the files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22387 | External Control of Critical State Data (CWE-642) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic web interface allows an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22387</link><description>External Control of Critical State Data (CWE-642) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic web interface allows an authenticated user to modify device I/O connections leading to unexpected behavior that in some circumstances could compromise site physical security controls. Gallagher recommend the diagnostic web page is not enabled (default is off) unless advised by Gallagher Technical support. This interface is intended only for diagnostic purposes.



This issue affects: Gallagher Controller 6000 and 7000 

9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240520a (distributed in 9.10.1268(MR1)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240521a (distributed in 9.00.1990(MR3)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240520a (distributed in 8.90.1947 (MR4)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240520a (distributed in 8.80.1726 (MR5)), 8.70 prior to vCR8.70.240520a (distributed in 8.70.2824 (MR7)), all versions of 8.60 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23194 | Improper output Neutralization for Logs (CWE-117) in the Command Centre API Diagnostics Endpoint could allow an attacker limited ability to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23194</link><description>Improper output Neutralization for Logs (CWE-117) in the Command Centre API Diagnostics Endpoint could allow an attacker limited ability to modify Command Centre log files. 

This issue affects: Gallagher Command Centre v9.10 prior to vEL9.10.1268 (MR1).</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23317 | External Control of File Name or Path (CWE-73) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 allows an attacker with local access to the Contro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23317</link><description>External Control of File Name or Path (CWE-73) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 allows an attacker with local access to the Controller to perform arbitrary code execution. 

This issue affects: 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240520a (distributed in 9.10.1268(MR1)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240521a (distributed in 9.00.1990(MR3)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240520a (distributed in 8.90.1947 (MR4)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240520a (distributed in 8.80.1726 (MR5)), 8.70 prior to vCR8.70.240520a (distributed in 8.70.2824 (MR7)), all versions of 8.60 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23485 | Improperly Preserved Integrity of Hardware Configuration State During a Power Save/Restore Operation (CWE-1304) in the Controller 6000 and 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23485</link><description>Improperly Preserved Integrity of Hardware Configuration State During a Power Save/Restore Operation (CWE-1304) in the Controller 6000 and 7000 can lead to secured door locks connected via Aperio Communication Hubs to momentarily allow free access. 

This issue affects: Gallagher Controller 6000 and 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240520a (distributed in 9.10.1268(MR1)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240521a (distributed in 9.00.1990(MR3)),  8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240520a (distributed in 8.90.1947 (MR4)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240520a (distributed in 8.80.1726 (MR5)), 8.70 prior to vCR8.70.240520a (distributed in 8.70.2824 (MR7)), all versions of 8.60 and prior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15039 | mhuertos phpLDAPadmin ajax_functions.js makeHttpRequest request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15039</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in mhuertos phpLDAPadmin up to 665dbc2690ebeb5392d38f1fece0a654225a0b38. Affected by this vulnerability is the function makeHttpRequest of the file htdocs/js/ajax_functions.js. The manipulation leads to http request smuggling. The attack can be launched remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named dd6e9583a2eb2ca085583765e8a63df5904cb036. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270523.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6210 | Duplicator &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6210</link><description>The Duplicator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain the full path to instances, which they may be able to use in combination with other vulnerabilities or to simplify reconnaissance work. On its own, this information is of very limited use.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6676 | witmy my-springsecurity-plus user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6676</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in witmy my-springsecurity-plus up to 2024-07-03 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/user. The manipulation of the argument params.dataScope leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271111.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40618 | Whale browser before 3.26.244.21 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization when processing a built-in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40618</link><description>Whale browser before 3.26.244.21 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization when processing a built-in extension.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 01:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6653 | code-projects Simple Task List Login loginForm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Task List 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file loginForm.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271060.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 01:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6447 | FULL &amp;lt;= 3.1.12 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via License Plan Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6447</link><description>The FULL – Cliente plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the license plan parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping as well as missing authorization and capability checks on the related functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that will execute whenever an administrative user accesses wp-admin dashboard</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39513 | Junos OS Evolved: Execution of a specific CLI command will cause a crash in the AFT manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39513</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows a local, low-privileged attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When a specific "clear" command is run, the Advanced Forwarding Toolkit manager (evo-aftmand-bt or evo-aftmand-zx) crashes and restarts.

The crash impacts all traffic going through the FPCs, causing a DoS. Running the command repeatedly leads to a sustained DoS condition.
This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S9-EVO, 
  *  from 21.2-EVO before 21.2R3-S7-EVO, 
  *  from 21.3-EVO before 21.3R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO,
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39514 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receiving specific traffic on devices with EVPN-VPWS with IGMP-snooping enabled will cause the rpd to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39514</link><description>An Improper Check or Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

An attacker can send specific traffic to the device, which causes the rpd to crash and restart. Continued receipt of this traffic will result in a sustained DoS condition.

This issue only affects devices with an EVPN-VPWS instance with IGMP-snooping enabled.

This issue affects Junos OS: 
  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S10, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2;


Junos OS Evolved: 
  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S10-EVO, 
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39517 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Upon processing specific L2 traffic, rpd can hang in devices with EVPN/VXLAN configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39517</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Layer 2 Address Learning Daemon (l2ald) on Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).

In an EVPN/VXLAN scenario, when a high amount specific Layer 2 packets are processed by the device, it can cause the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) to utilize all CPU resources which causes the device to hang. A manual restart of the rpd is required to restore services.

This issue affects both IPv4 and IPv6 implementations.
This issue affects
Junos OS:
All versions earlier than 21.4R3-S7;
22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S5;
22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S3;
22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R3-S2;
23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R2;
23.4 versions earlier than 23.4R1-S1.

Junos OS Evolved:
All versions earlier than 21.4R3-S7-EVO;
22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S5-EVO;
22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3-EVO;
22.3-EVO versions earlier than 22.3R3-S3-EVO;
22.4-EVO versions earlier than 22.4R3-S2-EVO;
23.2-EVO versions earlier than 23.2R2-EVO;
23.4-EVO versions earlier than 23.4R1-S1-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39518 | Junos OS: MX240, MX480, MX960 platforms using MPC10E: Memory leak will be observed when subscribed to a specific subscription on Junos Telemetry Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39518</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the telemetry sensor process (sensord) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX240, MX480, MX960 platforms using MPC10E causes a steady increase in memory utilization, ultimately leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).

When the device is subscribed to a specific subscription on Junos Telemetry Interface, a slow memory leak occurs and eventually all resources are consumed and the device becomes unresponsive. A manual reboot of the Line Card will be required to restore the device to its normal functioning. 

This issue is only seen when telemetry subscription is active.

The Heap memory utilization can be monitored using the following command:
  &gt; show system processes extensive

The following command can be used to monitor the memory utilization of the specific sensor
  &gt; show system info | match sensord
   PID   NAME                 MEMORY     PEAK MEMORY    %CPU   THREAD-COUNT CORE-AFFINITY   UPTIME

   1986  sensord            877.57MB   877.57MB         2       4           0,2-15          7-21:41:32


This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  from 21.2R3-S5 before 21.2R3-S7, 
  *  from 21.4R3-S4 before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.2R3 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3R2 before 22.3R3-S2, 
  *  from 22.4R1 before 22.4R3, 
  *  from 23.2R1 before 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39511 | Junos OS: The 802.1X Authentication Daemon crashes on running a specific command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39511</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability in the 802.1X Authentication (dot1x) Daemon of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows a local, low-privileged attacker with access to the CLI to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

On running a specific operational dot1x command, the dot1x daemon crashes. An attacker can cause a sustained DoS condition by running this command repeatedly.

When the crash occurs, the authentication status of any 802.1x clients is cleared, and any authorized dot1x port becomes unauthorized.  The client cannot re-authenticate until the dot1x daemon restarts.

This issue affects Junos OS:
  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S10;
  *  21.2 versions before 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S6;
  *  22.1 versions before 22.1R3-S5;
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions before 22.3R3-S2;
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3-S1;
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39512 | Junos OS Evolved: User is not logged out when the console cable is disconnected</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39512</link><description>An Improper Physical Access Control vulnerability in the console port control of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an attacker with physical access to the device to get access to a user account.

When the console cable is disconnected, the logged in user is not logged out. This allows a malicious attacker with physical access to the console to resume a previous session and possibly gain administrative privileges.

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 
  *  from 23.2R2-EVO before 23.2R2-S1-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4R1-EVO before 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39565 | Junos OS: J-Web: An unauthenticated, network-based attacker can perform XPATH injection attack against a device.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39565</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Data within XPath Expressions ('XPath Injection') vulnerability in J-Web shipped with Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to execute remote commands on the target device. 

While an administrator is logged into a J-Web session or has previously logged in and subsequently logged out of their J-Web session, the attacker can arbitrarily execute commands on the target device with the other user's credentials. In the worst case, the attacker will have full control over the device.
This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S7,
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4,
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S2,
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2,
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S1, 23.4R2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6036 | Denial of Service in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6036</link><description>A vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240410 allows any user to restart the server at will by sending a specific request to the `/queue/join?` endpoint with `"fn_index":66`. This unrestricted server restart capability can severely disrupt service availability, cause data loss or corruption, and potentially compromise system integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6652 | itsourcecode Gym Management System manage_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file manage_member.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271059.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39562 | Junos OS Evolved: A high rate of SSH connections causes a Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39562</link><description>A Missing Release of Resource after Effective Lifetime vulnerability the xinetd process, responsible for spawning SSH daemon (sshd) instances, of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by blocking SSH access for legitimate users.  Continued receipt of these connections will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

The issue is triggered when a high rate of concurrent SSH requests are received and terminated in a specific way, causing xinetd to crash, and leaving defunct sshd processes. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability blocks both SSH access as well as services which rely upon SSH, such as SFTP, and Netconf over SSH.

Once the system is in this state, legitimate users will be unable to SSH to the device until service is manually restored.  See WORKAROUND section below.

Administrators can monitor an increase in defunct sshd processes by utilizing the CLI command:

  &gt; show system processes | match sshd
  root     25219 30901  0 Jul16 ?        00:00:00 [sshd] 

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved:
  *  All versions prior to 21.4R3-S7-EVO
  *  22.3-EVO versions prior to 22.3R2-S2-EVO, 22.3R3-S2-EVO;
  *  22.4-EVO versions prior to 22.4R3-EVO;
  *  23.2-EVO versions prior to 23.2R2-EVO.



This issue does not affect Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved 22.1-EVO nor 22.2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39557 | Junos OS Evolved: MAC table changes cause a memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39557</link><description>An Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in the 

Layer 2 Address Learning Daemon (l2ald)

 of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a memory leak, eventually exhausting all system memory, leading to a system crash and Denial of Service (DoS).

Certain MAC table updates cause a small amount of memory to leak.  Once memory utilization reaches its limit, the issue will result in a system crash and restart.

To identify the issue, execute the CLI command:
 
user@device&gt; show platform application-info allocations app l2ald-agent
EVL Object Allocation Statistics:
 
 Node    Application       Context   Name                                 Live     Allocs     Fails       Guids
 re0     l2ald-agent                 net::juniper::rtnh::L2Rtinfo         1069096  1069302    0           1069302
 re0     l2ald-agent                 net::juniper::rtnh::NHOpaqueTlv       114      195        0           195



This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 


  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8-EVO,

  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39558 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of specific PIM packet causes rpd crash when PIM is configured along with MoFRR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39558</link><description>An Unchecked Return Value vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) on Juniper Networks Junos OS and Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows a logically adjacent, unauthenticated attacker sending a specific PIM packet to cause rpd to crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS), when PIM is configured with Multicast-only Fast Reroute (MoFRR). Continued receipt and processing of this packet may create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue is observed on Junos and Junos Evolved platforms where PIM is configured along with MoFRR. MoFRR tries to select the active path, but due to an internal timing issue, rpd is unable to select the forwarding next-hop towards the source, resulting in an rpd crash.

This issue affects:

Junos OS: 


  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S10, 
  *  from 21.2 before 21.2R3-S7, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R2; 




Junos OS Evolved: 


  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S10 -EVO,
  *  from 21.2-EVO before 21.2R3-S7 -EVO,
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S6 -EVO,
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S5 -EVO,
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S3-EVO,
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-EVO,
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39559 | Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of a specific TCP packet may result in a system crash (vmcore) on dual RE systems with NSR enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39559</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in packet processing of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved may allow a network-based unauthenticated attacker to crash the device (vmcore) by sending a specific TCP packet over an established TCP session with MD5 authentication enabled, destined to an accessible port on the device, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS).  The receipt of this packet must occur within a specific timing window outside the attacker's control (i.e., race condition).

Continued receipt and processing of this packet will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue only affects dual RE systems with Nonstop Active Routing (NSR) enabled.
Exploitation can only occur over TCP sessions with MD5 authentication enabled (e.g., BGP with MD5 authentication).

This issue affects Junos OS Evolved: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R2-S2-EVO, 22.4R3-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39560 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Memory leak due to RSVP neighbor persistent error leading to kernel crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39560</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the routing protocol daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a logically adjacent downstream RSVP neighbor to cause kernel memory exhaustion, leading to a kernel crash, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS).

The kernel memory leak and eventual crash will be seen when the downstream RSVP neighbor has a persistent error which will not be corrected.

System kernel memory can be monitored through the use of the 'show system statistics kernel memory' command as shown below:

user@router&gt; show system statistics kernel memory
Memory                 Size (kB)  Percentage  When
  Active                  753092       18.4%  Now
  Inactive                574300       14.0%  Now
  Wired                  443236       10.8%  Now
  Cached                1911204       46.6%  Now
  Buf                      32768      0.8%  Now
  Free                    385072      9.4%  Now
Kernel Memory                             Now
  Data                    312908      7.6%  Now
  Text                      2560      0.1%  Now
...

This issue affects:
Junos OS:


  *  All versions before 20.4R3-S9,
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S5,
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5,
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3,
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2,
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3,
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2;


Junos OS Evolved:


  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S5-EVO,
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39561 | Junos OS: SRX4600, SRX5000 Series: TCP packets with SYN/FIN or SYN/RST are transferred after enabling no-syn-check with Express Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39561</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the flow daemon (flowd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on 

SRX4600 and SRX5000 Series

 allows an attacker to send TCP packets with 

SYN/FIN or SYN/RST

 flags, bypassing the expected blocking of these packets.

A TCP packet with SYN/FIN or SYN/RST should be dropped in flowd. However, when no-syn-check and Express Path are enabled, these TCP packets are unexpectedly transferred to the downstream network.

This issue affects Junos OS on SRX4600 and SRX5000 Series: 


  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S8, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S7, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S2, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S1, 23.4R2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6037 | Arbitrary Folder Creation in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6037</link><description>A vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240410 allows an attacker to create arbitrary folders at any location on the server, including the root directory (C: dir). This can lead to uncontrolled resource consumption, resulting in resource exhaustion, denial of service (DoS), server unavailability, and potential data loss or corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39554 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: BGP multipath incremental calculation is resulting in an rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39554</link><description>A Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability the 

Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd)

 of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to inject incremental routing updates when BGP multipath is enabled, causing rpd to crash and restart, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS). Since this is a timing issue (race condition), the successful exploitation of this vulnerability is outside the attacker's control.  However, continued receipt and processing of this packet may create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

On all Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved platforms with BGP multipath enabled, a specific multipath calculation removes the original next hop from the multipath lead routes nexthop-set. When this change happens, multipath relies on certain internal timing to record the update.  Under certain circumstance and with specific timing, this could result in an rpd crash.

This issue only affects systems with BGP multipath enabled.


This issue affects:

Junos OS: 


  *  All versions of 21.1
  *  from 21.2 before 21.2R3-S7, 
  *  from 21.4 before 21.4R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S5, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S2, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2.




Junos OS Evolved: 


  *  All versions of 21.1-EVO,
  *  All versions of 21.2-EVO,
  *  from 21.4-EVO before 21.4R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S5-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO.



Versions of Junos OS before 21.1R1 are unaffected by this vulnerability.
Versions of Junos OS Evolved before 21.1R1-EVO are unaffected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39555 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Receipt of a specific malformed BGP update causes the session to reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39555</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (RPD) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an attacker sending a specific malformed BGP update message to cause the session to reset, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS).  Continued receipt and processing of these malformed BGP update messages will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

Upon receipt of a BGP update message over an established BGP session containing a specifically malformed tunnel encapsulation attribute, when segment routing is enabled, internal processing of the malformed attributes within the update results in improper parsing of remaining attributes, leading to session reset:

BGP SEND Notification code 3 (Update Message Error) subcode 1 (invalid attribute list)

Only systems with segment routing enabled are vulnerable to this issue.

This issue affects eBGP and iBGP, in both IPv4 and IPv6 implementations, and requires a remote attacker to have at least one established BGP session.

This issue affects:

Junos OS: 


  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S3, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2-S1, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S2, 23.4R2.


Junos OS Evolved: 

  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S8-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-S1-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4-EVO before 23.4R1-S2-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39556 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: Loading a malicious certificate from the CLI may result in a stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39556</link><description>A Stack-Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS and Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved may allow a local, low-privileged attacker with access to the CLI the ability to load a malicious certificate file, leading to a limited Denial of Service (DoS) or privileged code execution.

By exploiting the 'set security certificates' command with a crafted certificate file, a malicious attacker with access to the CLI could cause a crash of the command management daemon (mgd), limited to the local user's command interpreter, or potentially trigger a stack-based buffer overflow.


This issue affects:

 Junos OS: 


  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S7, 
  *  from 22.1 before 22.1R3-S6, 
  *  from 22.2 before 22.2R3-S4, 
  *  from 22.3 before 22.3R3-S3, 
  *  from 22.4 before 22.4R3-S2, 
  *  from 23.2 before 23.2R2, 
  *  from 23.4 before 23.4R1-S1, 23.4R2; 




Junos OS Evolved: 


  *  All versions before 21.4R3-S7-EVO, 
  *  from 22.1-EVO before 22.1R3-S6-EVO, 
  *  from 22.2-EVO before 22.2R3-S4-EVO, 
  *  from 22.3-EVO before 22.3R3-S3-EVO, 
  *  from 22.4-EVO before 22.4R3-S2-EVO, 
  *  from 23.2-EVO before 23.2R2-EVO, 
  *  from 23.4-EVO before 23.4R1-S1-EVO, 23.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6650 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System Master.php save_designation cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6650</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function save_designation of the file /classes/Master.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271058 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6148 | Bypass of GACS Policy Configuration settings in Citrix Workspace app for HTML5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6148</link><description>Bypass of GACS Policy Configuration settings in Citrix Workspace app for HTML5</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6149 | Redirection of users to a vulnerable URL in Citrix Workspace app for HTML5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6149</link><description>Redirection of users to a vulnerable URL in Citrix Workspace app for HTML5</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6150 | A non-admin user can cause short-term disruption in Target VM availability in Citrix Provisioning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6150</link><description>A non-admin user can cause short-term disruption in Target VM availability in Citrix Provisioning</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6286 | Local Privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6286</link><description>Local Privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges  in Citrix Workspace app for Windows</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6151 | Local Privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6151</link><description>Local Privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges in Virtual Delivery Agent for Windows used by Citrix Virtual Apps and Desktops and Citrix DaaS</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6236 | Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6236</link><description>Denial of Service   in NetScaler Console (formerly NetScaler ADM), NetScaler Agent, and NetScaler SDX</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25076 | An issue was discovered on Renesas SmartBond DA14691, DA14695, DA14697, and DA14699 devices. The bootrom function responsible for validating...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25076</link><description>An issue was discovered on Renesas SmartBond DA14691, DA14695, DA14697, and DA14699 devices. The bootrom function responsible for validating the Flash Product Header directly uses a user-controllable size value (Length of Flash Config Section) to control a read from the QSPI device into a fixed sized buffer, resulting in a buffer overflow and execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25077 | An issue was discovered on Renesas SmartBond DA14691, DA14695, DA14697, and DA14699 devices. The Nonce used for on-the-fly decryption of fla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25077</link><description>An issue was discovered on Renesas SmartBond DA14691, DA14695, DA14697, and DA14699 devices. The Nonce used for on-the-fly decryption of flash images is stored in an unsigned header, allowing its value to be modified without invalidating the signature used for secureboot image verification. Because the encryption engine for on-the-fly decryption uses AES in CTR mode without authentication, an attacker-modified Nonce can result in execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39693 | Next.js Denial of Service (DoS) condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39693</link><description>Next.js is a React framework. A Denial of Service (DoS) condition was identified in Next.js. Exploitation of the bug can trigger a crash, affecting the availability of the server. his vulnerability was resolved in Next.js 13.5 and later.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38353 | CodiMD - Missing Image Access Controls and Unauthorized Image Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38353</link><description>CodiMD allows realtime collaborative markdown notes on all platforms. CodiMD before 2.5.4 is missing authentication and access control vulnerability allowing an unauthenticated attacker to gain unauthorised access to image data uploaded to CodiMD. CodiMD does not require valid authentication to access uploaded images or to upload new image data. An attacker who can determine an uploaded image's URL can gain unauthorised access to uploaded image data. Due to the insecure random filename generation in the underlying Formidable library, an attacker can determine the filenames for previously uploaded images and the likelihood of this issue being exploited is increased. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38354 | Cross-site Scripting in Hackmd.io Notes lead by HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38354</link><description>CodiMD allows realtime collaborative markdown notes on all platforms. The notebook feature of Hackmd.io permits the rendering of iframe `HTML` tags with an improperly sanitized `name` attribute. This vulnerability enables attackers to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks via DOM clobbering. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37310 | EVerest has an integer overflow in the &amp;quot;v2g_incoming_v2gtp&amp;quot; function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37310</link><description>EVerest is an EV charging software stack. An integer overflow in the "v2g_incoming_v2gtp" function in the v2g_server.cpp implementation can allow a remote attacker to overflow the process' heap. This vulnerability is fixed in 2024.3.1 and 2024.6.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37148 | GLPI allows account takeover via SQL Injection in AJAX scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37148</link><description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in some AJAX scripts to alter another user account data and take control of it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37149 | GLPI allows remote code execution through the plugin loader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37149</link><description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated technician user can upload a malicious PHP script and hijack the plugin loader to execute this malicious script. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27095 | Decidim cross-site scripting (XSS) in the admin panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27095</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. The admin panel is subject to potential XSS attach in case the attacker manages to modify some records being uploaded to the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6 and 0.28.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32469 | Decidim has cross-site scripting (XSS) in the pagination</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32469</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. The pagination feature used in searches and filters is subject to potential XSS attack through a malformed URL using the GET parameter `per_page`. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6 and 0.28.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5492 | Open redirect vulnerability allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arbitrary websites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5492</link><description>Open redirect vulnerability allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to arbitrary websites in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6235 | Sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6235</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure in NetScaler Console</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5491 | Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5491</link><description>Denial of Service in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway in NetScaler</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37147 | GLPI allows Authenticated File Upload to Restricted Tickets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37147</link><description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can attach a document to any item, even if the user has no write access on it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5910 | Expedition: Missing Authentication Leads to Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link><description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5911 | PAN-OS: File Upload Vulnerability in the Panorama Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5912 | Cortex XDR Agent: Improper File Signature Verification Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link><description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5913 | PAN-OS: Improper Input Validation Vulnerability in PAN-OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6649 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System Users.php save_users cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_users of the file Users.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271057 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27090 | Decidim vulnerable to data disclosure through the embed feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27090</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework, written in Ruby on Rails, originally developed for the Barcelona City government online and offline participation website. If an attacker can infer the slug or URL of an unpublished or private resource, and this resource can be embbeded (such as a Participatory Process, an Assembly, a Proposal, a Result, etc), then some data of this resource could be accessed. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37770 | 14Finger v1.1 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability in the fingerprint function. This vulnerability allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37770</link><description>14Finger v1.1 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability in the fingerprint function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37110 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt; 3.26.7 - Unauthenticated Settings &amp;amp; Users Data Dump vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37110</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a before 3.26.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37113 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt; 3.26.7 - Unauthenticated Database Backup Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37113</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a before 3.26.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37115 | WordPress Newspack Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37115</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Blocks.This issue affects Newspack Blocks: from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6647 | Croogo Setting Theme unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6647</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Croogo up to 4.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/settings/settings/prefix/Theme of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content-Type leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271053 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37205 | WordPress affiliate-toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37205</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in SERVIT Software Solutions.This issue affects affiliate-toolkit: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37270 | WordPress TrustedLogin Vendor plugin &amp;lt; 1.1.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37270</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in TrustedLogin TrustedLogin Vendor.This issue affects TrustedLogin Vendor: from n/a before 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37498 | WordPress Tablesome plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.33 - Sensitive Data Exposure via API vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37498</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Pauple Table &amp; Contact Form 7 Database – Tablesome.This issue affects Table &amp; Contact Form 7 Database – Tablesome: from n/a through 1.0.33.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37504 | WordPress FileBird Document Library plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37504</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Ninja Team FileBird Document Library.This issue affects FileBird Document Library: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32759 | Johnson Controls Software House C●CURE 9000 installer password strength</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32759</link><description>Under certain circumstances the Software House C●CURE 9000 installer will utilize weak credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6646 | Netgear WN604 Web Interface downloadFile.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6646</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240710. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /downloadFile.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument file with the input config leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3325 | JasperReports Server Driver upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3325</link><description>Vulnerability in Jaspersoft JasperReport Servers.This issue affects JasperReport Servers: from 8.0.4 through 9.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6645 | WuKongOpenSource Wukong_nocode AviatorScript ExpressionUtil.java deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6645</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WuKongOpenSource Wukong_nocode up to 20230807. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file ExpressionUtil.java of the component AviatorScript Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271051.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5217 | Incomplete Input Validation in GlideExpression Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5217</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed an input validation vulnerability that was identified in the Washington DC, Vancouver, and earlier Now Platform releases. This vulnerability could enable an unauthenticated user to remotely execute code within the context of the Now Platform. The vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes below, which were released during the June 2024 patching cycle. If you have not done so already, we recommend applying security patches relevant to your instance as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6644 | zmops ArgusDBM AviatorScript CalculateAlarm.java getDefaultClassLoader deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6644</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zmops ArgusDBM up to 0.1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function getDefaultClassLoader of the file CalculateAlarm.java of the component AviatorScript Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271050 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4879 | Jelly Template Injection Vulnerability in ServiceNow UI Macros</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4879</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed an input validation vulnerability that was identified in the Vancouver and Washington DC releases of the Now Platform. This vulnerability could enable an unauthenticated user to remotely execute code within the context of the Now Platform. 

ServiceNow applied an update to hosted instances, and ServiceNow released the update to our partners and self-hosted customers. Listed below are the patches and hot fixes that address the vulnerability. If you have not done so already, we recommend applying security patches relevant to your instance as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5178 | Incomplete Input Validation in SecurelyAccess API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5178</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed a sensitive file read vulnerability that was identified in the Washington DC, Vancouver, and Utah Now Platform releases. This vulnerability could allow an administrative user to gain unauthorized access to sensitive files on the web application server.

The vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes, which were released during the June 2024 patching cycle. If you have not done so already, we recommend applying security patches relevant to your instance as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20456 | A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link><description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40412 | Tenda AX12 v1.0 v22.03.01.46 contains a stack overflow in the deviceList parameter of the sub_42E410 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40412</link><description>Tenda AX12 v1.0 v22.03.01.46 contains a stack overflow in the deviceList parameter of the sub_42E410 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40417 | A vulnerability was found in Tenda AX1806 1.0.0.1. Affected by this issue is the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetIpMacBin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40417</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AX1806 1.0.0.1. Affected by this issue is the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33859 | IBM Security ReaQta information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33859</link><description>IBM Security QRadar EDR 3.12 could disclose sensitive information due to an observable login response discrepancy.  IBM X-Force ID:  257697.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33860 | IBM Security ReaQta information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33860</link><description>IBM Security QRadar EDR 3.12 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.  IBM X-Force ID:  257702.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35006 | IBM Security ReaQta HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35006</link><description>IBM Security QRadar EDR 3.12 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.  IBM X-Force ID:  297165.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40331 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/dbBakMySQL_deal.php?mudi=backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40331</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/dbBakMySQL_deal.php?mudi=backup</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40332 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/moneyRecord_deal.php?mudi=delRecord</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40332</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/moneyRecord_deal.php?mudi=delRecord</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40336 | idccms v1.35 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) within the 'Image Advertising Management.'</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40336</link><description>idccms v1.35 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) within the 'Image Advertising Management.'</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40328 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/memberOnline_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;dataType=...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40328</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/memberOnline_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;amp;dataType=&amp;amp;dataID=6</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40329 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/softBak_deal.php?mudi=backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40329</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/softBak_deal.php?mudi=backup</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40333 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/softBak_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;dataID=2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40333</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/softBak_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;amp;dataID=2</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40334 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/serverFile_deal.php?mudi=upFileDel&amp;dataI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40334</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/serverFile_deal.php?mudi=upFileDel&amp;amp;dataID=3</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28827 | Privilege escalation in Windows agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28827</link><description>Incorrect permissions on the Checkmk Windows Agent's data directory in Checkmk &lt; 2.3.0p8, &lt; 2.2.0p29, &lt; 2.1.0p45, and &lt;= 2.0.0p39 (EOL) allows a local attacker to gain SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28828 | 1-Click compromize via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28828</link><description>Cross-Site request forgery in Checkmk &lt; 2.3.0p8, &lt; 2.2.0p29, &lt; 2.1.0p45, and &lt;= 2.0.0p39 (EOL) could lead to 1-click compromize of the site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3798 | Insecure handling of GET argument in Phoniebox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3798</link><description>Insecure handling of GET header parameter file included in requests being sent to an instance of the open-source project Phoniebox allows an attacker to create a website, which – when visited by a user – will send malicious requests to multiple hosts on the local network. If such a request reaches the server, it will cause one of the following (depending on the chosen payload): shell command execution, reflected XSS or cross-site request forgery.


This issue affects Phoniebox in all releases through 2.7. Newer releases were not tested, but they might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3799 | Shell command injection in Phoniebox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3799</link><description>Insecure handling of POST header parameter body included in requests being sent to an instance of the open-source project Phoniebox allows an attacker to create a website, which – when visited by a user – will send malicious requests to multiple hosts on the local network. If such a request reaches the server, it will cause a shell command execution.


This issue affects Phoniebox in all releases through 2.7. Newer releases were not tested, but they might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6556 | SmartCrawl WordPress SEO checker, SEO analyzer, SEO optimizer &amp;lt;= 3.10.8 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6556</link><description>The SmartCrawl WordPress SEO checker, SEO analyzer, SEO optimizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.8. This is due the plugin utilizing mobiledetect without preventing direct access to the files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:45:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6813 | Login by Auth0 &amp;lt;= 4.6.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via wle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6813</link><description>The Login by Auth0 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wle’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5664 | MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp;amp; Podcast by Sonaar &amp;lt;= 5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sonaar_audioplayer Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5664</link><description>The MP3 Audio Player – Music Player, Podcast Player &amp; Radio by Sonaar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' attribute within the plugin's sonaar_audioplayer shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6421 | Pepperl+Fuchs: Incorrectly configured FTP-Server in OIT Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6421</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can read out sensitive device information through a incorrectly configured FTP service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6422 | Pepperl+Fuchs: OIT Products can be manipulated via unintended Telnet access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6422</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can manipulate the device via Telnet, stop processes, read, delete and change data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39493 | crypto: qat - Fix ADF_DEV_RESET_SYNC memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39493</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: qat - Fix ADF_DEV_RESET_SYNC memory leak

Using completion_done to determine whether the caller has gone
away only works after a complete call.  Furthermore it's still
possible that the caller has not yet called wait_for_completion,
resulting in another potential UAF.

Fix this by making the caller use cancel_work_sync and then freeing
the memory safely.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39488 | arm64: asm-bug: Add .align 2 to the end of __BUG_ENTRY</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39488</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

arm64: asm-bug: Add .align 2 to the end of __BUG_ENTRY

When CONFIG_DEBUG_BUGVERBOSE=n, we fail to add necessary padding bytes
to bug_table entries, and as a result the last entry in a bug table will
be ignored, potentially leading to an unexpected panic(). All prior
entries in the table will be handled correctly.

The arm64 ABI requires that struct fields of up to 8 bytes are
naturally-aligned, with padding added within a struct such that struct
are suitably aligned within arrays.

When CONFIG_DEBUG_BUGVERPOSE=y, the layout of a bug_entry is:

	struct bug_entry {
		signed int      bug_addr_disp;	// 4 bytes
		signed int      file_disp;	// 4 bytes
		unsigned short  line;		// 2 bytes
		unsigned short  flags;		// 2 bytes
	}

... with 12 bytes total, requiring 4-byte alignment.

When CONFIG_DEBUG_BUGVERBOSE=n, the layout of a bug_entry is:

	struct bug_entry {
		signed int      bug_addr_disp;	// 4 bytes
		unsigned short  flags;		// 2 bytes
		&lt; implicit padding &gt;		// 2 bytes
	}

... with 8 bytes total, with 6 bytes of data and 2 bytes of trailing
padding, requiring 4-byte alginment.

When we create a bug_entry in assembly, we align the start of the entry
to 4 bytes, which implicitly handles padding for any prior entries.
However, we do not align the end of the entry, and so when
CONFIG_DEBUG_BUGVERBOSE=n, the final entry lacks the trailing padding
bytes.

For the main kernel image this is not a problem as find_bug() doesn't
depend on the trailing padding bytes when searching for entries:

	for (bug = __start___bug_table; bug &lt; __stop___bug_table; ++bug)
		if (bugaddr == bug_addr(bug))
			return bug;

However for modules, module_bug_finalize() depends on the trailing
bytes when calculating the number of entries:

	mod-&gt;num_bugs = sechdrs[i].sh_size / sizeof(struct bug_entry);

... and as the last bug_entry lacks the necessary padding bytes, this entry
will not be counted, e.g. in the case of a single entry:

	sechdrs[i].sh_size == 6
	sizeof(struct bug_entry) == 8;

	sechdrs[i].sh_size / sizeof(struct bug_entry) == 0;

Consequently module_find_bug() will miss the last bug_entry when it does:

	for (i = 0; i &lt; mod-&gt;num_bugs; ++i, ++bug)
		if (bugaddr == bug_addr(bug))
			goto out;

... which can lead to a kenrel panic due to an unhandled bug.

This can be demonstrated with the following module:

	static int __init buginit(void)
	{
		WARN(1, "hello\n");
		return 0;
	}

	static void __exit bugexit(void)
	{
	}

	module_init(buginit);
	module_exit(bugexit);
	MODULE_LICENSE("GPL");

... which will trigger a kernel panic when loaded:

	------------[ cut here ]------------
	hello
	Unexpected kernel BRK exception at EL1
	Internal error: BRK handler: 00000000f2000800 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
	Modules linked in: hello(O+)
	CPU: 0 PID: 50 Comm: insmod Tainted: G           O       6.9.1 #8
	Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
	pstate: 60400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
	pc : buginit+0x18/0x1000 [hello]
	lr : buginit+0x18/0x1000 [hello]
	sp : ffff800080533ae0
	x29: ffff800080533ae0 x28: 0000000000000000 x27: 0000000000000000
	x26: ffffaba8c4e70510 x25: ffff800080533c30 x24: ffffaba8c4a28a58
	x23: 0000000000000000 x22: 0000000000000000 x21: ffff3947c0eab3c0
	x20: ffffaba8c4e3f000 x19: ffffaba846464000 x18: 0000000000000006
	x17: 0000000000000000 x16: ffffaba8c2492834 x15: 0720072007200720
	x14: 0720072007200720 x13: ffffaba8c49b27c8 x12: 0000000000000312
	x11: 0000000000000106 x10: ffffaba8c4a0a7c8 x9 : ffffaba8c49b27c8
	x8 : 00000000ffffefff x7 : ffffaba8c4a0a7c8 x6 : 80000000fffff000
	x5 : 0000000000000107 x4 : 0000000000000000 x3 : 0000000000000000
	x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffff3947c0eab3c0
	Call trace:
	 buginit+0x18/0x1000 [hello]
	 do_one_initcall+0x80/0x1c8
	 do_init_module+0x60/0x218
	 load_module+0x1ba4/0x1d70
	 __do_sys_init_module+0x198/0x1d0
	 __arm64_sys_init_module+0x1c/0x28
	 invoke_syscall+0x48/0x114
	 el0_svc
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39489 | ipv6: sr: fix memleak in seg6_hmac_init_algo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39489</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv6: sr: fix memleak in seg6_hmac_init_algo

seg6_hmac_init_algo returns without cleaning up the previous allocations
if one fails, so it's going to leak all that memory and the crypto tfms.

Update seg6_hmac_exit to only free the memory when allocated, so we can
reuse the code directly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39490 | ipv6: sr: fix missing sk_buff release in seg6_input_core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39490</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv6: sr: fix missing sk_buff release in seg6_input_core

The seg6_input() function is responsible for adding the SRH into a
packet, delegating the operation to the seg6_input_core(). This function
uses the skb_cow_head() to ensure that there is sufficient headroom in
the sk_buff for accommodating the link-layer header.
In the event that the skb_cow_header() function fails, the
seg6_input_core() catches the error but it does not release the sk_buff,
which will result in a memory leak.

This issue was introduced in commit af3b5158b89d ("ipv6: sr: fix BUG due
to headroom too small after SRH push") and persists even after commit
7a3f5b0de364 ("netfilter: add netfilter hooks to SRv6 data plane"),
where the entire seg6_input() code was refactored to deal with netfilter
hooks.

The proposed patch addresses the identified memory leak by requiring the
seg6_input_core() function to release the sk_buff in the event that
skb_cow_head() fails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39491 | ALSA: hda: cs35l56: Fix lifetime of cs_dsp instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39491</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: hda: cs35l56: Fix lifetime of cs_dsp instance

The cs_dsp instance is initialized in the driver probe() so it
should be freed in the driver remove(). Also fix a missing call
to cs_dsp_remove() in the error path of cs35l56_hda_common_probe().

The call to cs_dsp_remove() was being done in the component unbind
callback cs35l56_hda_unbind(). This meant that if the driver was
unbound and then re-bound it would be using an uninitialized cs_dsp
instance.

It is best to initialize the cs_dsp instance in probe() so that it
can return an error if it fails. The component binding API doesn't
have any error handling so there's no way to handle a failure if
cs_dsp was initialized in the bind.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39492 | mailbox: mtk-cmdq: Fix pm_runtime_get_sync() warning in mbox shutdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39492</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mailbox: mtk-cmdq: Fix pm_runtime_get_sync() warning in mbox shutdown

The return value of pm_runtime_get_sync() in cmdq_mbox_shutdown()
will return 1 when pm runtime state is active, and we don't want to
get the warning message in this case.

So we change the return value &lt; 0 for WARN_ON().</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36450 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in sysinfo.cgi of Webmin versions prior to 1.910. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36450</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in sysinfo.cgi of Webmin versions prior to 1.910. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product. As a result, a session ID may be obtained, a webpage may be altered, or a server may be halted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36451 | Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges vulnerability exists in ajaxterm module of Webmin prior to 2.003. If this vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36451</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges vulnerability exists in ajaxterm module of Webmin prior to 2.003. If this vulnerability is exploited, a console session may be hijacked by an unauthorized user. As a result, data within a system may be referred, a webpage may be altered, or a server may be permanently halted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36452 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ajaxterm module of Webmin versions prior to 2.003. If this vulnerability is exploited, un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36452</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ajaxterm module of Webmin versions prior to 2.003. If this vulnerability is exploited, unintended operations may be performed when a user views a malicious page while logged in. As a result, data within a system may be referred, a webpage may be altered, or a server may be permanently halted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36453 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in session_login.cgi of Webmin versions prior to 1.970 and Usermin versions prior to 1.820. If thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36453</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in session_login.cgi of Webmin versions prior to 1.970 and Usermin versions prior to 1.820. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product. As a result, a webpage may be altered or sensitive information such as a credential may be disclosed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39927 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in Ricoh MFPs and printers. If a remote attacker sends a specially crafted request to the affected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39927</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in Ricoh MFPs and printers. If a remote attacker sends a specially crafted request to the affected products, the products may be able to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition and/or user's data may be destroyed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39886 | TONE store App version 3.4.2 and earlier contains an issue with unprotected primary channel. Since TONE store App communicates with TONE sto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39886</link><description>TONE store App version 3.4.2 and earlier contains an issue with unprotected primary channel. Since TONE store App communicates with TONE store website in cleartext, a man-in-the-middle attack may allow an attacker to obtain and/or alter communications of the affected App.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21521 | All versions of the package @discordjs/opus are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to providing an input object with a property toStr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21521</link><description>All versions of the package @discordjs/opus are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to providing an input object with a property toString to several different functions. Exploiting this vulnerability could lead to a system crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21522 | All versions of the package audify are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Array Index when frameSize is provided to the new OpusDecoder()....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21522</link><description>All versions of the package audify are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Array Index when frameSize is provided to the new OpusDecoder().decode or new OpusDecoder().decodeFloat functions it is not checked for negative values. This can lead to a process crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21523 | All versions of the package images are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to providing unexpected input types to several different fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21523</link><description>All versions of the package images are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to providing unexpected input types to several different functions. This makes it possible to reach an assert macro, leading to a process crash.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;By providing some specific integer values (like 0) to the size function, it is possible to obtain a Segmentation fault error, leading to the process crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21524 | All versions of the package node-stringbuilder are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read due to incorrect memory length calculation, by calling T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21524</link><description>All versions of the package node-stringbuilder are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read due to incorrect memory length calculation, by calling ToBuffer, ToString, or CharAt on a StringBuilder object with a non-empty string value input. It's possible to return previously allocated memory, for example, by providing negative indexes, leading to an Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21525 | All versions of the package node-twain are vulnerable to Improper Check or Handling of Exceptional Conditions due to the length of the sourc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21525</link><description>All versions of the package node-twain are vulnerable to Improper Check or Handling of Exceptional Conditions due to the length of the source data not being checked. Creating a new twain.TwainSDK with a productName or productFamily, manufacturer, version.info property of length &gt;= 34 chars leads to a buffer overflow vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21526 | All versions of the package speaker are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) when providing unexpected input types to the channels property...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21526</link><description>All versions of the package speaker are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) when providing unexpected input types to the channels property of the Speaker object makes it possible to reach an assert macro. Exploiting this vulnerability can lead to a process crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38875 | An issue was discovered in Django 4.2 before 4.2.14 and 5.0 before 5.0.7. urlize and urlizetrunc were subject to a potential denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38875</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 4.2 before 4.2.14 and 5.0 before 5.0.7. urlize and urlizetrunc were subject to a potential denial of service attack via certain inputs with a very large number of brackets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39329 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.7 and 4.2 before 4.2.14. The django.contrib.auth.backends.ModelBackend.authenticate() metho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39329</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.7 and 4.2 before 4.2.14. The django.contrib.auth.backends.ModelBackend.authenticate() method allows remote attackers to enumerate users via a timing attack involving login requests for users with an unusable password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39330 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.7 and 4.2 before 4.2.14. Derived classes of the django.core.files.storage.Storage base clas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39330</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.7 and 4.2 before 4.2.14. Derived classes of the django.core.files.storage.Storage base class, when they override generate_filename() without replicating the file-path validations from the parent class, potentially allow directory traversal via certain inputs during a save() call. (Built-in Storage sub-classes are unaffected.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39614 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.7 and 4.2 before 4.2.14. get_supported_language_variant() was subject to a potential denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39614</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.7 and 4.2 before 4.2.14. get_supported_language_variant() was subject to a potential denial-of-service attack when used with very long strings containing specific characters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6410 | ProfileGrid &amp;lt;= 5.8.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6410</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.9 via the 'pm_upload_image' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the profile picture of any user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 04:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6411 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.8.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authorization Bypass to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6411</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.9. This is due to a lack of validation on user-supplied data in the 'pm_upload_image' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update their user capabilities to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 04:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6550 | Gravity Forms: Multiple Form Instances &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6550</link><description>The Gravity Forms: Multiple Form Instances plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This is due to the plugin leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 03:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32467 | Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with hig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32467</link><description>Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to exposure of some UEFI code, leading to arbitrary code execution or escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32472 | Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with hig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32472</link><description>Dell Edge Gateway BIOS, versions 3200 and 5200, contains an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to exposure of some code in System Management Mode, leading to arbitrary code execution or escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38301 | Dell Alienware Command Center, version 5.7.3.0 and prior, contains an improper access control vulnerability. A low privileged attacker could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38301</link><description>Dell Alienware Command Center, version 5.7.3.0 and prior, contains an improper access control vulnerability. A low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service on the local system and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7061 | Advanced File Manager Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7061</link><description>The Advanced File Manager Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7062 | Advanced File Manager Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7062</link><description>The Advanced File Manager Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.4. This makes it possible for attackers with contributor access or higher to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4866 | UltraAddons – Elementor Addons (Header Footer Builder, Custom Font, Custom CSS,Woo Widget, Menu Builder, Anywhere Elementor Shortcode) &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4866</link><description>The UltraAddons – Elementor Addons (Header Footer Builder, Custom Font, Custom CSS,Woo Widget, Menu Builder, Anywhere Elementor Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5677 | Featured Image Generator &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Images Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5677</link><description>The Featured Image Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized image upload due to a missing capability check on the fig_save_after_generate_image function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary images to a post-related gallery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5792 | Houzez CRM &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Seller+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5792</link><description>The Houzez CRM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the notes ‘belong_to’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level (seller) access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22018 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-read flag is used.
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22018</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-read flag is used.
This flaw arises from an inadequate permission model that fails to restrict file stats through the fs.lstat API. As a result, malicious actors can retrieve stats from files that they do not have explicit read access to.
This vulnerability affects all users using the experimental permission model in Node.js 20 and Node.js 21.
Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 01:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25023 | IBM QRadar Suite Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25023</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.22.0 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  281429.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32670 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially ident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6433 | Relative Path Traversal in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6433</link><description>Relative Path Traversal in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>