<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 04:55:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-67897 | In Sequoia before 2.1.0, aes_key_unwrap panics if passed a ciphertext that is too short. A remote attacker can take advantage of this issue ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67897</link><description>In Sequoia before 2.1.0, aes_key_unwrap panics if passed a ciphertext that is too short. A remote attacker can take advantage of this issue to crash an application by sending a victim an encrypted message with a crafted PKESK or SKESK packet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 04:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13126 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.4.12 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13126</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the `post_args` and `topic_args` parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.12 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 04:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67896 | Exim before 4.99.1 allows remote heap corruption that will be further described on 2025-12-18.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67896</link><description>Exim before 4.99.1 allows remote heap corruption that will be further described on 2025-12-18.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 04:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14644 | itsourcecode Student Management System update_subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14644</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /update_subject.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 03:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14643 | code-projects Simple Attendance Record System check.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14643</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Attendance Record System 2.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /check.php. Performing manipulation of the argument student results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 03:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14641 | code-projects Computer Laboratory System admin_pic.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14641</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Computer Laboratory System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/admin_pic.php. This manipulation of the argument image causes unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 02:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14642 | code-projects Computer Laboratory System technical_staff_pic.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14642</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Computer Laboratory System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file technical_staff_pic.php. Such manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 02:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14640 | code-projects Student File Management System save_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14640</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Student File Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/save_student.php. Executing manipulation of the argument stud_no can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 02:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14639 | itsourcecode Student Management System uprec.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14639</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /uprec.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 02:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14638 | itsourcecode Online Pet Shop Management System update_cnp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14638</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Online Pet Shop Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pet1/update_cnp.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14637 | itsourcecode Online Pet Shop Management System addcnp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14637</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Online Pet Shop Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pet1/addcnp.php. This manipulation of the argument cnpname causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14636 | Tenda AX9 httpd image_check weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14636</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda AX9 22.03.01.46. This affects the function image_check of the component httpd. The manipulation results in use of weak hash. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14623 | code-projects Student File Management System update_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14623</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Student File Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_student.php. This manipulation of the argument stud_id causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 18:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14622 | code-projects Student File Management System save_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14622</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Student File Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/save_user.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14621 | code-projects Student File Management System update_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14621</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Student File Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update_user.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14620 | code-projects Student File Management System login_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14620</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Student File Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login_query.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14619 | code-projects Student File Management System login_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14619</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student File Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login_query.php. Performing manipulation of the argument stud_no results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14617 | Jehovahs Witnesses JW Library App org.jw.jwlibrary.mobile.activity.SiloContainer path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14617</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Jehovahs Witnesses JW Library App up to 15.5.1 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the component org.jw.jwlibrary.mobile.activity.SiloContainer. Such manipulation leads to path traversal. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14607 | OFFIS DCMTK dcmdata dcbytstr.cc makeDicomByteString memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14607</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in OFFIS DCMTK up to 3.6.9. Affected by this issue is the function DcmByteString::makeDicomByteString of the file dcmdata/libsrc/dcbytstr.cc of the component dcmdata. The manipulation results in memory corruption. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 3.7.0 can resolve this issue. The patch is identified as 4c0e5c10079392c594d6a7abd95dd78ac0aa556a. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 13:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14606 | tiny-rdm Tiny RDM Pickle Decoding pickle_convert.go pickle.loads deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14606</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in tiny-rdm Tiny RDM up to 1.2.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function pickle.loads of the file pickle_convert.go of the component Pickle Decoding. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 13:04:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14590 | code-projects Prison Management System search1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14590</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Prison Management System 2.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/search1.php. The manipulation of the argument keyname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14589 | code-projects Prison Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14589</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Prison Management System 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search.php. Executing manipulation of the argument keyname can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14542 | Command execution in python-utcp allows attackers to achieve remote code execution when fetching a remote Manual from a malicious endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14542</link><description>The vulnerability arises when a client fetches a tools’ JSON specification, known as a Manual, from a remote Manual Endpoint. While a provider may initially serve a benign manual (e.g., one defining an HTTP tool call), earning the clients’ trust, a malicious provider can later change the manual to exploit the client.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14588 | itsourcecode Student Management System update_program.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14588</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /update_program.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14587 | itsourcecode Online Pet Shop Management System available.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14587</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Online Pet Shop Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /pet1/available.php. Such manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 09:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0969 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.7.16 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via get_users Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0969</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.16 via the get_users() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including email addresses and hashed passwords of administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36747 | Hardcoded FTP Credentials within the firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36747</link><description>ShineLan-X contains a set of credentials for an FTP server was found within the firmware, allowing testers to establish an insecure FTP connection with the server. This may allow an attacker to replace legitimate files being deployed to devices with their own malicious versions, since the firmware signature verification is not enforced.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36748 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Growatt ShineLan-X</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36748</link><description>ShineLan-X contains a stored cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the local configuration web server. The JavaScript code snippet can be inserted in the communication module’s settings center. This may allow attackers to force a legitimate user’s browser’s JavaScript engine to run malicious code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36750 | Stored cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Growatt ShineLan-X</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36750</link><description>ShineLan-X contains a stored cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Plant Name field. A HTML payload will be displayed on the plant management page via a direct post. This may allow attackers to force a legitimate user’s browser’s JavaScript engine to run malicious code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36751 | Missing encryption on Local Configuration Interface or Cloud Endpoint Communication - Growatt MIC3300TL-X and ShineLan-X</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36751</link><description>Encryption is missing on the configuration interface for Growatt ShineLan-X and MIC 3300TL-X. This allows an attacker with access to the network to intercept and potentially manipulate communication requests between the inverter and its cloud endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36752 | Undocumented backup Account and No Password Configuration Capability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36752</link><description>Growatt ShineLan-X communication dongle has an undocumented backup account with undocumented credentials which allows significant level access to the device, such as allowing any attacker to access the Setting Center. This means that this is effectively backdoor for all devices utilizing a Growatt ShineLan-X communication dongle.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36753 | SWD Interface Open on Growatt ShineLan-X</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36753</link><description>The SWD debug interface on the Growatt ShineLan-X communication dongle is available by default, allowing an attacker to attain debug access to the device and to extracting secrets or domains from within the device</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36754 | Authentication bypass on web interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36754</link><description>The authentication mechanism on web interface is not properly implemented. It is possible to bypass authentication checks by crafting a post request with new settings since there is no session token or authentication in place. This would allow an attacker for instance to point the device to an arbitrary address for domain name resolution to e.g. facililitate a man-in-the-middle (MitM) attack.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7960 | King Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 51.1.39 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7960</link><description>The King Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Pricing Slider, Pricing Calculator, and Image Accordion widgets in all versions up to, and including, 51.1.39 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8195 | JetWidgets For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.20 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Comparison and Subscribe Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8195</link><description>The JetWidgets For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Comparison and Subscribe widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8199 | MarqueeAddons &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Testimonial Marquee Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8199</link><description>The MarqueeAddons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Testimonial Marquee widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8687 | Enter Addons &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown and Image Comparison Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8687</link><description>The Enter Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown and Image Comparison widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8780 | Livemesh SiteOrigin Widgets &amp;lt;= 3.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Hero Header and Pricing Table Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8780</link><description>The Livemesh SiteOrigin Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Hero Header and Pricing Table widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9856 | Popup Builder – Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups. &amp;lt;= 4.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9856</link><description>The Popup Builder – Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sg_popup' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 08:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10289 | Filter &amp;amp; Grids &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10289</link><description>The Filter &amp; Grids plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'phrase' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This only works on MariaDB as the query results in a syntax error on MySQL.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8779 | All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Team and Countdown Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8779</link><description>The All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Team and Countdown widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9207 | TI WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.10.0 - Unauthenticated HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9207</link><description>The TI WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.0. This is due to the plugin accepting hidden fields and not limiting the values or data that can input and is later output. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary HTML into wishlist items.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 07:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10738 | URL Shortener Plugin For WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10738</link><description>The URL Shortener Plugin For WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘analytic_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 06:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14586 | TOTOLINK X5000R cstecgi.cgi snprintf os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14586</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in TOTOLINK X5000R 9.1.0cu.2089_B20211224. Affected by this issue is the function snprintf of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=exportOvpn&amp;amp;type=user. This manipulation of the argument User causes os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 06:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9116 | WPS Visitor Counter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Reflected XSS via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;REQUEST_URI&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9116</link><description>The WPS Visitor Counter Plugin WordPress plugin through 1.4.8 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 06:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12362 | myCred – Points Management System For Gamification, Ranks, Badges, and Loyalty Program &amp;lt;= 2.9.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Withdrawal Request Approval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12362</link><description>The myCred – Points Management System For Gamification, Ranks, Badges, and Loyalty Program plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 2.9.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve withdrawal requests, modify user point balances, and manipulate the payment processing system via the cashcred_pay_now AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 05:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11164 | Mavix Education &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) &amp;#x27;Creativ Demo Importer&amp;#x27; Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11164</link><description>The Mavix Education theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mavix_education_activate_plugin' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate the Creativ Demo Importer plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11376 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.335 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11376</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'colibri_loop' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.335 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11693 | Export WP Page to Static HTML &amp;amp; PDF &amp;lt;= 4.3.4 - Unauthenticated Cookie Exposure via Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11693</link><description>The Export WP Page to Static HTML &amp; PDF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.4 through publicly exposed cookies.txt files containing authentication cookies. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to cookies that may have been injected into the log file if the site administrator triggered a back-up using a specific user role like 'administrator.'</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11707 | Login Lockdown &amp;amp; Protection &amp;lt;= 2.14 - IP Block Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11707</link><description>The Login Lockdown &amp; Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Block Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.14. This is due to $unblock_key key being insufficiently random allowing unauthenticated users, with access to an administrative user email, to generate valid unblock keys for their IP Address. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass blocks due to invalid login attempts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11970 | Emplibot – AI Content Writer with Keyword Research, Infographics, and Linking | SEO Optimized | Fully Automated &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11970</link><description>The Emplibot – AI Content Writer with Keyword Research, Infographics, and Linking | SEO Optimized | Fully Automated plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 via the emplibot_call_webhook_with_error() and emplibot_process_zip_data() functions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12076 | Social Media Auto Publish &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12076</link><description>The Social Media Auto Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12077 | WP to LinkedIn Auto Publish &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12077</link><description>The WP to LinkedIn Auto Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12109 | Header Footer Script Adder – Insert Code in Header, Body &amp;amp; Footer &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12109</link><description>The Header Footer Script Adder – Insert Code in Header, Body &amp; Footer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the script adder present in posts in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13077 | افزونه پیامک ووکامرس فوق حرفه ای (جدید) payamito sms woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Unauthenticated Time-Based Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13077</link><description>The افزونه پیامک ووکامرس فوق حرفه ای (جدید) payamito sms woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'columns' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13092 | Devs CRM – Manage tasks, attendance and teams all together &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Unauthenticated Information Expsoure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13092</link><description>The Devs CRM – Manage tasks, attendance and teams all together plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the /wp-json/devs-crm/v1/attendances REST API Endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve private user data, including password hashes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13093 | Devs CRM – Manage tasks, attendance and teams all together &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Lead Tag Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13093</link><description>The Devs CRM – Manage tasks, attendance and teams all together plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the '/wp-json/devs-crm/v1/bulk-update' REST-API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update leads tags.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13094 | WP3D Model Import Viewer &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13094</link><description>The WP3D Model Import Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the handle_import_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13705 | Custom Frames &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;class&amp;#x27; Shortcode Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13705</link><description>The Custom Frames plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' parameter of the 'customframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14288 | Gallery Blocks with Lightbox &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14288</link><description>The Gallery Blocks with Lightbox. Image Gallery, (HTML5 video , YouTube, Vimeo) Video Gallery and Lightbox for native gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of plugin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This is due to the plugin using the `edit_posts` capability check instead of `manage_options` for the `update_option` action type in the `pgc_sgb_action_wizard` AJAX handler. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to modify arbitrary plugin settings prefixed with `pgc_sgb_*`.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14365 | Eyewear prescription form &amp;lt;= 6.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary WooCommerce Category Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14365</link><description>The Eyewear prescription form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.1. This is due to missing capability checks on the RemoveItems AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary WooCommerce product categories, including all of their child categories, via the 'catIds' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14366 | Eyewear prescription form &amp;lt;= 6.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary WooCommerce Product Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14366</link><description>The Eyewear prescription form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.1. This is due to missing authorization checks on the SubmitCatProductRequest AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary WooCommerce products with custom names, prices, and category assignments via the 'Name', 'Price', and 'Parent' parameters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14367 | Easy Theme Options &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Settings Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14367</link><description>The Easy Theme Options plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing authorization checks in the eto_import_settings function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to import arbitrary plugin settings via the 'eto_import_settings' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14378 | Quick Testimonials &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14378</link><description>The Quick Testimonials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14394 | Popover Windows &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Popover Configuration Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14394</link><description>The Popover Windows plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14395 | Popover Windows &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Popover Configuration Update via AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14395</link><description>The Popover Windows plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple ajax actions (e.g., pop_submit, poptheme_submit) in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify the plugin's settings and content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14397 | Postem Ipsum &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation in postem_ipsum_generate_users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14397</link><description>The Postem Ipsum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the postem_ipsum_generate_users() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary user accounts with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14440 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.4.01 - Authentication Bypass via Cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14440</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.4.01. This is due to incorrect authentication checking in the 'jay_login_register_process_switch_back' function with the 'jay_login_register_process_switch_back' cookie value. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14446 | Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 1.1.37 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14446</link><description>The Popup Builder (Easy Notify Lite) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the easynotify_cp_reset() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.37. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset plugin settings to their default values.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14447 | AnnunciFunebri Impresa &amp;lt;= 4.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Options Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14447</link><description>The AnnunciFunebri Impresa plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the annfu_reset_options() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete all 29 plugin options, effectively resetting the plugin to its default state.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14451 | Solutions Ad Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;sam-redirect-to&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14451</link><description>The Solutions Ad Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect URL supplied via the 'sam-redirect-to' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14462 | Lucky Draw Contests &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14462</link><description>The Lucky Draw Contests plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in misc-settings.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14475 | Extensive VC Addons for WPBakery page builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion via &amp;#x27;shortcode_name&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14475</link><description>The Extensive VC Addons for WPBakery page builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1 via the `extensive_vc_get_module_template_part` function. This is due to insufficient path normalization and validation of the user-supplied `shortcode_name` parameter in the `extensive_vc_init_shortcode_pagination` AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files via the `shortcode_name` parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14476 | Doubly &amp;lt;= 1.0.46 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection via ZIP File Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14476</link><description>The Doubly – Cross Domain Copy Paste for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.46 via deserialization of untrusted input from the content.txt file within uploaded ZIP archives. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, delete files, retrieve sensitive data, or perform other actions depending on the available gadgets. This is only exploitable by subscribers, when administrators have explicitly enabled that access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14508 | MediaCommander – Bring Folders to Media, Posts, and Pages &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Media Folder Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14508</link><description>The MediaCommander – Bring Folders to Media, Posts, and Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data deletion due to a missing capability check on the import-csv REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1. This is due to the endpoint using `upload_files` capability check (Author level) for a destructive operation that can delete all folders. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to delete all folder organization data created by Administrators and other users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14539 | Shortcode Loader &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via &amp;#x27;code&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14539</link><description>The The Shortcode Ajax plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14540 | Userback &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin&amp;#x27;s Configuration Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14540</link><description>The Userback plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the userback_get_json function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract plugin's configuration data including the Userback API access token and site's posts/pages contents, including those that have private and draft status.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7058 | Kingcabs &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via progressbarLayout Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7058</link><description>The Kingcabs theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘progressbarLayout’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8617 | YITH WooCommerce Quick View &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via yith_quick_view Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8617</link><description>The YITH WooCommerce Quick View plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's yith_quick_view shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9218 | rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress 4.7.0 - 4.7.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Disclosure via handle_rest_pre_dispatch Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9218</link><description>The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to to Information Disclosure due to missing authorization in the handle_rest_pre_dispatch() function when the Godam plugin is active, in versions 4.7.0 to 4.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve media items associated with draft or private posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9488 | Redux Framework &amp;lt;= 4.5.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9488</link><description>The Redux Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘data’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9873 | a3 Lazy Load &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9873</link><description>The a3 Lazy Load plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 04:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12512 | GenerateBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Exposure via Metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12512</link><description>The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information exposure due to missing object-level authorization checks in versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to the plugin registering multiple REST API routes under `generateblocks/v1/meta/` that gate access with `current_user_can('edit_posts')`, which is granted to low-privileged roles such as Contributor. The handlers accept arbitrary entity IDs (user IDs, post IDs, etc.) and meta keys, returning any requested metadata with only a short blacklist of password-like keys for protection. There is no object-level authorization ensuring the caller is requesting only their own data, and there is no allowlist of safe keys. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to exfiltrate personally identifiable information (PII) and other sensitive profile data of administrator accounts or any other users by directly querying user meta keys via the exposed endpoints via the `get_user_meta_rest` function. In typical WordPress + WooCommerce setups, this includes names, email, phone, and address fields that WooCommerce stores in user meta, enabling targeted phishing, account takeover pretexting, and privacy breaches.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13089 | WP Directory Kit &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13089</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'hide_fields' and the 'attr_search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13403 | Employee Spotlight – Team Member Showcase &amp;amp; Meet the Team Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Tracking Opt-In/Opt-Out Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13403</link><description>The Employee Spotlight – Team Member Showcase &amp; Meet the Team Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized tracking settings modification due to missing authorization validation on the employee_spotlight_check_optin() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enable or disable tracking settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14050 | Design Import/Export &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via XML File Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14050</link><description>The Design Import/Export plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via XML File Import in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14056 | Custom Post Type UI &amp;lt;= 1.18.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;label&amp;#x27; Import Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14056</link><description>The Custom Post Type UI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'label' parameter during custom post type import in all versions up to, and including, 1.18.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the Tools → Get Code page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14278 | HT Slider for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14278</link><description>The HT Slider for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'slide_title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping in JavaScript. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14454 | Image Slider by Ays- Responsive Slider and Carousel &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Slider Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14454</link><description>The Image Slider by Ays- Responsive Slider and Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the bulk delete functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary sliders via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14477 | 404 Solution &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;filterText&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14477</link><description>The 404 Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This is due to improper sanitization of the `filterText` parameter in the `ajaxUpdatePaginationLinks` AJAX action. The sanitization logic can be bypassed by using the sequence `*$/` which becomes `*/` after the `$` character is removed, allowing attackers to escape SQL comment contexts. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database via a time-based blind SQL injection technique.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14581 | HAPPY – Helpdesk Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Ticket Reply</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14581</link><description>The HAPPY – Helpdesk Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on the 'submit_form_reply' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to submit replies to arbitrary support tickets by manipulating the 'happy_topic_id' parameter, regardless of whether they are the ticket owner or have been assigned to the ticket.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 03:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13970 | OpenPLC_V3 Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13970</link><description>OpenPLC_V3 is vulnerable to a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack 
due to the absence of proper CSRF validation. This issue allows an 
unauthenticated attacker to trick a logged-in administrator into 
visiting a maliciously crafted link, potentially enabling unauthorized 
modification of PLC settings or the upload of malicious programs which 
could lead to significant disruption or damage to connected systems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:07:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14584 | itsourcecode COVID Tracking System Admin Login login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14584</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode COVID Tracking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/login.php of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14585 | itsourcecode COVID Tracking System page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14585</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode COVID Tracking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/?page=zone. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67749 | PCSX2 has an Out-of-bounds Read due to unchecked offset and size passed to memcpy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67749</link><description>PCSX2 is a free and open-source PlayStation 2 (PS2) emulator. In versions 2.5.377 and below, an unchecked offset and size used in a memcpy operation inside PCSX2's CDVD SCMD 0x91 and SCMD 0x8F handlers allow a specially crafted disc image or ELF to cause an out-of-bounds read from emulator memory. Because the offset and size is controlled through MG header fields, a specially crafted ELF can read data beyond the bounds of mg_buffer and have it reflected back into emulated memory. This issue is fixed in version 2.5.378.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67721 | Aircompressor&amp;#x27;s Snappy and LZ4 Java-based decompressor implementation can leak information from reused output buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67721</link><description>Aircompressor is a library with ports of the Snappy, LZO, LZ4, and Zstandard compression algorithms to Java. In versions 3.3 and below, incorrect handling of malformed data in Java-based decompressor implementations for Snappy and LZ4 allow remote attackers to read previous buffer contents via crafted compressed input. With certain crafted compressed inputs, elements from the output buffer can end up in the uncompressed output, potentially leaking sensitive data. This is relevant for applications that reuse the same output buffer to uncompress multiple inputs. This can be the case of a web server that allocates a fix-sized buffer for performance purposes. There is similar vulnerability in GHSA-cmp6-m4wj-q63q. This issue is fixed in version 3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14582 | campcodes Online Student Enrollment System index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14582</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in campcodes Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php?page=user-profile. Performing manipulation of the argument userphoto results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14583 | campcodes Online Student Enrollment System register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14583</link><description>A flaw has been found in campcodes Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/register.php. Executing manipulation of the argument photo can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14611 | Gladinet CentreStack and TrioFox Hard Coded AES Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14611</link><description>Gladinet CentreStack and Triofox prior to version 16.12.10420.56791 used hardcoded values for their implementation of the AES cryptoscheme. This degrades security for public exposed endpoints that may make use of it and may offer arbitrary local file inclusion when provided a specially crafted request without authentication. This opens the door for future exploitation and can be leveraged with previous vulnerabilities to gain a full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43320 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to bypass launch constra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43320</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to bypass launch constraint protections and execute malicious code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43351 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access protec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43351</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43381 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. A malicious app may be able to delete ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43381</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. A malicious app may be able to delete protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43388 | An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43388</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43393 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to break...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43393</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43402 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43402</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43404 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43404</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43406 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43406</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43410 | The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2. An attacker with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43410</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of caches. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2. An attacker with physical access may be able to view deleted notes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43416 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43416</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43437 | An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved privacy controls. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43437</link><description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved privacy controls. This issue is fixed in iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43461 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access protect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43461</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43463 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43463</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Tahoe 26.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43464 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. Visiting a website may lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43464</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. Visiting a website may lead to an app denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43465 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43465</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43466 | An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43466</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43467 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43467</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43470 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. A standard user may be able to view...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43470</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. A standard user may be able to view files made from a disk image belonging to an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43471 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43471</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43473 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43473</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43482 | The issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43482</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43494 | A mail header parsing issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2, macOS Tah...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43494</link><description>A mail header parsing issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2, macOS Tahoe 26.1, visionOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. An attacker may be able to cause a persistent denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43497 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to break out...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43497</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43506 | A logic error was addressed with improved error handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. iCloud Private Relay may not activate whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43506</link><description>A logic error was addressed with improved error handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. iCloud Private Relay may not activate when more than one user is logged in at the same time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43509 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43509</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43510 | A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved lock state checking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43510</link><description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved lock state checking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2, macOS Tahoe 26.1, visionOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious application may cause unexpected changes in memory shared between processes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43511 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2. Processing malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43511</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43512 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to el...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43512</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43513 | A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43513</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43516 | A session management issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. A user with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43516</link><description>A session management issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. A user with Voice Control enabled may be able to transcribe another user's activity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43517 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43517</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43518 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43518</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to inappropriately access files through the spellcheck API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43519 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43519</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43520 | A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2, ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43520</link><description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 26.1, iOS 18.7.2 and iPadOS 18.7.2, macOS Tahoe 26.1, visionOS 26.1, tvOS 26.1, macOS Sonoma 14.8.2, macOS Sequoia 15.7.2, iOS 26.1 and iPadOS 26.1. A malicious application may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43521 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43521</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43522 | A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43522</link><description>A downgrade issue affecting Intel-based Mac computers was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43523 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43523</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43527 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to gain root...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43527</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43530 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43530</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43532 | A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. Pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43532</link><description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. Processing malicious data may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43538 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3. An app may be able to access sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43538</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43539 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. Processing a file may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43539</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. Processing a file may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43542 | This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. Password fields may be unintentionally...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43542</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. Password fields may be unintentionally revealed when remotely controlling a device over FaceTime.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46276 | An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved privacy controls. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46276</link><description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved privacy controls. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46285 | An integer overflow was addressed by adopting 64-bit timestamps. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46285</link><description>An integer overflow was addressed by adopting 64-bit timestamps. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46287 | An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46287</link><description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An attacker may be able to spoof their FaceTime caller ID.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46289 | A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be abl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46289</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved file handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.3, macOS Sequoia 15.7.3. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11266 | Grassroots DICOM (GDCM) Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11266</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the Grassroots DICOM library (GDCM). The issue is triggered during parsing of a malformed DICOM file containing encapsulated PixelData fragments (compressed image data stored as multiple fragments). This vulnerability leads to a segmentation fault caused by an out-of-bounds memory access due to unsigned integer underflow in buffer indexing. It is exploitable via file input, simply opening a crafted malicious DICOM file is sufficient to trigger the crash, resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14580 | Qualitor viewDocumento.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14580</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Qualitor up to 8.24.73. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Qualitor/html/bc/bcdocumento9/biblioteca/request/viewDocumento.php. Such manipulation of the argument cdscript leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. The vendor confirms the existence of the issue: "We became aware of the issue through an earlier direct notification from the original reporter, and our engineering team promptly investigated and implemented the necessary corrective measures. (...) Updated versions containing the fix have already been provided to our customer base".</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67634 | Software Acquisition Guide Supplier Response Web Tool XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67634</link><description>The CISA Software Acquisition Guide Supplier Response Web Tool before 2025-12-11 was vulnerable to cross-site scripting via text fields. If an attacker could convince a user to import a specially-crafted JSON file, the Tool would load JavaScript from the file into the page. The JavaScript would execute in the context of the user's browser when the user submits the page (clicks 'Next').</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58316 | Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 SQL Injection via Payment Success Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58316</link><description>Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the payment_success.php script that allows attackers to inject malicious SQL through the unfiltered 'cm' parameter. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted SQL queries to retrieve sensitive database information by manipulating the user ID parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67750 | Lightning Flow Scanner is Vulnerable to Code Injection via Unsafe Use of new Function() in APIVersion Rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67750</link><description>Lightning Flow Scanner provides a A CLI plugin, VS Code Extension and GitHub Action for analysis and optimization of Salesforce Flows. Versions 6.10.5 and below allow a maliciously crafted flow metadata file to cause arbitrary JavaScript execution during scanning. The APIVersion rule uses new Function() to evaluate expression strings, enabling an attacker to supply a malicious expression within rule configuration or crafted flow metadata. This could compromise developer machines, CI runners, or editor environments. This issue is fixed in version 6.10.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14578 | itsourcecode Student Management System update_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14578</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /update_account.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14010 | Typora 1.7.4 OS Command Injection via Export PDF Preferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14010</link><description>Typora 1.7.4 contains a command injection vulnerability in the PDF export preferences that allows attackers to execute arbitrary system commands. Attackers can inject malicious commands into the 'run command' input field during PDF export to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58299 | PCMan FTP Server 2.0 Remote Buffer Overflow via &amp;#x27;pwd&amp;#x27; Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58299</link><description>PCMan FTP Server 2.0 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the 'pwd' command that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can send a specially crafted payload during the FTP login process to overwrite memory and potentially gain system access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58305 | WonderCMS 4.3.2 Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution via Module Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58305</link><description>WonderCMS 4.3.2 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript through the module installation endpoint. Attackers can craft a specially designed XSS payload to install a reverse shell module and execute remote commands by tricking an authenticated administrator into accessing a malicious link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58311 | Dormakaba Saflok System 6000 Key Generation Cryptographic Weakness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58311</link><description>Dormakaba Saflok System 6000 contains a predictable key generation algorithm that allows attackers to derive card access keys from a 32-bit unique identifier. Attackers can exploit the deterministic key generation process by calculating valid access keys using a simple mathematical transformation of the card's unique identifier.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58314 | Atcom 2.7.x.x Authenticated Command Injection via Web Configuration CGI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58314</link><description>Atcom 100M IP Phones firmware version 2.7.x.x contains an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the web configuration CGI script that allows attackers to execute arbitrary system commands. Attackers can inject shell commands through the 'cmd' parameter in web_cgi_main.cgi, enabling remote code execution with administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67734 | Frappe Authenticated Users can Execute JavaScript through its Job Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67734</link><description>Frappe Learning Management System (LMS) is a learning system that helps users structure their content. Versions prior to 2.42.0 allowed authenticated attackers to enter JavaScript through the Company Website field of the Job Form, exposing users to an XSS attack. The script could then be executed in the browsers of users who opened the malicious job posting. This issue is fixed in version 2.42.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14572 | UTT 进取 512W formWebAuthGlobalConfig memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14572</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT 进取 512W up to 1.7.7-171114. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/formWebAuthGlobalConfig. Performing manipulation of the argument hidcontact results in memory corruption. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8083 | Vuetify Prototype Pollution via Preset options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8083</link><description>The  Preset configuration https://v2.vuetifyjs.com/en/features/presets  feature of Vuetify is vulnerable to  Prototype Pollution https://cheatsheetseries.owasp.org/cheatsheets/Prototype_Pollution_Prevention_Cheat_Sheet.html  due to the internal 'mergeDeep' utility function used to merge options with defaults. Using a specially-crafted, malicious preset can result in polluting all JavaScript objects with arbitrary properties, which can further negatively affect all aspects of the application's behavior. This can lead to a wide range of security issues, including resource exhaustion/denial of service or unauthorized access to data.

If the application utilizes Server-Side Rendering (SSR), this vulnerability could affect the whole server process.

This issue affects Vuetify versions greater than or equal to 2.2.0-beta.2 and less than 3.0.0-alpha.10.

Note:
Version 2.x of Vuetify is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://v2.vuetifyjs.com/en/about/eol/ .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14174 | Out of bounds memory access in ANGLE in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 143.0.7499.110 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14174</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in ANGLE in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 143.0.7499.110 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14372 | Use after free in Password Manager in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.110 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14372</link><description>Use after free in Password Manager in Google Chrome prior to 143.0.7499.110 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14373 | Inappropriate implementation in Toolbar in Google Chrome on Android prior to 143.0.7499.110 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14373</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Toolbar in Google Chrome on Android prior to 143.0.7499.110 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14570 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System view_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14570</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view_admin.php. This manipulation of the argument admin_id causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14571 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System borrow_book.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14571</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /borrow_book.php. Such manipulation of the argument roll_number leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8082 | Vuetify XSS via unsanitized &amp;#x27;titleDateFormat&amp;#x27; in &amp;#x27;VDatePicker&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8082</link><description>Improper neutralization of the title date in the 'VDatePicker' component in Vuetify, allows unsanitized HTML to be inserted into the page. This can lead to a  Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/xss  attack. The vulnerability occurs because the 'title-date-format' property of the 'VDatePicker' can accept a user created function and assign its output to the 'innerHTML' property of the title element without sanitization.

This issue affects Vuetify versions greater than or equal to 2.0.0 and less than 3.0.0.

Note:
Version 2.x of Vuetify is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://v2.vuetifyjs.com/en/about/eol/ .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14568 | haxxorsid Stock-Management-System User.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14568</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in haxxorsid Stock-Management-System up to fbbbf213e9c93b87183a3891f77e3cc7095f22b0. This impacts an unknown function of the file model/User.php. The manipulation of the argument employee_id/id/admin leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14569 | ggml-org whisper.cpp common-whisper.cpp read_audio_data use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14569</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ggml-org whisper.cpp up to 1.8.2. Affected is the function read_audio_data of the file /whisper.cpp/examples/common-whisper.cpp. The manipulation results in use after free. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40345 | usb: storage: sddr55: Reject out-of-bound new_pba</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40345</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: storage: sddr55: Reject out-of-bound new_pba

Discovered by Atuin - Automated Vulnerability Discovery Engine.

new_pba comes from the status packet returned after each write.
A bogus device could report values beyond the block count derived
from info-&gt;capacity, letting the driver walk off the end of
pba_to_lba[] and corrupt heap memory.

Reject PBAs that exceed the computed block count and fail the
transfer so we avoid touching out-of-range mapping entries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64011 | Nextcloud Server 30.0.0 is vulnerable to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in the /core/preview endpoint. Any authenticated user ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64011</link><description>Nextcloud Server 30.0.0 is vulnerable to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in the /core/preview endpoint. Any authenticated user can access previews of arbitrary files belonging to other users by manipulating the fileId parameter. This allows unauthorized disclosure of sensitive data, such as text files or images, without prior sharing permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29144 | Malwarebytes 1.0.14 for Linux doesn't properly compute signatures in some scenarios. This allows a bypass of detection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29144</link><description>Malwarebytes 1.0.14 for Linux doesn't properly compute signatures in some scenarios. This allows a bypass of detection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67818 | An issue was discovered in Weaviate OSS before 1.33.4. An attacker with access to insert data into the database can craft an entry name with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67818</link><description>An issue was discovered in Weaviate OSS before 1.33.4. An attacker with access to insert data into the database can craft an entry name with an absolute path (e.g., /etc/...) or use parent directory traversal (../../..) to escape the restore root when a backup is restored, potentially creating or overwriting files in arbitrary locations within the application's privilege scope.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67819 | An issue was discovered in Weaviate OSS before 1.33.4. Due to a lack of validation of the fileName field in the transfer logic, an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67819</link><description>An issue was discovered in Weaviate OSS before 1.33.4. Due to a lack of validation of the fileName field in the transfer logic, an attacker who can call the GetFile method while a shard is in the "Pause file activity" state and the FileReplicationService is reachable can read arbitrary files accessible to the service process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67342 | RuoYi versions 4.8.1 and earlier is affected by a stored XSS vulnerability in the /system/menu/edit endpoint. While the endpoint is protecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67342</link><description>RuoYi versions 4.8.1 and earlier is affected by a stored XSS vulnerability in the /system/menu/edit endpoint. While the endpoint is protected by an XSS filter, the protection can be bypassed. Additionally, because the menu is shared across all users, any user with menu modification permissions can impact all users by exploiting this stored XSS vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14567 | haxxorsid Stock-Management-System employees missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14567</link><description>A weakness has been identified in haxxorsid Stock-Management-System up to fbbbf213e9c93b87183a3891f77e3cc7095f22b0. This affects an unknown function of the file /api/employees. Executing manipulation can lead to missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67341 | jshERP versions 3.5 and earlier are affected by a stored XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to upload PDF files containi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67341</link><description>jshERP versions 3.5 and earlier are affected by a stored XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to upload PDF files containing XSS payloads. Additionally, these PDF files can be accessed via static URLs, making them accessible to all users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13733 | BuhoNTFS 1.3.2 - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13733</link><description>BuhoNTFS contains an insecure XPC service that allows local, unprivileged users to escalate their privileges to root via insecure functions.This issue affects BuhoNTFS: 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:25:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67344 | jshERP v3.5 and earlier is affected by a stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /msg/add endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67344</link><description>jshERP v3.5 and earlier is affected by a stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /msg/add endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65854 | Insecure permissions in the scheduled tasks feature of MineAdmin v3.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands and execute a full acco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65854</link><description>Insecure permissions in the scheduled tasks feature of MineAdmin v3.x allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands and execute a full account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65530 | An eval injection in the malware de-obfuscation routines of CloudLinux ai-bolit before v32.7.4 allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65530</link><description>An eval injection in the malware de-obfuscation routines of CloudLinux ai-bolit before v32.7.4 allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files as root via scanning a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66430 | Plesk 18.0 has Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66430</link><description>Plesk 18.0 has Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14565 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem login1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14565</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem up to 42cd892b40a18d50bd4ed1905fa89f939173a464. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /Profilers/SProfile/login1.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14566 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem reg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14566</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem up to 42cd892b40a18d50bd4ed1905fa89f939173a464. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Profilers/SProfile/reg.php. Performing manipulation of the argument USN results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12843 | Code Injection in Wave Term v0.12.2 allowing TCC Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12843</link><description>Code Injection using Electron Fuses in waveterm on MacOS allows TCC Bypass.
This issue affects waveterm: 0.12.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53960 | Apache StreamPark: Uses the user’s password as the secret key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53960</link><description>When encrypting sensitive data, weak encryption keys that are fixed or directly generated based on user passwords are used. Attackers can obtain these keys through methods such as reverse engineering, code leaks, or password guessing, thereby decrypting stored or transmitted encrypted data, leading to the leakage of sensitive information.










This issue affects Apache StreamPark: from 2.0.0 before 2.1.7.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.7, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36743 | SolarEdge SE3680H - Exposed Debug interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36743</link><description>SolarEdge SE3680H has an exposed debug/test interface accessible to unauthenticated actors, allowing disclosure of system internals and execution of debug commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36744 | SolarEdge SE3680H - Information Exposure during Bootloader Loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36744</link><description>SolarEdge SE3680H has unauthenticated disclosure of sensitive information during the bootloader loop. While the device repeatedly initializes and waits for boot instructions, the bootloader emits diagnostic output this behavior can leak operating system information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36745 | SolarEdge SE3680H contains Linux Kernel vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36745</link><description>SolarEdge SE3680H  ships with an outdated Linux kernel containing unpatched vulnerabilities in core subsystems. An attacker with network or local access can exploit these flaws to achieve remote code execution, privilege escalation, or disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36746 | SolarEdge Monitoring Platform contains a XSS upon report deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36746</link><description>SolarEdge monitoring platform contains a Cross‑Site Scripting (XSS) flaw that allows an authenticated user to inject payloads into report names, which may execute in a victim’s browser during a deletion attempt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54947 | Apache StreamPark: Use hard-coded key vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54947</link><description>In Apache StreamPark versions 2.0.0 through 2.1.7, a security vulnerability involving a hard-coded encryption key exists. This vulnerability occurs because the system uses a fixed, immutable key for encryption instead of dynamically generating or securely configuring the key. Attackers may obtain this key through reverse engineering or code analysis, potentially decrypting sensitive data or forging encrypted information, leading to information disclosure or unauthorized system access.

This issue affects Apache StreamPark: from 2.0.0 before 2.1.7.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.7, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54981 | Apache StreamPark: Weak Encryption Algorithm in StreamPark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54981</link><description>Weak Encryption Algorithm in StreamPark, The use of an AES cipher in ECB mode and a weak random number generator for encrypting sensitive data, including JWT tokens, may have risked exposing sensitive authentication data

This issue affects Apache StreamPark: from 2.0.0 before 2.1.7.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.7, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36755 | CleverDisplay BlueOne unauthorized BIOS access through physical USB keyboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36755</link><description>The CleverDisplay BlueOne hardware player is designed with its USB interfaces physically enclosed and inaccessible under normal operating conditions. Researchers demonstrated that, after cicumventing the device’s protective enclosure, it was possible to connect a USB keyboard and press ESC during boot to access the BIOS setup interface. BIOS settings could be viewed but not modified. This behavior slightly increases the attack surface by exposing internal system information (CWE-1244) once the enclosure is removed, but does not allow integrity or availability compromise under standard or tested configurations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58770 | TCG2 TPM RT Not Locked Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58770</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where a user may cause “Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges” by local access. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to escalation of authorization and potentially impact Integrity and Availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13506 | Improper Authorization in Nebim Neyir&amp;#x27;s Nebim V3 ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13506</link><description>Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability in Nebim Neyir Computer Industry and Services Inc. Nebim V3 ERP allows Expanding Control over the Operating System from the Database.This issue affects Nebim V3 ERP: from 2.0.59 before 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 12:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12407 | Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! &amp;lt;= 7.2.2.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Location Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12407</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'location_delete' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete locations via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12408 | Events Manager &amp;lt;= 7.2.2.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12408</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.2.2 via the 'get_location' action due to insufficient restrictions on which locations can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft event locations that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12965 | Magical Posts Display &amp;lt;= 1.2.54 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Magical Posts Accordion Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12965</link><description>The Magical Posts Display plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mpac_title_tag' parameter in the Magical Posts Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.54 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied HTML tag names. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14030 | AI Feeds &amp;lt;= 1.0.22 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;aife_post_meta&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14030</link><description>The AI Feeds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'aife_post_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14065 | Simple Bike Rental &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Booking Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14065</link><description>The Simple Bike Rental plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'simpbire_carica_prenotazioni' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve all booking records containing customers' personally identifiable information (PII), including names, email addresses, and phone numbers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14159 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Data Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14159</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'ays_sccp_results_export_file' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export sensitive plugin data including email addresses, IP addresses, physical addresses, user IDs, and other user information via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The exported data is stored in a publicly accessible file, allowing attackers to receive the sensitive information even though they are not authenticated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14442 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via Exposed CSV Export File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14442</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information exposure due to storage of exported CSV files in a publicly accessible directory with predictable filenames in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive user data including emails, IP addresses, usernames, roles, and location data by directly accessing the exported CSV file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12835 | WooMulti &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12835</link><description>The WooMulti WordPress plugin through 17 does not validate a file parameter when deleting files, which could allow any authenticated users, such as subscriber to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 10:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12841 | Bookit &amp;lt; 2.5.1 – Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12841</link><description>The Bookit WordPress plugin before 2.5.1 has a publicly accessible REST endpoint that allows unauthenticated update of the plugins Stripe payment options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 10:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12348 | Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters &amp;lt;= 5.9.10 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Action Scheduler Task Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12348</link><description>The Icegram Express - Email Subscribers, Newsletters and Marketing Automation Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 5.9.10. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the `run_action_scheduler_task` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute scheduled actions early or repeatedly by guessing action IDs, potentially triggering email sends, maintenance tasks, or other privileged operations, causing unexpected state changes and resource usage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13993 | MailerLite – Signup forms (official) &amp;lt;= 1.7.16 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13993</link><description>The MailerLite – Signup forms (official) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'form_description' and 'success_message' parameters in versions up to, and including, 1.7.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14074 | PDF for Contact Form 7 + Drag and Drop Template Builder &amp;lt;= 6.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14074</link><description>The PDF for Contact Form 7 + Drag and Drop Template Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post duplication due to a missing capability check on the 'rednumber_duplicate' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to duplicate arbitrary posts, including password protected or private ones.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23408 | Apache Fineract: weak password policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23408</link><description>Weak Password Requirements vulnerability in Apache Fineract.

This issue affects Apache Fineract: through 1.10.1. The issue is fixed in version 1.11.0.

Users are encouraged to upgrade to version 1.13.0, the latest release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26866 | Apache HugeGraph-Server: RAFT and deserialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26866</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists where a malicious Raft node can exploit insecure Hessian deserialization within the PD store. The fix enforces IP-based authentication to restrict cluster membership and implements a strict class whitelist to harden the Hessian serialization process against object injection attacks.




Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58130 | Apache Fineract: Server Key not masked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58130</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Apache Fineract.

This issue affects Apache Fineract: through 1.11.0. The issue is fixed in version 1.12.1.

Users are encouraged to upgrade to version 1.13.0, the latest release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58137 | Apache Fineract: IDOR via self-service API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58137</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Apache Fineract.

This issue affects Apache Fineract: through 1.11.0. The issue is fixed in version 1.12.1.

Users are encouraged to upgrade to version 1.13.0, the latest release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 09:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40829 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an uninitialized memory vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40829</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an uninitialized memory vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SLDPRT files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-27146)</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 08:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12960 | Simple CSV Table &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12960</link><description>The Simple CSV Table plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 via the `href` parameter in the `[csv]` shortcode. This is due to insufficient path validation before concatenating user-supplied input to a base directory path. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information such as database credentials and authentication keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 08:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67731 | Servify Express does not enforce rate limiting when parsing JSON</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67731</link><description>Servify Express is a Node.js package to start an Express server and log the port it's running on. Prior to 1.2, the Express server used express.json() without a size limit, which could allow attackers to send extremely large request bodies. This can cause excessive memory usage, degraded performance, or process crashes, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS). Any application using the JSON parser without limits and exposed to untrusted clients is affected. The issue is not a flaw in Express itself, but in configuration. This issue is fixed in version 1.2. To work around, consider adding a limit option to the JSON parser, rate limiting at the application or reverse-proxy level, rejecting unusually large requests before parsing, or using a reverse proxy (such as NGINX) to enforce maximum request body sizes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10583 | WP Fastest Cache Premium &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10583</link><description>The WP Fastest Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 via the 'get_server_time_ajax_request' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11876 | Mailgun Subscriptions &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11876</link><description>The Mailgun Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mailgun_subscription_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13891 | Image Gallery – Photo Grid &amp;amp; Video Gallery (Modula) &amp;lt;= 2.13.3 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Directory Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13891</link><description>The Image Gallery – Photo Grid &amp; Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.13.3. This is due to the modula_list_folders AJAX endpoint that lacks proper path validation and base directory restrictions. While the endpoint verifies user capabilities (Author+ with upload_files and edit_posts permissions), it fails to validate that user-supplied directory paths reside within safe directories. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to enumerate arbitrary directories on the server via the modula_list_folders endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14049 | VikRentItems Flexible Rental Management System &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;delto&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14049</link><description>The VikRentItems Flexible Rental Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'delto' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14169 | FunnelKit – Funnel Builder for WooCommerce Checkout &amp;lt;= 3.13.1.5 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14169</link><description>The FunnelKit - Funnel Builder for WooCommerce Checkout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'opid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.1.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4970 | BSK PDF Manager &amp;lt;= 3.7.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4970</link><description>The BSK PDF Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67730 | Frappe authenticated users can execute XSS through form description fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67730</link><description>Frappe Learning Management System (LMS) is a learning system that helps users structure their content. Versions prior to 2.42.0 allow authenticated users to add malicious HTML and JavaScript through description fields in the Job, Course and Batch forms. This issue is fixed in version 2.42.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67728 | Fireshare Public Uploads feature is vulnerable to OS Command Injection (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67728</link><description>Fireshare facilitates self-hosted media and link sharing. Versions 1.2.30 and below allow an authenticated user, or unauthenticated user if the Public Uploads setting is enabled, to craft a malicious filename when uploading a video file. The malicious filename is then concatenated directly into a shell command, which can be used for uploading files to arbitrary directories via path traversal, or executing system commands for Remote Code Execution (RCE). This issue is fixed in version 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67737 | AzuraCast Vulnerable to Pre-Auth File Deletion &amp;amp; Admin RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67737</link><description>AzuraCast is a self-hosted, all-in-one web radio management suite. Versions 0.23.1 mistakenly include an API endpoint that is intended for internal use by the SFTP software sftpgo, exposing it to the public-facing HTTP API for AzuraCast installations. A user with specific internal knowledge of a station's operations can craft a custom HTTP request that would affect the contents of a station's database, without revealing any internal information about the station. In order to carry out an attack, a malicious user would need to know a valid SFTP station username and the coordinating internal filesystem structure. This issue is fixed in version 0.23.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12570 | Fancy Product Designer &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12570</link><description>The Fancy Product Designer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping in the data-to-image.php and pdf-to-image.php files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12655 | Hippoo Mobile App for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12655</link><description>The Hippoo Mobile App for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file write via a missing authorization check in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to the REST API endpoint `/wp-json/hippoo/v1/wc/token/save_callback/{token_id}` being registered with `permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true'`, which allows unauthenticated access. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to write arbitrary JSON content to the server's publicly accessible upload directory via the vulnerable endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13660 | Guest Support &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Unauthenticated User Email Disclosure in guest_support_handler AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13660</link><description>The Guest Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to User Email Disclosure in versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This is due to the plugin exposing a public AJAX endpoint that allows anyone to search for and retrieve user email addresses without any authentication or capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enumerate user accounts and extract email addresses via the guest_support_handler=ajax endpoint with the request=get_users parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14068 | WPNakama &amp;lt;= 0.6.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;order_by&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14068</link><description>The WPNakama plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'order_by' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.6.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14356 | Ultra Addons for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.5.33 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) to Generate Form Submission PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14356</link><description>The Ultra Addons for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'uacf7_get_generated_pdf' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.33. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to generate and get form submission PDF, when the "PDF Generator" and the "Database" addons are enabled (disabled by default).</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67727 | Parse Server GitHub CI workflow vulnerable to RCE through Improper Privilege Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67727</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that runs Node.js. In versions prior to 8.6.0-alpha.2, a GitHub CI workflow is triggered in a way that grants the GitHub Actions workflow elevated permissions, giving it access to GitHub secrets and write permissions which are defined in the workflow. Code from a fork or lifecycle scripts is potentially included. Only the repository's CI/CD infrastructure is affected, including any public GitHub forks with GitHub Actions enabled. This issue is fixed version 8.6.0-alpha.2 and commits 6b9f896 and e3d27fe.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67726 | Tornado is Vulnerable to Quadratic DoS via Crafted Multipart Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67726</link><description>Tornado is a Python web framework and asynchronous networking library. Versions 6.5.2 and below use an inefficient algorithm when parsing parameters for HTTP header values, potentially causing a DoS. The _parseparam function in httputil.py is used to parse specific HTTP header values, such as those in multipart/form-data and repeatedly calls string.count() within a nested loop while processing quoted semicolons. If an attacker sends a request with a large number of maliciously crafted parameters in a Content-Disposition header, the server's CPU usage increases quadratically (O(n²)) during parsing. Due to Tornado's single event loop architecture, a single malicious request can cause the entire server to become unresponsive for an extended period. This issue is fixed in version 6.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10684 | Construction Light &amp;lt; 1.6.8 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10684</link><description>The Construction Light WordPress theme before 1.6.8 does not have authorisation and CSRF when activating  via an AJAX action, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to activate arbitrary .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 06:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67725 | Tornado is Vulnerable to Quadratic DoS via Repeated Header Coalescing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67725</link><description>Tornado is a Python web framework and asynchronous networking library. In versions 6.5.2 and below, a single maliciously crafted HTTP request can block the server's event loop for an extended period, caused by the HTTPHeaders.add method. The function accumulates values using string concatenation when the same header name is repeated, causing a Denial of Service (DoS).  Due to Python string immutability, each concatenation copies the entire string, resulting in O(n²) time complexity. The severity can vary from high if max_header_size has been increased from its default, to low if it has its default value of 64KB. This issue is fixed in version 6.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67724 | Tornado vulnerable to Header Injection and XSS via reason argument</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67724</link><description>Tornado is a Python web framework and asynchronous networking library. In versions 6.5.2 and below, the supplied reason phrase is used unescaped in HTTP headers (where it could be used for header injection) or in HTML in the default error page (where it could be used for XSS) and can be exploited by passing untrusted or malicious data into the reason argument. Used by both RequestHandler.set_status and tornado.web.HTTPError, the argument is designed to allow applications to pass custom "reason" phrases (the "Not Found" in HTTP/1.1 404 Not Found) to the HTTP status line (mainly for non-standard status codes). This issue is fixed in version 6.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67508 | gardenctl Gardener projects are vulnerable to Command Injection when used with non‑POSIX shells</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67508</link><description>gardenctl is a command-line client for the Gardener which configures access to clusters and cloud provider CLI tools. When using non‑POSIX shells such as Fish and PowerShell, versions 2.11.0 and below of gardenctl allow an attacker with administrative privileges for a Gardener project to craft malicious credential values. The forged credential values are used in infrastructure Secret objects that break out of the intended string context when evaluated in Fish or PowerShell environments used by the Gardener service operators. This issue is fixed in version 2.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53523 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities exist in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53523</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities exist in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. A logged-in user can prepare a malicious page or URL, and an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser when another user accesses it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54407 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54407</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. If a user accesses a crafted page or URL, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57883 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57883</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. If a user accesses a crafted page or URL, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58576 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58576</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. If a user accesses a malicious page while logged in, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61950 | In GroupSession, a Circular notice can be created with its memo field non-editable, but the authorization check is improperly implemented. W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61950</link><description>In GroupSession, a Circular notice can be created with its memo field non-editable, but the authorization check is improperly implemented. With some crafted request, a logged-in user may alter the memo field. The affected products and versions are GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61987 | GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. do not validat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61987</link><description>GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. do not validate origins in WebSockets. If a user accesses a crafted page, Chat information sent to the user may be exposed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62192 | SQL Injection vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62192</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.3.0, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.3.3, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.3.2. If exploited, information stored in the database may be obtained or altered by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64781 | In GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.7.1, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.7.1, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.7.1, "External p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64781</link><description>In GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.7.1, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.7.1, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.7.1, "External page display restriction" is set to "Do not limit" in the initial configuration. With this configuration, the user may be redirected to an arbitrary website when accessing a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65120 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.7.1, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.7.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65120</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.7.1, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.7.1, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.7.1. If a user accesses a crafted page or URL, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66284 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities exist in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.7.1, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.7.1, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66284</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities exist in GroupSession Free edition prior to ver5.7.1, GroupSession byCloud prior to ver5.7.1, and GroupSession ZION prior to ver5.7.1. A logged-in user can prepare a malicious page or URL, and an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser when another user accesses it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66492 | Masa CMS vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) through URL Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66492</link><description>Masa CMS is an open source Enterprise Content Management platform. Versions 7.2.8 and below, 7.3.1 through 7.3.13, 7.4.0-alpha.1 through 7.4.8 and 7.5.0 through 7.5.1 are vulnerable to XSS when an unsanitized value of the ajax URL query parameter is directly included within the  section of the HTML page. An attacker can execute arbitrary scripts in the context of the user's session, potentially leading to Session Hijacking, Data Theft, Defacement and Malware Distribution. This issue is fixed in versions 7.5.2, 7.4.9, 7.3.14, and 7.2.9. To work around this issue, configure a Web Application Firewall (WAF) rule (e.g., ModSecurity) to block requests containing common XSS payload characters in the ajax query parameter. Alternatively, implement server-side sanitization using middleware to strip or escape dangerous characters from the ajax parameter before it reaches the vulnerable rendering logic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12650 | Simple post listing &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12650</link><description>The Simple post listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class_name' parameter in the postlist shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page via mouse interaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12783 | Premmerce Brands for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 - Missing Authorization To Authenticated (Subscriber+) Brand Permalink Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12783</link><description>The Premmerce Brands for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the saveBrandsSettings function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify brand permalink settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12824 | Player Leaderboard 1.0.0 - 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12824</link><description>The Player Leaderboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 via the 'player_leaderboard' shortcode. This is due to the plugin using an unsanitized user-supplied value from the shortcode's 'mode' attribute in a call to include() without proper path validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve full remote code execution if combined with file upload capabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12830 | Better Elementor Addons &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Slider Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12830</link><description>The Better Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12834 | Accept Stripe Payments Using Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via failure_message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12834</link><description>The Accept Stripe Payments Using Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'failure_message' parameter in versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12883 | Campay Woocommerce Payment Gateway &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Unauthenticated Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12883</link><description>The Campay Woocommerce Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Payment Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This is due to the plugin not properly validating that a transaction has occurred through the payment gateway. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass payments and mark orders as successfully completed resulting in a loss of income.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12963 | LazyTasks – Project &amp;amp; Task Management with Collaboration, Kanban and Gantt Chart &amp;lt;= 1.2.29 - Missing Authorization to Uanuthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12963</link><description>The LazyTasks – Project &amp; Task Management with Collaboration, Kanban and Gantt Chart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.29. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity via the 'wp-json/lazytasks/api/v1/user/role/edit/' REST API endpoint prior to updating their details like email address. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account. It is also possible for attackers to abuse this endpoint to grant users with access to additional roles within the plugin</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12968 | Infility Global &amp;lt;= 2.14.23 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12968</link><description>The Infility Global plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation and capability checks in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.23. This is due to the `upload_file` function in the `infility_import_file` class only validating the MIME type which can be easily spoofed, and the `import_data` function missing capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13314 | Product Filtering by Categories, Tags, Price Range for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13314</link><description>The Product Filtering by Categories, Tags, Price Range for WooCommerce – Filter Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to a missing capability check on the 'filter_save_settings' and 'add_filter_options' AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings and create arbitrary filter options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13320 | WP User Manager &amp;lt;= 2.9.12 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via &amp;#x27;current_user_avatar&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13320</link><description>The WP User Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Deletion in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied file paths in the profile update functionality combined with improper handling of array inputs by PHP's filter_input() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server via the 'current_user_avatar' parameter in a two-stage attack which can make remote code execution possible. This only affects sites with the custom avatar setting enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13334 | Blaze Demo Importer 1.0.0 - 1.0.13 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Database Reset and File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13334</link><description>The Blaze Demo Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized database resets and file deletion due to a missing capability check on the "blaze_demo_importer_install_demo" function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to reset the database by truncating all tables (except options, usermeta, and users), delete all sidebar widgets, theme modifications, and content of the uploads folder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13363 | IMAQ Core &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to URL Structure Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13363</link><description>The IMAQ Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the URL structure settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's URL structure settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13366 | Rabbit Hole &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13366</link><description>The Rabbit Hole plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the plugin's reset functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The vulnerability is exacerbated by the fact that the reset operation is performed via a GET request, making exploitation trivial via image tags or hyperlinks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13408 | Foxtool All-in-One: Contact chat button, Custom login, Media optimize images &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Google OAuth Connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13408</link><description>The Foxtool All-in-One: Contact chat button, Custom login, Media optimize images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the foxtool_login_google() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to establish an OAuth Connection via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13440 | Premmerce Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Wishlist Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13440</link><description>The Premmerce Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.10. This is due to a missing capability check on the deleteWishlist() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary wishlists.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13747 | NewStatPress &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13747</link><description>The NewStatPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a regex bypass in nsp_shortcode function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13840 | BUKAZU Search widget &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;shortcode&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13840</link><description>The BUKAZU Search widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'shortcode' parameter of the 'bukazu_search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13843 | VigLink SpotLight By ShortCode &amp;lt;= 1.0.a - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;float&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13843</link><description>The VigLink SpotLight By ShortCode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'float' parameter of the 'spotlight' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.a due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13846 | Easy Map Creator &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13846</link><description>The Easy Map Creator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'width' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13850 | LS Google Map Router &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13850</link><description>The LS Google Map Router plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'map_type' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13866 | Flow-Flow Social Feed Stream 3.0.0 - 4.7.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via flow_flow_social_auth AJAX action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13866</link><description>The Flow-Flow Social Feed Stream plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the flow_flow_social_auth AJAX action in versions 3.0.0 to 4.7.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify plugin settings and store arbitrary JavaScript that executes whenever the plugin settings page is viewed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13884 | Hide Email Address &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13884</link><description>The Hide Email Address plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'inline_css' parameter in the `bg-hide-email-address` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13885 | Zenost Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13885</link><description>The Zenost Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'link' and 'target' parameters in the `button` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13889 | Simple Nivo Slider &amp;lt;= 0.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13889</link><description>The Simple Nivo Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' shortcode parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13904 | WPGancio &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13904</link><description>The WPGancio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gancio-event' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13906 | WP Flot &amp;lt;= 0.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13906</link><description>The WP Flot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'linechart' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13960 | GPXpress &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13960</link><description>The GPXpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gpxpress' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13961 | Data Visualizer &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13961</link><description>The Data Visualizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'visualize' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13962 | Divelogs Widget &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13962</link><description>The Divelogs Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'latestdive' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13963 | FX Currency Converter &amp;lt;= 0.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13963</link><description>The FX Currency Converter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'fxcc_convert' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13966 | Paypal Payment Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.01 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;buttom_image&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13966</link><description>The Paypal Payment Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'buttom_image' parameter of the [paypal-shortcode] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.01 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13969 | Reviews Sorted &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;space&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13969</link><description>The Reviews Sorted plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'space' parameter of the [reviews-slider] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13971 | TWW Protein Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.0.24 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Header&amp;#x27; Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13971</link><description>The TWW Protein Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Header' setting in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13972 | WatchTowerHQ &amp;lt;= 3.15.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Read via &amp;#x27;wht_download_big_object_origin&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13972</link><description>The WatchTowerHQ plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read via the 'wht_download_big_object_origin' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.15.0. This is due to insufficient path validation in the handle_big_object_download_request function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and a valid access token, to read arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information such as database credentials and authentication keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13975 | Contact Form 7 with ChatWork &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;api_token&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;roomid&amp;#x27; Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13975</link><description>The Contact Form 7 with ChatWork plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'api_token' and 'roomid' settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the settings page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13987 | Purchase and Expense Manager &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Purchase Record Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13987</link><description>The Purchase and Expense Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'sup_pt_handle_deletion' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary purchase records via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13988 | 评论小秘书 &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13988</link><description>The 评论小秘书 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in the plugin's settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13989 | WP Dropzone &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;callback&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13989</link><description>The WP Dropzone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'callback' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied 'callback' attributes, which are evaluated as JavaScript code via the `new Function()` constructor. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14032 | Bold Timeline Lite &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;title&amp;#x27; Parameter in &amp;#x27;bold_timeline_group&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14032</link><description>The Bold Timeline Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter in the 'bold_timeline_group' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14035 | DebateMaster &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Color Options via &amp;#x27;debate&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14035</link><description>The DebateMaster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the color options in the plugin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses a page with the debate shortcode. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14044 | Visitor Logic Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via &amp;#x27;lpblocks&amp;#x27; Cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14044</link><description>The Visitor Logic Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `lpblocks` cookie. This is due to the `lp_track()` function passing unsanitized cookie data directly to the `unserialize()` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code granted they can access the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14045 | URL Media Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Safe File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14045</link><description>The URL Media Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized safe file uploads due to a missing capability check on the url_media_uploader_url_upload_ajax_handler() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload safe media files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14048 | SimplyConvert &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;simplyconvert_hash&amp;#x27; Option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14048</link><description>The SimplyConvert plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'simplyconvert_hash' option in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14062 | Animated Pixel Marquee Creator &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;marquee&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14062</link><description>The Animated Pixel Marquee Creator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery via the 'marquee' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the marquee deletion function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary marquees via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14064 | BuddyTask &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Cross-Group Task Board Access and Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14064</link><description>The BuddyTask plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view, create, modify, and delete task boards belonging to any BuddyPress group, including private and hidden groups they are not members of.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14119 | App Landing Template Blocks for WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14119</link><description>The App Landing Template Blocks for WPBakery (Visual Composer) Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'atvc_video_play' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14125 | Complag &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14125</link><description>The Complag plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14129 | Like DisLike Voting &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14129</link><description>The Like DisLike Voting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14132 | Category Dropdown List &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14132</link><description>The Category Dropdown List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14137 | Simple AL Slider &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14137</link><description>The Simple AL Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14138 | WPLG Default Mail From &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14138</link><description>The WPLG Default Mail From plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14143 | Ayo Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;color&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14143</link><description>The Ayo Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'color' parameter of the ayo_action shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14158 | Coding Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14158</link><description>The Coding Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings including the theme configuration via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14160 | Upcoming for Calendly &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14160</link><description>The Upcoming for Calendly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's Calendly API key via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14161 | Truefy Embed &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to &amp;#x27;truefy_embed_options_update&amp;#x27; Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14161</link><description>The Truefy Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'truefy_embed_options_update' settings update action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings, including the API key, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14162 | BMLT WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.11.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Creation and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14162</link><description>The BMLT WordPress Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.4. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'BMLTPlugin_create_option' and 'BMLTPlugin_delete_option ' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14165 | Kirim.Email WooCommerce Integration &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14165</link><description>The Kirim.Email WooCommerce Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9. This is due to missing nonce validation on the plugin's settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's API credentials and integration settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14166 | WPMasterToolKit (WPMTK) &amp;lt;= 2.13.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14166</link><description>The WPMasterToolKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.13.0. This is due to the plugin allowing Author-level users to create and execute arbitrary PHP code through the Code Snippets feature without proper capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server, leading to remote code execution, privilege escalation, and complete site compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14170 | Vimeo SimpleGallery &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14170</link><description>The Vimeo SimpleGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to missing authorization checks on the `vimeogallery_admin` function hooked to `admin_menu`. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify arbitrary plugin settings via the `action` parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14344 | Multi Uploader for Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14344</link><description>The Multi Uploader for Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'plupload_ajax_delete_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14354 | Resource Library for Logged In Users &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Multiple Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14354</link><description>The Resource Library for Logged In Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing nonce validation on multiple administrative functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform various unauthorized actions including creating, editing, and deleting resources and categories via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14391 | Simple Theme Changer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Theme Switcher Configuration Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14391</link><description>The Simple Theme Changer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14392 | Simple Theme Changer &amp;lt;= 1.0. - Missing Authorization to Plugin Settings Update via AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14392</link><description>The Simple Theme Changer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the user_theme_admin, display_method_admin, and set_change_theme_button_name actions actions in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14393 | Wpik WordPress Basic Ajax Form &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14393</link><description>The Wpik WordPress Basic Ajax Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'dname' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14467 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Job Description Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14467</link><description>The WP Job Portal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.9. This is due to the plugin explicitly whitelisting the `</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13052 | An improper certificates validation vulnerability was found in the Notification settings of ADM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13052</link><description>When the user set the Notification's sender to send emails to the SMTP server via msmtp, an improper validated TLS/SSL certificates allows an attacker who can intercept network traffic between the SMTP client and server to execute a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack, which may obtain the sensitive information of the SMTP.

Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.RKD2 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.0.RN42.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13053 | A missing encryption of sensitive data vulnerability was found in the UPS settings of ADM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13053</link><description>When a user configures the NAS to retrieve UPS status or control the UPS, a non-enforced TLS certificate verification can allow an attacker able to intercept network traffic between the client and server can perform a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack, which may obtain the sensitive information of the UPS server configuation.

This issue affects ADM: from 4.1.0 through 4.3.3.RKD2, from 5.0.0 through 5.1.0.RN42.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13669 | High Level Synthesis Compiler Security Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13669</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in Altera High Level Synthesis Compiler on Windows allows Search Order Hijacking.This issue affects High Level Synthesis Compiler: from 19.1 through 24.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13670 | High Level Synthesis Compiler Security Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13670</link><description>The High Level Synthesis Compiler i++ command for Windows is vulnerable to a DLL planting vulnerability</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 03:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13665 | Quartus Prime Standard Security Advisory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13665</link><description>The System Console Utility for Windows is vulnerable to a DLL planting vulnerability</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13839 | LJUsers &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;name&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13839</link><description>The LJUsers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'name' parameter of the 'ljuser' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13886 | LT Unleashed &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via &amp;#x27;template&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13886</link><description>The LT Unleashed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 via the 'template' parameter in the `book` shortcode due to insufficient path sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where files such as wp-config.php can be included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 02:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10451 | H19Int15CallbackSmm: SMM memory corruption vulnerability in combined DXE/SMM (SMRAM write)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10451</link><description>Unchecked output buffer may allowed arbitrary code execution in SMM and potentially result in SMM memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>