<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-58435 | Open OnDemand didn&amp;#x27;t rotate password for VNC batch_connect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58435</link><description>Open OnDemand is an open-source HPC portal. Prior to versions 3.1.15 and 4.0.7, noVNC interactive applications did not correctly rotate the password when TurboVNC was higher than version 3.1.2. The likelihood of exploitation is low as a user would need to share their link to an active desktop session and the other user would need to be authenticated to the portal. But obtaining the link would allow that user to perform any actions as the original user and access their data. Open OnDemand 3.1.15 and 4.0.7 have patched this vulnerability and correctly rotate passwords for any version of TurboVNC. As a workaround, downgrade TurboVNC to a version lower than 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58442 | Saleor has user enumeration vulnerability due to different error messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58442</link><description>Saleor is an e-commerce platform. Starting in version 3.21.0 and prior to version 3.21.16, requesting certain fields in the response of `accountRegister` may result in errors that could unintentionally reveal whether a user with the provided email already exists in Saleor. Version 3.21.16 fixes the issue. As a workaround, rate-limit the mutation to reduce the impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34172 | Netgate pfSense CE HAProxy Package 0.63_10 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34172</link><description>In pfSense CE /usr/local/www/haproxy/haproxy_stats.php, the value of the showsticktablecontent parameter is displayed after being read from HTTP GET requests. This can enable reflected cross-site scripting when the victim is authenticated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36011 | IBM Jazz for Service Management information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36011</link><description>IBM Jazz for Service Management 1.1.3.0 through 1.1.3.24 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58180 | OctoPrint is Vulnerable to RCE Attacks via Unsanitized Filename in File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58180</link><description>OctoPrint provides a web interface for controlling consumer 3D printers. OctoPrint versions up until and including 1.11.2 contain a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to upload a file under a specially crafted filename that will allow arbitrary command execution if said filename becomes included in a command defined in a system event handler and said event gets triggered. If no event handlers executing system commands with uploaded filenames as parameters have been configured, this vulnerability does not have an impact. The vulnerability is patched in version 1.11.3. As a workaround, OctoPrint administrators who have event handlers configured that include any kind of filename based placeholders should disable those by setting their `enabled` property to `False` or unchecking the "Enabled" checkbox in the GUI based Event Manager. Alternatively, OctoPrint administrators should set `feature.enforceReallyUniversalFilenames` to `true` in `config.yaml` and restart OctoPrint, then vet the existing uploads and make sure to delete any suspicious looking files. As always, OctoPrint administrators are advised to not expose OctoPrint on hostile networks like the public internet, and to vet who has access to their instance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58430 | listmonk Vulnerable to CSRF to XSS Chain That Can Lead to Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58430</link><description>listmonk is a standalone, self-hosted, newsletter and mailing list manager. In versions up to and including 1.1.0, every http request in addition to the session cookie `session` there included `nonce`. The value is not checked and validated by the backend, removing `nonce` allows the requests to be processed correctly. This may seem harmless, but if chained to other vulnerabilities it can become a critical vulnerability. Cross-site request forgery and cross-site scripting chained together can result in improper admin account creation. As of time of publication, no patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36125 | IBM Hardware Management Console - Power Systems cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36125</link><description>IBM Hardware Management Console - Power 10.3.1050.0 and 11.1.1110.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58063 | CoreDNS: DNS Cache Pinning via etcd Lease ID Confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58063</link><description>CoreDNS is a DNS server that chains plugins. Starting in version 1.2.0 and prior to version 1.12.4, the CoreDNS etcd plugin contains a TTL confusion vulnerability where lease IDs are incorrectly used as TTL values, enabling DNS cache pinning attacks. This effectively creates a DoS condition for DNS resolution of affected services. The `TTL()` function in `plugin/etcd/etcd.go` incorrectly casts etcd lease IDs (64-bit integers) to uint32 and uses them as TTL values. Large lease IDs become very large TTLs when cast to uint32. This enables cache pinning attacks. Version 1.12.4 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47415 | RECWAVE Filepath Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47415</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CRESTRON TOUCHSCREENS x70 allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects TOUCHSCREENS x70: from 3.000.0110.001 before 3.001.0031.001.











Confirmed Affected Hardware: TSW-760, TSW-1060 



Confirmed Affected Firmware: 3.002.1061 - (no fix released, product discontinued)



 

For x70  



The Affected Firmware:- 3.000.0110.001  and versions below 



The Fixed Firmware:- 3.001.0031.001</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43786 | Enumeration of ERC from object entry in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.1, 2024.Q2.0 throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43786</link><description>Enumeration of ERC from object entry in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.1, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, 2023.Q4.0 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allow attackers to determine existent ERC in the application by exploit the time response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55053 | CWE-328: Use of Weak Hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55053</link><description>CWE-328: Use of Weak Hash</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55054 | CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting')</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55054</link><description>CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55051 | CWE-1392: Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55051</link><description>CWE-1392: Use of Default Credentials</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55052 | CWE-200 Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55052</link><description>CWE-200 Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55050 | CWE-1242: Inclusion of Undocumented Features</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55050</link><description>CWE-1242: Inclusion of Undocumented Features</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43781 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.110 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43781</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.110 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.8, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the URL in search bar portlet</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55049 | Use of Default Cryptographic Key (CWE-1394)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55049</link><description>Use of Default Cryptographic Key (CWE-1394)</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55729 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the ConfluenceLayoutSection macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55729</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the ac:type in the ConfluenceLayoutSection macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page The classes parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution. Version 1.26.5 has a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55730 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the confluence paste code macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55730</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the title in the confluence paste code macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page. The classes parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution. Version 1.26.5 has a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57060 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the rules parameter in the dns_forward_rule_store function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57060</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the rules parameter in the dns_forward_rule_store function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55047 | CWE-798 Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55047</link><description>CWE-798 Use of Hard-coded Credentials</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55048 | Multiple CWE-78</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55048</link><description>Multiple CWE-78</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55728 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the panel macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55728</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the classes parameter in the panel macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page The classes parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution. Version 1.26.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10164 | lmsys sglang update_weights_from_tensor main deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10164</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in lmsys sglang 0.4.6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file /update_weights_from_tensor. The manipulation of the argument serialized_named_tensors results in deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29089 | An issue in TP-Link AX10 Ax1500 v.1.3.10 Build (20230130) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29089</link><description>An issue in TP-Link AX10 Ax1500 v.1.3.10 Build (20230130) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55727 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution from width parameter in the column macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55727</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the width parameter in the column macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page or who can access the CKEditor converter. The width parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution when the macro has been installed by a user with programming right, or it at least allows executing Velocity code as the wiki admin. Version 1.26.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54242 | Premiere Pro | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54242</link><description>Premiere Pro versions 25.3, 24.6.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file, and scope is unchanged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54256 | Dreamweaver Desktop | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) (CWE-352)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54256</link><description>Dreamweaver Desktop versions 21.5 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must click on a malicious link, and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57278 | The LB-Link BL-CPE300M AX300 4G LTE Router firmware version BL-R8800_B10_ALK_SL_V01.01.02P42U14_06 does not implement proper session handlin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57278</link><description>The LB-Link BL-CPE300M AX300 4G LTE Router firmware version BL-R8800_B10_ALK_SL_V01.01.02P42U14_06 does not implement proper session handling. After a user authenticates from a specific IP address, the router grants access to any other client using that same IP, without requiring credentials or verifying client identity. There are no session tokens, cookies, or unique identifiers in place. This flaw allows an attacker to obtain full administrative access simply by configuring their device to use the same IP address as a previously authenticated user. This results in a complete authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43775 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.5, 2024...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43775</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.5, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.12, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via remote app title field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57085 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the v17 parameter in the UploadCfg function. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57085</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the v17 parameter in the UploadCfg function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57086 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the String parameter in the formDeleteMeshNode function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57086</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the String parameter in the formDeleteMeshNode function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57665 | Element Plus Link component (el-link) through 2.10.6 implements insufficient input validation for the href attribute, creating a security ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57665</link><description>Element Plus Link component (el-link) through 2.10.6 implements insufficient input validation for the href attribute, creating a security abstraction gap that obscures URL-based attack vectors. The component passes user-controlled href values directly to underlying anchor elements without protocol validation, URL sanitization, or security headers. This allows attackers to inject malicious URLs using dangerous protocols (javascript:, data:, file:) or redirect users to external malicious sites. While native HTML anchor elements present similar risks, UI component libraries bear additional responsibility for implementing security safeguards and providing clear risk documentation. The vulnerability enables XSS attacks, phishing campaigns, and open redirect exploits affecting applications that use Element Plus Link components with user-controlled or untrusted URL inputs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10198 | LizardBytes Sunshine for Windows contains a DLL search-order hijacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10198</link><description>Sunshine for Windows, version v2025.122.141614, contains a DLL search-order hijacking vulnerability, allowing attackers to insert a malicious DLL in user-writeable PATH directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10199 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in LizardBytes&amp;#x27; Sunshine for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10199</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Sunshine for Windows (version v2025.122.141614 and likely prior versions) due to an unquoted service path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57078 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pppoeServerWhiteMacIndex parameter in the formModifyPppAuthWhi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57078</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pppoeServerWhiteMacIndex parameter in the formModifyPppAuthWhiteMac function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9269 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability found in embedded web server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9269</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the embedded web server in various Lexmark devices. This vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to force the device to send an arbitrary HTTP request to a third-party server. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to internal network access / potential data disclosure from a device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57087 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the countryCode parameter in the werlessAdvancedSet function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57087</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the countryCode parameter in the werlessAdvancedSet function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47997 | Microsoft SQL Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47997</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49692 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49692</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49734 | PowerShell Direct Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49734</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53796 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53796</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53797 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53797</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53798 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53798</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53799 | Windows Imaging Component Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53799</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53800 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53800</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53801 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53801</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53802 | Windows Bluetooth Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53802</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53803 | Windows Kernel Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53803</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53804 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53804</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53805 | HTTP.sys Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53805</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53806 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53806</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53807 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53807</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53808 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53808</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53809 | Local Security Authority Subsystem Service (LSASS) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53809</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53810 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53810</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54091 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54091</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54092 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54092</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54093 | Windows TCP/IP Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54093</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54094 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54094</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54095 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54095</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54096 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54096</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54097 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54097</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54098 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54098</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54099 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54099</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54101 | Windows SMB Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54101</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54102 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54102</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54103 | Windows Management Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54103</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54104 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54104</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54105 | Microsoft Brokering File System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54105</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54106 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54106</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54107 | MapUrlToZone Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54107</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54108 | Capability Access Management Service (camsvc) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54108</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54109 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54109</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54110 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54110</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54111 | Windows UI XAML Phone DatePickerFlyout Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54111</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54112 | Microsoft Virtual Hard Disk Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54112</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54113 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54113</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54114 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service (Cdpsvc) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54114</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54115 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54115</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54116 | Windows MultiPoint Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54116</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54261 | ColdFusion | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54261</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.3, 2023.15, 2021.21 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution by an attacker. Scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54894 | Local Security Authority Subsystem Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54894</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54895 | SPNEGO Extended Negotiation (NEGOEX) Security Mechanism Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54895</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54896 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54896</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54897 | Microsoft SharePoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54897</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54898 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54898</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54899 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54899</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54900 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54900</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54901 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54901</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54902 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54902</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54903 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54903</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54904 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54904</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54905 | Microsoft Word Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54905</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54906 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54906</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54907 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54907</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54908 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54908</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54910 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54910</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54911 | Windows BitLocker Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54911</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54912 | Windows BitLocker Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54912</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54913 | Windows UI XAML Maps MapControlSettings Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54913</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54915 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54915</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54916 | Windows NTFS Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54916</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54917 | MapUrlToZone Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54917</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54918 | Windows NTLM Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54918</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54919 | Windows Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54919</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55223 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55224 | Windows Hyper-V Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55224</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55225 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55225</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55226 | Graphics Kernel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55226</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55227 | Microsoft SQL Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55227</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55228 | Windows Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55228</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55232 | Microsoft High Performance Compute (HPC) Pack Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55232</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55234 | Windows SMB Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55234</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55236 | Graphics Kernel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55236</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55243 | Microsoft OfficePlus Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55243</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55245 | Xbox Gaming Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55245</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55316 | Azure Arc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55316</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55317 | Microsoft AutoUpdate (MAU) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55317</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57070 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the gstUp parameter in the guestWifiRuleRefresh function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57070</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the gstUp parameter in the guestWifiRuleRefresh function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57071 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the vpnUsers parameter in the formAddVpnUsers function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57071</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the vpnUsers parameter in the formAddVpnUsers function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57072 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the staticRouteGateway parameter in the formSetStaticRoute functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57072</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the staticRouteGateway parameter in the formSetStaticRoute function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57062 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the delDhcpIndex parameter in the formDelDhcpRule function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57062</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the delDhcpIndex parameter in the formDelDhcpRule function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57063 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the portMappingIndex parameter in the formDelPortMapping function....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57063</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the portMappingIndex parameter in the formDelPortMapping function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57069 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pPppUser parameter in the getsinglepppuser function. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57069</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pPppUser parameter in the getsinglepppuser function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54246 | Adobe Experience Manager | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54246</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54247 | Adobe Experience Manager | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54247</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54248 | Adobe Experience Manager | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54248</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read access. Scope is changed</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54249 | Adobe Experience Manager | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) (CWE-918)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54249</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to manipulate server-side requests and bypass security controls allowing unauthorized read access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54250 | Adobe Experience Manager | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54250</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54251 | Adobe Experience Manager | XML Injection (aka Blind XPath Injection) (CWE-91)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54251</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an XML Injection vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to manipulate XML queries and gain limited unauthorized write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54252 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54252</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. This could result in bypassing security features within the application. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57061 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formIPMacBindModify function via the ruleId, ip, mac, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57061</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formIPMacBindModify function via the ruleId, ip, mac, v6 and remark parameters. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57064 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the bindDhcpIndex parameter in the modifyDhcpRule function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57064</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the bindDhcpIndex parameter in the modifyDhcpRule function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57538 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the HTTP Proxy field within the Datacenter configuration panel of Proxmox Virtual Envir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57538</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the HTTP Proxy field within the Datacenter configuration panel of Proxmox Virtual Environment (PVE) 8.4 allows an authenticated user to inject malicious input. The input is stored and executed in the context of other users' browsers when they view the affected configuration page. This can lead to arbitrary JavaScript execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57539 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the U2F Origin field of the Datacenter configuration in Proxmox Virtual Environment (PV...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57539</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the U2F Origin field of the Datacenter configuration in Proxmox Virtual Environment (PVE) 8.4 allows authenticated users to store malicious input. The payload is rendered unsafely in the Web UI and executed when viewed by other users, potentially leading to session hijacking or other attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57540 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the WebAuthn Relying Party field within the Datacenter configuration of Proxmox ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57540</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the WebAuthn Relying Party field within the Datacenter configuration of Proxmox Virtual Environment (PVE) 8.4. Authenticated users can inject JavaScript code that is later executed in the browsers of users who view the configuration page, enabling client-side attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58975 | WordPress Advanced Settings Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58975</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Helmut Wandl Advanced Settings allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Advanced Settings: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58976 | WordPress Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.31.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58976</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Equalize Digital Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital: from n/a through 1.31.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58977 | WordPress WP eBay Product Feeds Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58977</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Rhys Wynne WP eBay Product Feeds allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects WP eBay Product Feeds: from n/a through 3.4.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58978 | WordPress PDF Generator for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58978</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Swings PDF Generator for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects PDF Generator for WordPress: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58979 | WordPress BerqWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.53 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58979</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BerqWP BerqWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects BerqWP: from n/a through 2.2.53.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58980 | WordPress Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58980</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in recorp Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58981 | WordPress Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.31.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58981</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Equalize Digital Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital: from n/a through 1.31.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58982 | WordPress Pixeline&amp;#x27;s Email Protector Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58982</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pixeline Pixeline&amp;#039;s Email Protector allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Pixeline&amp;#039;s Email Protector: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58983 | WordPress Include Me Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58983</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stefano Lissa Include Me allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Include Me: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58984 | WordPress Welcart e-Commerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58984</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nanbu Welcart e-Commerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Welcart e-Commerce: from n/a through 2.11.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58985 | WordPress Additional Custom Product Tabs for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58985</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Additional Custom Product Tabs for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Additional Custom Product Tabs for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58987 | WordPress Football Pool Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AntoineH Football Pool allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Football Pool: from n/a through 2.12.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58988 | WordPress My Tickets Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58988</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joe Dolson My Tickets allows Stored XSS. This issue affects My Tickets: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58989 | WordPress Dynamic Text Field For Contact Form 7 Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in silverplugins217 Dynamic Text Field For Contact Form 7 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dynamic Text Field For Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58990 | WordPress ShopLentor Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58990</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HasTech ShopLentor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShopLentor: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58991 | WordPress WooCommerce Booking Bundle Hours Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58991</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cristiano Zanca WooCommerce Booking Bundle Hours allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Booking Bundle Hours: from n/a through 0.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58993 | WordPress Tutor LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58993</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themeum Tutor LMS allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Tutor LMS: from n/a through 3.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58997 | WordPress Mow Theme &amp;lt;= 4.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58997</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Frenify Mow allows Code Injection. This issue affects Mow: from n/a through 4.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5005 | Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM index_event.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5005</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM up to 8.6.5.4. This affects an unknown function of the file crm/WeiXinApp/dingtalk/index_event.php. The manipulation of the argument corpurl results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5500 | ZhenShi Mibro Fit App com.xiaoxun.xunoversea.mibrofit AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5500</link><description>A flaw has been found in ZhenShi Mibro Fit App 1.6.3.17499 on Android. This impacts an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.xiaoxun.xunoversea.mibrofit. This manipulation causes improper export of android application components. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30875 | WordPress WP Weixin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alexandre Froger WP Weixin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Weixin: from n/a through 1.3.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32486 | WordPress Material Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32486</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password vulnerability in Hossein Material Dashboard. This issue affects Material Dashboard: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32688 | WordPress Target Video Easy Publish plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sovica Target Video Easy Publish. This issue affects Target Video Easy Publish: from n/a through 3.8.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32689 | WordPress Download Manager and Payment Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.13 - Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32689</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in ThemesGrove WP SmartPay. This issue affects WP SmartPay: from n/a through 2.7.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39523 | WordPress GoodBarber plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.26 - Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39523</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in GoodBarber GoodBarber. This issue affects GoodBarber: from n/a through 1.0.26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39541 | WordPress WP Simple Booking Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39541</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Roland Murg WP Simple Booking Calendar. This issue affects WP Simple Booking Calendar: from n/a through 2.0.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39553 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.9 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39553</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in andy_moyle Church Admin. This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 5.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47437 | WordPress LiteSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47437</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in LiteSpeed Technologies LiteSpeed Cache. This issue affects LiteSpeed Cache: from n/a through 7.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47569 | WordPress WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47569</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPSwings WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card - Create, Sell and Manage Gift Cards with Customized Email Templates. This issue affects WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card - Create, Sell and Manage Gift Cards with Customized Email Templates: from n/a through 2.8.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47570 | WordPress WooCommerce Photo Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in villatheme WooCommerce Photo Reviews. This issue affects WooCommerce Photo Reviews: from n/a through 1.3.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47571 | WordPress Super Store Finder plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47571</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in highwarden Super Store Finder. This issue affects Super Store Finder: from n/a through 6.9.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47579 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.5.2 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47579</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods Photography. This issue affects Photography: from n/a through 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47694 | WordPress Blog Designer PRO plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in solwin Blog Designer PRO. This issue affects Blog Designer PRO: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47695 | WordPress Blog Designer PRO plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Authenticated Non-Arbitrary Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47695</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in solwin Blog Designer PRO. This issue affects Blog Designer PRO: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48101 | WordPress Constant Contact for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48101</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in webdevstudios Constant Contact for WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Constant Contact for WordPress: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49430 | WordPress Ultimate Video Player Plugin &amp;lt;= 10.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49430</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in FWDesign Ultimate Video Player allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Ultimate Video Player: from n/a through 10.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49860 | WordPress Majestic Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49860</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Majestic Support Majestic Support. This issue affects Majestic Support: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53291 | WordPress Spreadconnect plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53291</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in spoddev2021 Spreadconnect. This issue affects Spreadconnect: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53303 | WordPress ThemeMove Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53303</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeMove ThemeMove Core allows Object Injection. This issue affects ThemeMove Core: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53340 | WordPress Awesome Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53340</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in awesomesupport Awesome Support. This issue affects Awesome Support: from n/a through 6.3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53348 | WordPress Kalium Theme &amp;lt;= 3.18.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53348</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Laborator Kalium. This issue affects Kalium: from n/a through 3.18.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54709 | WordPress Sala Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54709</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in uxper Sala. This issue affects Sala: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57057 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the listStr parameter in the ipMacBindListStore function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57057</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the listStr parameter in the ipMacBindListStore function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57058 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formSetDebugCfg function via the pEnable, pLevel, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57058</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formSetDebugCfg function via the pEnable, pLevel, and pModule parameters. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57059 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the dhcpIndex parameter in the addDhcpRule function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57059</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the dhcpIndex parameter in the addDhcpRule function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58215 | WordPress Ziston Theme &amp;lt; 1.4.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58215</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Ziston allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ziston: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59005 | WordPress Categorify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59005</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in frenify Categorify allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Categorify: from n/a through 1.0.7.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59008 | WordPress ZIP Code Based Content Protection plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59008</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PressTigers ZIP Code Based Content Protection allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ZIP Code Based Content Protection: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55143 | Reflected text injection in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55143</link><description>Reflected text injection in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary text into a crafted HTTP response. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55144 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55144</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure restricted settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55141 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55141</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure authentication related settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55142 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55142</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure authentication related settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55139 | SSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Iva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55139</link><description>SSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to enumerate internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55147 | CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Iva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55147</link><description>CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute sensitive actions on behalf of the victim user. User interaction is required</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55148 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55148</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure restricted settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52915 | K7RKScan.sys 23.0.0.10, part of the K7 Security Anti-Malware suite, allows an admin-privileged user to send crafted IOCTL requests to termin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52915</link><description>K7RKScan.sys 23.0.0.10, part of the K7 Security Anti-Malware suite, allows an admin-privileged user to send crafted IOCTL requests to terminate processes that are protected through a third-party implementation. This is caused by insufficient caller validation in the driver's IOCTL handler, enabling unauthorized processes to perform those actions in kernel space. Successful exploitation can lead to denial of service by disrupting critical third-party services or applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55145 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55145</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723  and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker to hijack existing HTML5 connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55146 | An unchecked return value in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55146</link><description>An unchecked return value in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to trigger a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8711 | CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Iva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8711</link><description>CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute limited actions on behalf of the victim user. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52322 | An issue in Open5GS v2.7.2 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted Create Session Request message to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52322</link><description>An issue in Open5GS v2.7.2 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted Create Session Request message to the SMF (PGW-C), using the IP address of a legitimate UE in the PDN Address Allocation (PAA) field</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8712 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 22...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8712</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 22.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure restricted settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9712 | Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9712</link><description>Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9872 | Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9872</link><description>Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10183 | XML External Entity Injection in TecConnect 4.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10183</link><description>A blind XML External Entity (XXE) injection in the OpenMessaging webservice in TecCom TecConnect 4.1 allows an unauthenticated attacker to exfiltrate arbitrary files to an attacker-controlled server. TecConnect 4.1 is considered end-of-life as of December 2023. Users are advised to upgrade to TecCom Connect 5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52277 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in YesWiki v.4.54 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the meta co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52277</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in YesWiki v.4.54 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the meta configuration robots field</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10107 | TRENDnet TEW-831DR formSysCmd command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10107</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TRENDnet TEW-831DR 1.0 (601.130.1.1410). Impacted is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSysCmd. The manipulation of the argument sysHost leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43776 | A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43776</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.19 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows an remote authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript through Custom Object field label. The malicious payload is stored and executed through Process Builder's Configuration tab without proper escaping.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33045 | Legacy Serial Redirection SMRAM Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33045</link><description>APTIOV contains vulnerabilities in the BIOS where a privileged user may cause “Write-what-where Condition” and “Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor” through local access. The successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities can lead to information disclosure, arbitrary data writing, and impact Confidentiality, Integrity, and Availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47416 | ConsoleFindCommandMatchList</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47416</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the ConsoleFindCommandMatchList function in libsymproc. so imported by ctpd that may lead to unauthorized execution of an attacker-defined file that gets prioritized by the ConsoleFindCommandMatchList.



A third-party researcher discovered that the ConsoleFindCommandMatchList enumerates the /dev/shm/symproc/c directory in alphabetical order to identify console commands. Permission levels are inferred from the integer values present in each command's file name. 



Confirmed Affected Hardware: TSW-760, TSW-1060 



Confirmed Affected Firmware: 3.002.1061 



Fixed Firmware: no fixed released (product is discontinued and end of life)



 



For x70  



The Affected Firmware:- 3.000.0110.001  and versions below 



The Fixed Firmware:- 3.001.0031.001</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9951 | Remote code execution via Heap Buffer Overflow in FFmpeg JPEG2000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9951</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow write exists in jpeg2000dec FFmpeg which allows an attacker to potentially gain remote code execution or cause denial of service via the channel definition cdef atom of JPEG2000.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45325 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiDDoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45325</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiDDoS-F version 7.0.0 through 7.02 and before 6.6.3 may allow a privileged attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53609 | A Relative Path Traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0.2 through 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53609</link><description>A Relative Path Traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0.2 through 7.0.11 may allow an authenticated attacker to perform an arbitrary file read on the underlying system via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54236 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54236</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A successful attacker can abuse this to achieve session takeover, increasing the confidentiality and integrity impact to high. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9994 | Amp’ed RF BT-AP 111 Bluetooth access point&amp;#x27;s HTTP admin interface does not require authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9994</link><description>The Amp’ed RF BT-AP 111 Bluetooth access point's HTTP admin interface does not have an authentication feature, allowing unauthorized access to anyone with network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7350 | Rockwell Automation Stratix® IOS Cross-Site Request Forgery to Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7350</link><description>A security issue affecting multiple Cisco devices also directly impacts Stratix® 5410, 5700, and 8000 devices. This can lead to remote code execution by uploading and running malicious configurations without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7970 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Activation Manager Lack of Encryption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7970</link><description>A security issue exists within FactoryTalk Activation Manager.  An error in the implementation of cryptography within the software could allow attackers to decrypt traffic. This could result in data exposure, session hijacking, or full communication compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9065 | Rockwell Automation ThinManager® Server-Side Request Forgery Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9065</link><description>A server-side request forgery security issue exists within Rockwell Automation ThinManager® software due to the lack of input sanitization. Authenticated attackers can exploit this vulnerability by specifying external SMB paths, exposing the ThinServer® service account NTLM hash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9161 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Optix Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9161</link><description>A security issue exists within FactoryTalk Optix MQTT broker due to the lack of URI sanitization. This flaw enables the loading of remote Mosquito plugins, which can be used to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9364 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Analytics™ LogixAI® Exposed Redis DB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9364</link><description>An open database issue exists in the affected product and version. The security issue stems from an over permissive Redis instance. This could result in an attacker on the intranet accessing sensitive data and potential alteration of data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8007 | Rockwell Automation 1756-ENT2R, EN4TR, EN4TRXT Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8007</link><description>A security issue exists in the protected mode of 1756-EN4TR and 1756-EN2TR communication modules, where a Concurrent Forward Close operation can trigger a Major Non-Recoverable (MNFR) fault. This condition may lead to unexpected system crashes and loss of device availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8008 | Rockwell Automation 1756-ENT2R, EN4TR, EN4TRXT Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8008</link><description>A security issue exists in the protected mode of EN4TR devices, where sending specifically crafted messages during a Forward Close operation can cause the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9160 | Rockwell Automation CompactLogix® 5480 Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9160</link><description>A code execution security issue exists in the affected product. An attacker with physical access could abuse the maintenance menu of the controller with a crafted payload. The security issue can result in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9166 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix® 5580 V35.013 Denial-Of-Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9166</link><description>A denial-of-service security issue exists in the affected product and version. The security issue stems from the controller repeatedly attempting to forward messages. The issue could result in a major nonrecoverable fault on the controller.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8277 | Libssh: memory exhaustion via repeated key exchange in libssh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8277</link><description>A flaw was found in libssh's handling of key exchange (KEX) processes when a client repeatedly sends incorrect KEX guesses. The library fails to free memory during these rekey operations, which can gradually exhaust system memory. This issue can lead to crashes on the client side, particularly when using libgcrypt, which impacts application stability and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10095 | SQL injection in SMPP component of SMSEagle firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10095</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in the SMPP server component of the SMSEagle firmware, specifically affecting the handling of certain parameters within the server's database interactions. The vulnerability is isolated to the SMPP server, which operates with its own dedicated database, separate from the main software's database. This isolation limits the scope of the vulnerability to the SMPP server's operations. The vulnerability arises from improper sanitization of user input in the SMPP server's scripts.

This issue has been fixed in version 6.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 10:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24404 | Apache HertzBeat (incubating): RCE by parse http sitemap xml response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24404</link><description>XML Injection RCE by parse http sitemap xml response vulnerability in Apache HertzBeat.












The attacker needs to have an authenticated account with access, and add monitor parsed by xml, returned special content can trigger the XML parsing vulnerability.

This issue affects Apache HertzBeat (incubating): before 1.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48208 | Apache HertzBeat (incubating): Jmx JNDI injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48208</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an LDAP Query ('LDAP Injection') vulnerability in Apache HertzBeat .












The attacker needs to have an authenticated account with access, and the attack can only be triggered by crafting custom commands. A successful attack would result in arbitrary script execution.

This issue affects Apache HertzBeat: through 1.7.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.7.3], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41701 | Beckhoff: Deserialization of untrusted data by TwinCAT 3 Engineering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41701</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can trick a local user into executing arbitrary commands by opening a deliberately manipulated project file with an affected engineering tool. These arbitrary commands are executed in the user context.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59013 | Open Redirect in TYPO3 CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59013</link><description>An open‑redirect vulnerability in GeneralUtility::sanitizeLocalUrl of TYPO3 CMS 9.0.0–9.5.54, 10.0.0–10.4.53, 11.0.0–11.5.47, 12.0.0–12.4.36, and 13.0.0–13.4.17 allows an attacker to redirect users to arbitrary external sites, enabling phishing attacks by supplying a manipulated, sanitized URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59014 | Denial of Service in TYPO3 Bookmark Toolbar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59014</link><description>An uncaught exception in the Bookmark Toolbar of TYPO3 CMS versions 11.0.0–11.5.47, 12.0.0–12.4.36, and 13.0.0–13.4.17 lets administrator‑level backend users trigger a denial‑of‑service condition in the backend user interface by saving manipulated data in the bookmark toolbar.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59015 | Insufficient Entropy in Password Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59015</link><description>A deterministic three‑character prefix in the Password Generation component of TYPO3 CMS versions 12.0.0–12.4.36 and 13.0.0–13.4.17 reduces entropy, allowing attackers to carry out brute‑force attacks more quickly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59016 | Information Disclosure via File Abstraction Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59016</link><description>Error messages containing sensitive information in the File Abstraction Layer in TYPO3 CMS versions 9.0.0-9.5.54, 10.0.0-10.4.53, 11.0.0-11.5.47, 12.0.0-12.4.36, and 13.0.0-13.4.17 allow backend users to disclose full file paths via failed low-level file-system operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59017 | Broken Access Control in Backend AJAX Routes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59017</link><description>Missing authorization checks in the Backend Routing of TYPO3 CMS versions 9.0.0‑9.5.54, 10.0.0‑10.4.53, 11.0.0‑11.5.47, 12.0.0‑12.4.36, and 13.0.0‑13.4.17 allow backend users to directly invoke AJAX backend routes without having access to the corresponding backend modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59018 | Information Disclosure in Workspaces Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59018</link><description>Missing authorization checks in the Workspace Module of TYPO3 CMS versions 9.0.0‑9.5.54, 10.0.0‑10.4.53, 11.0.0‑11.5.47, 12.0.0‑12.4.36, and 13.0.0‑13.4.17 allow backend users to directly invoke the corresponding AJAX backend route to disclose sensitive information without having access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59019 | Information Disclosure via CSV Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59019</link><description>Missing authorization checks in the CSV download feature of TYPO3 CMS versions 11.0.0‑11.5.47, 12.0.0‑12.4.36, and 13.0.0‑13.4.17 allow backend users to disclose information from arbitrary database tables stored within the users' web mounts without having access to them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40594 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS G220 V6.4 (All versions &lt; V6.4 HF2), SINAMICS S200 V6.4 (All versions), SINAMICS S210 V6.4 (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40594</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS G220 V6.4 (All versions &lt; V6.4 HF2), SINAMICS S200 V6.4 (All versions), SINAMICS S210 V6.4 (All versions &lt; V6.4 HF2). The affected devices allow a factory reset to be executed without the required privileges due to improper privilege management as well as manipulation of configuration data because of leaked privileges of previous sessions. This could allow an unauthorized attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40757 | A vulnerability has been identified in APOGEE PXC Series (BACnet) (All versions), APOGEE PXC Series (P2 Ethernet) (All versions), TALON TC S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40757</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in APOGEE PXC Series (BACnet) (All versions), APOGEE PXC Series (P2 Ethernet) (All versions), TALON TC Series (BACnet) (All versions). Affected devices connected to the network allow unrestricted access to sensitive files, such as databases. This could allow an attacker to download encrypted .db file containing passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40795 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40795</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40796 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40796</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40797 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40797</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40798 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40798</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40802 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device may be susceptible to resource...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40802</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device may be susceptible to resource exhaustion when subjected to high volumes of query requests.
This could allow an attacker to cause a temporary denial of service, with the system recovering once the activity stops.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40803 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device exposes certain non-critical i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40803</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device exposes certain non-critical information from the device. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker to access sensitive data, potentially leading to a breach of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40804 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Virtualization as a Service (SIVaaS) (All versions). The affected application exposes a netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40804</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Virtualization as a Service (SIVaaS) (All versions). The affected application exposes a network share without any authentication. This could allow an attacker to access or alter sensitive data without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10134 | Goza - Nonprofit Charity WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10134</link><description>The Goza - Nonprofit Charity WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the alone_import_pack_restore_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 08:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9539 | AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp;amp; custom integrations in WordPress &amp;lt;= 5.3.6 - Missing Authorization To Authenticated (Subscriber+) Remote Code Execution via Automation Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9539</link><description>The AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp; custom integrations in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the automatorwp_ajax_import_automation_from_url function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary automations, which can lead to Remote Code Execution or Privilege escalation once such automation is activated by the administrator</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9542 | AutomatorWP &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9542</link><description>The AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp; custom integrations in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple plugin's functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify integration settings or view existing automations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8889 | Compress Then Upload &amp;lt; 1.0.5 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8889</link><description>The Compress &amp; Upload WordPress plugin before 1.0.5 does not properly validate uploaded files, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9111 | WPBOT &amp;lt; 7.1.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9111</link><description>The AI ChatBot for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 7.1.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9058 | Mikado Core &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9058</link><description>The Mikado Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9061 | Wilmer Core &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9061</link><description>The Wilmer Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 2.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9489 | WP-Members Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via Profile Names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9489</link><description>The The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.2. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 04:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43777 | Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43777</link><description>Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.19 exposes "Internal Server Error" in the response body when a login attempt is made with a deleted Client Secret.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 03:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10122 | Maccms10 Database.php rep sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Maccms10 2025.1000.4050. Affected is the function rep of the file application/admin/controller/Database.php. Performing manipulation of the argument where results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 03:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10123 | D-Link DIR-823X set_static_leases sub_415028 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10123</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X up to 250416. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_415028 of the file /goform/set_static_leases. Executing manipulation of the argument Hostname can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 03:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10121 | uverif kami_list addbatch sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10121</link><description>A flaw has been found in uverif up to 3.2. This affects the function addbatch of the file /admin/kami_list. This manipulation of the argument note causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42911 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver (Service Data Download)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42911</link><description>SAP NetWeaver (Service Data Download) allows an authenticated user to call a remote-enabled function module, which could grant access to information about the SAP system and operating system. This leads to a low impact on confidentiality, with no effect on the integrity and availability of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42912 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42912</link><description>SAP HCM My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This issue has a significant impact on the application's integrity, while confidentiality and availability remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42913 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42913</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP HCM My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application allows an authenticated attacker with in-depth system knowledge to escalate privileges and perform activities that are otherwise restricted, resulting in a low impact on the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42914 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42914</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP HCM My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application allows an authenticated attacker with in-depth system knowledge to escalate privileges and perform activities that are otherwise restricted, resulting in a low impact on the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42915 | Missing Authorization Check in Fiori app (Manage Payment Blocks)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42915</link><description>Fiori app Manage Payment Blocks does not perform the necessary authorization checks, allowing an attacker with basic user privileges to abuse functionalities that should be restricted to specific user groups.This issue could impact both the confidentiality and integrity of the application without affecting the availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42916 | Missing input validation vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA (Private Cloud or On-Premise)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42916</link><description>Due to missing input validation, an attacker with high privilege access to ABAP reports could delete the content of arbitrary database tables, if the tables are not protected by an authorization group. This leads to a high impact on integrity and availability of the database but no impact on confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42917 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (Approve Timesheets Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42917</link><description>SAP HCM Approve Timesheets Fiori 2.0 application does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This issue has a significant impact on the application's integrity, while confidentiality and availability remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42918 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP (Background Processing)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42918</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP allows authenticated users with access to background processing to gain unauthorized read access to profile parameters.  This results in a low impact on confidentiality, with no impact on integrity or availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42920 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Supplier Relationship Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42920</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SAP Supplier Relationship Management, an unauthenticated attacker could generate a malicious link and make it publicly accessible. If an authenticated victim clicks on the link, the injected input is processed during the page generation, resulting in the execution of malicious content. This execution allows the attacker to access and modify information within the victim's browser scope, impacting confidentiality and integrity, while availability remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42922 | Insecure File Operations vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Deploy Web Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42922</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java allows an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user to use a flaw in an available service to upload an arbitrary file. This file when executed can lead to a full compromise of confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42923 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SAP Fiori App (F4044 Manage Work Center Groups)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42923</link><description>Due to insufficient CSRF protection in SAP Fiori App Manage Work Center Groups, an authenticated user could be tricked by an attacker to send unintended request to the web server. This has low impact on integrity and no impact on confidentiality and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42925 | Predictable Object Identifier vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (IIOP Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42925</link><description>Due to the lack of randomness in assigning Object Identifiers in the SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA IIOP service, an authenticated attacker with low privileges could predict the identifiers by conducting a brute force search. By leveraging knowledge of several identifiers generated close to the same time, the attacker could determine a desired identifier which could enable them to access limited system information. This poses a low risk to confidentiality without impacting the integrity or availability of the service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42926 | Missing Authentication check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42926</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java does not perform an authentication check when an attacker attempts to access internal files within the web application.Upon successfully exploitation, an unauthenticated attacker could access these files to gather additional sensitive information about the system.This vulnerability has a low impact on confidentiality and does not affect the integrity or availability of the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42927 | Information Disclosure due to Outdated OpenSSL Version in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Adobe Document Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42927</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java application uses Adobe Document Service, installed with a vulnerable version of OpenSSL.Successful exploitation of known vulnerabilities in the outdated OpenSSL library would allow user with high system privileges to access and modify system information.This vulnerability has a low impact on confidentiality and integrity, with no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42929 | Missing input validation vulnerability in SAP Landscape Transformation Replication Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42929</link><description>Due to missing input validation, an attacker with high privilege access to ABAP reports could delete the content of arbitrary database tables, if the tables are not protected by an authorization group. This leads to a high impact on integrity and availability of the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42930 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in SAP Business Planning and Consolidation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42930</link><description>SAP Business Planning and Consolidation allows an authenticated standard user to call a function module by crafting specific parameters that causes a loop, consuming excessive resources and resulting in system unavailability. This leads to high impact on the availability of the application, there is no impact on confidentiality or integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42933 | Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information in SAP Business One (SLD)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42933</link><description>When a user logs in via SAP Business One native client, the SLD backend service fails to enforce proper encryption of certain APIs. This leads to exposure of sensitive credentials within http response body. As a result, it has a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42938 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42938</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SAP NetWeaver ABAP Platform, an unauthenticated attacker could generate a malicious link and make it publicly accessible. If an authenticated user clicks on this link, the injected input is processed during the website�s page generation, resulting in the creation of malicious content. When executed, this content allows the attacker to access or modify information within the victim's browser scope, impacting the confidentiality and integrity�while availability remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42944 | Insecure Deserialization vulnerability in SAP Netweaver (RMI-P4)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42944</link><description>Due to a deserialization vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver, an unauthenticated attacker could exploit the system through the RMI-P4 module by submitting malicious payload to an open port. The deserialization of such untrusted Java objects could lead to arbitrary OS command execution, posing a high impact to the application's confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42958 | Missing Authentication check in SAP NetWeaver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42958</link><description>Due to a missing authentication check in the SAP NetWeaver application on IBM i-series, the application allows high privileged unauthorized users to read, modify, or delete sensitive information, as well as access administrative or privileged functionalities. This results in a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10116 | SiempreCMS file_upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10116</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SiempreCMS up to 1.3.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /docs/admin/file_upload.php. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10117 | SourceCodester Simple To-Do List System Add New Task fetch_tasks.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10117</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Simple To-Do List System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /fetch_tasks.php of the component Add New Task. Executing manipulation with the input  can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10118 | itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10118</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10120 | Tenda AC20 GetParentControlInfo strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10120</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC20 up to 16.03.08.12. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument mac results in buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43778 | A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.11, 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43778</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.11, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20 allows an remote authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript through the name of a fieldset in Kaleo Forms Admin. The malicious payload is stored and executed without proper sanitization or escaping.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10114 | PHPGurukul Small CRM profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10114</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10115 | SiempreCMS user_search_ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10115</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SiempreCMS up to 1.3.6. This affects an unknown part of the file user_search_ajax.php. This manipulation of the argument name/userName causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43774 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.17 allows a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43774</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.17 allows a remote authenticated user to inject JavaScript code via Style Book theme name. This malicious payload is then reflected and executed within the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10113 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10113</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/room/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58756 | MONAI&amp;#x27;s unsafe torch usage may lead to arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58756</link><description>MONAI (Medical Open Network for AI) is an AI toolkit for health care imaging. In versions up to and including 1.5.0, in `model_dict = torch.load(full_path, map_location=torch.device(device), weights_only=True)` in monai/bundle/scripts.py , `weights_only=True` is loaded securely. However, insecure loading methods still exist elsewhere in the project, such as when loading checkpoints. This is a common practice when users want to reduce training time and costs by loading pre-trained models downloaded from other platforms. Loading a checkpoint containing malicious content can trigger a deserialization vulnerability, leading to code execution. As of time of publication, no known fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58757 | MONAI&amp;#x27;s unsafe use of Pickle deserialization may lead to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58757</link><description>MONAI (Medical Open Network for AI) is an AI toolkit for health care imaging. In versions up to and including 1.5.0, the `pickle_operations` function in `monai/data/utils.py` automatically handles dictionary key-value pairs ending with a specific suffix and deserializes them using `pickle.loads()` . This function also lacks any security measures. The deserialization may lead to code execution. As of time of publication, no known fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10112 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10112</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/department/index.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58755 | MONAI has path traversal issue that may lead to arbitrary file writes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58755</link><description>MONAI (Medical Open Network for AI) is an AI toolkit for health care imaging. The extractall function `zip_file.extractall(output_dir)` is used directly to process compressed files. It is used in many places in the project. In versions up to and including 1.5.0, when the Zip file containing malicious content is decompressed, it overwrites the system files. In addition, the project allows the download of the zip content through the link, which increases the scope of exploitation of this vulnerability. As of time of publication, no known fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43763 | A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exist in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43763</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exist in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.131, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20 that affects custom object attachment fields. This flaw allows an attacker to manipulate the application into making unauthorized requests to other instances, creating new object entries that link to external resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10111 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10111</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/instructor/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58752 | Vite&amp;#x27;s `server.fs` settings were not applied to HTML files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58752</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for JavaScript. Prior to versions 7.1.5, 7.0.7, 6.3.6, and 5.4.20, any HTML files on the machine were served regardless of the `server.fs` settings. Only apps that explicitly expose the Vite dev server to the network (using --host or server.host config option) and use `appType: 'spa'` (default) or `appType: 'mpa'` are affected. This vulnerability also affects the preview server. The preview server allowed HTML files not under the output directory to be served. Versions 7.1.5, 7.0.7, 6.3.6, and 5.4.20 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58751 | Vite middleware may serve files starting with the same name with the public directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58751</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for JavaScript. Prior to versions 7.1.5, 7.0.7, 6.3.6, and 5.4.20, files starting with the same name with the public directory were served bypassing the `server.fs` settings. Only apps that explicitly expose the Vite dev server to the network (using --host or `server.host` config option), use the public directory feature (enabled by default), and have a symlink in the public directory are affected. Versions 7.1.5, 7.0.7, 6.3.6, and 5.4.20 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 23:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58745 | WeGIA has a bypass for the fix for CVE-2025-22133 - Arbitrary File Upload leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58745</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. The fix for CVE-2025-22133 was not enough to remediate the arbitrary file upload vulnerability. The WeGIA only check MIME types for Excel files at endpoint `/html/socio/sistema/controller/controla_xlsx.php`, which can be bypassed by using magic bytes of Excel file in a PHP file. As a result, attacker can upload webshell to the server for remote code execution. Version 3.4.11 contains an updated fix.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58746 | Volkov Labs Business Links plugin vulnerable to privilege escalation attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58746</link><description>The Volkov Labs Business Links panel for Grafana provides an interface to navigate using external links, internal dashboards, time pickers, and dropdown menus. Prior to version 2.4.0, a malicious actor with Editor privileges can escalate their privileges to Administrator and perform arbitrary administrative actions. This is possible because the plugin allows arbitrary JavaScript code injection in the [Layout] → [Link] → [URL] field. Version 2.4.0 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10109 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10109</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_payment. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10110 | ChanCMS search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10110</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ChanCMS up to 3.3.1. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /search/. The manipulation with the input '%20or%201=1%20%23/words.html leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58454 | WeGIA vulnerable to Blind Time-Based SQL Injection in endpoint &amp;#x27;listar_despachos.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_memorando&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58454</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in WeGIA versions 3.4.10 and prior inthe endpoint /WeGIA/html/memorando/listar_despachos.php, in the id_memorando parameter. This vulnerability allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to sensitive information. Version 3.4.11 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58452 | WeGIA vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in endpoint &amp;#x27;listar_despachos.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_memorando&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58452</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the listar_despachos.php endpoint of the WeGIA application prior to version 3.4.11. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts in the id_memorando parameter. Version 3.4.11 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58453 | SQL Injection (Blind Time-Based) endpoint &amp;#x27;exibe_anexo.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_anexo&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58453</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in WeGIA versions 3.4.10 and prior in the endpoint /WeGIA/html/memorando/exibe_anexo.php, in the id_anexo parameter. This vulnerability allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to sensitive information. Version 3.4.11 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1761 | IBM Concert Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1761</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from allocated memory due to improper clearing of heap memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10108 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_loan. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58451 | Cattown Vulnerable to Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity and Uncontrolled Resource Consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58451</link><description>Cattown is a JavaScript markdown parser. Versions prior to 1.0.2 used regular expressions with inefficient, potentially exponential worst-case complexity. This could cause excessive CPU usage due to excessive backtracking on crafted inputs. In turn, the excessive CPU usage could lead to resource exhaustion, where processing malicious inputs could cause high CPU or memory usage, potentially leading to denial of service. Version 1.0.2 contains a patch. Additionally, users should review and restrict input sources if untrusted inputs are processed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10106 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /cms/collect/search. Such manipulation of the argument keyword leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58450 | pREST has Systemic SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58450</link><description>pREST (PostgreSQL REST), is an API that delivers an application on top of a Postgres database. SQL injection is possible in versions prior to 2.0.0-rc3. The validation present in versions prior to 2.0.0-rc3 does not provide adequate protection from injection attempts. Version 2.0.0-rc3 contains a patch to mitigate such attempts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58444 | MCP Inspector is Vulnerable to Potential Command Execution via XSS When Connecting to an Untrusted MCP Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58444</link><description>The MCP inspector is a developer tool for testing and debugging MCP servers. A cross-site scripting issue was reported in versions of the MCP Inspector local development tool prior to 0.16.6 when connecting to untrusted remote MCP servers with a malicious redirect URI. This could be leveraged to interact directly with the inspector proxy to trigger arbitrary command execution. Users are advised to update to 0.16.6 to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58449 | Maho Vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58449</link><description>Maho is a free and open source ecommerce platform. In Maho prior to 25.9.0, an authenticated staff user with access to the `Dashboard` and `Catalog\Manage Products` permissions can create a custom option on a listing with a file input field. By allowing file uploads with a `.php` extension, the user can use the filed to upload malicious PHP files, gaining remote code execution. Version 25.9.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57766 | Fides&amp;#x27;s Admin UI User Password Change Does Not Invalidate Current Session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57766</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. Prior to version 2.69.1, admin UI user password changes in Fides do not invalidate active user sessions, creating a vulnerability chaining opportunity where attackers who have obtained session tokens through other attack vectors (such as XSS) can maintain access even after password reset. This issue is not directly exploitable on its own and requires a prerequisite vulnerability to obtain valid session tokens in the first place. Version 2.69.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57815 | Fides Lacks Brute-Force Protections on Authentication Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57815</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. Prior to version 2.69.1, the Fides Admin UI login endpoint relies on a general IP-based rate limit for all API traffic and lacks specific anti-automation controls designed to protect against brute-force attacks. This could allow attackers to conduct credential testing attacks, such as credential stuffing or password spraying, which poses a risk to accounts with weak or previously compromised passwords. Version 2.69.1 fixes the issue. For organizations with commercial Fides Enterprise licenses, configuring Single Sign-On (SSO) through an OIDC provider (like Azure, Google, or Okta) is an effective workaround. When OIDC SSO is enabled, username/password authentication can be disabled entirely, which eliminates this attack vector. This functionality is not available for Fides Open Source users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57816 | Fides Webserver API Rate Limiting Vulnerability in Proxied Environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57816</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. Prior to version 2.69.1, the Fides Webserver API's built-in IP-based rate limiting is ineffective in environments with CDNs, proxies or load balancers. The system incorrectly applies rate limits based on directly connected infrastructure IPs rather than client IPs, and stores counters in-memory rather than in a shared store. This allows attackers to bypass intended rate limits and potentially cause denial of service. This vulnerability only affects deployments relying on Fides's built-in rate limiting for protection. Deployments using external rate limiting solutions (WAFs, API gateways, etc.) are not affected. Version 2.69.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57817 | Fides Webserver API is Vulnerable to OAuth Client Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57817</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. Prior to version 2.69.1, the OAuth client creation and update endpoints of the Fides Webserver API do not properly authorize scope assignment. This allows highly privileged users with `client:create` or `client:update` permissions to escalate their privileges to owner-level. Version 2.69.1 fixes the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58365 | XWiki Blog Application: Privilege Escalation (PR) from account through blog content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58365</link><description>The XWiki blog application allows users of the XWiki platform to create and manage blog posts. Prior to version 9.14, the blog application in XWiki allowed remote code execution for any user who has edit right on any page. Normally, these are all logged-in users as they can edit their own user profile. For an exploit, it is sufficient to add an object of type `Blog.BlogPostClass` to any page and to add some script macro with the exploit code to the "Content" field of that object. The vulnerability has been patched in the blog application version 9.14 by executing the content of blog posts with the rights of the appropriate author. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10105 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10105</link><description>A flaw has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cms/article/search. This manipulation of the argument keyword causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52288 | Assertion failure in function ngap_build_downlink_nas_transport in file src/amf/ngap-build.c, the Access and Mobility Management Function (A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52288</link><description>Assertion failure in function ngap_build_downlink_nas_transport in file src/amf/ngap-build.c, the Access and Mobility Management Function (AMF) component, in Open5GS thru 2.7.5 allowing attackers to cause a denial of service or other unspecified impacts via repeated UE connect and disconnect message sequences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10104 | code-projects Online Event Judging System review_search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10104</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Event Judging System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /review_search.php. The manipulation of the argument txtsearch leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52389 | An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Envasadora H2O Eireli - Soda Cristal v40.20.4 allows authenticated attackers to access sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52389</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Envasadora H2O Eireli - Soda Cristal v40.20.4 allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive data for other users via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54994 | @akoskm/create-mcp-server-stdio has Command Injection in MCP Server due to unsafe `exec` API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54994</link><description>@akoskm/create-mcp-server-stdio is an MCP server starter kit that uses the StdioServerTransport. Prior to version 0.0.13, the MCP Server is written in a way that is vulnerable to command injection vulnerability attacks as part of some of its MCP Server tool definition and implementation. The MCP Server exposes the tool `which-app-on-port` which relies on Node.js child process API `exec` which is an unsafe and vulnerable API if concatenated with untrusted user input. Version 0.0.13 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53838 | LinkAce has a Stored One Click XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53838</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in versions prior to 2.1.9 that allows an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript, which is then executed in the context of a user's browser when the malicious link is clicked. This is a one-click XSS, meaning the victim only needs to click a crafted link — no further interaction is required. The application contains a stored XSS vulnerability due to insufficient filtering and escaping of user-supplied data inserted into link attributes. Malicious JavaScript code can be saved in the database along with the link and executed in the user’s browser when clicking the link, leading to arbitrary script execution within the context of the site. Version 2.1.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48341 | dingfanzu CMS V1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/doAdminAction.php?act=addShop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48341</link><description>dingfanzu CMS V1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/doAdminAction.php?act=addShop</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10103 | code-projects Online Event Judging System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10103</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Event Judging System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /home.php. Executing manipulation of the argument main_event can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55849 | WeiPHP v5.0 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the SucaiController.class.php file and the cancelTemplatee</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55849</link><description>WeiPHP v5.0 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the SucaiController.class.php file and the cancelTemplatee</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43722 | Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions prior to 9.12.0.0, contains an improper privilege management vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43722</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions prior to 9.12.0.0, contains an improper privilege management vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10102 | code-projects Online Event Judging System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10102</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Event Judging System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /index.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9112 | Doccure &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9112</link><description>The Doccure theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to incorrect file type validation in the 'doccure_temp_file_uploader' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9113 | Doccure &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9113</link><description>The Doccure theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'doccure_temp_upload_to_media' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9114 | Doccure &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9114</link><description>The Doccure theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change in versions up to, and including, 1.4.8. This is due to the plugin providing user-controlled access to objects, letting a user bypass authorization and access system resources. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10100 | SourceCodester Simple Forum Discussion System admin_class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10100</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Simple Forum Discussion System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin_class.php?action=login. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57285 | codeceptjs 3.7.3 contains a command injection vulnerability in the emptyFolder function (lib/utils.js). The execSync command directly concat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57285</link><description>codeceptjs 3.7.3 contains a command injection vulnerability in the emptyFolder function (lib/utils.js). The execSync command directly concatenates the user-controlled directoryPath parameter without sanitization or escaping, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10099 | Portabilis i-Educar Editar usuário educar_usuario_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10099</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /intranet/educar_usuario_cad.php of the component Editar usuário Page. This manipulation of the argument email/data_inicial/data_expiracao causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56265 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Chat Trigger component of N8N v1.95.3, v1.100.1, and v1.101.1 allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56265</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Chat Trigger component of N8N v1.95.3, v1.100.1, and v1.101.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56266 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability in Avigilon ACM v7.10.0.20 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56266</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability in Avigilon ACM v7.10.0.20 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56267 | A CSV injection vulnerability in the /id_profiles endpoint of Avigilon ACM v7.10.0.20 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via suuplyi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56267</link><description>A CSV injection vulnerability in the /id_profiles endpoint of Avigilon ACM v7.10.0.20 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via suuplying a crafted Excel file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:29:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10098 | PHPGurukul User Management System edit-user-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10098</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul User Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-user-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51586 | An issue was discoverd in file controllers/admin/AdminLoginController.php in PrestaShop before 8.2.1 allowing attackers to gain sensitive in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51586</link><description>An issue was discoverd in file controllers/admin/AdminLoginController.php in PrestaShop before 8.2.1 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information via the reset password feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10097 | SimStudioAI sim route.ts code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10097</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SimStudioAI sim up to 1.0.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file apps/sim/app/api/function/execute/route.ts. The manipulation of the argument code leads to code injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10096 | SimStudioAI sim route.ts server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10096</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SimStudioAI sim up to 1.0.0. This affects an unknown function of the file apps/sim/app/api/files/parse/route.ts. Executing manipulation of the argument filePath can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called 3424a338b763115f0269b209e777608e4cd31785. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40928 | JSON::XS before version 4.04 for Perl has an integer buffer overflow causing a segfault when parsing crafted JSON, enabling denial-of-service attacks or other unspecified impact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40928</link><description>JSON::XS before version 4.04 for Perl has an integer buffer overflow causing a segfault when parsing crafted JSON, enabling denial-of-service attacks or other unspecified impact</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40929 | Cpanel::JSON::XS before version 4.40 for Perl has an integer buffer overflow causing a segfault when parsing crafted JSON, enabling denial-of-service attacks or other unspecified impact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40929</link><description>Cpanel::JSON::XS before version 4.40 for Perl has an integer buffer overflow causing a segfault when parsing crafted JSON, enabling denial-of-service attacks or other unspecified impact</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40930 | JSON::SIMD before version 1.07 and earlier for Perl has an integer buffer overflow causing a segfault when parsing crafted JSON, enabling denial-of-service attacks or other unspecified impact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40930</link><description>JSON::SIMD before version 1.07 and earlier for Perl has an integer buffer overflow causing a segfault when parsing crafted JSON, enabling denial-of-service attacks or other unspecified impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52161 | Scholl Communications AG Weblication CMS Core v019.004.000.000 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52161</link><description>Scholl Communications AG Weblication CMS Core v019.004.000.000 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50238 | The on-endpoint Microsoft vulnerable driver blocklist is not fully synchronized with the online Microsoft recommended driver block rules. So...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50238</link><description>The on-endpoint Microsoft vulnerable driver blocklist is not fully synchronized with the online Microsoft recommended driver block rules. Some entries present on the online list have been excluded from the on-endpoint blocklist longer than the expected periodic monthly Windows updates. It is possible to fully synchronize the driver blocklist using WDAC policies. NOTE: The vendor explains that Windows Update provides a smaller, compatibility-focused driver blocklist for general users, while the full XML list is available for advanced users and organizations to customize at the risk of usability issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55998 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Smart Search &amp; Filter Shopify App 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55998</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Smart Search &amp; Filter Shopify App 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by including a malicious payload into the color filter parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59033 | The Microsoft vulnerable driver block list is implemented as Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) policy. On systems that do not have...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59033</link><description>The Microsoft vulnerable driver block list is implemented as Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) policy. On systems that do not have hypervisor-protected code integrity (HVCI) enabled, entries that specify only the to-be-signed (TBS) part of the code signer certificate are properly blocked, but entries that specify the signing certificateâ€™s TBS hash along with a 'FileAttribRef' qualifier (such as file name or version) will not be blocked. This vulnerability affects any Windows system that does not have HVCI enabled or supported (HVCI is available in Windows 10, Windows 11, and Windows Server 2016 and later). NOTE: The vendor states that the driver blocklist is intended for use with HVCI, while systems without HVCI should use App Control, and any custom blocklist entries require a granular approach for proper enforcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7709 | Out Of Bounds write in FTS5 Extension in SQLite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7709</link><description>An integer overflow exists in the  FTS5 https://sqlite.org/fts5.html  extension. It occurs when the size of an array of tombstone pointers is calculated and truncated into a 32-bit integer. A pointer to partially controlled data can then be written out of bounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57141 | rsbi-os 4.7 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in sqlite-jdbc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57141</link><description>rsbi-os 4.7 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in sqlite-jdbc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56630 | FoxCMS v1.2.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the column_model parameter in the app/admin/controller/Column.php file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56630</link><description>FoxCMS v1.2.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the column_model parameter in the app/admin/controller/Column.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36855 | EOL .NET 6.0 Runtime Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36855</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36854 | EOL ASP.NET 6.0 Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36854</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36853 | EOL .NET 6.0 Runtime Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36853</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22956 | OPSI before 4.3 allows any client to retrieve any ProductPropertyState, including those of other clients. This can lead to privilege escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22956</link><description>OPSI before 4.3 allows any client to retrieve any ProductPropertyState, including those of other clients. This can lead to privilege escalation if any ProductPropertyState contains a secret only intended to be accessible by a subset of clients. One example of this is a domain join account password for the windomain package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3212 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows access to already freed memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3212</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to perform valid GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r51p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r49p4, from r50p0 through r54p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10093 | D-Link DIR-852 Device Configuration getcfg.php phpcgi_main information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10093</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-852 up to 1.00CN B09. Affected by this vulnerability is the function phpcgi_main of the file /getcfg.php of the component Device Configuration Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40641 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the Multi-purpose Inventory Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40641</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability stored in Multi-Purpose Inventory Management System, consisting of a stored XSS due to lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the product_name parameter in /Controller_Products/update. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10092 | Jinher OA XML Type xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10092</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jinher OA up to 1.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /c6/Jhsoft.Web.projectmanage/TaskManage/AddTask.aspx/?Type=add of the component XML Handler. The manipulation results in xml external entity reference. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40642 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in WebWork</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40642</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WebWork, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code through the 'q' and 'engine' request parameters in /search.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10091 | Jinher OA XML Type xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10091</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Jinher OA up to 1.2. This affects an unknown function of the file /c6/Jhsoft.Web.projectmanage/ProjectManage/XmlHttp.aspx/?Type=add of the component XML Handler. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5993 | Path Traversal in ITCube CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5993</link><description>ITCube CRM in versions from 2023.2 through 2025.2 is vulnerable to path traversal. Unauthenticated remote attacker is able to exploit vulnerable parameter fileName and construct payloads that allow to download any file accessible by the the web server process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125128 | 'sanitize-html' prior to version 1.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The function 'naughtyHref' doesn't properly validate the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125128</link><description>'sanitize-html' prior to version 1.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The function 'naughtyHref' doesn't properly validate the hyperreference (`href`) attribute in anchor tags (`&lt;a&gt;`), allowing bypasses that contain different casings, whitespace characters, or hexadecimal encodings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25225 | `sanitize-html` prior to version 2.0.0-beta is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The `sanitizeHtml()` function in `index.js` does no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25225</link><description>`sanitize-html` prior to version 2.0.0-beta is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS). The `sanitizeHtml()` function in `index.js` does not sanitize content when using the custom `transformTags` option, which is intended to convert attribute values into text. As a result, malicious input can be transformed into executable code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10090 | Jinher OA GetTreeDate.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10090</link><description>A flaw has been found in Jinher OA up to 1.2. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /C6/Jhsoft.Web.departments/GetTreeDate.aspx. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58782 | Apache Jackrabbit Core, Apache Jackrabbit JCR Commons: JNDI injection risk with JndiRepositoryFactory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58782</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Jackrabbit Core and Apache Jackrabbit JCR Commons.

This issue affects Apache Jackrabbit Core: from 1.0.0 through 2.22.1; Apache Jackrabbit JCR Commons: from 1.0.0 through 2.22.1.

Deployments that accept JNDI URIs for JCR lookup from untrusted users allows them to inject malicious JNDI references, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution through deserialization of untrusted data.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.22.2. JCR lookup through JNDI has been disabled by default in 2.22.2. Users of this feature need to enable it explicitly and are adviced to review their use of JNDI URI for JCR lookup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10088 | SourceCodester Time Tracker index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10088</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Time Tracker 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /index.html. Performing manipulation of the argument project-name results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10087 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software profit_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10087</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/profit_report.php. Such manipulation of the argument product_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41664 | Improper Permission Handling Enables Unauthorized Access to Firmware and Certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41664</link><description>A low-privileged remote attacker could gain unauthorized access to critical resources, such as firmware and certificates, due to improper permission handling during the runtime of services (e.g., FTP/SFTP). This access could allow the attacker to escalate privileges and modify firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41682 | Credential Disclosure via Insecure Storage on Charge Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41682</link><description>An authenticated, low-privileged attacker can obtain credentials stored on the charge controller including the manufacturer password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41708 | Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Data via Insecure HTTP Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41708</link><description>Due to an unsecure default configuration HTTP is used instead of HTTPS for the web interface. An unauthenticated attacker on the same network could exploit this to learn sensitive data during transmission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10086 | fuyang_lipengjun platform AdPositionController queryAll improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10086</link><description>A weakness has been identified in fuyang_lipengjun platform 1.0.0. This issue affects the function queryAll of the file /adposition/queryAll of the component AdPositionController. This manipulation causes improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Affects another part than CVE-2025-9936.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8085 | Ditty &amp;lt; 3.1.58 - Unauthenticated SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8085</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.58 lacks authorization and authentication for requests to its displayItems endpoint, allowing unauthenticated visitors to make requests to arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10085 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software manage_website.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10085</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file manage_website.php. The manipulation results in unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10084 | elunez eladmin SysLogController 1 queryErrorLogDetail improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10084</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in elunez eladmin up to 2.7. This affects the function queryErrorLogDetail of the file /api/logs/error/1 of the component SysLogController. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58422 | RICOH Streamline NX versions 3.5.1 to 24R3 are vulnerable to tampering with operation history. If an attacker can perform a man-in-the-middl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58422</link><description>RICOH Streamline NX versions 3.5.1 to 24R3 are vulnerable to tampering with operation history. If an attacker can perform a man-in-the-middle attack, they may alter the values of HTTP requests, which could result in tampering with the operation history of the product’s management tool.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10083 | SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10083</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/profile.php. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10082 | SourceCodester Online Polling System manage-admins.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10082</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-admins.php. Such manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10081 | SourceCodester Pet Management System profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10081</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Pet Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/profile.php. This manipulation of the argument website_image causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10080 | running-elephant Datart API AESUtil.java getTokensecret hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10080</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in running-elephant Datart up to 1.0.0-rc3. Affected by this issue is the function getTokensecret of the file datart/security/src/main/java/datart/security/util/AESUtil.java of the component API. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10079 | PHPGurukul Small CRM get-quote.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10079</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /get-quote.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Contact can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10078 | SourceCodester Online Polling System candidates.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10078</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/candidates.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 02:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10077 | SourceCodester Online Polling System registeracc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10077</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /registeracc.php. Such manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 02:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10076 | SourceCodester Online Polling System manage-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10076</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /manage-profile.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10075 | SourceCodester Online Polling System manage-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10075</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Online Polling System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /manage-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10074 | Portabilis i-Educar tipos cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10074</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /usuarios/tipos/. The manipulation of the argument Tipos de Usuário/Descrição leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10073 | Portabilis i-Educar turma improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10073</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /module/Api/turma. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 23:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10072 | Portabilis i-Educar enturmar access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10072</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /matricula/[ID_STUDENT]/enturmar/. Performing manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 23:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10071 | Portabilis i-Educar cancelar-enturmacao-em-lote access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10071</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cancelar-enturmacao-em-lote/. Such manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10070 | Portabilis i-Educar enturmacao-em-lote access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10070</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /enturmacao-em-lote/. This manipulation causes improper access controls. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 22:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48042 | Before action hooks may execute in certain scenarios despite a request being forbidden</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48042</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in ash-project ash allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/ash/actions/create/bulk.ex, lib/ash/actions/destroy/bulk.ex, lib/ash/actions/update/bulk.ex and program routines 'Elixir.Ash.Actions.Create.Bulk':run/5, 'Elixir.Ash.Actions.Destroy.Bulk':run/6, 'Elixir.Ash.Actions.Update.Bulk:run'/6.

This issue affects ash: from pkg:hex/ash before pkg:hex/ash@3.5.39, before 3.5.39, before 5d1b6a5d00771fd468a509778637527b5218be9a.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39727 | mm: swap: fix potential buffer overflow in setup_clusters()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39727</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: swap: fix potential buffer overflow in setup_clusters()

In setup_swap_map(), we only ensure badpages are in range (0, last_page]. 
As maxpages might be &lt; last_page, setup_clusters() will encounter a buffer
overflow when a badpage is &gt;= maxpages.

Only call inc_cluster_info_page() for badpage which is &lt; maxpages to fix
the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39729 | crypto: ccp - Fix dereferencing uninitialized error pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39729</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: ccp - Fix dereferencing uninitialized error pointer

Fix below smatch warnings:
drivers/crypto/ccp/sev-dev.c:1312 __sev_platform_init_locked()
error: we previously assumed 'error' could be null</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39730 | NFS: Fix filehandle bounds checking in nfs_fh_to_dentry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39730</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

NFS: Fix filehandle bounds checking in nfs_fh_to_dentry()

The function needs to check the minimal filehandle length before it can
access the embedded filehandle.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39731 | f2fs: vm_unmap_ram() may be called from an invalid context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39731</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: vm_unmap_ram() may be called from an invalid context

When testing F2FS with xfstests using UFS backed virtual disks the
kernel complains sometimes that f2fs_release_decomp_mem() calls
vm_unmap_ram() from an invalid context. Example trace from
f2fs/007 test:

f2fs/007 5s ...  [12:59:38][    8.902525] run fstests f2fs/007
[   11.468026] BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at mm/vmalloc.c:2978
[   11.471849] in_atomic(): 1, irqs_disabled(): 1, non_block: 0, pid: 68, name: irq/22-ufshcd
[   11.475357] preempt_count: 1, expected: 0
[   11.476970] RCU nest depth: 0, expected: 0
[   11.478531] CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 68 Comm: irq/22-ufshcd Tainted: G        W           6.16.0-rc5-xfstests-ufs-g40f92e79b0aa #9 PREEMPT(none)
[   11.478535] Tainted: [W]=WARN
[   11.478536] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
[   11.478537] Call Trace:
[   11.478543]  
[   11.478545]  dump_stack_lvl+0x4e/0x70
[   11.478554]  __might_resched.cold+0xaf/0xbe
[   11.478557]  vm_unmap_ram+0x21/0xb0
[   11.478560]  f2fs_release_decomp_mem+0x59/0x80
[   11.478563]  f2fs_free_dic+0x18/0x1a0
[   11.478565]  f2fs_finish_read_bio+0xd7/0x290
[   11.478570]  blk_update_request+0xec/0x3b0
[   11.478574]  ? sbitmap_queue_clear+0x3b/0x60
[   11.478576]  scsi_end_request+0x27/0x1a0
[   11.478582]  scsi_io_completion+0x40/0x300
[   11.478583]  ufshcd_mcq_poll_cqe_lock+0xa3/0xe0
[   11.478588]  ufshcd_sl_intr+0x194/0x1f0
[   11.478592]  ufshcd_threaded_intr+0x68/0xb0
[   11.478594]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_fn+0x10/0x10
[   11.478599]  irq_thread_fn+0x20/0x60
[   11.478602]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_fn+0x10/0x10
[   11.478603]  irq_thread+0xb9/0x180
[   11.478605]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_dtor+0x10/0x10
[   11.478607]  ? __pfx_irq_thread+0x10/0x10
[   11.478609]  kthread+0x10a/0x230
[   11.478614]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[   11.478615]  ret_from_fork+0x7e/0xd0
[   11.478619]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[   11.478621]  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
[   11.478623]  

This patch modifies in_task() check inside f2fs_read_end_io() to also
check if interrupts are disabled. This ensures that pages are unmapped
asynchronously in an interrupt handler.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39732 | wifi: ath11k: fix sleeping-in-atomic in ath11k_mac_op_set_bitrate_mask()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39732</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath11k: fix sleeping-in-atomic in ath11k_mac_op_set_bitrate_mask()

ath11k_mac_disable_peer_fixed_rate() is passed as the iterator to
ieee80211_iterate_stations_atomic(). Note in this case the iterator is
required to be atomic, however ath11k_mac_disable_peer_fixed_rate() does
not follow it as it might sleep. Consequently below warning is seen:

BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at wmi.c:304
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl
 __might_resched.cold
 ath11k_wmi_cmd_send
 ath11k_wmi_set_peer_param
 ath11k_mac_disable_peer_fixed_rate
 ieee80211_iterate_stations_atomic
 ath11k_mac_op_set_bitrate_mask.cold

Change to ieee80211_iterate_stations_mtx() to fix this issue.

Tested-on: WCN6855 hw2.0 PCI WLAN.HSP.1.1-03125-QCAHSPSWPL_V1_V2_SILICONZ_LITE-3.6510.30</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39733 | team: replace team lock with rtnl lock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39733</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

team: replace team lock with rtnl lock

syszbot reports various ordering issues for lower instance locks and
team lock. Switch to using rtnl lock for protecting team device,
similar to bonding. Based on the patch by Tetsuo Handa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39734 | Revert &amp;quot;fs/ntfs3: Replace inode_trylock with inode_lock&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39734</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "fs/ntfs3: Replace inode_trylock with inode_lock"

This reverts commit 69505fe98f198ee813898cbcaf6770949636430b.

Initially, conditional lock acquisition was removed to fix an xfstest bug
that was observed during internal testing. The deadlock reported by syzbot
is resolved by reintroducing conditional acquisition. The xfstest bug no
longer occurs on kernel version 6.16-rc1 during internal testing. I
assume that changes in other modules may have contributed to this.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10068 | itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum add_views.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10068</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Online Discussion Forum 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/admin_forum/add_views.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 04:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10067 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System empty_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10067</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/empty_table.php. Performing manipulation of the argument scripts results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10066 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System dymanic_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10066</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/dymanic_table.php. Such manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10064 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System dom_data_two_headers.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10064</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/dom_data_two_headers.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10065 | itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System dom_data_th.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10065</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode POS Point of Sale System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /inventory/main/vendors/datatables/unit_testing/templates/dom_data_th.php. This manipulation of the argument scripts causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36100 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36100</link><description>IBM MQ LTS 9.1.0.0 through 9.1.0.29, 9.2.0.0 through 9.2.0.36, 9.3.0.0 through 9.3.0.30 and 9.4.0.0 through 9.4.0.12 and IBM MQ CD 9.3.0.0 through 9.3.5.1 and 9.4.0.0 through 9.4.3.0  Java and JMS stores a password in client configuration files when trace is enabled which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 01:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>