<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-13702 | CRM and Lead Management by vcita &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13702</link><description>The CRM and Lead Management by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'vCitaMeetingScheduler' and 'vCitaSchedulingCalendar' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13801 | BWL Advanced FAQ Manager &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13801</link><description>The BWL Advanced FAQ Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'baf_set_notice_status' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to '1' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1514 | Active Products Tables for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.6.7 -  Unauthenticated Arbitrary Filter Call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1514</link><description>The Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Use constructor to create tables plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized filter calling due to insufficient restrictions on the get_smth() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call arbitrary WordPress filters with a single parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2009 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2009</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the logging functionality in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2167 | Event post &amp;lt;= 5.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2167</link><description>The Event post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'events_list' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2257 | Total Upkeep – WordPress Backup Plugin plus Restore &amp;amp; Migrate by BoldGrid &amp;lt;= 1.16.10 - Authenticated (Admin+) Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2257</link><description>The Total Upkeep – WordPress Backup Plugin plus Restore &amp; Migrate by BoldGrid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.16.10 via the compression_level setting. This is due to the plugin using the compression_level setting in proc_open() without any validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30155 | HCL SX is susceptible to cookie with Insecure, Improper, or Missing SameSite attribute vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30155</link><description>HCL SX does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may potentially be able to obtain access to the cookie values via a Cross-Site-Forgery-Request (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52972 | Huawei PCs have a vulnerability that allows low-privilege users to bypass SDDL permission checks . Successful exploitation this vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52972</link><description>Huawei PCs have a vulnerability that allows low-privilege users to bypass SDDL permission checks . Successful exploitation this vulnerability could lead to termination of some system processes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11847 | WP SVG Upload &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11847</link><description>The wp-svg-upload WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which enables users with at least the author role to SVG with malicious JavaScript to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12683 | Smart Maintenance Mode &amp;lt; 1.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12683</link><description>The Smart Maintenance Mode WordPress plugin before 1.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13146 | Booknetic &amp;lt; 4.1.5 - Staff Creation via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13146</link><description>The Booknetic WordPress plugin before 4.1.5 does not have CSRF check when creating Staff accounts, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add arbitrary Staff members via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1784 | Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.19.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1784</link><description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the uagb block in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 05:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30742 | httpd.c in atophttpd 2.8.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant out-of-bounds read because a certain 1024-character req string would not ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30742</link><description>httpd.c in atophttpd 2.8.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant out-of-bounds read because a certain 1024-character req string would not have a final '\0' character.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1490 | Smart Maintenance Mode &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via setstatus Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1490</link><description>The Smart Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘setstatus’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2165 | SH Email Alert &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2165</link><description>The SH Email Alert plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2573 | Amazing service box Addons For WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2573</link><description>The Amazing service box Addons For WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2576 | Ayyash Studio &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2576</link><description>The Ayyash Studio — The kick-start kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 03:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47516 | Pagure: argument injection in pagurerepo.log()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47516</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pagure. An argument injection in Git during retrieval of the repository history leads to remote code execution on the Pagure instance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2276 | Ultimate Dashboard &amp;lt;= 3.8.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Modules Activation/Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2276</link><description>The Ultimate Dashboard – Custom WordPress Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_module_actions function in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate/deactivate plugin modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2302 | Advanced Woo Search &amp;lt;= 3.28 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via aws_search_terms Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2302</link><description>The Advanced Woo Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aws_search_terms shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30222 | Shescape has potential environment variable exposure on Windows with CMD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30222</link><description>Shescape is a simple shell escape library for JavaScript. Versions 1.7.2 through 2.1.1 are vulnerable to potential environment variable exposure on Windows with CMD. This impact users of Shescape on Windows that explicitly configure `shell: 'cmd.exe'` or `shell: true` using any of `quote`/`quoteAll`/`escape`/`escapeAll`. An attacker may be able to get read-only access to environment variables. This bug has been patched in v2.1.2. For those who are already using v2 of Shescape, no further changes are required. Those who are are using v1 of Shescape should follow the migration guide to upgrade to v2. There is no plan to release a patch compatible with v1 of Shescape. As a workaround, users can remove all instances of `%` from user input before using Shescape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30219 | RabbitMQ has XSS Vulnerability in an Error Message in Management UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30219</link><description>RabbitMQ is a messaging and streaming broker. Versions prior to 4.0.3 are vulnerable to a sophisticated attack that could modify virtual host name on disk and then make it unrecoverable (with other on disk file modifications) can lead to arbitrary JavaScript code execution in the browsers of management UI users. When a virtual host on a RabbitMQ node fails to start, recent versions
will display an error message (a notification) in the management UI. The error message includes virtual host name, which was not escaped prior to open source RabbitMQ 4.0.3 and Tanzu RabbitMQ 4.0.3, 3.13.8. An attack that both makes a virtual host fail to start and creates a new virtual host name with an XSS code snippet or changes the name of an existing virtual host on disk could trigger arbitrary JavaScript code execution in the management UI (the user's browser). Open source RabbitMQ `4.0.3` and Tanzu RabbitMQ `4.0.3` and `3.13.8` patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27837 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. Access to arbitrary files can occur through a truncated path with invalid UTF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27837</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. Access to arbitrary files can occur through a truncated path with invalid UTF-8 characters, for base/gp_mswin.c and base/winrtsup.cpp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30741 | pixelfed before 0.12.5 allows anyone to follow private accounts on other Fediverse servers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30741</link><description>pixelfed before 0.12.5 allows anyone to follow private accounts on other Fediverse servers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27830 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs during serialization of DollarBlend in a font, for b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27830</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs during serialization of DollarBlend in a font, for base/write_t1.c and psi/zfapi.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27831 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The DOCXWRITE TXTWRITE device has a text buffer overflow via long characters ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27831</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The DOCXWRITE TXTWRITE device has a text buffer overflow via long characters to devices/vector/doc_common.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27832 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The NPDL device has a Compression buffer overflow for contrib/japanese/gdevnp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27832</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The NPDL device has a Compression buffer overflow for contrib/japanese/gdevnpdl.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27833 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs for a long TTF font name to pdf/pdf_fmap.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27833</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs for a long TTF font name to pdf/pdf_fmap.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27835 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs when converting glyphs to Unicode in psi/zbfont.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27835</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs when converting glyphs to Unicode in psi/zbfont.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27836 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The BJ10V device has a Print buffer overflow in contrib/japanese/gdev10v.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27836</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. The BJ10V device has a Print buffer overflow in contrib/japanese/gdev10v.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29789 | OpenEMR Has Directory Traversal in Load Code feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29789</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions prior to 7.3.0 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal in the Load Code feature. Version 7.3.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55028 | A template injection vulnerability in the Dashboard of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55028</link><description>A template injection vulnerability in the Dashboard of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted Vue file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55029 | NASA Fprime v3.4.3 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55029</link><description>NASA Fprime v3.4.3 was discovered to contain multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55030 | A command injection vulnerability in the Command Dispatcher Service of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55030</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the Command Dispatcher Service of NASA Fprime v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25371 | NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to path traversal in the OSAL module, allowing the override of any arbitrary file on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25371</link><description>NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to path traversal in the OSAL module, allowing the override of any arbitrary file on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25372 | NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to segmentation fault via sending a malicious telecommand to the Memory Management Module...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25372</link><description>NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila is vulnerable to segmentation fault via sending a malicious telecommand to the Memory Management Module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25373 | The Memory Management Module of NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila has insecure permissions, which can be exploited to gain an RCE on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25373</link><description>The Memory Management Module of NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila has insecure permissions, which can be exploited to gain an RCE on the platform.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25374 | In NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila, it is possible to put the onboard software in a state that will prevent the launch of any external ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25374</link><description>In NASA cFS (Core Flight System) Aquila, it is possible to put the onboard software in a state that will prevent the launch of any external application, causing a platform denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27834 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs via an oversized Type 4 function in a PDF document t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27834</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0. A buffer overflow occurs via an oversized Type 4 function in a PDF document to pdf/pdf_func.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48818 | An issue in IIT Bombay, Mumbai, India Bodhitree of cs101 version allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48818</link><description>An issue in IIT Bombay, Mumbai, India Bodhitree of cs101 version allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30118 | An issue was discovered on the Audi Universal Traffic Recorder 2.88. It has Susceptibility to denial of service. It uses the same default cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30118</link><description>An issue was discovered on the Audi Universal Traffic Recorder 2.88. It has Susceptibility to denial of service. It uses the same default credentials for all devices and does not implement proper multi-device authentication, allowing attackers to deny the owner access by occupying the only available connection. The SSID remains broadcast at all times, increasing exposure to potential attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30216 | CryptoLib Has Heap Overflow in Crypto_TM_ProcessSecurity due to Unchecked Secondary Header Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30216</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. In versions 1.3.3 and prior, a Heap Overflow vulnerability occurs in the `Crypto_TM_ProcessSecurity` function (`crypto_tm.c:1735:8`). When processing the Secondary Header Length of a TM protocol packet, if the Secondary Header Length exceeds the packet's total length, a heap overflow is triggered during the memcpy operation that copies packet data into the dynamically allocated buffer `p_new_dec_frame`. This allows an attacker to overwrite adjacent heap memory, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution or system instability. A patch is available at commit 810fd66d592c883125272fef123c3240db2f170f.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 19:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31896 | IBM SPSS Statistics information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31896</link><description>IBM SPSS Statistics 26.0, 27.0.1, 28.0.1, and 29.0.2 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28904 | WordPress Web Directory Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28904</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Shamalli Web Directory Free allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Web Directory Free: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30567 | WordPress WP01 &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30567</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wp01ru WP01 allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WP01: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2312 | cifs.upcall  makes an upcall to the wrong namespace in containerized environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2312</link><description>A flaw was found in cifs-utils. When trying to obtain Kerberos credentials, the cifs.upcall program from the cifs-utils package makes an upcall to the wrong namespace in containerized environments. This issue may lead to disclosing sensitive data from the host's Kerberos credentials cache.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58104 | A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58104</link><description>A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing security and execute arbitrary code on affected installations. 

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58105 | A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58105</link><description>A vulnerability  in the Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent Plug-in User Interface Manager could allow a local attacker to bypass existing security and execute arbitrary code on affected installations. 

This CVE address an addtional bypass not covered in CVE-2024-58104.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30214 | Frappe vulnerable to information disclosure leading to account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30214</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0, making crafted requests could lead to information disclosure that could further lead to account takeover. Versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0 fix the issue. There's no workaround to fix this without upgrading.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30213 | Frappe has Possibility of Remote Code Execution due to improper validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30213</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to versions 14.91.0 and 15.52.0, a system user was able to create certain documents in a specific way that could lead to remote code execution. Versions 14.9.1 and 15.52.0 contain a patch for the vulnerability. There's no workaround; an upgrade is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26742 | WordPress Gallery for Social Photo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0.35 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Gallery for Social Photo allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gallery for Social Photo: from n/a through 1.0.0.35.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27147 | GLPI Inventory plugin has Improper Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27147</link><description>The GLPI Inventory Plugin handles various types of tasks for GLPI agents, including network discovery and inventory (SNMP), software deployment, VMWare ESX host remote inventory, and data collection (files, Windows registry, WMI). Versions prior to 1.5.0 have an improper access control vulnerability. Version 1.5.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30212 | Frappe has possibility of SQL injection due to improper validations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30212</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. An SQL Injection vulnerability has been identified in Frappe Framework prior to versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0 which could allow a malicious actor to access sensitive information. Versions 14.89.0 and 15.51.0 fix the issue. Upgrading is required; no other workaround is present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55604 | Appsmith&amp;#x27;s Broken Access Control Allows Viewer Role User to Query Datasources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55604</link><description>Appsmith is a platform to build admin panels, internal tools, and dashboards. Users invited as "App Viewer" should not have access to development information of a workspace. Datasources are such a component in a workspace. Yet, in versions of Appsmith prior to 1.51, app viewers are able to get a list of datasources in a workspace they're a member of. This information disclosure does NOT expose sensitive data in the datasources, such as database passwords and API Keys. The attacker needs to have been invited to a workspace as a "viewer", by someone in that workspace with access to invite. The attacker then needs to be able to signup/login to that Appsmith instance. The issue is patched in version 1.51. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2530 | Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Access of Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2530</link><description>Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Access of Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of dae files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23698.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2531 | Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2531</link><description>Luxion KeyShot DAE File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of dae files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23704.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2532 | Luxion KeyShot USDC File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2532</link><description>Luxion KeyShot USDC File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of usdc files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42533 | SQL injection vulnerability in the authentication module in Convivance StandVoice 4.5 through 6.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42533</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the authentication module in Convivance StandVoice 4.5 through 6.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the GEST_LOGIN parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22230 | Authentication bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22230</link><description>VMware Tools for Windows contains an authentication bypass vulnerability due to improper access control. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges on a guest VM may gain ability to perform certain high privilege operations within that VM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30091 | In Tiny MoxieManager PHP before 4.0.0, remote code execution can occur in the installer command. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30091</link><description>In Tiny MoxieManager PHP before 4.0.0, remote code execution can occur in the installer command. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary code. Attacker-controlled data to InstallCommand can be inserted into config.php, and InstallCommand is available after an installation has completed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29635 | A command injection vulnerability in D-Link DIR-823X 240126 and 240802 allows an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary commands on remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29635</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in D-Link DIR-823X 240126 and 240802 allows an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary commands on remote devices by sending a POST request to /goform/set_prohibiting via the corresponding function, triggering remote command execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11499 | A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-4-104 controlled station functionality, that allows an authenticated and authorized attacker to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11499</link><description>A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-4-104 controlled station functionality, that allows an authenticated and authorized attacker to perform a CMU restart. The vulnerability can be triggered if certificates are updated while in use on active connections.

The affected CMU will automatically recover itself if an attacker successfully exploits this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12169 | A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-5-104 controlled station functionality and IEC 61850 functionality, that allows an attacker perfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12169</link><description>A vulnerability exists in RTU500 IEC 60870-5-104 controlled station functionality and IEC 61850 functionality, that allows an attacker performing a specific attack sequence to restart the affected CMU. This vulnerability only applies, if secure communication using IEC 62351-3 (TLS) is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1445 | A vulnerability exists in RTU IEC 61850 client and server functionality that could impact the availability if renegotiation of an open IEC61...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1445</link><description>A vulnerability exists in RTU IEC 61850 client and server functionality that could impact the availability if renegotiation of an open IEC61850 TLS connection takes place in specific timing situations, when IEC61850 communication is active.

Precondition is that IEC61850 as client or server are configured using TLS on RTU500 device. It affects the CMU the IEC61850 stack is configured on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27631 | The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to LDAP injection attack potentially allowing an attacker to inject code into a query and execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27631</link><description>The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to LDAP injection attack potentially allowing an attacker to inject code into a query and execute remote commands that can read and update data on the website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27632 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability in TRMTracker application may allow an attacker by modifying the host header value in an HTTP request ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27632</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability in TRMTracker application may allow an attacker by modifying the host header value in an HTTP request to leverage multiple attack vectors, including defacing the site content through web-cache poisoning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27633 | The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to reflected Cross-site scripting attack. The application allows client-side code injection tha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27633</link><description>The TRMTracker web application is vulnerable to reflected Cross-site scripting attack. The application allows client-side code injection that might be used to compromise the confidentiality and integrity of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29932 | In JetBrains GoLand before 2025.1 an XXE during debugging was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29932</link><description>In JetBrains GoLand before 2025.1 an XXE during debugging was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-1804 | Accountsservice incorrectly drops privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1804</link><description>accountsservice no longer drops permissions when writting .pam_environment</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10037 | A vulnerability exists in the RTU500 web server component that can cause a denial of service to the RTU500 CMU application if a specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10037</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the RTU500 web server component that can cause a denial of service to the RTU500 CMU application if a specially crafted message sequence is executed on a WebSocket connection.
An attacker must be properly authenticated and the test mode function of RTU500 must be enabled to exploit this vulnerability.

The affected CMU will automatically recover itself if an attacker successfully exploits this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2109 | WP Compress &amp;lt;= 6.30.15 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery via init Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2109</link><description>The WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp; Speed Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.30.15 via the init() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53678 | Apache VCL: SQL injection vulnerability in New Block Allocation form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache VCL. Users can modify form data submitted when requesting a new Block Allocation such that a SELECT SQL statement is modified. The data returned by the SELECT statement is not viewable by the attacker.

This issue affects all versions of Apache VCL from 2.2 through 2.5.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.5.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53679 | Apache VCL: XSS vulnerability in User Lookup impacting user privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache VCL in the User Lookup form. A user with sufficient rights to be able to view this part of the site can craft a URL or be tricked in to clicking a URL that will give a specified user elevated rights.



This issue affects all versions of Apache VCL through 2.5.1.



Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.5.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2756 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp AC3D File ACLoader.cpp ConvertObjectSection heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2756</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This affects the function Assimp::AC3DImporter::ConvertObjectSection of the file code/AssetLib/AC/ACLoader.cpp of the component AC3D File Handler. The manipulation of the argument tmp leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2757 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp MD5 File MD5Parser.cpp AI_MD5_PARSE_STRING_IN_QUOTATION heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2757</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This vulnerability affects the function AI_MD5_PARSE_STRING_IN_QUOTATION of the file code/AssetLib/MD5/MD5Parser.cpp of the component MD5 File Handler. The manipulation of the argument data leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2542 | Your Simple SVG Support &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2542</link><description>The Your Simple SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2635 | Digital License Manager &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via remove_query_arg Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2635</link><description>The Digital License Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg() function without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2755 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp AC3D File ACLoader.cpp ConvertObjectSection out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2755</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function Assimp::AC3DImporter::ConvertObjectSection of the file code/AssetLib/AC/ACLoader.cpp of the component AC3D File Handler. The manipulation of the argument src.entries leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2753 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp LWS File LWSLoader.cpp MergeScenes out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function SceneCombiner::MergeScenes of the file code/AssetLib/LWS/LWSLoader.cpp of the component LWS File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2754 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp AC3D File ACLoader.cpp ConvertObjectSection heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2754</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Assimp::AC3DImporter::ConvertObjectSection of the file code/AssetLib/AC/ACLoader.cpp of the component AC3D File Handler. The manipulation of the argument it leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13690 | WP Church Donation &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13690</link><description>The WP Church Donation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several donation form submission parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13710 | Estatebud – Properties &amp;amp; Listings &amp;lt;= 5.5.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13710</link><description>The Estatebud – Properties &amp; Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'estatebud_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13731 | Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Alert Box Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13731</link><description>The Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Alert Box block in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2319 | EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup 4.11.13 - 5.25.08 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2319</link><description>The EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions 4.11.13 to 5.25.08. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ELISQLREPORTS_menu' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Version 5.25.10 adds a nonce check, which makes this vulnerability exploitable by admins only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2510 | Frndzk Expandable Bottom Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2510</link><description>The Frndzk Expandable Bottom Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'text' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2559 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: jwt token cache exhaustion leading to denial of service (dos) in keycloak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2559</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. When the configuration uses JWT tokens for authentication, the tokens are cached until expiration. If a client uses JWT tokens with an excessively long expiration time, for example, 24 or 48 hours, the cache can grow indefinitely, leading to an OutOfMemoryError. This issue could result in a denial of service condition, preventing legitimate users from accessing the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2752 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSM File fast_atof.h fast_atoreal_move out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2752</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function fast_atoreal_move in the library include/assimp/fast_atof.h of the component CSM File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 08:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2750 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSM File CSMLoader.cpp InternReadFile out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2750</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This affects the function Assimp::CSMImporter::InternReadFile of the file code/AssetLib/CSM/CSMLoader.cpp of the component CSM File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds write. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2751 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp CSM File CSMLoader.cpp InternReadFile out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2751</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function Assimp::CSMImporter::InternReadFile of the file code/AssetLib/CSM/CSMLoader.cpp of the component CSM File Handler. The manipulation of the argument na leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12623 | DICOM Support &amp;lt;= 0.10.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12623</link><description>The DICOM Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'dcm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.10.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1320 | teachPress &amp;lt;= 9.0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Import Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1320</link><description>The teachPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the import.php page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete imports via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2252 | Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy &amp;lt;= 3.3.6.1 - Unauthenticated Private Post Title Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2252</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.6.1 via the edd_ajax_get_download_title() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract private post titles of downloads. The impact here is minimal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2743 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Material Upload Interface upload-temporary path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2743</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin-api/mp/material/upload-temporary of the component Material Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2744 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Material Upload Interface upload-news-image path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2744</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-api/mp/material/upload-news-image of the component Material Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 07:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2740 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System eligibility.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2740</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/eligibility.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2742 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Material Upload Interface upload-permanent path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2742</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin-api/mp/material/upload-permanent of the component Material Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10105 | Jobs for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.7.11 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10105</link><description>The Job Postings WordPress plugin before 2.7.11 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10472 | Stylish Price List  &amp;lt; 7.1.12 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10472</link><description>The Stylish Price List  WordPress plugin before 7.1.12 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10554 | WP-Advanced-Search &amp;lt; 3.3.9.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10554</link><description>The WordPress WP-Advanced-Search WordPress plugin before 3.3.9.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10560 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.30 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10560</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.30 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10565 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.62 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10565</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.62 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10566 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.62 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10566</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.62 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10638 | Product Labels For Woocommerce &amp;lt; 1.5.11 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10638</link><description>The Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) WordPress plugin before 1.5.11 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10679 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt; 9.2.1 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10679</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10703 | Registrations for The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 2.13.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10703</link><description>The Registrations for the Events Calendar  WordPress plugin before 2.13.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11272 | Contact Form &amp;amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms &amp;lt; 2.6.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11272</link><description>The Contact Form &amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms WordPress plugin before 2.6.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11273 | Contact Form &amp;amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms &amp;lt; 2.6.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11273</link><description>The Contact Form &amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms WordPress plugin before 2.6.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11503 | WP Tabs &amp;lt; 2.2.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11503</link><description>The WP Tabs  WordPress plugin before 2.2.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12109 | Product Labels For Woocommerce &amp;lt; 1.5.9 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12109</link><description>The Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) WordPress plugin before 1.5.9 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12682 | Smart Maintenance Mode &amp;lt; 1.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12682</link><description>The Smart Maintenance Mode WordPress plugin before 1.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12769 | Simple Banner &amp;lt; 3.0.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12769</link><description>The Simple Banner  WordPress plugin before 3.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13118 | IP Based Login &amp;lt; 2.4.1 - Log Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13118</link><description>The IP Based Login WordPress plugin before 2.4.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users delete all logs via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13122 | AFI &amp;lt; 1.100.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13122</link><description>The AFI  WordPress plugin before 1.100.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13123 | AFI &amp;lt; 1.100.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13123</link><description>The AFI  WordPress plugin before 1.100.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13617 | Downloable by American Osteopathic Association &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13617</link><description>The aoa-downloadable WordPress plugin through 0.1.0 doesn't validate a parameter in its download function, allowing unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary files from the server</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13618 | Downloable by American Osteopathic Association &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Unauthenticated SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13618</link><description>The aoa-downloadable WordPress plugin through 0.1.0 lacks authorization and authentication for requests to its download.php endpoint, allowing unauthenticated visitors to make requests to arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13863 | Stylish Google Sheet Reader &amp;lt; 4.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13863</link><description>The Stylish Google Sheet Reader 4.0  WordPress plugin before 4.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9770 | WP-Recall &amp;lt; 16.26.12 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9770</link><description>The WP-Recall  WordPress plugin before 16.26.12 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0717 | Social Slider Feed &amp;lt; 2.2.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0717</link><description>To exploit the vulnerability, it is necessary:</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1452 | Favorites  &amp;lt; 2.3.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1452</link><description>The Favorites WordPress plugin before 2.3.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1798 | Design Comuni Italia &amp;lt; 1.1.2 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1798</link><description>The  does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputting them back in a page, allowing unauthenticated users the ability to perform stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2738 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System manage-scdetails.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2738</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/manage-scdetails.php. The manipulation of the argument namesc leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2739 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System manage-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2739</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sertitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 06:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44903 | SQL Injection can occur in the SirsiDynix Horizon Information Portal (IPAC20): through 3.25_9382. This is in ipac.jsp in a SELECT WHERE stat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44903</link><description>SQL Injection can occur in the SirsiDynix Horizon Information Portal (IPAC20): through 3.25_9382. This is in ipac.jsp in a SELECT WHERE statement, in a part of the uri= variable in the second part of the full= inner variable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27810 | Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, in some cases of failed memory allocation or hardware errors, uses uninitialized stack memory ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27810</link><description>Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, in some cases of failed memory allocation or hardware errors, uses uninitialized stack memory to compose the TLS Finished message, potentially leading to authentication bypasses such as replays.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10210 | Path traversal in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10210</link><description>An External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-005P may allow an authenticated network-based attacker to access data from the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27809 | Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, on the client side, accepts servers that have trusted certificates for arbitrary hostnames unl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27809</link><description>Mbed TLS before 2.28.10 and 3.x before 3.6.3, on the client side, accepts servers that have trusted certificates for arbitrary hostnames unless the TLS client application calls mbedtls_ssl_set_hostname.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2737 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2737</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0845 | DesignThemes Core Features &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0845</link><description>The DesignThemes Core Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2224 | Directorist &amp;lt;= 8.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Publishing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2224</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access  and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'parse_query' function in all versions up to, and including, 8.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the post_status of any post to 'publish'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2735 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System add-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2735</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sertitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2736 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System bwdates-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bwdates-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45481 | Improper authentication in SSH of B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45481</link><description>An Incomplete Filtering of Special Elements vulnerability in scripts using the SSH server on B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated local attacker to authenticate as another legitimate user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45482 | Privilege escalation in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45482</link><description>An Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere vulnerability in the SSH server on B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P1 may allow an authenticated local attacker from a trusted remote server to execute malicious commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45483 | Missing GRUB password in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45483</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in the GRUB configuration used B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-01 may allow an unauthenticated physical attacker to alter the boot configuration of the operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45484 | Enabled ICMP redirection in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45484</link><description>An Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in the operating system network configuration used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to per-form Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks against the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 05:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10208 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10208</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated network-based attacker to insert malicious code which is then executed in the context of the user’s browser session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10209 | Incorrect Permission Assignment in APROL file system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10209</link><description>An Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in the file system used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-01 may allow an authenticated local attacker to read and alter the configuration of another engineering or runtime user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45480 | Unauthorized local file reading in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45480</link><description>An improper control of generation of code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in the AprolCreateReport component of B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated network-based attacker to read files from the local system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10207 | Server-Side Request Forgery (authenticated) in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10207</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated network-based attacker to force the web server to request arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10206 | Server-Side Request Forgery (unauthenticated) in APROL Web Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10206</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in the APROL Web Portal used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated network-based attacker to force the web server to request arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8313 | Default or Guessable SNMP community names in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8313</link><description>An Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere and Initialization of a Resource with an Insecure Default vulnerability in the SNMP component of B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an unauthenticated adjacent-based attacker to read and alter configuration using SNMP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8314 | Improper session handling in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8314</link><description>An Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm and Exposure of Data Element to Wrong Ses-sion vulnerability in the session handling used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated network attacker to take over a currently active user session without login credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8315 | Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges in B&amp;amp;R APROL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8315</link><description>An Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerability in scripts used in B&amp;amp;R APROL &lt;4.4-00P5 may allow an authenticated local attacker to read credential information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2733 | mannaandpoem OpenManus Prompt python_execute.py os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2733</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in mannaandpoem OpenManus up to 2025.3.13. This affects an unknown part of the file app/tool/python_execute.py of the component Prompt Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2734 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2734</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2732 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getWifiNeighbour command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2732</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/wizard/getWifiNeighbour of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 04:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2731 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getDualbandSync command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2731</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/wizard/getDualbandSync of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 03:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2729 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request networkSetup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2729</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/wizard/networkSetup of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 03:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2730 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getssidname command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/wizard/getssidname of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 03:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2727 | H3C Magic NX30 Pro HTTP POST Request getNetworkStatus command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2727</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in H3C Magic NX30 Pro up to V100R007. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/wizard/getNetworkStatus of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2728 | H3C Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400 getNetworkConf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2728</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in H3C Magic NX30 Pro and Magic NX400 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/wizard/getNetworkConf. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2725 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request auth command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2725</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/login/auth of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2726 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request esps command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2726</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/esps of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2724 | GNOME libgsf sorting_key_copy out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2724</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. Affected is the function sorting_key_copy. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2723 | GNOME libgsf gsf_property_settings_collec heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2723</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function gsf_property_settings_collec. The manipulation of the argument n_alloced_params leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2722 | GNOME libgsf gsf_prop_settings_collect_va heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2722</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function gsf_prop_settings_collect_va. The manipulation of the argument n_alloced_params leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2721 | GNOME libgsf gsf_base64_encode_simple heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2721</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function gsf_base64_encode_simple. The manipulation of the argument size_t leads to heap-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1097 | ingress-nginx controller - configuration injection via unsanitized auth-tls-match-cn annotation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1097</link><description>A security issue was discovered in  ingress-nginx https://github.com/kubernetes/ingress-nginx  where the `auth-tls-match-cn` Ingress annotation can be used to inject configuration into nginx. This can lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the ingress-nginx controller, and disclosure of Secrets accessible to the controller. (Note that in the default installation, the controller can access all Secrets cluster-wide.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1098 | ingress-nginx controller - configuration injection via unsanitized mirror annotations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1098</link><description>A security issue was discovered in  ingress-nginx https://github.com/kubernetes/ingress-nginx  where the `mirror-target` and `mirror-host` Ingress annotations can be used to inject arbitrary configuration into nginx. This can lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the ingress-nginx controller, and disclosure of Secrets accessible to the controller. (Note that in the default installation, the controller can access all Secrets cluster-wide.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1974 | ingress-nginx admission controller RCE escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1974</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where under certain conditions, an unauthenticated attacker with access to the pod network can achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the ingress-nginx controller. This can lead to disclosure of Secrets accessible to the controller. (Note that in the default installation, the controller can access all Secrets cluster-wide.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24513 | ingress-nginx controller - auth secret file path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24513</link><description>A security issue was discovered in  ingress-nginx https://github.com/kubernetes/ingress-nginx  where attacker-provided data are included in a filename by the ingress-nginx Admission Controller feature, resulting in directory traversal within the container. This could result in denial of service, or when combined with other vulnerabilities, limited disclosure of Secret objects from the cluster.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24514 | ingress-nginx controller - configuration injection via unsanitized auth-url annotation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24514</link><description>A security issue was discovered in  ingress-nginx https://github.com/kubernetes/ingress-nginx  where the `auth-url` Ingress annotation can be used to inject configuration into nginx. This can lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the ingress-nginx controller, and disclosure of Secrets accessible to the controller. (Note that in the default installation, the controller can access all Secrets cluster-wide.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2717 | D-Link DIR-823X HTTP POST Request diag_nslookup sub_41710C os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2717</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 240126/240802. This issue affects the function sub_41710C of the file /goform/diag_nslookup of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument target_addr leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2720 | GNOME libgsf gsf_base64_encode_simple uninitialized variable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2720</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME libgsf up to 1.14.53 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function gsf_base64_encode_simple. The manipulation of the argument size leads to use of uninitialized variable. The attack needs to be approached locally. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2716 | China Mobile P22g-CIac Samba Path path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2716</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in China Mobile P22g-CIac 1.0.00.488. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Samba Path Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2715 | timschofield webERP Confirm Dispatch and Invoice Page ConfirmDispatch_Invoice.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2715</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in timschofield webERP up to 5.0.0.rc+13. This affects an unknown part of the file ConfirmDispatch_Invoice.php of the component Confirm Dispatch and Invoice Page. The manipulation of the argument Narrative leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 22:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26512 | CVE-2025-26512 Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in SnapCenter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26512</link><description>SnapCenter versions prior to 
6.0.1P1 and 6.1P1 are susceptible to a vulnerability which may allow an 
authenticated SnapCenter Server user to become an admin user on a remote
 system where a SnapCenter plug-in has been installed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 22:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2714 | JoomlaUX JUX Real Estate addagent cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2714</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoomlaUX JUX Real Estate 3.4.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /extensions/realestate/index.php/agents/agent-register/addagent. The manipulation of the argument plan_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 22:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2712 | Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC top.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2712</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC 5.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /help/top.jsp. The manipulation of the argument langcode leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2711 | Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC systop.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2711</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC 5.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /help/systop.jsp. The manipulation of the argument langcode leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 21:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29313 | Use of incorrectly resolved name or reference in OpenDaylight Service Function Chaining (SFC) Subproject SFC Sodium-SR4 and below allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29313</link><description>Use of incorrectly resolved name or reference in OpenDaylight Service Function Chaining (SFC) Subproject SFC Sodium-SR4 and below allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29314 | Insecure Shiro cookie configurations in OpenDaylight Service Function Chaining (SFC) Subproject SFC Sodium-SR4 and below allow attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29314</link><description>Insecure Shiro cookie configurations in OpenDaylight Service Function Chaining (SFC) Subproject SFC Sodium-SR4 and below allow attackers to access sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29315 | An issue in the Shiro-based RBAC (Role-based Access Control) mechanism of OpenDaylight Service Function Chaining (SFC) Subproject SFC Sodium...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29315</link><description>An issue in the Shiro-based RBAC (Role-based Access Control) mechanism of OpenDaylight Service Function Chaining (SFC) Subproject SFC Sodium-SR4 and below allows attackers to execute privileged operations via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29100 | Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the fromSetRouteStatic function via the parameter list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29100</link><description>Tenda AC8 V16.03.34.06 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the fromSetRouteStatic function via the parameter list.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29135 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC7 V15.03.06.44 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code through a stack ove...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29135</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC7 V15.03.06.44 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code through a stack overflow attack using the security parameter of the formWifiBasicSet function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29312 | An issue in onos v2.7.0 allows attackers to trigger unexpected behavior within a device connected to a legacy switch via changing the link t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29312</link><description>An issue in onos v2.7.0 allows attackers to trigger unexpected behavior within a device connected to a legacy switch via changing the link type from indirect to direct.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29310 | An issue in onos v2.7.0 allows attackers to trigger a packet deserialization problem when supplying a crafted LLDP packet. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29310</link><description>An issue in onos v2.7.0 allows attackers to trigger a packet deserialization problem when supplying a crafted LLDP packet. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands or access network information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29311 | Limited secret space in LLDP packets used in onos v2.7.0 allows attackers to obtain the private key via a bruteforce attack. Attackers are a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29311</link><description>Limited secret space in LLDP packets used in onos v2.7.0 allows attackers to obtain the private key via a bruteforce attack. Attackers are able to leverage this vulnerability into creating crafted LLDP packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2710 | Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC menu.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2710</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC 5.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /menu.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flag leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2709 | Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC login.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2709</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Yonyou UFIDA ERP-NC 5.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.jsp. The manipulation of the argument key/redirect leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2231 | PDF-XChange Editor RTF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2231</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor RTF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of RTF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25473.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2708 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Backend File Upload Interface upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2708</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin-api/infra/file/upload of the component Backend File Upload Interface. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2707 | zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro Front-End Store Interface upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2707</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in zhijiantianya ruoyi-vue-pro 2.4.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /app-api/infra/file/upload of the component Front-End Store Interface. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30162 | East-west traffic not subject to egress policy enforcement for requests via Gateway API load balancers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30162</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. For Cilium users who use Gateway API for Ingress for some services and use LB-IPAM or BGP for LB Service implementation and use network policies to block egress traffic from workloads in a namespace to workloads in other namespaces, egress traffic from workloads covered by such network policies to LoadBalancers configured by `Gateway` resources will incorrectly be allowed. LoadBalancer resources not deployed via a Gateway API configuration are not affected by this issue. This issue affects: Cilium v1.15 between v1.15.0 and v1.15.14 inclusive, v1.16 between v1.16.0 and v1.16.7 inclusive, and v1.17 between v1.17.0 and v1.17.1 inclusive. This issue is fixed in Cilium v1.15.15, v1.16.8, and v1.17.2. A Clusterwide Cilium Network Policy can be used to work around this issue for users who are unable to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30163 | Node based network policies may incorrectly allow workload traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30163</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. Node based network policies (`fromNodes` and `toNodes`) will incorrectly permit traffic to/from non-node endpoints that share the labels specified in `fromNodes` and `toNodes` sections of network policies. Node based network policy is disabled by default in Cilium. This issue affects: Cilium v1.16 between v1.16.0 and v1.16.7 inclusive and v1.17 between v1.17.0 and v1.17.1 inclusive. This issue is fixed in Cilium v1.16.8 and v1.17.2. Users can work around this issue by ensuring that the labels used in `fromNodes` and `toNodes` fields are used exclusively by nodes and not by other endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2706 | Digiwin ERP UploadAjaxAPI.ashx unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2706</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Digiwin ERP 5.0.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Api/TinyMce/UploadAjaxAPI.ashx. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2746 | Kentico Xperience Staging Sync Server digest password authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2746</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authentication bypass via the Staging Sync Server password handling of empty SHA1 usernames in digest authentication. Authentication bypass allows an attacker to control administrative objects.This issue affects Xperience through 13.0.172.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2747 | Kentico Xperience Staging Sync Server None password type authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2747</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows authentication bypass via the Staging Sync Server component password handling for the server defined None type. Authentication bypass allows an attacker to control administrative objects.This issue affects Xperience through 13.0.178.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2748 | Kentico Xperience stored cross-site scripting in multiple-file upload functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2748</link><description>The Kentico Xperience application does not fully validate or filter files uploaded via the multiple-file upload functionality, which allows for stored XSS.This issue affects Kentico Xperience through 13.0.178.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2749 | Kentico Xperience Staging media files upload authenticated remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2749</link><description>An authenticated remote code execution in Kentico Xperience allows authenticated users Staging Sync Server to upload arbitrary data to path relative locations. This results in path traversal and arbitrary file upload, including content that can be executed server side leading to remote code execution.This issue affects Kentico Xperience through 13.0.178.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22223 | Spring Security 6.4.0 - 6.4.3 may not correctly locate method security annotations on parameterized types or methods. This may cause an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22223</link><description>Spring Security 6.4.0 - 6.4.3 may not correctly locate method security annotations on parameterized types or methods. This may cause an authorization bypass. 

You are not affected if you are not using @EnableMethodSecurity, or
you do not have method security annotations on parameterized types or methods, or all method security annotations are attached to target methods</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 17:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30112 | On 70mai Dash Cam 1S devices, by connecting directly to the dashcam's network and accessing the API on port 80 and RTSP on port 554, an atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30112</link><description>On 70mai Dash Cam 1S devices, by connecting directly to the dashcam's network and accessing the API on port 80 and RTSP on port 554, an attacker can bypass the device authorization mechanism from the official mobile app that requires a user to physically press on the power button during a connection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 17:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30208 | Vite bypasses server.fs.deny when using `?raw??`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30208</link><description>Vite, a provider of frontend development tooling, has a vulnerability in versions prior to 6.2.3, 6.1.2, 6.0.12, 5.4.15, and 4.5.10. `@fs` denies access to files outside of Vite serving allow list. Adding `?raw??` or `?import&amp;amp;raw??` to the URL bypasses this limitation and returns the file content if it exists. This bypass exists because trailing separators such as `?` are removed in several places, but are not accounted for in query string regexes. The contents of arbitrary files can be returned to the browser. Only apps explicitly exposing the Vite dev server to the network (using `--host` or `server.host` config option) are affected. Versions 6.2.3, 6.1.2, 6.0.12, 5.4.15, and 4.5.10 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 17:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30205 | kanidm-provision leaks provisioned admin credentials into the system log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30205</link><description>kanidim-provision is a helper utility that uses kanidm's API to provision users, groups and oauth2 systems. Prior to version 1.2.0, a faulty function intrumentation in the (optional) kanidm patches provided by kandim-provision will cause the provisioned admin credentials to be leaked to the system log. This only impacts users which both use the provided patches and provision their `admin` or `idm_admin` account credentials this way. No other credentials are affected. Users should recompile kanidm with the newest patchset from tag `v1.2.0` or higher. As a workaround, the user can set the log level `KANIDM_LOG_LEVEL` to any level higher than `info`, for example `warn`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29778 | Kyverno ignores subjectRegExp and IssuerRegExp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29778</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for cloud native platform engineering teams. Prior to version 1.14.0-alpha.1, Kyverno ignores subjectRegExp and IssuerRegExp while verifying artifact's sign with keyless mode. It allows the attacker to deploy kubernetes resources with the artifacts that were signed by unexpected certificate. Deploying these unauthorized kubernetes resources can lead to full compromise of kubernetes cluster. Version 1.14.0-alpha.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0255 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is susceptible to command injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0255</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch could allow a remote privileged authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending specially crafted input containing special elements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9103 | Persistent XSS in blocked messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9103</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script in Attributes in a Web Page vulnerability in Forcepoint Email Security (Blocked Messages module) allows Stored XSS.
This issue affects Email Security through 8.5.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2705 | Digiwin ERP FileUploadApi.ashx DoWebUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2705</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Digiwin ERP 5.1. Affected is the function DoUpload/DoWebUpload of the file /Api/FileUploadApi.ashx. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23204 | GraphQl securityAfterResolver not called</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23204</link><description>API Platform Core is a system to create hypermedia-driven REST and GraphQL APIs. Starting in version 3.3.8, a security check that gets called after GraphQl resolvers is always replaced by another one as there's no break in a clause. As this falls back to `security`, the impact is there only when there's only a security after resolver and none inside security. The test in version 3.3.8 is probably broken. As of time of publication, a fixed version is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25610 | A buffer underwrite ('buffer underflow') vulnerability in the administrative interface of Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25610</link><description>A buffer underwrite ('buffer underflow') vulnerability in the administrative interface of Fortinet FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, version 7.0.0 through 7.0.6, version 6.4.0 through 6.4.11 and version 6.2.12 and below, FortiProxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, version 7.0.0 through 7.0.8, version 2.0.12 and below and FortiOS-6K7K version 7.0.5, version 6.4.0 through 6.4.10 and version 6.2.0 through 6.2.10 and below allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via specifically crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26091 | A use of a cryptographically weak pseudo-random number generator vulnerability in the authenticator of the Identity Based Encryption service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26091</link><description>A use of a cryptographically weak pseudo-random number generator vulnerability in the authenticator of the Identity Based Encryption service of FortiMail 6.4.0 through 6.4.4, and 6.2.0 through 6.2.7 may allow an unauthenticated attacker to infer parts of users authentication tokens and reset their credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0256 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is susceptible to a sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0256</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information about other users on the system due to missing authorization for a function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26105 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability (CWE-121) in the profile parser of FortiSandbox version 3.2.2 and below, version 3.1.4 and below...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26105</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability (CWE-121) in the profile parser of FortiSandbox version 3.2.2 and below, version 3.1.4 and below may allow an authenticated attacker to potentially execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29294 | An issue in H3C R3000 V100R009 and NX600 V100R0011 and NX15000 V100R005 and NX30 V100R0011 and NX54 V100R011 and BX54 V100R004 and BX54-E V1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29294</link><description>An issue in H3C R3000 V100R009 and NX600 V100R0011 and NX15000 V100R005 and NX30 V100R0011 and NX54 V100R011 and BX54 V100R004 and BX54-E V100R0010 and NX18 Plus V100R006 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the set_ipv6_static function and the clear_ipv6_info function</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55279 | Uguu through 1.8.9 allows Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via JavaScript in XML files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55279</link><description>Uguu through 1.8.9 allows Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via JavaScript in XML files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1558 | Denial of Service Via Malicious GIF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1558</link><description>Mattermost Mobile Apps versions &lt;=2.25.0 fail to properly validate GIF images prior to rendering which allows a malicious user to cause the Android application to crash via message containing a maliciously crafted GIF.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 15:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30521 | WordPress GP Back To Top plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30521</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in giangmd93 GP Back To Top allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects GP Back To Top: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30522 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Material Design plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30522</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Damian Orzol Contact Form 7 Material Design allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Material Design: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30523 | WordPress Super Simple Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30523</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Marcel-NL Super Simple Subscriptions allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Super Simple Subscriptions: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30525 | WordPress WP Profitshare plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30525</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ProfitShare.ro WP Profitshare allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Profitshare: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30526 | WordPress Typekit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30526</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in lucksy Typekit plugin for WordPress allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Typekit plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30527 | WordPress My Bootstrap Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30527</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in codetoolbox My Bootstrap Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects My Bootstrap Menu: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30528 | WordPress Awesome Logos plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 -  CSRF to SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30528</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpshopee Awesome Logos allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Awesome Logos: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30529 | WordPress Auto Load Next Post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.14 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30529</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sébastien Dumont Auto Load Next Post allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Auto Load Next Post: from n/a through 1.5.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30530 | WordPress AI Preloader plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30530</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Atikul AI Preloader allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AI Preloader: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30531 | WordPress WP Ride Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30531</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in GBS Developer WP Ride Booking allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Ride Booking: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30532 | WordPress Weather Layer plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30532</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MorganF Weather Layer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Weather Layer: from n/a through 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30533 | WordPress Message ticker plugin &amp;lt;= 9.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30533</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gopiplus Message ticker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Message ticker: from n/a through 9.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30534 | WordPress Image Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30534</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in captcha.soft Image Captcha allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Image Captcha: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30535 | WordPress External image replace plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30535</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in muro External image replace allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects External image replace: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30536 | WordPress Beautiful Link Preview plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zeitwesentech Beautiful Link Preview allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Beautiful Link Preview: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30537 | WordPress Upload Quota per User - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.3 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30537</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cristian Sarov Upload Quota per User allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Upload Quota per User: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30538 | WordPress Simple Optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7  - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30538</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ChrisHurst Simple Optimizer allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple Optimizer: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30539 | WordPress BMo Expo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Benedikt Mo BMo Expo allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BMo Expo: from n/a through 1.0.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30540 | WordPress AvaiBook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30540</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in avaibook AvaiBook allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AvaiBook: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30541 | WordPress Info Boxes Shortcode And Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30541</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OTWthemes Info Boxes Shortcode and Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Info Boxes Shortcode and Widget: from n/a through 1.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30542 | WordPress WP SoundCloud Ultimate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30542</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpsolutions SoundCloud Ultimate allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects SoundCloud Ultimate: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30543 | WordPress Menu Duplicator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30543</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in swayam.tejwani Menu Duplicator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Menu Duplicator: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30545 | WordPress issuuPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30545</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pixeline issuuPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects issuuPress: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30546 | WordPress Cackle plugin &amp;lt;= 4.33 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30546</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in boroV Cackle allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Cackle: from n/a through 4.33.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30549 | WordPress Yummly Rich Recipes plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30549</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yummly Yummly Rich Recipes allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Yummly Rich Recipes: from n/a through 4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30550 | WordPress CallPhone&amp;#x27;r plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30550</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPShop.ru CallPhone'r allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CallPhone'r: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30551 | WordPress Pretty file links plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in smartredfox Pretty file links allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Pretty file links: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30552 | WordPress WordPress Admin Bar Improved plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30552</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Donald Gilbert WordPress Admin Bar Improved allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WordPress Admin Bar Improved: from n/a through 3.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30553 | WordPress GMO Font Agent plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Z.com byGMO GMO Font Agent allows Stored XSS. This issue affects GMO Font Agent: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30555 | WordPress WordPres 同步微博 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30555</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in iiiryan WordPres 同步微博 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WordPres 同步微博: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30556 | WordPress  Fix Rss Feeds plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30556</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flyaga Fix Rss Feeds allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Fix Rss Feeds: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30557 | WordPress Easy 301 Redirects plugin &amp;lt;= 1.33 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30557</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in odihost Easy 301 Redirects allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Easy 301 Redirects: from n/a through 1.33.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30558 | WordPress ANAC XML Render plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30558</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in EnzoCostantini55 ANAC XML Render allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ANAC XML Render: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30560 | WordPress jQuery Dropdown Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30560</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sana Ullah jQuery Dropdown Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects jQuery Dropdown Menu: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30561 | WordPress CAS Maestro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30561</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Henrique Mouta CAS Maestro allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CAS Maestro: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30564 | WordPress Custom Script Integration - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 2.1 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30564</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpwox Custom Script Integration allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Script Integration: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30565 | WordPress banner-manager plugin &amp;lt;= 16.04.19 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30565</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in karrikas banner-manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects banner-manager: from n/a through 16.04.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30566 | WordPress Clink - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aryan Themes Clink allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Clink: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30568 | WordPress Super Static Cache - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30568</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in hitoy Super Static Cache allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Super Static Cache: from n/a through 3.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30569 | WordPress WP Featured Entries - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.0 SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30569</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Jahertor WP Featured Entries allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Featured Entries: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30570 | WordPress دکمه، شبکه اجتماعی خرید - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AliRezaMohammadi دکمه، شبکه اجتماعی خرید allows SQL Injection. This issue affects دکمه، شبکه اجتماعی خرید: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30571 | WordPress STEdb Forms - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in STEdb Corp. STEdb Forms allows SQL Injection. This issue affects STEdb Forms: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30572 | WordPress Simple Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30572</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Igor Yavych Simple Rating allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Rating: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30573 | WordPress My Default Post Content - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 0.7.3 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mrdenny My Default Post Content allows Stored XSS. This issue affects My Default Post Content: from n/a through 0.7.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30574 | WordPress Mobile Navigation - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.5 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jenst Mobile Navigation allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Mobile Navigation: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30575 | WordPress Login Redirect - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Arefly Login Redirect allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Login Redirect: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30576 | WordPress Hacklog Remote Image Autosave - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30576</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in HuangYe WuDeng Hacklog Remote Image Autosave allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Hacklog Remote Image Autosave: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30577 | WordPress Browser Address Bar Color plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30577</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mendibass Browser Address Bar Color allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Browser Address Bar Color: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30578 | WordPress AdSense Privacy Policy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30578</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in hotvanrod AdSense Privacy Policy allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AdSense Privacy Policy: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30581 | WordPress Top Bar - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;=3.3 Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30581</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PluginOps Top Bar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Top Bar: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30583 | WordPress Pro Rank Tracker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30583</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ProRankTracker Pro Rank Tracker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Pro Rank Tracker: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30584 | WordPress AlphaOmega Captcha &amp;amp; Anti-Spam Filter plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30584</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in alphaomegaplugins AlphaOmega Captcha &amp;amp; Anti-Spam Filter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AlphaOmega Captcha &amp;amp; Anti-Spam Filter: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30585 | WordPress Generate Post Thumbnails - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 0.8 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30585</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in marynixie Generate Post Thumbnails allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Generate Post Thumbnails: from n/a through 0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30586 | WordPress cTabs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30586</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in bbodine1 cTabs allows Stored XSS. This issue affects cTabs: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30587 | WordPress LH OGP Meta plugin &amp;lt;= 1.73 - CSRF to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30587</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shawfactor LH OGP Meta allows Stored XSS. This issue affects LH OGP Meta: from n/a through 1.73.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30588 | WordPress Map Contact plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30588</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ryan_xantoo Map Contact allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Map Contact: from n/a through 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30590 | WordPress Flickr set slideshows - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 0.9 SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Dourou Flickr set slideshows allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Flickr set slideshows: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30591 | WordPress Music Press Pro - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30591</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tuyennv Music Press Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Music Press Pro: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30592 | WordPress Advanced Dewplayer - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.6 Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30592</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in westerndeal Advanced Dewplayer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Advanced Dewplayer: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30593 | WordPress Include URL - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 0.3.5 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in samsk Include URL allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Include URL: from n/a through 0.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30595 | WordPress include-file - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30595</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tstafford include-file allows Stored XSS. This issue affects include-file: from n/a through 1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30597 | WordPress IG Shortcodes - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 3.1 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30597</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in iografica IG Shortcodes allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects IG Shortcodes: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30598 | WordPress OSS Upload - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 4.8.9 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30598</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Link OSS Upload allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects OSS Upload: from n/a through 4.8.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30599 | WordPress WP Parallax Content Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wp-maverick WP Parallax Content Slider allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Parallax Content Slider: from n/a through 0.9.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30600 | WordPress WP Hotjar plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30600</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in thiagogsrwp WP Hotjar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Hotjar: from n/a through 0.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30601 | WordPress Flipdish Ordering System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.16 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30601</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flipdish Flipdish Ordering System allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Flipdish Ordering System: from n/a through 1.4.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30602 | WordPress Related Posts via Categories plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30602</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in alphasis Related Posts via Categories allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Related Posts via Categories: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30603 | WordPress CopyLink plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30603</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DEJAN CopyLink allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CopyLink: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30604 | WordPress JiangQie Official Website Mini Program plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30604</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in jiangqie JiangQie Official Website Mini Program allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects JiangQie Official Website Mini Program: from n/a through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30605 | WordPress sourceplay-navermap plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30605</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ldwin79 sourceplay-navermap allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects sourceplay-navermap: from n/a through 0.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30606 | WordPress Easy Page Transition plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30606</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Logan Carlile Easy Page Transition allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy Page Transition: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30608 | WordPress WordPress SQL Backup - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30608</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Anthony WordPress SQL Backup allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WordPress SQL Backup: from n/a through 3.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30609 | WordPress AppExperts – WordPress to Mobile App – WooCommerce to iOs and Android Apps - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30609</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in AppExperts AppExperts – WordPress to Mobile App – WooCommerce to iOs and Android Apps allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects AppExperts – WordPress to Mobile App – WooCommerce to iOs and Android Apps: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30610 | WordPress WP Social Widget - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30610</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in catchsquare WP Social Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Social Widget: from n/a through 2.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30612 | WordPress Replace Default Words plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30612</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mandegarweb Replace Default Words allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Replace Default Words: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30615 | WordPress WP e-Commerce Style Email plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.2 - CSRF to Remote Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30615</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jacob Schwartz WP e-Commerce Style Email allows Code Injection. This issue affects WP e-Commerce Style Email: from n/a through 0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30617 | WordPress Rewrite - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30617</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in takien Rewrite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Rewrite: from n/a through 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30619 | WordPress SpeakPipe - &amp;lt;= &amp;lt;= 0.2 Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30619</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SpeakPipe SpeakPipe allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects SpeakPipe: from n/a through 0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30620 | WordPress WP Odoo Form Integrator plugin &amp;lt;=1.1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30620</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in coderscom WP Odoo Form Integrator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Odoo Form Integrator: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30621 | WordPress Translator plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30621</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kornelly Translator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Translator: from n/a through 0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30623 | WordPress wA11y – The Web Accessibility Toolbox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30623</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rachel Cherry wA11y – The Web Accessibility Toolbox allows Stored XSS. This issue affects wA11y – The Web Accessibility Toolbox: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8773 | Protocol Downgrade in SIMPLE.ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8773</link><description>SIMPLE.ERP client is vulnerable to MS SQL protocol downgrade request from a server side, what could lead to an unencrypted communication vulnerable to data interception and modification.

This issue affect SIMPLE.ERP from 6.20 to 6.30. Only the 6.30 version received a patch 6.30@a03.9, which make it possible for an administrator to enforce encrypted communication. Versions 6.20 and 6.25 remain unpatched.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8774 | Privilege Escalation in SIMPLE.ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8774</link><description>The SIMPLE.ERP client stores superuser password in a recoverable format, allowing any authenticated SIMPLE.ERP user to escalate privileges to a database administrator.

This issue affect SIMPLE.ERP from 6.20 through 6.30. Only the 6.30 version received a patch 6.30@a03.9, which removed the vulnerability. Versions 6.20 and 6.25 remain unpatched.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0835 | GPU DDK - _WrapExtMemReleasePages called twice if _FlushUMVirtualRange fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0835</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to corrupt kernel heap memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0478 | GPU DDK - PMMETA_PROTECT PMR can be exported as dma-buf file / GEM object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0478</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to issue reads and writes to arbitrary physical memory pages.

Under certain circumstances this exploit could be used to corrupt data pages not allocated by the GPU driver but memory pages in use by the kernel and drivers running on the platform, altering their behaviour.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 11:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2702 | Softwin WMX3 ImageAdd.ashx ImageAdd unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2702</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Softwin WMX3 3.1. This issue affects the function ImageAdd of the file /ImageAdd.ashx. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2701 | AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System port_setup.php popen os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2701</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function popen of the file /manager/network/port_setup.php. The manipulation of the argument SwitchVersion/SwitchWrite/SwitchIP/SwitchIndex/SwitchState leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 09:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2700 | michelson Dante Editor Insert Link cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2700</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in michelson Dante Editor up to 0.4.4. This affects an unknown part of the component Insert Link Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 08:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2699 | GetmeUK ContentTools Image cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2699</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GetmeUK ContentTools up to 1.6.16. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument onload leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 08:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2690 | yiisoft Yii2 MockClass.php generate deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2690</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in yiisoft Yii2 up to 2.0.39. This affects the function Generate of the file phpunit\src\Framework\MockObject\MockClass.php. The manipulation leads to deserialization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2689 | yiisoft Yii2 SortableIterator.php getIterator deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2689</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in yiisoft Yii2 up to 2.0.45. Affected by this issue is the function getIterator of the file symfony\finder\Iterator\SortableIterator.php. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 07:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2688 | TOTOLINK A3000RU Syslog Configuration File ExportSyslog.sh access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2688</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in TOTOLINK A3000RU up to 5.9c.5185. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSyslog.sh of the component Syslog Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10558 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.30 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10558</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.30 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13124 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.8.33 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13124</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.33 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1062 | Slider, Gallery, Carousel by MetaSlider &amp;lt; 3.95.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1062</link><description>The Slider, Gallery, and Carousel by MetaSlider  WordPress plugin before 3.95.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1203 | Slider, Gallery, Carousel by MetaSlider &amp;lt; 3.95.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1203</link><description>The Slider, Gallery, and Carousel by MetaSlider  WordPress plugin before 3.95.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2687 | PHPGurukul eLearning System Image index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2687</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul eLearning System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/index.php of the component Image Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2686 | mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 Backend admin doFilter access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2686</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 up to d4836f6b49cd0ac79a4021b15ce99ff7229d4694 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function doFilter of the file /admin/ of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument Request leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 05:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2684 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System search-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2684</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 05:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2683 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2683</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 04:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2682 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2682</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit-subadmin.php?said=3. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 04:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2681 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System edit-locker.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2681</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit-locker.php?ltid=6. The manipulation of the argument lockersize leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2680 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System edit-assign-locker.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2680</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit-assign-locker.php?ltid=1. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2679 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2679</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2678 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System changeimage1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /changeimage1.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 02:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2677 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System changeidproof.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2677</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /changeidproof.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 02:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2676 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System add-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2676</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument sadminusername leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2675 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System add-lockertype.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2675</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /add-lockertype.php. The manipulation of the argument lockerprice leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2674 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2674</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>