<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 20:15:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-12919 | EverShop Order Order.resolvers.js resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12919</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in EverShop up to 2.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/modules/oms/graphql/types/Order/Order.resolvers.js of the component Order Handler. The manipulation of the argument uuid results in improper control of resource identifiers. The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12918 | yungifez Skuul School Management System View Fee Invoice fee-invoices resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12918</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yungifez Skuul School Management System up to 2.6.5. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/fees/fee-invoices/ of the component View Fee Invoice. Performing manipulation of the argument invoice_id results in improper control of resource identifiers. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12917 | TOZED ZLT T10 Reboot proc_post denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12917</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in TOZED ZLT T10 T10PLUS_3.04.15. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /reqproc/proc_post of the component Reboot Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 07:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40108 | serial: qcom-geni: Fix blocked task</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40108</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

serial: qcom-geni: Fix blocked task

Revert commit 1afa70632c39 ("serial: qcom-geni: Enable PM runtime for
serial driver") and its dependent commit 86fa39dd6fb7 ("serial:
qcom-geni: Enable Serial on SA8255p Qualcomm platforms") because the
first one causes regression - hang task on Qualcomm RB1 board (QRB2210)
and unable to use serial at all during normal boot:

  INFO: task kworker/u16:0:12 blocked for more than 42 seconds.
        Not tainted 6.17.0-rc1-00004-g53e760d89498 #9
  "echo 0 &gt; /proc/sys/kernel/hung_task_timeout_secs" disables this message.
  task:kworker/u16:0   state:D stack:0     pid:12    tgid:12    ppid:2      task_flags:0x4208060 flags:0x00000010
  Workqueue: async async_run_entry_fn
  Call trace:
   __switch_to+0xe8/0x1a0 (T)
   __schedule+0x290/0x7c0
   schedule+0x34/0x118
   rpm_resume+0x14c/0x66c
   rpm_resume+0x2a4/0x66c
   rpm_resume+0x2a4/0x66c
   rpm_resume+0x2a4/0x66c
   __pm_runtime_resume+0x50/0x9c
   __driver_probe_device+0x58/0x120
   driver_probe_device+0x3c/0x154
   __driver_attach_async_helper+0x4c/0xc0
   async_run_entry_fn+0x34/0xe0
   process_one_work+0x148/0x290
   worker_thread+0x2c4/0x3e0
   kthread+0x118/0x1c0
   ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20

The issue was reported on 12th of August and was ignored by author of
commits introducing issue for two weeks.  Only after complaining author
produced a fix which did not work, so if original commits cannot be
reliably fixed for 5 weeks, they obviously are buggy and need to be
dropped.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40109 | crypto: rng - Ensure set_ent is always present</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40109</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: rng - Ensure set_ent is always present

Ensure that set_ent is always set since only drbg provides it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12916 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System Frontend portal_login command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12916</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System 3.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /fort/portal_login of the component Frontend. This manipulation of the argument loginUrl causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Upgrading to version 3.0.11 and 3.0.12 is recommended to address this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12915 | 70mai X200 Init Script file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12915</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 70mai X200 up to 20251019. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Init Script Handler. The manipulation results in file inclusion. The attack requires a local approach. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12914 | aaPanel BaoTa Backend database sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12914</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in aaPanel BaoTa up to 11.1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /database?action=GetDatabaseAccess of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 21:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12913 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site roomdel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12913</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/roomdel.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 20:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11448 | Gallery Plugin for WordPress – Envira Photo Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.11.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Gallery Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11448</link><description>The Gallery Plugin for WordPress – Envira Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the '/envira-convert/v1/bulk-convert' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to convert galleries to Envira galleries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11967 | Mail Mint &amp;lt;= 1.18.10 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11967</link><description>The Mail Mint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the process_contact_attribute_import function in all versions up to, and including, 1.18.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11980 | Quick Featured Images &amp;lt;= 13.7.3 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection via delete_orphaned</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11980</link><description>The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'delete_orphaned' function in all versions up to, and including, 13.7.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database, granted they can convince an author-level user or higher to add a malicious custom field value.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12092 | CYAN Backup &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12092</link><description>The CYAN Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'delete' functionality in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12399 | Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12399</link><description>The Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the /wp-json/srr/v1/app/upload/file REST endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12643 | Saphali LiqPay for donate &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12643</link><description>The Saphali LiqPay for donate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'saphali_liqpay' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12837 | aThemes Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Call To Action Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12837</link><description>The aThemes Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Call To Action widget in versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12098 | Academy LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;enqueue_social_login_script&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12098</link><description>The Academy LMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for Complete eLearning Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.8 via the 'enqueue_social_login_script' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including the Facebook App Secret if Facebook Social Login is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 08:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12099 | Academy LMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for Complete eLearning Solution &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection via &amp;#x27;import_all_courses&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12099</link><description>The Academy LMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for Complete eLearning Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.8 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'import_all_courses' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 08:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12621 | Flexible Refund and Return Order for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.42 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Refund Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12621</link><description>The Flexible Refund and Return Order for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'create_refund' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.42. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update the status of refund requests, including approving and refusing refunds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12498 | EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Booking Note Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12498</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized booking note creation due to a missing capability check on the 'booking_add_notes' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add a note to the backend view of any booking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9334 | Better Find and Replace &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9334</link><description>The Better Find and Replace – AI-Powered Suggestions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Limited Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.7. This is due to insufficient input validation and restriction on the 'rtafar_ajax' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to call arbitrary plugin functions and execute code within those functions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11748 | Groups &amp;lt;= 6.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Group Join</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11748</link><description>The Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.0 via the 'group_id' parameter of the group_join function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to register for groups other than ones set in the shortcode.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11972 | Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI &amp;lt;= 3.40.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11972</link><description>The Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post_types' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.40.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12000 | WPFunnels &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12000</link><description>The WPFunnels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the wpfnl_delete_log() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12042 | Course Booking System &amp;lt;= 6.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Booking Data Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12042</link><description>The Course Booking System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check in the csv-export.php file in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to directly access the file and obtain an export of all booking data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12064 | WP2Social Auto Publish &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12064</link><description>The WP2Social Auto Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12112 | Insert Headers and Footers Code – HT Script &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12112</link><description>The Insert Headers and Footers Code – HT Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via adding scripts in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 due to insufficient capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12125 | HTML Forms &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12125</link><description>The HTML Forms – Simple WordPress Forms Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12161 | Smart Auto Upload Images &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12161</link><description>The Smart Auto Upload Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the auto-image creation functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12167 | Contact Form 7 AWeber Extension &amp;lt;= 0.1.42 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12167</link><description>The Contact Form 7 AWeber Extension plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_aweber_logreset' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.42. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the AWeber logs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12177 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.30 - Unauthenticated Cron Trigger due to Hardcoded Cron Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12177</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a hardcoded Cron key used in the deleteExpired() and clearTempDataCPCron() functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.30. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger these cron jobs leading to deletion of expired posts and clearing cache.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12193 | Mang Board WP &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12193</link><description>The Mang Board WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mp' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12353 | WPFunnels &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Unauthorized User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12353</link><description>The WPFunnels – The Easiest Funnel Builder For WordPress And WooCommerce To Collect Leads And Increase Sales plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user registration in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2. This is due to the plugin relying on a user controlled value 'optin_allow_registration' to determine if user registration is allowed, instead of the site-specific setting. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register new user accounts, even when user registration is disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7663 | Ovatheme Events Manager &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7663</link><description>The Ovatheme Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several functions in the /class-ovaem-ajax.php file in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete ticket files, download tickets, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11452 | Asgaros Forum &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11452</link><description>The Asgaros Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the '$_COOKIE['asgarosforum_unread_exclude']' cookie in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12583 | Simple Downloads List &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12583</link><description>The Simple Downloads List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_neofix_sdl_edit' AJAX endpoint along with many others in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to alter many of the plugin's settings/downloads and inject malicious web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64492 | SuiteCRM is Vulnerable to Authenticated Time Based Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64492</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 8.9.0 and below contain a time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to infer data from the database by measuring response times, potentially leading to the extraction of sensitive information. It is possible for an attacker to enumerate database, table, and column names, extract sensitive data, or escalate privileges. This is fixed in version 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64493 | SuiteCRM is Vulnerable to Authenticated Blind SQL Injection via GraphQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64493</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions 8.6.0 through 8.9.0, there is an authenticated, blind (time-based) SQL-injection inside the appMetadata-operation of the GraphQL-API. This allows extraction of arbitrary data from the database, and does not require administrative access. This issue is fixed in version 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64494 | Soft Serve does not sanitize ANSI escape sequences in user input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64494</link><description>Soft Serve is a self-hostable Git server for the command line. In versions prior to 0.10.0, there are several places where the user can insert data (e.g. names) and ANSI escape sequences are not being removed, which can then be used, for example, to show fake alerts. In the same token, git messages, when printed, are also not being sanitized. This issue is fixed in version 0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64495 | Open WebUI vulnerable to Stored DOM XSS via prompts when &amp;#x27;Insert Prompt as Rich Text&amp;#x27; is enabled resulting in ATO/RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64495</link><description>Open WebUI is a self-hosted artificial intelligence platform designed to operate entirely offline. In versions 0.6.34 and below, the functionality that inserts custom prompts into the chat window is vulnerable to DOM XSS when 'Insert Prompt as Rich Text' is enabled, since the prompt body is assigned to the DOM sink .innerHtml without sanitisation. Any user with permissions to create prompts can abuse this to plant a payload that could be triggered by other users if they run the corresponding / command to insert the prompt. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.35.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64496 | Open WebUI Affected by an External Model Server (Direct Connections) Code Injection via SSE Events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64496</link><description>Open WebUI is a self-hosted artificial intelligence platform designed to operate entirely offline. Versions 0.6.224 and prior contain a code injection vulnerability in the Direct Connections feature that allows malicious external model servers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers via Server-Sent Event (SSE) execute events. This leads to authentication token theft, complete account takeover, and when chained with the Functions API, enables remote code execution on the backend server. The attack requires the victim to enable Direct Connections (disabled by default) and add the attacker's malicious model URL, achievable through social engineering of the admin and subsequent users. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.35.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64491 | SuiteCRM is vulnerable to unauthenticated reflected XSS through its Login page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64491</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.7 and below allow unauthenticated reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). Successful exploitation could lead to full account takeover, for example by altering the login form to send credentials to an attacker-controlled server. As a reflected XSS issue, exploitation requires the victim to open a crafted malicious link, which can be delivered via phishing, social media, or other communication channels. This issue is fixed in version 7.14.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64489 | SuiteCRM: Privilege Escalation via Improper Session Invalidation and Inactive User Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64489</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.7 and prior, 8.0.0-beta.1 through 8.9.0 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability where user sessions are not invalidated upon account deactivation. An inactive user with an active session can continue to access the application and, critically, can self-reactivate their account. This undermines administrative controls and allows unauthorized persistence. This issue is fixed in versions 7.14.8 and 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64490 | SuiteCRM&amp;#x27;s Inconsistent RBAC Enforcement Enables Access Control Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64490</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.7 and prior, 8.0.0-beta.1 through 8.9.0 allow a low-privileged user with a restrictive role to view and create work items through the Resource Calendar and project screens, even when the related modules (Projects, Project Tasks, Tasks, Leads, Accounts, Meetings, Calls) are explicitly set to Disabled/None in Role Management. This indicates inconsistent ACL/RBAC enforcement across modules and views, resulting in unauthorized data exposure and modification. This issue is fixed in versions 7.14.8 and 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64488 | SuiteCRM: Authenticated SQL Injection Possible in Reschedule Call Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64488</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions 7.14.7 and below and 8.0.0-beta.1 through 8.9.0 8.0.0-beta.1, an attacker can craft a malicious call_id that alters the logic of the SQL query or injects arbitrary SQL. An attack can lead to unauthorized data access and data ex-filtration, complete database compromise, and other various issues. This issue is fixed in versions 7.14.8 and 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12905 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Mark of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12905</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Mark of the Web via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12906 | Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12906</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12907 | Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Devtools in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12907</link><description>Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Devtools in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via user action in Devtools. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12908 | Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Downloads in Google Chrome on Android prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12908</link><description>Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Downloads in Google Chrome on Android prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12909 | Insufficient policy enforcement in Devtools in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12909</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in Devtools in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via Devtools. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12910 | Inappropriate implementation in Passkeys in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a local attacker to obtain potentially sensitive in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12910</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Passkeys in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a local attacker to obtain potentially sensitive information via debug logs. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12911 | Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12911</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Permissions in Google Chrome prior to 140.0.7339.80 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64485 | CVAT: Mounted share file overwrite via crafted request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64485</link><description>CVAT is an open source interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. In versions 2.4.0 through 2.48.1, a malicious CVAT user with at least the User global role may create files in the root of the mounted file share, or overwrite existing files. If no file share is mounted, the user will be able to create files in the share directory of the import worker container, potentially filling up disk space. This issue is fixed in version 2.49.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64486 | calibre is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution when opening FB2 files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64486</link><description>calibre is an e-book manager. In versions 8.13.0 and prior, calibre does not validate filenames when handling binary assets in FB2 files, allowing an attacker to write arbitrary files on the filesystem when viewing or converting a malicious FictionBook file. This can be leveraged to achieve arbitrary code execution. This issue is fixed in version 8.14.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64433 | KubeVirt Arbitrary Container File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64433</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Prior to 1.5.3 and 1.6.1, a vulnerability was discovered that allows a VM to read arbitrary files from the virt-launcher pod's file system. This issue stems from improper symlink handling when mounting PVC disks into a VM. Specifically, if a malicious user has full or partial control over the contents of a PVC, they can create a symbolic link that points to a file within the virt-launcher pod's file system. Since libvirt can treat regular files as block devices, any file on the pod's file system that is symlinked in this way can be mounted into the VM and subsequently read. Although a security mechanism exists where VMs are executed as an unprivileged user with UID 107 inside the virt-launcher container, limiting the scope of accessible resources, this restriction is bypassed due to a second vulnerability. The latter causes the ownership of any file intended for mounting to be changed to the unprivileged user with UID 107 prior to mounting. As a result, an attacker can gain access to and read arbitrary files located within the virt-launcher pod's file system or on a mounted PVC from within the guest VM. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.3 and 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64437 | KubeVirt Isolation Detection Flaw Allows Arbitrary File Permission Changes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64437</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. In versions before 1.5.3 and 1.6.1, the virt-handler does not verify whether the launcher-sock is a symlink or a regular file. This oversight can be exploited, for example, to change the ownership of arbitrary files on the host node to the unprivileged user with UID 107 (the same user used by virt-launcher) thus, compromising the CIA (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability) of data on the host. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker should be in control of the file system of the virt-launcher pod. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.3 and 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64435 | KubeVirt VMI Denial-of-Service (DoS) Using Pod Impersonation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64435</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Prior to 1.7.0-beta.0, a logic flaw in the virt-controller allows an attacker to disrupt the control over a running VMI by creating a pod with the same labels as the legitimate virt-launcher pod associated with the VMI. This can mislead the virt-controller into associating the fake pod with the VMI, resulting in incorrect status updates and potentially causing a DoS (Denial-of-Service). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.7.0-beta.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64436 | KubeVirt Excessive Role Permissions Could Enable Unauthorized VMI Migrations Between Nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64436</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. In 1.5.0 and earlier, the permissions granted to the virt-handler service account, such as the ability to update VMI and patch nodes, could be abused to force a VMI migration to an attacker-controlled node. This vulnerability could otherwise allow an attacker to mark all nodes as unschedulable, potentially forcing the migration or creation of privileged pods onto a compromised node.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64434 | KubeVirt Improper TLS Certificate Management Handling Allows API Identity Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64434</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Prior to 1.5.3 and 1.6.1, due to the peer verification logic in virt-handler (via verifyPeerCert), an attacker who compromises a virt-handler instance, could exploit these shared credentials to impersonate virt-api and execute privileged operations against other virt-handler instances potentially compromising the integrity and availability of the VM managed by it. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.3 and 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 23:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37736 | Elastic Cloud Enterprise Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37736</link><description>Improper Authorization in Elastic Cloud Enterprise can lead to Privilege Escalation where the built-in readonly user can call APIs that should not be allowed. The list of APIs that are affected by this issue is:





post:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts
delete:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}
patch:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}
post:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}/keys
delete:/platform/configuration/security/service-accounts/{user_id}/keys/{api_key_id}
patch:/user
post:/users
post:/users/auth/keys
delete:/users/auth/keys
delete:/users/auth/keys/_all
delete:/users/auth/keys/{api_key_id}
delete:/users/{user_id}/auth/keys
delete:/users/{user_id}/auth/keys/{api_key_id}
delete:/users/{user_name}
patch:/users/{user_name}</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36870 | Ruijie Gateway EG &amp;amp; NBR Models v11.1(6)B9P1 - 11.9(4)B12P1 RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36870</link><description>Various Ruijie Gateway EG and NBR models firmware versions 11.1(6)B9P1 &lt; 11.9(4)B12P1 contain a code execution vulnerability in the EWEB management system that can be abused via front-end functionality. Attackers can exploit front-end code when features such as guest authentication, local server authentication, or screen mirroring are enabled to gain access or execute commands on affected devices. Exploitation evidence was first observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-06-07 UTC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12418 | Potential Denial of Service in Supported Versions of Revenera InstallShield</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12418</link><description>Potential Denial of Service issue in all supported versions of Revenera InstallShield version 2025 R1, 2024 R2, 2023 R2, and prior. When e.g., a local administrator performs an uninstall, a symlink may get followed on removal of a user writeable configuration directory and induce a Denial of Service as a result. The issue is resolved through the hotfixes InstallShield2025R1-CVE-2025-12418-SecurityPatch, InstallShield2024R2-CVE-2025-12418-SecurityPatch, and InstallShield2023R2-CVE-2025-12418-SecurityPatch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60574 | A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been identified in tQuadra CMS 4.2.1117. The issue exists in the "/styles/" path, which fails...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60574</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been identified in tQuadra CMS 4.2.1117. The issue exists in the "/styles/" path, which fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input. An attacker can exploit this by sending a crafted GET request to retrieve arbitrary files from the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63420 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CrushFTP 11.3.7_50 Admin Panel (Reports / 'Who Created Folder') allows authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63420</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CrushFTP 11.3.7_50 Admin Panel (Reports / 'Who Created Folder') allows authenticated attackers with permissions to create folders to inject malicious HTML/JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12863 | Libxml2: namespace use-after-free in xmlsettreedoc() function of libxml2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12863</link><description>A flaw was found in the xmlSetTreeDoc() function of the libxml2 XML parsing library. This function is responsible for updating document pointers when XML nodes are moved between documents. Due to improper handling of namespace references, a namespace pointer may remain linked to a freed memory region when the original document is destroyed. As a result, subsequent operations that access the namespace can lead to a use-after-free condition, causing an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12875 | mruby array.c ary_fill_exec out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12875</link><description>A weakness has been identified in mruby 3.4.0. This vulnerability affects the function ary_fill_exec of the file mrbgems/mruby-array-ext/src/array.c. Executing manipulation of the argument start/length can lead to out-of-bounds write. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This patch is called 93619f06dd378db6766666b30c08978311c7ec94. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63544 | TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /order_notes via the id parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63544</link><description>TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /order_notes via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64442 | HumHub is vulnerable to XSS through its Meta Search component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64442</link><description>HumHub is an Open Source Enterprise Social Network. Versions below 1.17.4 have a XSS vulnerability in the Meta-Search feature which allows malicious input to be executed in search previews. This issue is fixed in version 1.17.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64481 | Open redirect endpoint in Datasette</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64481</link><description>Datasette is an open source multi-tool for exploring and publishing data. In versions 0.65.1 and below and 1.0a0 through 1.0a19, deployed instances of Datasette include an open redirect vulnerability. Hits to the path //example.com/foo/bar/ (the trailing slash is required) will redirect the user to https://example.com/foo/bar. This problem has been patched in both Datasette 0.65.2 and 1.0a21. To workaround this issue, if Datasette is running behind a proxy, that proxy could be configured to replace // with / in incoming request URLs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12896 | Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12896</link><description>Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authorized access to a locked storage device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12902 | Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12902</link><description>Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local or physical access to gain un-authorized access to a locked Storage Device or create a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63543 | TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /search_results endpoint via the q parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63543</link><description>TechStore 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /search_results endpoint via the q parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64439 | LangGraph Checkpoint affected by RCE in &amp;quot;json&amp;quot; mode of JsonPlusSerializer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64439</link><description>LangGraph SQLite Checkpoint is an implementation of LangGraph CheckpointSaver that uses SQLite DB (both sync and async, via aiosqlite). In versions 2.1.2 and below, the JsonPlusSerializer (used as the default serialization protocol for all checkpointing) contains a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability when deserializing payloads saved in the "json" serialization mode. By default, the serializer attempts to use "msgpack" for serialization. However, prior to version 3.0 of the checkpointer library, if illegal Unicode surrogate values caused serialization to fail, it would fall back to using the "json" mode. This issue is fixed in version 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63639 | The chat feature in the application Sourcecodester FAQ Bot with AI Assistant v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) due to imprope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63639</link><description>The chat feature in the application Sourcecodester FAQ Bot with AI Assistant v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) due to improper handling of user-supplied input. An attacker can inject malicious HTML or JavaScript into chat messages, which executes in the browser of any user viewing the conversation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63640 | Sourcecodester Medicine Reminder App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Medicine Name" and "Notes (Optional)" fields w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63640</link><description>Sourcecodester Medicine Reminder App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Medicine Name" and "Notes (Optional)" fields when creating an "Upcoming Reminder", allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary potentially malicious HTML/JavaScript code that executes in the victim's browser upon clicking the "Save Reminder" button.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63638 | Sourcecodester AI-Powered To-Do List App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Task Title" and "Description (Optional)" f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63638</link><description>Sourcecodester AI-Powered To-Do List App v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "Task Title" and "Description (Optional)" fields when creating a Task, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary potentially malicious HTML/JavaScript code that executes in the victim's browser upon clicking the "Add Task" button.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10230 | Samba: command injection in wins server hook script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10230</link><description>A flaw was found in Samba, in the front-end WINS hook handling: NetBIOS names from registration packets are passed to a shell without proper validation or escaping. Unsanitized NetBIOS name data from WINS registration packets are inserted into a shell command and executed by the Samba Active Directory Domain Controller’s wins hook, allowing an unauthenticated network attacker to achieve remote command execution as the Samba process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36006 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36006</link><description>IBM Db2 10.5.0 through 10.5.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial due to the improper release of resources after use.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36008 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36008</link><description>IBM Db2 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to improper allocation of resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7700 | Ffmpeg: null pointer dereference in ffmpeg als decoder (libavcodec/alsdec.c)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7700</link><description>A flaw was found in FFmpeg’s ALS audio decoder, where it does not properly check for memory allocation failures. This can cause the application to crash when processing certain malformed audio files. While it does not lead to data theft or system control, it can be used to disrupt services and cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36131 | IBM Db2 information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36131</link><description>IBM Db2 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) clpplus command exposes user credentials to the terminal which could be obtained by a third party with physical access to the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12890 | Bluetooth: peripheral: Invalid handling of malformed connection request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12890</link><description>Improper handling of  malformed Connection Request with the interval set to be 1 (which supposed to be illegal) and the chM 0x7CFFFFFFFF triggers a crash. The peripheral will not be connectable after it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36136 | IBM denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36136</link><description>IBM Db2 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to the database monitor script incorrectly detecting that the instance is still starting under specific conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36185 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36185</link><description>IBM Db2 12.1.0 through 12.1.2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to improper neutralization of special elements in data query logic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2534 | IBM Db2  denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2534</link><description>IBM Db2 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33012 | IBM Db2 improper account lockout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33012</link><description>IBM Db2 10.5.0 through 10.5.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux could allow an authenticated user to regain access after account lockout due to password use after expiration date.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36186 | IBM Db2 privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36186</link><description>IBM Db2 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) under specific configurations could allow a local user to execute malicious code that escalate their privileges to root due to execution of unnecessary privileges operated at a higher than minimum level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64432 | KubeVirt Affected by an Authentication Bypass in Kubernetes Aggregation Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64432</link><description>KubeVirt is a virtual machine management add-on for Kubernetes. Versions 1.5.3 and below, and 1.6.0 contained a flawed implementation of the Kubernetes aggregation layer's authentication flow which could enable bypass of RBAC controls. It was discovered that the virt-api component fails to correctly authenticate the client when receiving API requests over mTLS. In particular, it fails to validate the CN (Common Name) field in the received client TLS certificates against the set of allowed values defined in the extension-apiserver-authentication configmap. Failre to validate certain fields in the client TLS certificate may allow an attacker to bypass existing RBAC controls by directly communicating with the aggregated API server, impersonating the Kubernetes API server and its aggregator component. This issue is fixed in versions 1.5.3 and 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47118 | IBM Db2 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47118</link><description>IBM Db2 10.5.0 through 10.5.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.3 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36135 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway are Vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36135</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_1, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7_1, 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61261 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CKeditor v46.1.0 &amp; Angular v18.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61261</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CKeditor v46.1.0 &amp; Angular v18.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63717 | The change password functionality at /pet_grooming/admin/change_pass.php in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 is vulnerabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63717</link><description>The change password functionality at /pet_grooming/admin/change_pass.php in SourceCodester Pet Grooming Management Software 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks. The application does not implement adequate anti-CSRF tokens or same-site cookie restrictions, allowing attackers to trick authenticated users into unknowingly changing their passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64431 | IDOR Vulnerabilities in ZITADEL&amp;#x27;s Organization API allows Cross-Tenant Data Tempering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64431</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management platform. Versions 4.0.0-rc.1 through 4.6.2 are vulnerable to secure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) attacks through its V2Beta API, allowing authenticated users with specific administrator roles within one organization to access and modify data belonging to other organizations. Note that this vulnerability is limited to organization-level data (name, domains, metadata). No other related data (such as users, projects, applications, etc.) is affected. This issue is fixed in version 4.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12829 | An uninitialized stack read issue exists in Amazon Ion-C versions &lt;v1.1.4 that may allow a threat actor to craft data and serialize it to Io...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12829</link><description>An uninitialized stack read issue exists in Amazon Ion-C versions &lt;v1.1.4 that may allow a threat actor to craft data and serialize it to Ion text in such a way that sensitive data in memory could be exposed through UTF-8 escape sequences. To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version v1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12873 | Campcodes School File Management update_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12873</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes School File Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update_user.php. Performing manipulation of the argument user_id results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63716 | The SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks that allow unauthorized state-changing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63716</link><description>The SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks that allow unauthorized state-changing operations. The application lacks CSRF protection mechanisms such as anti-CSRF tokens or same-origin verification for critical endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9458 | PRT File Parsing Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9458</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63713 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester "MatchMaster" 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63713</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester "MatchMaster" 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via crafted input in the custom test creation feature. The vulnerability exists because the application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in test titles and matching pair items before rendering them in the DOM during test execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63718 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the SourceCodester PQMS (Patient Queue Management System) 1.0 in the api_patient_schedule.php endpoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63718</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the SourceCodester PQMS (Patient Queue Management System) 1.0 in the api_patient_schedule.php endpoint. The appointmentID parameter is not properly sanitized, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64430 | Parse Server Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in File Upload via URI Format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64430</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. In versions 4.2.0 through 7.5.3, and 8.0.0 through 8.3.1-alpha.1, there is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the file upload functionality when trying to upload a Parse.File with uri parameter, allowing execution of an arbitrary URI. The vulnerability stems from a file upload feature in which Parse Server retrieves the file data from a URI that is provided in the request. A request to the provided URI is executed, but the response is not stored in Parse Server's file storage as the server crashes upon receiving the response. This issue is fixed in versions 7.5.4 and 8.4.0-alpha.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57697 | AstrBot Project v3.5.22 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in function _encode_image_bs64. Since the _encode_image_bs64 function defin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57697</link><description>AstrBot Project v3.5.22 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in function _encode_image_bs64. Since the _encode_image_bs64 function defined in entities.py opens the image specified by the user in the request body and returns the image content as a base64-encoded string without checking the legitimacy of the image path, attackers can construct a series of malicious URLs to read any specified file, resulting in sensitive data leakage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63714 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester User Account Generator 1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63714</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SourceCodester User Account Generator 1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the user's browser session via crafted input in the Username Prefix field. The vulnerability exists due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input when rendering generated account data to the DOM, allowing persistent injection of malicious HTML elements that execute when clicked by users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64347 | Apollo Router Improperly Enforces Renamed Access Control Directives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64347</link><description>Apollo Router Core is a configurable Rust graph router written to run a federated supergraph using Apollo Federation 2. Versions 1.61.12-rc.0 and below and 2.8.1-rc.0 allow unauthorized access to protected data through schema elements with access control directives (@authenticated, @requiresScopes, and @policy) that were renamed via @link imports. Router did not enforce renamed access control directives on schema elements (e.g. fields and types), allowing queries to bypass those element-level access controls. This issue is fixed in versions 1.61.12 and 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57698 | AstrBot Project v3.5.22 contains a directory traversal vulnerability. The handler function install_plugin_upload of the interface '/plugin/i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57698</link><description>AstrBot Project v3.5.22 contains a directory traversal vulnerability. The handler function install_plugin_upload of the interface '/plugin/install-upload' parses the filename from the request body provided by the user, and directly uses the filename to assign to file_path without checking the validity of the filename. The variable file_path is then passed as a parameter to the function `file.save`, so that the file in the request body can be saved to any location in the file system through directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12862 | projectworlds Online Notes Sharing Platform userprofile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12862</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in projectworlds Online Notes Sharing Platform 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/userprofile.php. Such manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3222 | Smallworld SWMFS Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3222</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in GE Vernova Smallworld on Windows, Linux allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Smallworld: 5.3.3 and prior versions for Linux, and 5.3.4. and prior versions for Windows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63785 | A DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the text editor feature of the Onlook web application 0.2.32. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63785</link><description>A DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the text editor feature of the Onlook web application 0.2.32. This vulnerability occurs because user-supplied input is not properly sanitized before being directly injected into the DOM via innerHTML when editing a text element. An attacker can exploit this to inject malicious HTML and script code, which is then executed within the context of the preview iframe, allowing for the execution of arbitrary scripts in the user's session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7719 | Smallworld SWMFS Arbitrary File Ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7719</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in GE Vernova Smallworld on Windows, Linux allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Smallworld: 5.3.5. and previous versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63784 | An Open Redirect vulnerability exists in the OAuth callback handler in file onlook/apps/web/client/src/app/auth/callback/route.ts in Onlook ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63784</link><description>An Open Redirect vulnerability exists in the OAuth callback handler in file onlook/apps/web/client/src/app/auth/callback/route.ts in Onlook web application 0.2.32. The vulnerability occurs because the application trusts the X-Forwarded-Host header value without proper validation when constructing a redirect URL. A remote attacker can send a manipulated X-Forwarded-Host header to redirect an authenticated user to an arbitrary external website under their control, which can be exploited for phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12861 | DedeBIZ spec_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12861</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/spec_add.php. This manipulation of the argument flags[] causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63783 | A Broken Object Level Authorization (BOLA) vulnerability was discovered in the tRPC project mutation APIs (update, delete, add/remove tag) o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63783</link><description>A Broken Object Level Authorization (BOLA) vulnerability was discovered in the tRPC project mutation APIs (update, delete, add/remove tag) of the Onlook web application 0.2.32. The vulnerability exists because the API fails to verify the ownership or membership of the currently authenticated user for the requested project ID. An authenticated attacker can send a malicious request containing another user's project ID to unlawfully modify, delete, or manipulate tags on that project, which can severely compromise data integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63686 | There is an arbitrary file download vulnerability in GuoMinJim PersonManage thru commit 5a02b1ab208feacf3a34fc123c9381162afbaa95 (2020-11-23...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63686</link><description>There is an arbitrary file download vulnerability in GuoMinJim PersonManage thru commit 5a02b1ab208feacf3a34fc123c9381162afbaa95 (2020-11-23) in the document query function under the Download Center menu in the PersonManage system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63687 | An issue was discovered in rymcu forest thru commit f782e85 (2025-09-04) in function doBefore in file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/core/se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63687</link><description>An issue was discovered in rymcu forest thru commit f782e85 (2025-09-04) in function doBefore in file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/core/service/security/AuthorshipAspect.java, allowing authorized attackers to delete arbitrary users posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63689 | Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilitites in ycf1998 money-pos system before commit 11f276bd20a41f089298d804e43cb1c39d041e59 (2025-09-14) allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63689</link><description>Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilitites in ycf1998 money-pos system before commit 11f276bd20a41f089298d804e43cb1c39d041e59 (2025-09-14) allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the orderby parameter</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47207 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47207</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several product versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52425 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52425</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. A remote attacker can exploit the vulnerability to execute unauthorized code or commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuMagie 2.7.0 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52865 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52865</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53408 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53408</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63690 | In pig-mesh Pig versions 3.8.2 and below, when setting up scheduled tasks in the Quartz management function under the system management modu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63690</link><description>In pig-mesh Pig versions 3.8.2 and below, when setting up scheduled tasks in the Quartz management function under the system management module, it is possible to execute any Java class with a parameterless constructor and its methods with parameter type String through reflection. At this time, the eval method in Tomcat's built-in class jakarta.el.ELProcessor can be used to execute commands, leading to a remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63691 | In pig-mesh In Pig version 3.8.2 and below, within the Token Management function under the System Management module, the token query interfa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63691</link><description>In pig-mesh In Pig version 3.8.2 and below, within the Token Management function under the System Management module, the token query interface (/api/admin/sys-token/page) has an improper permission verification issue, which leads to information leakage. This interface can be called by any user who has completed login authentication, and it returns the plaintext authentication Tokens of all users currently logged in to the system. As a result, ordinary users can obtain the administrator's authentication Token through this interface, thereby forging an administrator account, gaining the system's management permissions, and taking over the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53409 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53409</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53410 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53410</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53411 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53411</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53412 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53412</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53413 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53413</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54167 | Notification Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54167</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Notification Center. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Notification Center 2.1.0.3443 and later
Notification Center 1.9.2.3163 and later
Notification Center 3.0.0.3466 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54168 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54168</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuLog Center. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuLog Center 1.8.2.923 ( 2025/08/27 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57706 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57706</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.5018 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57712 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57712</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 5.0.0.3 ( 2025/08/28 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58463 | Download Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58463</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Download Station. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Download Station 5.10.0.305 ( 2025/09/16 ) and later
Download Station 5.10.0.304 ( 2025/09/08 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58464 | QuMagie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58464</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect QuMagie. If a remote attacker, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuMagie 2.7.3 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58465 | Download Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58465</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Download Station. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Download Station 5.10.0.305 ( 2025/09/16 ) and later
Download Station 5.10.0.304 ( 2025/09/08 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58469 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58469</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuLog Center. The remote attackers can then exploit the vulnerability to gain privileges or hijack user identities.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuLog Center 1.8.2.927 ( 2025/09/17 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12859 | DedeBIZ templets_one_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12859</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/templets_one_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12860 | DedeBIZ freelist_main.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12860</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/freelist_main.php. The manipulation of the argument orderby results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12857 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site roombook.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12857</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/roombook.php. Such manipulation of the argument rid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34299 | Monsta FTP &amp;lt;= 2.11 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34299</link><description>Monsta FTP versions 2.11 and earlier contain a vulnerability that allows unauthenticated arbitrary file uploads. This flaw enables attackers to execute arbitrary code by uploading a specially crafted file from a malicious (S)FTP server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12855 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site newsletterdel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12855</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/newsletterdel.php. The manipulation of the argument eid results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12856 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site reservation.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12856</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/reservation.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10968 | SQLi in GG Soft&amp;#x27;s PaperWork</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10968</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection'), CWE - 564 - SQL Injection: Hibernate vulnerability in GG Soft Software Services Inc. PaperWork allows Blind SQL Injection, SQL Injection.This issue affects PaperWork: from 6.1.0.9390 before 6.1.0.9398.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12853 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php delete_house sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12853</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects the function delete_house of the file /admin_class.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12854 | newbee-mall-plus seckillExecution executeSeckill authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12854</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in newbee-mall-plus up to 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects the function executeSeckill of the file /seckillExecution/. The manipulation of the argument userid leads to authorization bypass. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10870 | SQL injection in DIAL&amp;#x27;s CentrosNet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10870</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in DIAL's CentrosNet v2.64. Allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases by sending POST and GET requests with the 'ultralogin' parameter in '/centrosnet/ultralogin.php'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 09:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46413 | Use of password hash with insufficient computational effort issue exists in BUFFALO Wi-Fi router 'WSR-1800AX4 series'. When WPS is enabled, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46413</link><description>Use of password hash with insufficient computational effort issue exists in BUFFALO Wi-Fi router 'WSR-1800AX4 series'. When WPS is enabled, PIN code and/or Wi-Fi password may be obtained by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 09:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10966 | missing SFTP host verification with wolfSSH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10966</link><description>curl's code for managing SSH connections when SFTP was done using the wolfSSH
powered backend was flawed and missed host verification mechanisms.

This prevents curl from detecting MITM attackers and more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12520 | WP Airbnb Review Slider &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12520</link><description>The WP Airbnb Review Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.2 due to insufficient URL validation that allows users to pull in a malicious HTML file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12527 | Page &amp;amp; Post Notes &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Note Update/Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12527</link><description>The Page &amp; Post Notes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of notes due to a missing capability check on the 'yydev_notes_save_dashboard_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify notes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64346 | archives: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64346</link><description>archives is a Go library for extracting archives (tar, zip, etc.). Version 1.0.0 does not prevent a malicious user to feed a specially crafted archive to the library causing RCE, modification of files or other malignancies in the context of whatever the user is running this library as, through the program that imports it. Severity depends on user permissions, environment and how arbitrary archives are passed. This issue is fixed in version 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64343 | (conda) Constructor: Excessive permissions during and after installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64343</link><description>(conda) Constructor is a tool that enables users to create installers for conda package collections. In versions 3.12.2 and below, the  installation directory inherits permissions from its parent directory. Outside of restricted directories, the permissions are very permissive and often allow write access by authenticated users. Any logged in user can make modifications during the installation for both single-user and all-user installations. This constitutes a local attack vector if the installation is in a directory local users have access to. For single-user installations in a shared directory, these permissions persist after the installation. This issue is fixed in version 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64339 | ClipBucket v5: Stored XSS Vulnerability in Manage Playlists</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64339</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. In versions 5.5.2-#146 and below, the Manage Playlists feature is vulnerable to stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS),specifically in the Playlist Name field. An authenticated low-privileged user can create a playlist with a malicious name containing HTML/JavaScript code, which is rendered unescaped on playlist detail and listing pages. This results in arbitrary JavaScript execution in every viewer’s browser, including administrators. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2-#147.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12352 | Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 2.9.20 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;copy_post_image&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12352</link><description>The Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the copy_post_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.20. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This only impacts sites that have allow_url_fopen set to `On`, the post creation form enabled along with a file upload field for the post</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4519 | IDonate 2.1.5 - 2.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via idonate_donor_password Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4519</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the idonate_donor_password() function in versions 2.1.5 to 2.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to initiate a password reset for any user (including administrators) and elevate their privileges for full site takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4522 | IDonate 2.0.0 - 2.1.9 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary User Deletion via admin_post_donor_delete Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4522</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference via the admin_post_donor_delete() function in versions 2.0.0 to 2.1.9. By supplying an arbitrary user_id parameter value to the wp_delete_user() function, authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above could delete arbitrary user accounts, including those of administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64336 | ClipBucket v5&amp;#x27;s Manage Photo Feature is Vulnerable to Stored XSS Attack via Photo Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64336</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. In versions 5.5.2-#146 and below, the Manage Photos feature is vulnerable to stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS). An authenticated regular user can upload a photo with a malicious Photo Title containing HTML/JavaScript code. While the payload does not execute in the user-facing photo gallery or detail pages, it is rendered unsafely in the Admin → Manage Photos section, resulting in JavaScript execution in the administrator’s browser. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2-#147.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64329 | containerd CRI server: Host memory exhaustion through Attach goroutine leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64329</link><description>containerd is an open-source container runtime. Versions 1.7.28 and below, 2.0.0-beta.0 through 2.0.6, 2.1.0-beta.0 through 2.1.4, and 2.2.0-beta.0 through 2.2.0-rc.1 contain a bug in the CRI Attach implementation where a user can exhaust memory on the host due to goroutine leaks. This issue is fixed in versions 1.7.29, 2.0.7, 2.1.5 and 2.2.0. To workaround this vulnerability, users can set up an admission controller to control accesses to pods/attach resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5483 | LC Wizard 1.2.10 - 1.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5483</link><description>The LC Wizard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check in the ghl-wizard/inc/wp_user.php file in versions 1.2.10 to 1.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new user accounts with the administrator role when the PRO functionality is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64328 | FreePBX Administration GUI is Vulnerable to Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64328</link><description>FreePBX Endpoint Manager is a module for managing telephony endpoints in FreePBX systems. In versions 17.0.2.36 and above before 17.0.3, the filestore module within the Administrative interface is vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection by an authenticated known user via the testconnection -&gt; check_ssh_connect() function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to obtain remote access to the system as an asterisk user. This issue is fixed in version 17.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64180 | Manager-io/Manager: Complete Bypass of SSRF Protection via Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64180</link><description>Manager-io/Manager is accounting software. In Manager Desktop and Server versions 25.11.1.3085 and below, a critical vulnerability permits unauthorized access to internal network resources. The flaw lies in the fundamental design of the DNS validation mechanism. A Time-of-Check Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) condition that allows attackers to bypass network isolation and access internal services, cloud metadata endpoints, and protected network segments. The Desktop edition requires no authentication; the Server edition requires only standard authentication. This issue is fixed in version 25.11.1.3086.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64184 | Dosage vulnerable to Directory Traversal through crafted HTTP responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64184</link><description>Dosage is a comic strip downloader and archiver. When downloading comic images in versions 3.1 and below, Dosage constructs target file names from different aspects of the remote comic (page URL, image URL, page content, etc.). While the basename is properly stripped of directory-traversing characters, the file extension is taken from the HTTP Content-Type header. This allows a remote attacker (or a Man-in-the-Middle, if the comic is served over HTTP) to write arbitrary files outside the target directory (if additional conditions are met). This issue is fixed in version 3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64187 | OctoPrint is vulnerable to XSS through Action Command Notifications and Prompts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64187</link><description>OctoPrint provides a web interface for controlling consumer 3D printers. Versions 1.11.3 and below are affected by a vulnerability that allows injection of arbitrary HTML and JavaScript into Action Command notifications and prompts popups generated by the printer. An attacker who successfully convinces a victim to print a specially crafted file could exploit this issue to disrupt ongoing prints, extract information (including sensitive configuration settings, if the targeted user has the necessary permissions for that), or perform other actions on behalf of the targeted user within the OctoPrint instance. This issue is fixed in version 1.11.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64323 | kgateway is missing xDS authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64323</link><description>kgateway is a Cloud-Native API and AI Gateway. Versions 2.0.4 and below and 2.1.0-agw-cel-rbac through 2.1.0-rc.2 lack authentication, allowing any client with unrestricted network access to the xDS port to retrieve potentially sensitive configuration data including certificate data, backend service information, routing rules, and cluster metadata. This issue is solved in versions 2.0.5 and 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11546 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver.9.5 to Ver.10.7, from Ver.10.8.21 to Ver.10.8.36, from Ver.10.9.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11546</link><description>Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver.9.5 to Ver.10.7, from Ver.10.8.21 to Ver.10.8.36, from Ver.10.9.11 to Ver.10.9.24, from Ver.10.10.21 to Ver.10.10.31, Ver.10.11.6 and UNIVERGE IX-R/IX-V Ver1.3.16, Ver1.3.21 allows an attacker sends specially crafted network packets to the product, arbitrary OS commands may be executed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48985 | A vulnerability in Vercel’s AI SDK has been fixed in versions 5.0.52, 5.1.0-beta.9, and 6.0.0-beta. This issue may have allowed users to byp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48985</link><description>A vulnerability in Vercel’s AI SDK has been fixed in versions 5.0.52, 5.1.0-beta.9, and 6.0.0-beta. This issue may have allowed users to bypass filetype whitelists when uploading files. All users are encouraged to upgrade.

More details: https://vercel.com/changelog/cve-2025-48985-input-validation-bypass-on-ai-sdk</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52662 | A vulnerability in Nuxt DevTools has been fixed in version **2.6.4***. This issue may have allowed Nuxt auth token extraction via XSS under ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52662</link><description>A vulnerability in Nuxt DevTools has been fixed in version **2.6.4***. This issue may have allowed Nuxt auth token extraction via XSS under certain configurations. All users are encouraged to upgrade.

More details: https://vercel.com/changelog/cve-2025-52662-xss-on-nuxt-devtools</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>