<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 18:59:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-49946 | In Forgejo before 1.20.5-1, certain endpoints do not check whether an object belongs to a repository for which permissions are being checked...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49946</link><description>In Forgejo before 1.20.5-1, certain endpoints do not check whether an object belongs to a repository for which permissions are being checked. This allows remote attackers to read private issues, read private pull requests, delete issues, and perform other unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 18:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49947 | Forgejo before 1.20.5-1 allows 2FA bypass when docker login uses Basic Authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49947</link><description>Forgejo before 1.20.5-1 allows 2FA bypass when docker login uses Basic Authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 18:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49948 | Forgejo before 1.20.5-1 allows remote attackers to test for the existence of private user accounts by appending .rss (or another extension) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49948</link><description>Forgejo before 1.20.5-1 allows remote attackers to test for the existence of private user accounts by appending .rss (or another extension) to a URL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 18:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45178 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45178</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5 CLI is vulnerable to a denial of service when a specially crafted request is used.  IBM X-Force ID:  268073.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 17:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36768 | rl-institut NESP2 database.py sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36768</link><description>A vulnerability was found in rl-institut NESP2 Initial Release/1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file app/database.py. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 07c0cdf36cf6a4345086d07b54423723a496af5e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-246642 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 11:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25094 | ระบบบัญชีออนไลน์ Online Accounting System image.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25094</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ระบบบัญชีออนไลน์ Online Accounting System up to 1.4.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ckeditor/filemanager/browser/default/image.php. The manipulation of the argument fid with the input ../../../etc/passwd leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.0.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 9d9618422b980335bb30be612ea90f4f56cb992c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-246641 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49926 | app/Lib/Tools/EventTimelineTool.php in MISP before 2.4.179 allows XSS in the event timeline widget.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49926</link><description>app/Lib/Tools/EventTimelineTool.php in MISP before 2.4.179 allows XSS in the event timeline widget.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 03:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6474 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System manage-phlebotomist.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6474</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file manage-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246640.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 23:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47100 | In Perl before 5.38.2, S_parse_uniprop_string in regcomp.c can write to unallocated space because a property name associated with a \p{...} ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47100</link><description>In Perl before 5.38.2, S_parse_uniprop_string in regcomp.c can write to unallocated space because a property name associated with a \p{...} regular expression construct is mishandled. The earliest affected version is 5.30.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 23:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6473 | SourceCodester Online Quiz System take-quiz.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6473</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Quiz System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file take-quiz.php. The manipulation of the argument quiz_taker/year_section leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246639.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 20:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6472 | PHPEMS Content Section api.cls.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6472</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPEMS 7.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file app\content\cls\api.cls.php of the component Content Section Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246629 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6467 | Thecosy IceCMS Comment Like improper enforcement of a single, unique action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6467</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Thecosy IceCMS 2.0.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Websquare/likeClickComment/ of the component Comment Like Handler. The manipulation leads to improper enforcement of a single, unique action. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246617 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 14:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6466 | Thecosy IceCMS User Comment planet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6466</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Thecosy IceCMS 2.0.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /planet of the component User Comment Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246616.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 13:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6465 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System registered-user-testing.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6465</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file registered-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument regmobilenumber leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246615.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 12:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6464 | SourceCodester User Registration and Login System add-user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6464</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-user.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 09:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39256 | Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39256</link><description>Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify the content in an unsecured folder during product installation and upgrade, leading to privilege escalation on the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39257 | Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39257</link><description>Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A local malicious standard user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify the content in an unsecured folder when product installation repair is performed, leading to privilege escalation on the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49914 | InteraXon Muse 2 devices allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (incorrect Muse App report of an outstanding, calm meditation s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49914</link><description>InteraXon Muse 2 devices allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (incorrect Muse App report of an outstanding, calm meditation state) via a 480 MHz RF carrier that is modulated by a "false" brain wave, aka a Brain-Hack attack. For example, the Muse App does not display the reception of a strong RF carrier, and alert the user that a report may be misleading if this carrier has been modulated by a low-frequency signal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48801 | In TOTOLINK X6000R_Firmware V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file sub_415534 function obtains fields from the front-end, connects them thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48801</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R_Firmware V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file sub_415534 function obtains fields from the front-end, connects them through the snprintf function, and passes them to the CsteSystem function, resulting in a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48887 | A deserialization vulnerability in Jupiter v1.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via sending a crafted RPC request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48887</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability in Jupiter v1.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via sending a crafted RPC request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6463 | SourceCodester User Registration and Login System add-user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6463</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-user.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246613 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48886 | A deserialization vulnerability in NettyRpc v1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via sending a crafted RPC request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48886</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability in NettyRpc v1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via sending a crafted RPC request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49281 | Open Redirect in Login Function of Calendarinho</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49281</link><description>Calendarinho is an open source calendaring application to manage large teams of consultants. An Open Redirect issue occurs when a web application redirects users to external URLs without proper validation. This can lead to phishing attacks, where users are tricked into visiting malicious sites, potentially leading to information theft and reputational damage to the website used for redirection. The problem is has been patched in commit `15b2393`. Users are advised to update to a commit after `15b2393`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48314 | Unescaped passing of the request URL in Collabora Online</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48314</link><description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice technology. Users of Nextcloud with Collabora Online Built-in CODE Server app can be vulnerable to attack via proxy.php. This vulnerability has been fixed in Collabora Online - Built-in CODE Server (richdocumentscode) release 23.5.403. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49276 | Attribute Injection leading to XSS(Cross-Site-Scripting) in uptime-kuma</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49276</link><description>Uptime Kuma is an open source self-hosted monitoring tool. In affected versions the Google Analytics element in vulnerable to Attribute Injection leading to Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS). Since the custom status interface can set an independent Google Analytics ID and the template has not been sanitized, there is an attribute injection vulnerability here, which can lead to XSS attacks. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `f28dccf4e` which is included in release version 1.23.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46746 | Authenticated PostHog users vulnerable to SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46746</link><description>PostHog provides open-source product analytics, session recording, feature flagging and A/B testing that you can self-host. A server-side request forgery (SSRF), which can only be exploited by authenticated users, was found in Posthog. Posthog did not verify whether a URL was local when enabling webhooks, allowing authenticated users to forge a POST request. This vulnerability has been addressed in `22bd5942` and will be included in subsequent releases. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44381 | October CMS safe mode bypass using Page template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44381</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform to assist with development workflow. An authenticated backend user with the `editor.cms_pages`, `editor.cms_layouts`, or `editor.cms_partials` permissions who would normally not be permitted to provide PHP code to be executed by the CMS due to `cms.safe_mode` being enabled can craft a special request to include PHP code in the CMS template. This issue has been patched in version 3.4.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44382 | October CMS safe mode bypass using Twig sandbox escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44382</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform to assist with development workflow. An authenticated backend user with the `editor.cms_pages`, `editor.cms_layouts`, or `editor.cms_partials` permissions who would normally not be permitted to provide PHP code to be executed by the CMS due to `cms.safe_mode` being enabled can write specific Twig code to escape the Twig sandbox and execute arbitrary PHP. This issue has been patched in 3.4.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44402 | ASAR Integrity bypass via filetype confusion in electron</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44402</link><description>Electron is an open source framework for writing cross-platform desktop applications using JavaScript, HTML and CSS. This only impacts apps that have the `embeddedAsarIntegrityValidation` and `onlyLoadAppFromAsar` fuses enabled.  Apps without these fuses enabled are not impacted.  This issue is specific to macOS as these fuses are only currently supported on macOS. Specifically this issue can only be exploited if your app is launched from a filesystem the attacker has write access too.  i.e. the ability to edit files inside the `.app` bundle on macOS which these fuses are supposed to protect against. There are no app side workarounds, you must update to a patched version of Electron.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6462 | SourceCodester User Registration and Login System delete-user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6462</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/delete-user.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246612.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46174 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46174</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  269506.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40699 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40699</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service due to improper input validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  265161.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42019 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42019</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service due to improper input validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  265161.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42022 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42022</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 265938.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42009 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42009</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  265504.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43021 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43021</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system. IBM X-Force ID: 266167.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49277 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in dpaste</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49277</link><description>dpaste is an open source pastebin application written in Python using the Django framework. A security vulnerability has been identified in the expires parameter of the dpaste API, allowing for a POST Reflected XSS attack. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of a user's browser, potentially leading to unauthorized access, data theft, or other malicious activities. Users are strongly advised to upgrade to dpaste release v3.8 or later versions, as dpaste versions older than v3.8 are susceptible to the identified security vulnerability. No known workarounds have been identified, and applying the patch is the most effective way to remediate the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 20:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43015 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43015</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  266064.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38268 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38268</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  260585.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26024 | IBM Planning Analytics on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26024</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0 could allow an attacker on a shared network to obtain sensitive information caused by insecure network communication.  IBM X-Force ID:  247898.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 19:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42006 | IBM i information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42006</link><description>IBM Administration Runtime Expert for i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information caused by improper authority checks.  IBM X-Force ID:  265266.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48893 | Senayan Library Management Systems SLIMS 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/staff_act.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48893</link><description>Senayan Library Management Systems SLIMS 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/staff_act.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48813 | Senayan Library Management Systems (Slims) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/fines_report.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48813</link><description>Senayan Library Management Systems (Slims) 9 Bulian v9.6.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin/modules/reporting/customs/fines_report.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48842 | D-Link Go-RT-AC750 revA_v101b03 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the service parameter at hedwig.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48842</link><description>D-Link Go-RT-AC750 revA_v101b03 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the service parameter at hedwig.cgi.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49371 | RuoYi up to v4.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via /system/dept/edit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49371</link><description>RuoYi up to v4.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via /system/dept/edit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4518 | A vulnerability exists in the input validation of the GOOSE 
messages where out of range values received and processed 
by the IED caused a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4518</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the input validation of the GOOSE 
messages where out of range values received and processed 
by the IED caused a reboot of the device. In order for an 
attacker to exploit the vulnerability, goose receiving blocks need 
to be configured.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45168 | IBM AIX command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45168</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the invscout command to execute arbitrary commands.  IBM X-Force ID:  267966.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28896 | Weak encoding for password in UDS services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28896</link><description>Access to critical Unified Diagnostics Services (UDS) of the Modular Infotainment Platform 3 (MIB3) infotainment is transmitted via Controller Area Network (CAN) bus in a form that can be easily decoded by attackers with physical access to the vehicle.

Vulnerability discovered on Škoda Superb III (3V3) - 2.0 TDI manufactured in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28895 | Hard-coded password for access to power controller chip memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28895</link><description>The password for access to the debugging console of the PoWer Controller chip (PWC) of the MIB3 infotainment is hard-coded in the firmware. The console allows attackers with physical access to the MIB3 unit to gain full control over the PWC chip.

Vulnerability found on Škoda Superb III (3V3) - 2.0 TDI manufactured in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5636 | Malicious File Upload in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5636</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows Command Injection.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5637 | Plaintext Storage of a Password in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5637</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5635 | User Enumeration in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5635</link><description>Improper Protection for Outbound Error Messages and Alert Signals vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows Account Footprinting.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6461 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in viliusle/minipaint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6461</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository viliusle/minipaint prior to 4.14.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5634 | SQLi in ArslanSoft&amp;#x27;s Education Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ArslanSoft Education Portal allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Education Portal: before v1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6449 | The Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'validate' f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6449</link><description>The Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'validate' function and insufficient blocklisting on the 'wpcf7_antiscript_file_name' function in versions up to, and including, 5.8.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with editor-level capabilities or above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, but due to the htaccess configuration, remote code cannot be executed in most cases. By default, the file will be deleted from the server immediately. However, in some cases, other plugins may make it possible for the file to live on the server longer. This can make remote code execution possible when combined with another vulnerability, such as local file inclusion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5427 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5427</link><description>A local non-privileged user can make improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3443 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3443</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 12.1 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for a Guest user to add an emoji on confidential work items.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3949 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3949</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for unauthorized users to view a public projects' release descriptions via an atom endpoint when release access on the public was set to only project members.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3964 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3964</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 13.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for users to access composer packages on public projects that have package registry disabled in the project settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4317 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4317</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 9.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for a user with the Developer role to update a pipeline schedule from an unprotected branch to a protected branch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4658 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4658</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 8.13 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to abuse the `Allowed to merge` permission as a guest user, when granted the permission through a group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4912 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4912</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 10.5 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted mermaid diagram input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5226 | Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5226</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. Under certain circumstances, a malicious actor bypass prohibited branch checks using a specially crafted branch name to manipulate repository content in the UI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5995 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5995</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to abuse the policy bot to gain access to internal projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6033 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6033</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Jira integration configuration in GitLab CE/EE, affecting all versions from 15.10 prior to 16.6.1, 16.5 prior to 16.5.3, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.3 allows attacker to execute javascript in victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5915 | A vulnerability of Uncontrolled Resource Consumption has been identified in STARDOM provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5915</link><description>A vulnerability of Uncontrolled Resource Consumption has been identified in STARDOM provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation. This vulnerability may allow to a remote attacker to cause a denial-of-service condition to the FCN/FCJ controller by sending a crafted packet. While sending the packet, the maintenance homepage of the controller could not be accessed. Therefore, functions of the maintenance homepage, changing configuration, viewing logs, etc. are not available. But the controller’s operation is not stopped by the condition.

The affected products and versions are as follows: STARDOM FCN/FCJ R1.01 to R4.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45252 | DLL Hijacking vulnerability in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, due to the installation of the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45252</link><description>DLL Hijacking vulnerability in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, due to the installation of the service in a directory that grants write privileges to standard users, allows attackers to manipulate files, execute arbitrary code, and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45253 | An issue was discovered in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, allows attackers to manipulate files...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45253</link><description>An issue was discovered in Huddly HuddlyCameraService before version 8.0.7, not including version 7.99, allows attackers to manipulate files and escalate privileges via RollingFileAppender.DeleteFile method performed by the log4net library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48016 | Restaurant Table Booking System V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rtbs/admin/index.php via the username parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48016</link><description>Restaurant Table Booking System V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rtbs/admin/index.php via the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43089 | Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains insufficient protection for the Policy folder. A local malicious standard user co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43089</link><description>Dell Rugged Control Center, version prior to 4.7, contains insufficient protection for the Policy folder. A local malicious standard user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify the content of the policy file, leading to unauthorized access to resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43453 | An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the IP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43453</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the IP parameter of the setDiagnosisCfg component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43454 | An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43454</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hostName parameter of the switchOpMode component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43455 | An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43455</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X6000R V9.4.0cu.652_B20230116 and V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the command parameter of the setting/setTracerouteCfg component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>