<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-47241 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains an Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability. A low pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47241</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains an Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access and modification of transmitted data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6080 | Privilege Escalation to SYSTEM in Lakeside Software Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6080</link><description>Lakeside Software’s SysTrack LsiAgent Installer version 10.7.8 for Windows contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability which allows attackers SYSTEM level access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42508 | This vulnerability could be exploited, leading to unauthorized disclosure of information to authenticated users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42508</link><description>This vulnerability could be exploited, leading to unauthorized disclosure of information to authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9537 | ScienceLogic SL1 unspecified vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9537</link><description>ScienceLogic SL1 (formerly EM7) is affected by an unspecified vulnerability involving an unspecified third-party component packaged with SL1. The vulnerability is addressed in SL1 versions 12.1.3+, 12.2.3+, and 12.3+.  Remediations have been made available for all SL1 versions back to version lines 10.1.x, 10.2.x, 11.1.x, 11.2.x, and 11.3.x.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 14:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47240 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.24 contains an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A local attacker with low privileges can acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47240</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.24 contains an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A local attacker with low privileges can access the file system and could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain write access to unauthorized data and cause a version update failure condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9674 | Debrandify · Remove or Replace WordPress Branding &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9674</link><description>The Debrandify · Remove or Replace WordPress Branding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43300 | WordPress Movie Database plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43300</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bert Kößler Movie Database allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Movie Database: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49224 | WordPress Mitm Bug Tracker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mahesh Patel Mitm Bug Tracker allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mitm Bug Tracker: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49225 | WordPress wpPricing Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Swebdeveloper wpPricing Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects wpPricing Builder: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49228 | WordPress bVerse Convert plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CrossedCode bVerse Convert allows Stored XSS.This issue affects bVerse Convert: from n/a through 1.3.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49230 | WordPress  Ajax Custom CSS/JS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49230</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Harpreet Singh Ajax Custom CSS/JS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ajax Custom CSS/JS: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49231 | WordPress WordPress Video plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Peter CyClop WordPress Video allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Video: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49232 | WordPress El mejor Cluster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49232</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Javier Loureiro El mejor Cluster allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects El mejor Cluster: from n/a through 1.1.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49233 | WordPress MAS Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MadrasThemes MAS Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects MAS Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49234 | WordPress Plexx Elementor Extension plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themeworm Plexx Elementor Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Plexx Elementor Extension: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49236 | WordPress Crazy Call To Action Box plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hafiz Uddin Ahmed Crazy Call To Action Box allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Crazy Call To Action Box: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49238 | WordPress ADIF Log Search Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0f - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49238</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M. Konieczny, DH9SB ADIF Log Search Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ADIF Log Search Widget: from n/a through 1.0f.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49239 | WordPress Add Categories Post Footer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nikhil Vaghela Add Categories Post Footer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Add Categories Post Footer: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49240 | WordPress AB Categories Search Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49240</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Agustin Berasategui AB Categories Search Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AB Categories Search Widget: from n/a through 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49241 | WordPress Tito plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tady Walsh Tito allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Tito: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49243 | WordPress Dynamic Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49243</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Jon Vincent Mendoza Dynamic Elementor Addons allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dynamic Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10057 | RSS Feed Widget &amp;lt;= 2.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via rfw-youtube-videos Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10057</link><description>The RSS Feed Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's rfw-youtube-videos shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9425 | Advanced Category and Custom Taxonomy Image &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ad_tax_image Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9425</link><description>The Advanced Category and Custom Taxonomy Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ad_tax_image shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47486 | There is an XSS vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could inject scripts into certain pages by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47486</link><description>There is an XSS vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could inject scripts into certain pages by building malicious data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47485 | There is a CSV injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could build malicious data to gene...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47485</link><description>There is a CSV injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could build malicious data to generate executable commands in the CSV file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47487 | There is a SQL injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47487</link><description>There is a SQL injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4740 | MXsecurity Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4740</link><description>MXsecurity software versions v1.1.0 and prior are vulnerable because of the use of hard-coded credentials. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to tamper with sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49570 | Insecure Trust of Basic Constraints certificate in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11210)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49570</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software trusts a certificate issued by an entity that isn't authorized to issue certificates. This occurs when the "Basic Constraints" extension in the certificate indicates that it is meant to be an "End Entity”. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4739 | MXsecurity License Generation Function Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4739</link><description>The lack of access restriction to a resource from unauthorized users makes MXsecurity software versions v1.1.0 and prior vulnerable. By acquiring a valid authenticator, an attacker can pose as an authorized user and successfully access the resource.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49567 | Insecure Trust of certificates using collision hash functions in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11239)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49567</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the product incorrectly checks the site's certificate, which allows an attacker to make MITM SSL connections to an arbitrary site. The product trusts certificates that are issued using the MD5 and SHA1 collision hash functions which allow attackers to create rogue certificates that appear legitimate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6058 | HTTPS Certificate Validation Issue in Bitdefender Safepay (VA-11167)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6058</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Safepay's handling of HTTPS connections. The issue arises when the product blocks a connection due to an untrusted server certificate but allows the user to add the site to exceptions, resulting in the product trusting the certificate for subsequent HTTPS scans. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack by using a self-signed certificate, which the product will trust after the site has been added to exceptions. This can lead to the interception and potential alteration of secure communications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6057 | Insecure Trust of DSA-Signed Certificates in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11166)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6057</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of certificates issued using the DSA signature algorithm. The product does not properly check the certificate chain, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites using a DSA-signed certificate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10055 | Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpsaio_snapchat Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10055</link><description>The Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpsaio_snapchat shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10078 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10078</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to add, modify, or delete plugin options and posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10079 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10079</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'text' parameter in the 'ajax_import_content' function. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10080 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10080</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via post meta in versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6056 | Insecure Trust of Self-Signed Certificates in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11164)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6056</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of self-signed certificates. The product is found to trust certificates signed with the RIPEMD-160 hashing algorithm without proper validation, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6055 | Improper Certificate Validation in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11158)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6055</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software fails to properly validate website certificates. Specifically, if a site certificate lacks the "Server Authentication" specification in the Extended Key Usage extension, the product does not verify the certificate's compliance with the site, deeming such certificates as valid. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9206 | MAS Companies For WP Job Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9206</link><description>The MAS Companies For WP Job Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9703 | Arconix Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9703</link><description>The Arconix Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46897 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. A logged-in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46897</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. A logged-in user with the permission of table management may obtain and/or alter the information of the unauthorized table.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47793 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. When accessing the edit screen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47793</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. When accessing the edit screen containing custom columns (column type: images or files), an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38820 | CVE-2024-38820: Spring Framework DataBinder Case Sensitive Match Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38820</link><description>The fix for CVE-2022-22968 made disallowedFields patterns in DataBinder case insensitive. However, String.toLowerCase() has some Locale dependent exceptions that could potentially result in fields not protected as expected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10014 | Flat UI Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via flatbtn Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10014</link><description>The Flat UI Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's flatbtn shortcode in version 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10040 | Infinite-Scroll &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10040</link><description>The Infinite-Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_ajax_edit and process_ajax_delete function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make changes to plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10049 | Edit WooCommerce Templates &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10049</link><description>The Edit WooCommerce Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8740 | GetResponse Forms by Optin Cat &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8740</link><description>The GetResponse Forms by Optin Cat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8790 | Social Share With Floating Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8790</link><description>The Social Share With Floating Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8916 | Suki Sites Import &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8916</link><description>The Suki Sites Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9350 | DPD Baltic Shipping &amp;lt;= 1.2.83 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9350</link><description>The DPD Baltic Shipping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search_value' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.83 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9361 | Bulk images optimizer: Resize, optimize, convert to webp, rename ... &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9361</link><description>The Bulk images optimizer: Resize, optimize, convert to webp, rename … plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_configuration' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9364 | SendGrid for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9364</link><description>The SendGrid for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_mailplus_clear_logs' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9366 | Easy Menu Manager | WPZest &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9366</link><description>The Easy Menu Manager | WPZest plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9373 | Elemenda &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9373</link><description>The Elemenda plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9382 | Gantry 4 Framework &amp;lt;= 4.1.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9382</link><description>The Gantry 4 Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'override_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9383 | Parcel Pro &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9383</link><description>The Parcel Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'action' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9452 | Branding &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9452</link><description>The Branding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9848 | Product Customizer Light &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9848</link><description>The Product Customizer Light plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9892 | Add Widget After Content &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9892</link><description>The Add Widget After Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10119 | SECOM WRTM326 - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10119</link><description>The wireless router WRTM326 from SECOM does not properly validate a specific parameter. An unauthenticated remote attacker could execute arbitrary system commands by sending crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10118 | SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10118</link><description>SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC does not properly filter user input in the specific functionality. Unauthenticated remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability to inject and execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9264 | Grafana SQL Expressions allow for remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9264</link><description>The SQL Expressions experimental feature of Grafana allows for the evaluation of `duckdb` queries containing user input. These queries are insufficiently sanitized before being passed to `duckdb`, leading to a command injection and local file inclusion vulnerability. Any user with the VIEWER or higher permission is capable of executing this attack.  The `duckdb` binary must be present in Grafana's $PATH for this attack to function; by default, this binary is not installed in Grafana distributions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 03:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49023 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49023</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 23:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43566 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43566</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43578 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43578</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43579 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43579</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43580 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43580</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43587 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43587</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43595 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43595</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43596 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43596</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10093 | VSO ConvertXtoDvd ConvertXtoDvd.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10093</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in VSO ConvertXtoDvd 7.0.0.83. Affected is an unknown function in the library avcodec.dll of the file ConvertXtoDvd.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7316 | Denial of Service (DoS) Vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7316</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS) condition on the product by sending specially crafted packets to TCP port 683, causing an emergency stop.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26785 | MariaDB v10.5 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26785</link><description>MariaDB v10.5 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39593 | Insecure permissions in the sys_exec function of Oracle MYSQL MariaDB v10.5 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39593</link><description>Insecure permissions in the sys_exec function of Oracle MYSQL MariaDB v10.5 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27766 | An issue in MYSQL MariaDB v.11.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lib_mysqludf_sys.so function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27766</link><description>An issue in MYSQL MariaDB v.11.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lib_mysqludf_sys.so function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30875 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in JavaScript Library jquery-ui v.1.13.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30875</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in JavaScript Library jquery-ui v.1.13.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the window.addEventListener component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33453 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in esp-idf v.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the externalId component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33453</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in esp-idf v.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the externalId component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48924 | MessagePack allows untrusted data to lead to DoS attack due to hash collisions and stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48924</link><description>### Impact

When this library is used to deserialize messagepack data from an untrusted source, there is a risk of a denial of service attack by an attacker that sends data contrived to produce hash collisions, leading to large CPU consumption disproportionate to the size of the data being deserialized.

This is similar to [a prior advisory](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/security/advisories/GHSA-7q36-4xx7-xcxf), which provided an inadequate fix for the hash collision part of the vulnerability.

### Patches

The following steps are required to mitigate this risk.

1. Upgrade to a version of the library where a fix is available.
1. Review the steps in [this previous advisory](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/security/advisories/GHSA-7q36-4xx7-xcxf) to ensure you have your application configured for untrusted data.

### Workarounds

If upgrading MessagePack to a patched version is not an option for you, you may apply a manual workaround as follows:

1. Declare a class that derives from `MessagePackSecurity`.
2. Override the `GetHashCollisionResistantEqualityComparer` method to provide a collision-resistant hash function of your own and avoid calling `base.GetHashCollisionResistantEqualityComparer()`.
3. Configure a `MessagePackSerializerOptions` with an instance of your derived type by calling `WithSecurity` on an existing options object.
4. Use your custom options object for all deserialization operations. This may be by setting the `MessagePackSerializer.DefaultOptions` static property, if you call methods that rely on this default property, and/or by passing in the options object explicitly to any `Deserialize` method.

### References

- Learn more about best security practices when reading untrusted data with [MessagePack 1.x](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/tree/v1.x#security) or [MessagePack 2.x](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp#security).
- The .NET team's [discussion on hash collision vulnerabilities of their `HashCode` struct](https://github.com/GrabYourPitchforks/runtime/blob/threat_models/docs/design/security/System.HashCode.md).

### For more information

If you have any questions or comments about this advisory:

* [Start a public discussion](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/discussions)
* [Email us privately](mailto:andrewarnott@live.com)</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 20:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49248 | WordPress Ad Inserter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.37 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49248</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Igor Funa Ad Inserter allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ad Inserter: from n/a through 2.7.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49255 | WordPress Da Reactions plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49255</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Daniele Alessandra Da Reactions allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Da Reactions: from n/a through 5.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49259 | WordPress Primary Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49259</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Primary Addon for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Primary Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49261 | WordPress Arkhe Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.23.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LOOS,Inc. Arkhe Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Arkhe Blocks: from n/a through 2.23.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49262 | WordPress Country Flags for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wepic Country Flags for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Country Flags for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49263 | WordPress My Favorites plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49263</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Takashi Matsuyama My Favorites allows Stored XSS.This issue affects My Favorites: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49264 | WordPress Events Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49264</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Events Addon for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Events Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49276 | WordPress Clio Grow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49276</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themis Solutions, Inc. Clio Grow allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Clio Grow: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49277 | WordPress UltraAddons – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49277</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeAstrology Team UltraAddons Elementor Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49278 | WordPress Omnipress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49278</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in omnipressteam Omnipress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Omnipress: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49279 | WordPress Hyperlink Group Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49279</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in TipTopPress Hyperlink Group Block allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Hyperlink Group Block: from n/a through 1.17.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49280 | WordPress Lightbox slider -- Responsive Lightbox Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49280</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Weblizar Lightbox slider – Responsive Lightbox Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Lightbox slider – Responsive Lightbox Gallery: from n/a through 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49281 | WordPress Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49281</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NinjaTeam Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49282 | WordPress Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49282</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in dFactory Responsive Lightbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive Lightbox: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49283 | WordPress CURCY plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49283</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VillaTheme CURCY allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CURCY: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49288 | WordPress Email Template Customizer for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49288</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VillaTheme Email Template Customizer for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Email Template Customizer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49289 | WordPress Cooked Pro plugin &amp;lt; 1.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49289</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gora Tech LLC Cooked Pro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cooked Pro: from n/a before 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49292 | WordPress Exclusive Addons for Elementor  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49292</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Exclusive Addons Exclusive Addons Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Exclusive Addons Elementor: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49295 | WordPress Simple Testimonials Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49295</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Testimonials Showcase.This issue affects Simple Testimonials Showcase: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49296 | WordPress Custom Add to Cart Button Label and Link plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49296</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coder426 Custom Add to Cart Button Label and Link allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Add to Cart Button Label and Link: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49298 | WordPress PeproDev Ultimate Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49298</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev Ultimate Invoice allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PeproDev Ultimate Invoice: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49301 | WordPress G Meta Keywords plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49301</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sinan Yorulmaz G Meta Keywords allows Stored XSS.This issue affects G Meta Keywords: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49302 | WordPress WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49302</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Portfoliohub WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49307 | WordPress Admin Management Xtended plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Oliver Schlöbe Admin Management Xtended allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Admin Management Xtended: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49308 | WordPress Animator – Scroll Triggered Animations plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49308</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Toast Plugins Animator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Animator: from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49309 | WordPress Digitally theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49309</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Digitally allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Digitally: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49310 | WordPress Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49310</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesflat Themesflat Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themesflat Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49311 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49311</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49316 | WordPress Akismet htaccess writer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49316</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zodiac Akismet htaccess writer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Akismet htaccess writer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10099 | Stored XSS in comfyanonymous/comfyui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10099</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in comfyanonymous/comfyui version 0.2.2 and possibly earlier. The vulnerability occurs when an attacker uploads an HTML file containing a malicious XSS payload via the `/api/upload/image` endpoint. The payload is executed when the file is viewed through the `/view` API endpoint, leading to potential execution of arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10100 | Path Traversal in binary-husky/gpt_academic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10100</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in binary-husky/gpt_academic version 3.83. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the file parameter, which is open to path traversal through URL encoding. This allows attackers to view any file on the host system, including sensitive files such as critical application files, SSH keys, API keys, and configuration values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10101 | Stored XSS in binary-husky/gpt_academic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10101</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in binary-husky/gpt_academic version 3.83. The vulnerability occurs at the /file endpoint, which renders HTML files. Malicious HTML files containing XSS payloads can be uploaded and stored in the backend, leading to the execution of the payload in the victim's browser when the file is accessed. This can result in the theft of session cookies or other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49319 | WordPress Awesome Contact Form7 for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49319</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in B.M. Rafiul Alam Awesome Contact Form7 for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Awesome Contact Form7 for Elementor: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7755 | HMS Networks EWON FLEXY 202 Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7755</link><description>The EWON FLEXY 202 transmits credentials using a weak encoding method base64. An attacker who is present in the network can sniff the traffic and decode the credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43997 | WordPress easy.jobs- Best Recruitment Plugin for Job Board Listing, Manager, Career Page for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43997</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in easy.Jobs EasyJobs allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects EasyJobs: from n/a through 2.4.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49220 | WordPress Cookie Scanner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49220</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cookie Scanner – Nikel Schubert Cookie Scanner allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cookie Scanner: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49221 | WordPress cSlider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49221</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Julian Weinert // cs&amp;amp;m cSlider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects cSlider: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49223 | WordPress CJ Change Howdy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS  vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49223</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shibu Lijack a.K.A CyberJack CJ Change Howdy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CJ Change Howdy: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49229 | WordPress Better Author Bio plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.10.11 - CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49229</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Arif Nezami Better Author Bio allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Better Author Bio: from n/a through 2.7.10.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49237 | WordPress Ahmeti Wp Timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49237</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ahmet Imamoglu Ahmeti Wp Timeline allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ahmeti Wp Timeline: from n/a through 5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49304 | WordPress  Pinpoint Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49304</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PINPOINT.WORLD Pinpoint Booking System allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pinpoint Booking System: from n/a through 2.9.9.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49313 | WordPress VKontakte Wall Post plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49313</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RudeStan VKontakte Wall Post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects VKontakte Wall Post: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49217 | WordPress Adding drop down roles in registration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49217</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Madiri Salman Aashish Adding drop down roles in registration allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Adding drop down roles in registration: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49219 | WordPress RS-Members plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49219</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in themexpo RS-Members allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects RS-Members: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49322 | WordPress Job Board Manager for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49322</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in CodePassenger Job Board Manager for WordPress allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Job Board Manager for WordPress: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47304 | WordPress Fluent Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPManageNinja LLC Fluent Support allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Fluent Support: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47312 | WordPress Classic Editor and Classic Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47312</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPGrim Classic Editor and Classic Widgets allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Classic Editor and Classic Widgets: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49244 | WordPress SV Product Import Export for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in cmssoft CSV Product Import Export for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection.This issue affects CSV Product Import Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49246 | WordPress Ajax Rating with Custom Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49246</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in anand23 Ajax Rating with Custom Login allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Ajax Rating with Custom Login: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49297 | WordPress Zoho CRM Lead Magnet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.9.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49297</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Zoho CRM Zoho CRM Lead Magnet allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Zoho CRM Lead Magnet: from n/a through 1.7.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49299 | WordPress Surfer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0.502 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49299</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Surfer allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Surfer: from n/a through 1.5.0.502.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48629 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the IPAddress paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48629</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the IPAddress parameter in the SetGuestZoneRouterSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48630 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the MacAddress paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48630</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the MacAddress parameter in the SetMACFilters2 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48631 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SSID parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48631</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SSID parameter in the SetWLanRadioSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48632 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the LocalIPAd...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48632</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the LocalIPAddress, TCPPorts, and UDPPorts parameters in the SetPortForwardingSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48633 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the ExternalP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48633</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the ExternalPort, InternalPort, ProtocolNumber, and LocalIPAddress parameters in the SetVirtualServerSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48634 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the key parameter in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48634</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the key parameter in the SetWLanRadioSecurity function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48635 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:2/VID param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48635</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:2/VID parameter in the SetVLANSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48636 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:0/VID param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48636</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:0/VID parameter in the SetVLANSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48637 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:1/VID param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48637</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:1/VID parameter in the SetVLANSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48638 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SubnetMask paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48638</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SubnetMask parameter in the SetGuestZoneRouterSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49235 | WordPress Contact Forms, Live Support, CRM, Video Messages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49235</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in VideoWhisper.Com Contact Forms, Live Support, CRM, Video Messages allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Contact Forms, Live Support, CRM, Video Messages: from n/a through 1.10.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49284 | WordPress WP SendFox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49284</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in BogdanFix WP SendFox allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects WP SendFox: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49285 | WordPress SSV MailChimp plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49285</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Moridrin SSV MailChimp allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects SSV MailChimp: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49291 | WordPress Cooked Pro plugin &amp;lt; 1.8.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49291</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Gora Tech LLC Cooked Pro.This issue affects Cooked Pro: from n/a before 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49305 | WordPress Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPFactory Email Verification for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Email Verification for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.8.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49314 | WordPress JiangQie Free Mini Program plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49314</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in 酱茄 JiangQie Free Mini Program allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects JiangQie Free Mini Program: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49287 | WordPress PDF-Rechnungsverwaltung plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49287</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Marco Heine PDF-Rechnungsverwaltung allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PDF-Rechnungsverwaltung: from n/a through 0.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49312 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49312</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge.This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49317 | WordPress Point Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49317</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ZIPANG Point Maker allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Point Maker: from n/a through 0.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49318 | WordPress My Reading Library plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49318</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Scott Olson My Reading Library allows Object Injection.This issue affects My Reading Library: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49400 | Tacquito prior to commit 07b49d1358e6ec0b5aa482fcd284f509191119e2 was not properly performing regex matches on authorized commands and argum...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49400</link><description>Tacquito prior to commit 07b49d1358e6ec0b5aa482fcd284f509191119e2 was not properly performing regex matches on authorized commands and arguments. Configured allowed commands/arguments were intended to require a match on the entire string, but instead only enforced a match on a sub-string. That would have potentially allowed unauthorized commands to be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10072 | ESAFENET CDG EncryptPolicyService.java actionAddEncryptPolicyGroup sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10072</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This issue affects the function actionAddEncryptPolicyGroup of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/EncryptPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument checklist leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10073 | flairNLP flair Mode File Loader clustering.py ClusteringModel code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10073</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in flairNLP flair 0.14.0. Affected is the function ClusteringModel of the file flair\models\clustering.py of the component Mode File Loader. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48192 | Tenda G3 v15.01.0.5(2848_755)_EN was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc_ro/shadow, which allows attackers to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48192</link><description>Tenda G3 v15.01.0.5(2848_755)_EN was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc_ro/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49396 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49396</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable due to insufficiently protected credentials, which may allow an attacker to impersonate Elvaco and send false information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49397 | Cross-site Scripting in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49397</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting attack which may allow an attacker to bypass authentication and takeover admin accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49398 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49398</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to unrestricted file uploads, which may allow an attacker to remotely execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49399 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49399</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to an attacker being able to use commands without providing a password which may allow an attacker to leak information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10071 | ESAFENET CDG EncryptPolicyService.java actionUpdateEncryptPolicyEdit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10071</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This vulnerability affects the function actionUpdateEncryptPolicyEdit of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/EncryptPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument encryptPolicyId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9414 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in LCDS LAquis SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9414</link><description>In LAquis SCADA version 4.7.1.511, a cross-site scripting vulnerability could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary code into a web page. This could allow an attacker to steal cookies, redirect users, or perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25104 | CoinGate Plugin Payment callback.php postProcess logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25104</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CoinGate Plugin up to 1.2.7 on PrestaShop. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function postProcess of the file modules/coingate/controllers/front/callback.php of the component Payment Handler. The manipulation leads to business logic errors. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.8 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 0a3097db0aec7c5d66686c142c6abaa1e126ca16. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10069 | ESAFENET CDG MailDecryptApplicationService.java actionPassMainApplication sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10069</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function actionPassMainApplication of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/MailDecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10070 | ESAFENET CDG PolicyPushControlAction.java actionPolicyPush sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10070</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This affects the function actionPolicyPush of the file /com/esafenet/policy/action/PolicyPushControlAction.java. The manipulation of the argument policyId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47459 | Substance3D - Sampler | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47459</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS) condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48920 | PutongOJ: unprivileged users can escalate privileges by constructing requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48920</link><description>PutongOJ is online judging software. Prior to version 2.1.0-beta.1, unprivileged users can escalate privileges by constructing requests. This can lead to unauthorized access, enabling users to perform admin-level operations, potentially compromising sensitive data and system integrity. This problem has been fixed in v2.1.0.beta.1. As a workaround, one may apply the patch from commit `211dfe9` manually.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9683 | Quay: quay allows successful authentication with trucated version of the password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9683</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quay, which allows successful authentication even when a truncated password version is provided. This flaw affects the authentication mechanism, reducing the overall security of password enforcement.  While the risk is relatively low due to the typical length of the passwords used (73 characters), this vulnerability can still be exploited to reduce the complexity of brute-force or password-guessing attacks. The truncation of passwords weakens the overall authentication process, thereby reducing the effectiveness of password policies and potentially increasing the risk of unauthorized access in the future.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2005-10003 | mikexstudios Xcomic os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2005-10003</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in mikexstudios Xcomic up to 0.8.2. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.8.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 6ed8e3cc336e29f09c7e791863d0559939da98bf. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6333 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in Altalink, Versalink &amp;amp; WorkCentre Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6333</link><description>Authenticated Remote Code Execution in Altalink, Versalink &amp; WorkCentre Products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49315 | WordPress FREE DOWNLOAD MANAGER plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49315</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CodeFlock FREE DOWNLOAD MANAGER allows Path Traversal.This issue affects FREE DOWNLOAD MANAGER: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49579 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47197 insecure plugin iframe allowed arbitrary JavaScript execution and unauthorized API requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49579</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47197 insecure plugin iframe allowed arbitrary JavaScript execution and unauthorized API requests</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49580 | In JetBrains Ktor before 3.0.0 improper caching in HttpCache Plugin could lead to response information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49580</link><description>In JetBrains Ktor before 3.0.0 improper caching in HttpCache Plugin could lead to response information disclosure</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48021 | WordPress Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe Add-on plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48021</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scott Paterson Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp; Stripe Add-on allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp; Stripe Add-on: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6728 | Nokia SR OS: BOF File Encryption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6728</link><description>Nokia SR OS bof.cfg file encryption is vulnerable to a brute force attack. This weakness allows an attacker in possession of the encrypted file to decrypt the bof.cfg file and obtain the BOF configuration content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6729 | Nokia SR OS: File Access Security Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6729</link><description>Nokia SR OS routers allow read-write access to the entire file system via SFTP or SCP for users configured with "access console." Consequently, a low privilege authenticated user with "access console" can read or replace the router configuration file as well as other files stored in the Compact Flash or SD card without using CLI commands. This type of attack can lead to a compromise or denial of service of the router after the system is rebooted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48022 | WordPress Shortcode For Elementor Templates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48022</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SysBasics Shortcode For Elementor Templates allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Shortcode For Elementor Templates: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48023 | WordPress Restaurant Reservations Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48023</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RestaurantConnect, Inc Restaurant Reservations Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Restaurant Reservations Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48025 | WordPress Simple Baseball Scoreboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48025</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DOGROW.NET Simple Baseball Scoreboard allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Baseball Scoreboard: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48031 | WordPress Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48031</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sumit Surai Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG): from n/a through 4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48032 | WordPress Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48032</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sumit Surai Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG): from n/a through 4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48036 | WordPress SKT Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48036</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48037 | WordPress Contact Form Widget – Contact Query, Contact Page, Form Maker, Query Table plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48037</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in A WP Life Contact Form Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Contact Form Widget: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48046 | WordPress Contact Form by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.28 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48046</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Supsystic Contact Form by Supsystic allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Form by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.7.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48048 | WordPress Wsify Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48048</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WSIFY – Sales can fly Wsify Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Wsify Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48024 | WordPress Keep Backup Daily plugin &amp;lt;=2.0.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48024</link><description>: Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Keep Backup Daily allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Keep Backup Daily: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48038 | WordPress wp-Monalisa plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48038</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hans Matzen wp-Monalisa allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects wp-Monalisa: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48043 | WordPress ShortPixel Image Optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48043</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ShortPixel ShortPixel Image Optimizer allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects ShortPixel Image Optimizer: from n/a through 5.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48047 | WordPress Linked Variation for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48047</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Razon Komar Pal Linked Variation for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Linked Variation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49320 | WordPress Encyclopedia / Glossary / Wiki plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.60 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49320</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dennis Hoppe Encyclopedia / Glossary / Wiki allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Encyclopedia / Glossary / Wiki: from n/a through 1.7.60.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10068 | OpenSight Software FlashFXP FlashFXP.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10068</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSight Software FlashFXP 5.4.0.3970. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function in the library libcrypto-1_1.dll of the file FlashFXP.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45713 | SolarWinds Kiwi CatTools Sensitive Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45713</link><description>SolarWinds Kiwi CatTools is susceptible to a sensitive data disclosure vulnerability when a non-default setting has been enabled for troubleshooting purposes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9898 | Parallax Image &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via dd-parallax Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9898</link><description>The Parallax Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's dd-parallax shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10025 | Vulnerability in SICK CLV6xx, SICK Lector6xx and SICK RFx6xx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10025</link><description>A vulnerability in the .sdd file allows an attacker to read default passwords stored in plain text within the code. By exploiting these plaintext credentials, an attacker can log into affected SICK products as an “Authorized Client” if the customer has not changed the default password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49386 | Sensitive information disclosure due to spell-jacking. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49386</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure due to spell-jacking. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49389 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49389</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49390 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49390</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49391 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49391</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49392 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on enrollment invitation page. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Win...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49392</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on enrollment invitation page. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8920 | Fonto – Custom Web Fonts Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8920</link><description>The Fonto – Custom Web Fonts Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9184 | SendPulse Free Web Push &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9184</link><description>The SendPulse Free Web Push plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to incorrect use of the wp_kses_allowed_html function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3184 | Multiple CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerabilities were found in GoAhead Web Server up to version 6.0.0 when compiled with the ME_GOA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3184</link><description>Multiple CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerabilities were found in GoAhead Web Server up to version 6.0.0 when compiled with the ME_GOAHEAD_REPLACE_MALLOC flag. Without a memory notifier for allocation failures, remote attackers can exploit these vulnerabilities by sending malicious requests, leading to a crash and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3186 | CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the evalExpr() function of GoAhead Web Server (version &lt;= 6.0.0) when compiled with the ME...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3186</link><description>CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the evalExpr() function of GoAhead Web Server (version &lt;= 6.0.0) when compiled with the ME_GOAHEAD_JAVASCRIPT flag. This vulnerability allows a remote attacker with the privileges to modify JavaScript template (JST) files to trigger a crash and cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by providing malicious templates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3187 | This issue tracks two CWE-416 Use After Free (UAF) and one CWE-415 Double Free vulnerabilities in Goahead versions &lt;= 6.0.0. These are cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3187</link><description>This issue tracks two CWE-416 Use After Free (UAF) and one CWE-415 Double Free vulnerabilities in Goahead versions &lt;= 6.0.0. These are caused by JST values not being nulled when freed during parsing of JST templates. If the ME_GOAHEAD_JAVASCRIPT flag is enabled, a remote attacker with the privileges to modify JavaScript template (JST) files could exploit this by providing malicious templates. This may lead to memory corruption, potentially causing a Denial of Service (DoS) or, in rare cases, code execution, though the latter is highly context-dependent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9951 | Wordpress Photo Album Plus &amp;lt;= 8.8.05.003 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9951</link><description>The WP Photo Album Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wppa-tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.05.003 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9213 | Persian WooCommerce SMS &amp;lt;= 7.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9213</link><description>The افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5429 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.1.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5429</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.1.0 does not validate and escape some of its Slider Settings before outputting them back in attributes, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9351 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.35.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Draft Quiz Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9351</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.35.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the quiz 'create_module' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create draft quizzes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9352 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.35.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Draft Custom Form Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9352</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.35.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the custom form 'create_module' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create draft forms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49593 | In Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) before 6.3.9 and Secure Custom Fields before 6.3.6.3 (plugins for WordPress), using the Field Group editor t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49593</link><description>In Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) before 6.3.9 and Secure Custom Fields before 6.3.6.3 (plugins for WordPress), using the Field Group editor to edit one of the plugin's fields can result in execution of a stored XSS payload. NOTE: if you wish to use the WP Engine alternative update mechanism for the free version of ACF, then you can follow the process shown at the advancedcustomfields.com blog URL within the References section below.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 04:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7417 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.986 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Private Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7417</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.986 via the data_fetch. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to extract data from password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8719 | Flexmls® IDX Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.22 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8719</link><description>The Flexmls® IDX Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters like 'MaxBeds' and 'MinBeds' in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9263 | WP Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking Calendar and Online Scheduling Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.25 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password/Email Reset/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9263</link><description>The WP Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking Calendar and Online Scheduling Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.25 via the save() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the emails and passwords of arbitrary user accounts, including administrators, which makes account takeover and privilege escalation possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9347 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9347</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpext-export' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45766 | Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45766</link><description>Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45767 | Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45767</link><description>Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9215 | Co-Authors, Multiple Authors and Guest Authors in an Author Box with PublishPress Authors &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary User Email Update and Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9215</link><description>The Co-Authors, Multiple Authors and Guest Authors in an Author Box with PublishPress Authors plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference to Privilege Escalation/Account Takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.1 via the action_edited_author() due to missing validation on the 'authors-user_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to update arbitrary user accounts email addresses, including administrators, which can then be leveraged to reset that user's account password and gain access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9240 | ReDi Restaurant Reservation &amp;lt;= 24.0902 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9240</link><description>The ReDi Restaurant Reservation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 24.0902. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9861 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9861</link><description>The Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This is due to missing validation on the token being supplied during the otp login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they know the phone number associated with that user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9862 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9862</link><description>The Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change in versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This is due to the plugin providing user-controlled access to objects, letting a user bypass authorization and access system resources, and the user current password check is missing. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9863 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Privilege Escalation via Registration due to Administrator Default User Role Value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9863</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 3.6.0 due to the insecure 'administrator' default value for the 'default_user_role' option. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an administrator user even if the registration form is disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9940 | Calculated Fields Form &amp;lt;= 5.2.45 - HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9940</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.45. This is due to the plugin not properly neutralizing HTML elements from submitted forms. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary HTML that will render when the administrator views form submissions in their email.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7993 | Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk Revit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7993</link><description>A maliciously crafted PDF file, when parsed through Autodesk Revit, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 22:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7994 | Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in Autodesk Revit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7994</link><description>A maliciously crafted RFA file, when parsed through Autodesk Revit, can force a Stack-Based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 22:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48918 | Lack of Input Validation in RDS Light - Potential for Injection Attacks and Memory Tampering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48918</link><description>RDS Light is a simplified version of the Reflective Dialogue System (RDS), a self-reflecting AI framework. Versions prior to 1.1.0 contain a vulnerability that involves a lack of input validation within the RDS AI framework, specifically within the user input handling code in the main module (`main.py`). This leaves the framework open to injection attacks and potential memory tampering. Any user or external actor providing input to the system could exploit this vulnerability to inject malicious commands, corrupt stored data, or affect API calls. This is particularly critical for users employing RDS AI in production environments where it interacts with sensitive systems, performs dynamic memory caching, or retrieves user-specific data for analysis. Impacted areas include developers using the RDS AI system as a backend for AI-driven applications and systems running RDS AI that may be exposed to untrusted environments or receive unverified user inputs. The vulnerability has been patched in version 1.1.0 of the RDS AI framework. All user inputs are now sanitized and validated against a set of rules designed to mitigate malicious content. Users should upgrade to version 1.1.0 or higher and ensure all dependencies are updated to their latest versions. For users unable to upgrade to the patched version, a workaround can be implemented. The user implementing the workaround should implement custom validation checks for user inputs to filter out unsafe characters and patterns (e.g., SQL injection attempts, script injections) and limit or remove features that allow user input until the system can be patched.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 21:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44762 | A discrepancy in error messages for invalid login attempts in Webmin Usermin v2.100 allows attackers to enumerate valid user accounts.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44762</link><description>A discrepancy in error messages for invalid login attempts in Webmin Usermin v2.100 allows attackers to enumerate valid user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47889 | Action Mailer has possible ReDoS vulnerability in block_format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47889</link><description>Action Mailer is a framework for designing email service layers. Starting in version 3.0.0 and prior to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, and 7.2.1.1, there is a possible ReDoS vulnerability in the block_format helper in Action Mailer. Carefully crafted text can cause the block_format helper to take an unexpected amount of time, possibly resulting in a DoS vulnerability. All users running an affected release should either upgrade to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, or 7.2.1.1 or apply the relevant patch immediately. As a workaround, users can avoid calling the `block_format` helper or upgrade to Ruby 3.2. Ruby 3.2 has mitigations for this problem, so Rails applications using Ruby 3.2 or newer are unaffected. Rails 8.0.0.beta1 requires Ruby 3.2 or greater so is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48180 | ClassCMS &lt;=4.8 is vulnerable to file inclusion in the nowView method in/class/cms/cms.php, which can include a file uploaded to the/class/te...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48180</link><description>ClassCMS &lt;=4.8 is vulnerable to file inclusion in the nowView method in/class/cms/cms.php, which can include a file uploaded to the/class/template directory to execute PHP code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48758 | dingfanzu CMS V1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the addPro parameter of the component doAdminAction.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48758</link><description>dingfanzu CMS V1.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the addPro parameter of the component doAdminAction.php which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46212 | An issue in the component /index.php?page=backup/export of REDAXO CMS v5.17.1 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46212</link><description>An issue in the component /index.php?page=backup/export of REDAXO CMS v5.17.1 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46213 | REDAXO CMS v2.11.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46213</link><description>REDAXO CMS v2.11.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47888 | Action Text has possible ReDoS vulnerability in plain_text_for_blockquote_node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47888</link><description>Action Text brings rich text content and editing to Rails. Starting in version 6.0.0 and prior to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, and 7.2.1.1, there is a possible ReDoS vulnerability in the `plain_text_for_blockquote_node helper` in Action Text. Carefully crafted text can cause the `plain_text_for_blockquote_node` helper to take an unexpected amount of time, possibly resulting in a DoS vulnerability. All users running an affected release should either upgrade to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, or 7.2.1.1 or apply the relevant patch immediately. As a workaround, users can avoid calling `plain_text_for_blockquote_node` or upgrade to Ruby 3.2. Ruby 3.2 has mitigations for this problem, so Rails applications using Ruby 3.2 or newer are unaffected. Rails 8.0.0.beta1 depends on Ruby 3.2 or greater so is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47887 | Action Controller has possible ReDoS vulnerability in HTTP Token authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47887</link><description>Action Pack is a framework for handling and responding to web requests. Starting in version 4.0.0 and prior to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, and 7.2.1.1, there is a possible ReDoS vulnerability in Action Controller's HTTP Token authentication. For applications using HTTP Token authentication via `authenticate_or_request_with_http_token` or similar, a carefully crafted header may cause header parsing to take an unexpected amount of time, possibly resulting in a DoS vulnerability. All users running an affected release should either upgrade to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, or 7.2.1.1 or apply the relevant patch immediately. One may choose to use Ruby 3.2 as a workaround.Ruby 3.2 has mitigations for this problem, so Rails applications using Ruby 3.2 or newer are unaffected. Rails 8.0.0.beta1 depends on Ruby 3.2 or greater so is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 20:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47522 | Suricata ja4: invalid alpn leads to panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47522</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to version 7.0.7, invalid ALPN in TLS/QUIC traffic when JA4 matching/logging is enabled can lead to Suricata aborting with a panic. This issue has been addressed in 7.0.7. One may disable ja4 as a workaround.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 19:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47836 | Admidio vulnerable to HTML Injection In The Messages Section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47836</link><description>Admidio is an open-source user management solution. Prior to version 4.3.12, an unsafe deserialization vulnerability allows any unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the server. Version 4.3.12 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 19:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47188 | Suricata http/byte-ranges: missing hashtable random seed leads to potential DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47188</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to version 7.0.7, missing initialization of the random seed for "thash" leads to byte-range tracking having predictable hash table behavior. This can lead to an attacker forcing lots of data into a single hash bucket, leading to severe performance degradation. This issue has been addressed in 7.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 19:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47187 | Suricata datasets: missing hashtable random seed leads to potential DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47187</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to version 7.0.7, missing initialization of the random seed for "thash" leads to datasets having predictable hash table behavior. This can lead to dataset file loading to use excessive time to load, as well as runtime performance issues during traffic handling. This issue has been addressed in 7.0.7. As a workaround, avoid loading datasets from untrusted sources. Avoid dataset rules that track traffic in rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 19:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45796 | Suricata defrag: off by one can lead to policy bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45796</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to version 7.0.7, a logic error during fragment reassembly can lead to failed reassembly for valid traffic. An attacker could craft packets to trigger this behavior.This issue has been addressed in 7.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 18:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45797 | LibHTP&amp;#x27;s unbounded header handling leads to denial service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45797</link><description>LibHTP is a security-aware parser for the HTTP protocol and the related bits and pieces. Prior to version 0.5.49, unbounded processing of HTTP request and response headers can lead to excessive CPU time and memory utilization, possibly leading to extreme slowdowns. This issue is addressed in 0.5.49.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 18:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45795 | Suricata detect/datasets: reachable assertion with unimplemented rule option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45795</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to version 7.0.7, rules using datasets with the non-functional / unimplemented "unset" option can trigger an assertion during traffic parsing, leading to denial of service. This issue is addressed in 7.0.7. As a workaround, use only trusted and well tested rulesets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41128 | Action Dispatch has possible ReDoS vulnerability in query parameter filtering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41128</link><description>Action Pack is a framework for handling and responding to web requests. Starting in version 3.1.0 and prior to versions 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, and 7.2.1.1, there is a possible ReDoS vulnerability in the query parameter filtering routines of Action Dispatch. Carefully crafted query parameters can cause query parameter filtering to take an unexpected amount of time, possibly resulting in a DoS vulnerability. All users running an affected release should either upgrade to version 6.1.7.9, 7.0.8.5, 7.1.4.1, or 7.2.1.1 or apply the relevant patch immediately. One may use Ruby 3.2 as a workaround. Ruby 3.2 has mitigations for this problem, so Rails applications using Ruby 3.2 or newer are unaffected. Rails 8.0.0.beta1 depends on Ruby 3.2 or greater so is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9143 | Low-level invalid GF(2^m) parameters lead to OOB memory access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9143</link><description>Issue summary: Use of the low-level GF(2^m) elliptic curve APIs with untrusted
explicit values for the field polynomial can lead to out-of-bounds memory reads
or writes.

Impact summary: Out of bound memory writes can lead to an application crash or
even a possibility of a remote code execution, however, in all the protocols
involving Elliptic Curve Cryptography that we're aware of, either only "named
curves" are supported, or, if explicit curve parameters are supported, they
specify an X9.62 encoding of binary (GF(2^m)) curves that can't represent
problematic input values. Thus the likelihood of existence of a vulnerable
application is low.

In particular, the X9.62 encoding is used for ECC keys in X.509 certificates,
so problematic inputs cannot occur in the context of processing X.509
certificates.  Any problematic use-cases would have to be using an "exotic"
curve encoding.

The affected APIs include: EC_GROUP_new_curve_GF2m(), EC_GROUP_new_from_params(),
and various supporting BN_GF2m_*() functions.

Applications working with "exotic" explicit binary (GF(2^m)) curve parameters,
that make it possible to represent invalid field polynomials with a zero
constant term, via the above or similar APIs, may terminate abruptly as a
result of reading or writing outside of array bounds.  Remote code execution
cannot easily be ruled out.

The FIPS modules in 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 17:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10033 | Aap-gateway: xss on aap-gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10033</link><description>A vulnerability was found in aap-gateway. A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the gateway component. This flaw allows a malicious user to perform actions that impact users by using the "?next=" in a URL, which can lead to redirecting, injecting malicious script, stealing sessions and data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 17:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38814 | An authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in VMware HCX was privately reported to VMware. A
 malicious authenticated user with non-admini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38814</link><description>An authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in VMware HCX was privately reported to VMware. A
 malicious authenticated user with non-administrator privileges may be 
able to enter specially crafted SQL queries and perform unauthorized 
remote code execution on the HCX manager. 
Updates are available to remediate this vulnerability in affected VMware products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 17:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46605 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /admin.php?page=album of Piwigo v14.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46605</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /admin.php?page=album of Piwigo v14.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Description field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 17:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46606 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /admin.php?page=photo of Piwigo v14.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46606</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /admin.php?page=photo of Piwigo v14.5.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Description field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 17:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4184 | Multiple XXE sinks in ALM archive post-build step in OpenText Application Automation Tools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4184</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in OpenText Application Automation Tools allows DTD Injection.This issue affects OpenText Application Automation Tools: 24.1.0 and below.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4189 | Multiple XXE sinks in Run LoadRunner script step in OpenText Application Automation Tools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4189</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in OpenText Application Automation Tools allows DTD Injection.This issue affects OpenText Application Automation Tools: 24.1.0 and below.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4211 | Multiple missing permission checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4211</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Application Automation Tools allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.


Multiple missing permission checks - ALM job config has been discovered in OpenText Application Automation Tools. The vulnerability could allow users with Overall/Read permission to enumerate ALM server names, usernames and client IDs configured to be used with ALM servers.


This issue affects OpenText Application Automation Tools: 24.1.0 and below.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4690 | Insecure usage for DocumentBuilderFactory and TransformerFactory in OpenText Application Automation Tools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4690</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in OpenText Application Automation Tools allows DTD Injection.This issue affects OpenText Application Automation Tools: 24.1.0 and below.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4692 | Multiple missing permission checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4692</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Application Automation Tools allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.


Multiple missing permission checks - Service Virtualization config has been discovered in in OpenText Application Automation Tools. The vulnerability could allow users with Overall/Read permission to enumerate Service Virtualization server names.

This issue affects OpenText Application Automation Tools: 24.1.0 and below.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32266 | Code injection vulnerability found in OpenText Application Lifecycle Management (ALM),Quality Center.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32266</link><description>Untrusted Search Path vulnerability in OpenText™ Application Lifecycle Management (ALM),Quality Center allows Code Inclusion. The vulnerability allows a user to archive a malicious DLLs on the system prior to the installation.  

This issue affects Application Lifecycle Management (ALM),Quality Center: 15.00, 15.01, 15.01 P1, 15.01 P2, 15.01 P3, 15.01 P4, 15.01 P5, 15.51, 15.51 P1, 15.51 P2, 15.51 P3, 16.00, 16.01 P1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20280 | Cisco UCS Central Software Configuration Backup Static Key Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20280</link><description>A vulnerability in the backup feature of Cisco UCS Central Software could allow an attacker with access to a backup file to learn sensitive information that is stored in the full state and configuration backup files.

This vulnerability is due to a weakness in the encryption method that is used for the backup function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a backup file and leveraging a static key that is used for the backup configuration feature. A successful exploit could allow an attacker with access to a backup file to learn sensitive information that is stored in full state backup files and configuration backup files, such as local user credentials, authentication server passwords, Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) community names, and the device SSL server certificate and key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20420 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Firmware Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20420</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to run commands as an Admin user. 

This vulnerability is due to incorrect authorization verification by the HTTP server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run commands as the Admin user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20421 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Firmware Cross-Site Request Forgery Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20421</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20458 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Software Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20458</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view or delete the configuration or change the firmware on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of authentication on specific HTTP endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a specific URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view or delete the configuration or change the firmware.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20459 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Muliplatform Firmware Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20459</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Multiplatform Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with high privileges to execute arbitrary commands as the root user on the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of input sanitization in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20460 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Firmware Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20460</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user&amp;nbsp;to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20461 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Firmware Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20461</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI&amp;nbsp;of Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.

This vulnerability exists because CLI input is not properly sanitized. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious characters to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write to the underlying operating system as the root user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20462 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Muliplatform Firmware Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20462</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Series Multiplatform Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to view passwords on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect sanitization of HTML content from an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view passwords that belong to other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20463 | Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter Firmware Command Injection and Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20463</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ATA 190 Series Analog Telephone Adapter firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to modify the configuration or reboot an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to the HTTP server allowing state changes in GET requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to the web-based management interface on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make limited modifications to the configuration or reboot the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20512 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Management Portal Reflected  Cross-Site  Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20512</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Contact Center Management Portal (Unified CCMP) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45071 | IBM WebSphere Application Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45071</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45072 | IBM WebSphere Application Server XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45072</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A privileged user could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29155 | Denial of service on Microchip RN4870 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29155</link><description>On Microchip RN4870 devices, when more than one consecutive PairReqNoInputNoOutput request is 
received, the device becomes incapable of completing the pairing 
process. A third party can inject a second PairReqNoInputNoOutput request 
just after a real one, causing the pair request to be blocked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 15:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49265 | WordPress Booking.com Banner Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49265</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Partnerships at Booking.Com Booking.Com Banner Creator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Booking.Com Banner Creator: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 15:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9348 | Docker Desktop before v4.34.3 allows RCE via unsanitized GitHub source link in Build view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9348</link><description>Docker Desktop before v4.34.3 allows RCE via unsanitized GitHub source link in Build view.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49266 | WordPress WP-Spreadplugin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49266</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Thimo Grauerholz WP-Spreadplugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-Spreadplugin: from n/a through 4.8.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49267 | WordPress Unlimited Addon For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;=2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49267</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nayon46 Unlimited Addon For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Unlimited Addon For Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49268 | WordPress disconnected theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49268</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sunburntkamel disconnected allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects disconnected: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45844 | BIG-IP monitors vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45844</link><description>BIG-IP monitor functionality may allow an attacker to bypass access control restrictions, regardless of the port lockdown settings.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47139 | F5 BIG-IQ Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47139</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IQ Configuration utility that allows an attacker with the Administrator role to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48744 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /trms/listed- teachers.php in PHPGurukul Teachers Record Management System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48744</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /trms/listed- teachers.php in PHPGurukul Teachers Record Management System v2.1, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "searchinput" POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9893 | Nextend Social Login Pro &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9893</link><description>The Nextend Social Login Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.14. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32189 | Insecure handling SSH key in SUSE Manager when bootstrapping new clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32189</link><description>Insecure handling of ssh keys used to bootstrap clients allows local attackers to potentially gain access to the keys</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49252 | WordPress leyka plugin &amp;lt;= 3.31.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49252</link><description>: Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Teplitsa of social technologies Leyka.This issue affects Leyka: from n/a through 3.31.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49270 | WordPress Smart Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49270</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HashThemes Smart Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Smart Blocks: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22033 | obs-service-download_url is vulnerable to argument injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22033</link><description>The OBS service obs-service-download_url was vulnerable to a command injection vulnerability. The attacker could provide a configuration to the service that allowed to execute command in later steps</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22034 | Crafted projects can overwrite special files in the .osc config directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22034</link><description>Attackers could put the special files in .osc into the actual package sources (e.g. _apiurl). This allows the attacker to change the configuration of osc for the victim</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48034 | WordPress Creates 3D Flipbook, PDF Flipbook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48034</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Fliperrr Team Creates 3D Flipbook, PDF Flipbook allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Creates 3D Flipbook, PDF Flipbook: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49216 | WordPress Feed Comments Number plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49216</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Joshua Clayton Feed Comments Number allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Feed Comments Number: from n/a through 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:55:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49245 | WordPress Ahime Image Printer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49245</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Ahime Ahime Image Printer.This issue affects Ahime Image Printer: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49258 | WordPress Limb Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49258</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Limb WordPress Gallery Plugin – Limb Image Gallery.This issue affects WordPress Gallery Plugin – Limb Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47351 | WordPress MaxSlider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47351</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in The CSSIgniter Team MaxSlider allows Path Traversal.This issue affects MaxSlider: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47645 | WordPress WPOptin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47645</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Sajid Javed Top Bar – PopUps – by WPOptin allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Top Bar – PopUps – by WPOptin: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48029 | WordPress SB Random Posts Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48029</link><description>: Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Hung Trang Si SB Random Posts Widget allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects SB Random Posts Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49242 | WordPress Digital Lottery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49242</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Shafiq Digital Lottery allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Digital Lottery: from n/a through 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49260 | WordPress Limb Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49260</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Limb WordPress Gallery Plugin – Limb Image Gallery allows Code Injection.This issue affects WordPress Gallery Plugin – Limb Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22029 | tomcat packaging allows for escalation to root from tomcat user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22029</link><description>Insecure permissions in the packaging of tomcat allow local users that win a race during package installation to escalate to root</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22030 | Rancher agents can be hijacked by taking over the Rancher Server URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22030</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Rancher that can be exploited
 in narrow circumstances through a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack. An 
attacker would need to have control of an expired domain or execute a 
DNS spoofing/hijacking attack against the domain to exploit this 
vulnerability. The targeted domain is the one used as the Rancher URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22032 | Rancher&amp;#x27;s RKE1 Encryption Config kept in plain-text within cluster AppliedSpec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22032</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in which an RKE1 cluster keeps 
constantly reconciling when secrets encryption configuration is enabled.
 When reconciling, the Kube API secret values are written in plaintext 
on the AppliedSpec. Cluster owners, Cluster members, and Project members
 (for projects within the cluster), all have RBAC permissions to view 
the cluster object from the apiserver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48026 | WordPress Disc Golf Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48026</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Grayson Robbins Disc Golf Manager allows Object Injection.This issue affects Disc Golf Manager: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48028 | WordPress IP Loc8 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48028</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Boyan Raichev IP Loc8 allows Object Injection.This issue affects IP Loc8: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48030 | WordPress Telecash Ricaricaweb plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48030</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Gabriele Valenti Telecash Ricaricaweb allows Object Injection.This issue affects Telecash Ricaricaweb: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49218 | WordPress Recently plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49218</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Al Imran Akash Recently allows Object Injection.This issue affects Recently: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49226 | WordPress TAKETIN To WP Membership plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49226</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in TAKETIN TAKETIN To WP Membership allows Object Injection.This issue affects TAKETIN To WP Membership: from n/a through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49227 | WordPress Free Stock Photos Foter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49227</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Innovaweb Sp. Z o.O. Free Stock Photos Foter allows Object Injection.This issue affects Free Stock Photos Foter: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49251 | WordPress  Maan Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49251</link><description>: Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Maantheme Maan Addons For Elementor allows Local Code Inclusion.This issue affects Maan Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47637 | WordPress LiteSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.1 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47637</link><description>: Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in LiteSpeed Technologies LiteSpeed Cache allows Path Traversal.This issue affects LiteSpeed Cache: from n/a through 6.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47649 | WordPress Iconize plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47649</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in THATplugin Iconize.This issue affects Iconize: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48027 | WordPress External featured image from bing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48027</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in xaraartech External featured image from bing allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects External featured image from bing: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48035 | WordPress ACF Images Search And Insert plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48035</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Takayuki Imanishi ACF Images Search And Insert allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects ACF Images Search And Insert: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49253 | WordPress Analyse Uploads plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49253</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in James Park Analyse Uploads allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Analyse Uploads: from n/a through 0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49254 | WordPress ajax-extend plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49254</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Sunjianle allows Code Injection.This issue affects ajax-extend: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32194 | Rancher permissions on &amp;#x27;namespaces&amp;#x27; in any API group grants &amp;#x27;edit&amp;#x27; permissions on namespaces in &amp;#x27;core&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32194</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified when granting a create or * global role for a resource type of "namespaces"; no matter the API group, the subject will receive *
 permissions for core namespaces. This can lead to someone being capable
 of accessing, creating, updating, or deleting a namespace in the 
project.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32196 | Rancher&amp;#x27;s External RoleTemplates can lead to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32196</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified whereby privilege escalation checks are not properly enforced for RoleTemplateobjects when external=true, which in specific scenarios can lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10023 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System add_new_medicine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10023</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /php/add_new_medicine.php. The manipulation of the argument name/packing/generic_name/suppliers_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10024 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_medicine_stock.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10024</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /php/manage_medicine_stock.php. The manipulation of the argument name/packing/generic_name/suppliers_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48042 | WordPress Contact Form by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.28 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48042</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine vulnerability in Supsystic Contact Form by Supsystic allows Command Injection.This issue affects Contact Form by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.7.28.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49257 | WordPress Azz Anonim Posting plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49257</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Denis Azz Anonim Posting allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Azz Anonim Posting: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49271 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.121 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49271</link><description>: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) allows : Command Injection.This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.121.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36841 | WooCommerce Smart Coupons &amp;lt;= 4.6.0 - Unauthenticated Coupon Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36841</link><description>The WooCommerce Smart Coupons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on the woocommerce_coupon_admin_init function in versions up to, and including, 4.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send themselves gift certificates of any value, which could be redeemed for products sold on the victim’s storefront.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49247 | WordPress BuddyPress Better Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49247</link><description>: Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in sooskriszta, webforza BuddyPress Better Registration allows : Authentication Bypass.This issue affects BuddyPress Better Registration: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32191 | rke&amp;#x27;s credentials are stored in the RKE1 Cluster state ConfigMap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32191</link><description>When RKE provisions a cluster, it stores the cluster state in a configmap called `full-cluster-state` inside the `kube-system` namespace of the cluster itself. The information available in there allows non-admin users to escalate to admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 12:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32192 | Rancher API Server Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32192</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in which unauthenticated cross-site 
scripting (XSS) in the API Server's public API endpoint can be 
exploited, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim browser</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 12:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32193 | Norman API Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32193</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in which unauthenticated cross-site 
scripting (XSS) in Norman's public API endpoint can be exploited. This 
can lead to an attacker exploiting the vulnerability to trigger 
JavaScript code and execute commands remotely.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 12:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32190 | mlocate&amp;#x27;s %post script allows RUN_UPDATEDB_AS user to make arbitrary files world readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32190</link><description>mlocate's %post script allows RUN_UPDATEDB_AS user to make arbitrary files world readable by abusing insecure file operations that run with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10021 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_purchase.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10021</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /php/manage_purchase.php?action=search&amp;amp;tag=VOUCHER_NUMBER. The manipulation of the argument text leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10022 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System manage_supplier.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10022</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /php/manage_supplier.php?action=search. The manipulation of the argument text leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 12:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6380 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6380</link><description>A reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 11:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8040 | Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8040</link><description>An authorization bypass through user-controlled key vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an authenticated attacker to access some unauthorized data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 11:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8921 | Zita Elementor Site Library &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8921</link><description>The Zita Elementor Site Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 11:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9444 | ElementsReady Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 6.4.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9444</link><description>The ElementsReady Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 09:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9858 | Insecure user permissions in Google Cloud Migrate to Containers for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9858</link><description>There exists an insecure default user permission in Google Cloud Migrate to containers from version 1.1.0 to 1.2.2 Windows installs. A local "m2cuser" was greated with administrator privileges. This posed a security risk if the "analyze" or "generate" commands were interrupted or skipping the action to delete the local user “m2cuser”. We recommend upgrading to 1.2.3 or beyond</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32188 | JWT token compromise can allow malicious actions including Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32188</link><description>A user can reverse engineer the JWT token (JSON Web Token) used in authentication for Manager and API access, forging a valid NeuVector Token to perform malicious activity in NeuVector. This can lead to an RCE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22650 | Rancher does not automatically clean up a user deleted or disabled from the configured Authentication Provider</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22650</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in which Rancher does not automatically clean up a user which has been deleted from the configured authentication provider (AP). This characteristic also applies to disabled or revoked users, Rancher will not reflect these modifications which may leave the user’s tokens still usable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45216 | Apache Solr: Authentication bypass possible using a fake URL Path ending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45216</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Solr.

Solr instances using the PKIAuthenticationPlugin, which is enabled by default when Solr Authentication is used, are vulnerable to Authentication bypass.
A fake ending at the end of any Solr API URL path, will allow requests to skip Authentication while maintaining the API contract with the original URL Path.
This fake ending looks like an unprotected API path, however it is stripped off internally after authentication but before API routing.


This issue affects Apache Solr: from 5.3.0 before 8.11.4, from 9.0.0 before 9.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.7.0, or 8.11.4, which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45217 | Apache Solr: ConfigSets created during a backup restore command are trusted implicitly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45217</link><description>Insecure Default Initialization of Resource vulnerability in Apache Solr.

New ConfigSets that are created via a Restore command, which copy a configSet from the backup and give it a new name, are created without setting the "trusted" metadata.
ConfigSets that do not contain the flag are trusted implicitly if the metadata is missing, therefore this leads to "trusted" ConfigSets that may not have been created with an Authenticated request.
"trusted" ConfigSets are able to load custom code into classloaders, therefore the flag is supposed to only be set when the request that uploads the ConfigSet is Authenticated &amp; Authorized.

This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.6.0 before 8.11.4, from 9.0.0 before 9.7.0. This issue does not affect Solr instances that are secured via Authentication/Authorization.

Users are primarily recommended to use Authentication and Authorization when running Solr. However, upgrading to version 9.7.0, or 8.11.4 will mitigate this issue otherwise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45219 | Apache CloudStack: Uploaded and registered templates and volumes can be used to abuse KVM-based infrastructure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45219</link><description>Account users in Apache CloudStack by default are allowed to upload and register templates for deploying instances and volumes for attaching them as data disks to their existing instances. Due to missing validation checks for KVM-compatible templates or volumes in CloudStack 4.0.0 through 4.18.2.3 and 4.19.0.0 through 4.19.1.1, an attacker that can upload or register templates and volumes, can use them to deploy malicious instances or attach uploaded volumes to their existing instances on KVM-based environments and exploit this to gain access to the host filesystems that could result in the compromise of resource integrity and confidentiality, data loss, denial of service, and availability of KVM-based infrastructure managed by CloudStack.


Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache CloudStack 4.18.2.4 or 4.19.1.2, or later, which addresses this issue. 

Additionally, all user-uploaded or registered KVM-compatible templates and volumes can be scanned and checked that they are flat files that should not be using any additional or unnecessary features. For example, operators can run this on their secondary storage(s) and inspect output. An empty output for the disk being validated means it has no references to the host filesystems; on the other hand, if the output for the disk being validated is not empty, it might indicate a compromised disk.


for file in $(find /path/to/storage/ -type f -regex [a-f0-9\-]*.*); do echo "Retrieving file [$file] info. If the output is not empty, that might indicate a compromised disk; check it carefully."; qemu-img info -U $file | grep file: ; printf "\n\n"; done
The command can also be run for the file-based primary storages; however, bear in mind that (i) volumes created from templates will have references for the templates at first and (ii) volumes can be consolidated while migrating, losing their references to the templates. Therefore, the command execution for the primary storages can show both false positives and false negatives.

For checking the whole template/volume features of each disk, operators can run the following command:


for file in $(find /path/to/storage/ -type f -regex [a-f0-9\-]*.*); do echo "Retrieving file [$file] info."; qemu-img info -U $file; printf "\n\n"; done</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45461 | Apache CloudStack Quota plugin: Access checks not enforced in Quota</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45461</link><description>The CloudStack Quota feature allows cloud administrators to implement a quota or usage limit system for cloud resources, and is disabled by default. In environments where the feature is enabled, due to missing access check enforcements, non-administrative CloudStack user accounts are able to access and modify quota-related configurations and data. This issue affects Apache CloudStack from 4.7.0 through 4.18.2.3; and from 4.19.0.0 through 4.19.1.1, where the Quota feature is enabled.




Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache CloudStack 4.18.2.4 or 4.19.1.2, or later, which addresses this issue. Alternatively, users that do not use the Quota feature are advised to disabled the plugin by setting the global setting "quota.enable.service" to "false".</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45462 | Apache CloudStack: Incomplete session invalidation on web interface logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45462</link><description>The logout operation in the CloudStack web interface does not expire the user session completely which is valid until expiry by time or restart of the backend service. An attacker that has access to a user's browser can use an unexpired session to gain access to resources owned by the logged out user account. This issue affects Apache CloudStack from 4.15.1.0 through 4.18.2.3; and from 4.19.0.0 through 4.19.1.1.




Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache CloudStack 4.18.2.4 or 4.19.1.2, or later, which addresses this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45693 | Apache CloudStack: Request origin validation bypass makes account takeover possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45693</link><description>Users logged into the Apache CloudStack's web interface can be tricked to submit malicious CSRF requests due to missing validation of the origin of the requests. This can allow an attacker to gain privileges and access to resources of the authenticated users and may lead to account takeover, disruption, exposure of sensitive data and compromise integrity of the resources owned by the user account that are managed by the platform.

This issue affects Apache CloudStack from 4.15.1.0 through 4.18.2.3 and 4.19.0.0 through 4.19.1.1



Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache CloudStack 4.18.2.4 or 4.19.1.2, or later, which addresses this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22649 | Rancher &amp;#x27;Audit Log&amp;#x27; leaks sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22649</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified which may lead to sensitive data being leaked into Rancher's audit logs. [Rancher Audit Logging](https://ranchermanager.docs.rancher.com/how-to-guides/advanced-user-guides/enable-api-audit-log) is an opt-in feature, only deployments that have it enabled and have [AUDIT_LEVEL](https://ranchermanager.docs.rancher.com/how-to-guides/advanced-user-guides/enable-api-audit-log#audit-log-levels) set to `1 or above` are impacted by this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15042 | Frontend File Manager &amp;lt; 4.0 &amp;amp; N-Media Post Front-end Form &amp;lt; 1.1 &amp;amp; - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15042</link><description>The Frontend File Manager (versions &lt; 4.0), N-Media Post Front-end Form (versions &lt; 1.1) plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation via the `nm_filemanager_upload_file` and `nm_postfront_upload_file` AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected sites server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20193 | Product Vendors &amp;lt;= 2.0.35 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20193</link><description>The Product Vendors is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'vendor_description' parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.0.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20194 | Formidable Form Builder &amp;lt; 2.05.03 - Unauthenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20194</link><description>The Formidable Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure in versions up to, and including, 2.05.03 via the frm_forms_preview AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export all of the form entries for a given form.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36840 | Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36840</link><description>The Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on the wp_ajax_route_url() function called via a nopriv AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 2.3.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call that function and perform a wide variety of actions such as including random template, injecting malicious web scripts, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36842 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid &amp;lt;= 0.9.35 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36842</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability check on the wpvivid_upload_import_files and wpvivid_upload_files AJAX actions that allows low-level authenticated attackers to upload zip files that can be subsequently extracted. This affects versions up to, and including 0.9.35.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4452 | Google Language Translator &amp;lt;= 6.0.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4452</link><description>The Google Language Translator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters in versions up to, and including, 6.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Specifically affects users with older browsers that lack proper URL encoding support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7295 | Video Grid &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7295</link><description>The Video Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search_term parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7296 | BigBlueButton &amp;lt;= 3.0.0-beta.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7296</link><description>The BigBlueButton plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the the moderator code and viewer code fields in versions up to, and including, 3.0.0-beta.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with author privileges or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45711 | SolarWinds Serv-U FTP Service Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45711</link><description>SolarWinds Serv-U is vulnerable  to a directory traversal  vulnerability where remote code execution is possible depending on privileges given to the authenticated user.  This issue requires a user to be authenticated and this is present when software environment variables are abused. Authentication is required for this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45714 | SolarWinds Serv-U  Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45714</link><description>Application is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) an authenticated attacker with users’ permissions can modify a variable with a payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9061 | WP Popup Builder – Popup Forms and Marketing Lead Generation &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via wp_ajax_nopriv_shortcode_Api_Add</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9061</link><description>The The WP Popup Builder – Popup Forms and Marketing Lead Generation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via the wp_ajax_nopriv_shortcode_Api_Add AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 1.3.5 with a nonce check, which effectively prevented access to the affected function. However, version 1.3.6 incorporates the correct authorization check to prevent unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9540 | Sina Extension for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Sina Modal Box Widget Elementor Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9540</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.7 via the render function in widgets/advanced/sina-modal-box.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft Elementor template data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45710 | SolarWinds Platform Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45710</link><description>SolarWinds Platform is susceptible to an Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. This requires a low privilege account and local access to the affected node machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45715 | SolarWinds Platform Edit Function Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45715</link><description>The SolarWinds Platform was susceptible to a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability when performing an edit function to existing elements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10018 | Mapplic Lite and Mapplic &amp;lt;= (Various Versions) - Server Side Request Forgery to Cross-Site Scirpting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10018</link><description>The Mapplic and Mapplic Lite plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in versions up to, and including 6.1, 1.0 respectively. This makes it possible for attackers to forgery requests coming from a vulnerable site's server and ultimately perform an XSS attack if requesting an SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15040 | Kento Post View Counter &amp;lt;= 2.8 - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15040</link><description>The Kento Post View Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'kento_pvc_geo' parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15041 | MainWP Dashboard – The Private WordPress Manager for Multiple Website Maintenance Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15041</link><description>The MainWP Dashboard – The Private WordPress Manager for Multiple Website Maintenance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘mwp_setup_purchase_username’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20192 | Formidable Form Builder &amp;lt; 2.05.03 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20192</link><description>The Formidable Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters submitted during form entries like 'after_html' in versions before 2.05.03 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25105 | File Manager &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload/Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25105</link><description>The  File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check in the /inc/root.php file in versions up to, and including, 3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary files from the server and upload arbitrary files that can be used for remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25213 | Advanced Access Manager &amp;lt;= 5.9.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25213</link><description>The Advanced Access Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read in versions up to, and including, 5.9.8.1 due to insufficient validation on the aam-media parameter. This allows unauthenticated attackers to read any file on the server, including sensitive files such as wp-config.php</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25214 | ShopWP &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25214</link><description>The ShopWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on several REST API routes in versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call the endpoints and perform unauthorized actions such as updating the plugin's settings and injecting malicious scripts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25215 | ARI-Adminer &amp;lt;= 1.1.14 - Missing Authorization and No Direct File Access Restrictions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25215</link><description>The ARI-Adminer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a lack of file access controls in nearly every file of the plugin in versions up to, and including, 1.1.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call the files directly and perform a wide variety of unauthorized actions such as accessing a site's database and making changes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25216 | Rich Reviews &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25216</link><description>The Rich Review plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the POST body 'update' parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25217 | SiteGround Optimizer &amp;lt;= 5.0.12 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25217</link><description>The SiteGround Optimizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass leading to Remote Code Execution and Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 5.0.12 due to incorrect use of an access control attribute on the switch_php function called via the /switch-php REST API route. This allows attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36831 | NextScripts: Social Networks Auto-Poster &amp;lt;= 4.3.17 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36831</link><description>The NextScripts: Social Networks Auto-Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks on multiple user privilege/security functions provided in versions up to, and including 4.3.17. This makes it possible for low-privileged attackers, like subscribers, to perform restricted actions that would be otherwise locked to a administrative-level user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36832 | Indeed Membership Pro 7.3 - 8.6 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36832</link><description>The Ultimate Membership Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in versions between, and including, 7.3 to 8.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to login as any user, including the site administrator with a default user ID of 1, via the username or user ID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36833 | Indeed Membership Pro 7.3 - 8.6 - Missing Authorization Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36833</link><description>The Indeed Membership Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks on various AJAX actions in versions 7.3 - 8.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attacker, with minimal permission, such as a subscriber, to perform a variety of actions such as modifying settings and viewing sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36834 | Discount Rules for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36834</link><description>The Discount Rules for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to missing authorization via several AJAX actions in versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to missing capability checks on various functions. This makes it possible for subscriber-level attackers to execute various actions and perform a wide variety of actions such as modifying rules and saving configurations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36835 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid &amp;lt;= 0.9.35 - Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36835</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure of a WordPress site's database due to missing capability checks on the wp_ajax_wpvivid_add_remote AJAX action that allows low-level authenticated attackers to send back-ups to a remote location of their choice for review. This affects versions up to, and including 0.9.35.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36836 | WP Fastest Cache &amp;lt;= 0.9.0.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36836</link><description>The WP Fastest Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary file deletion in versions up to, and including, 0.9.0.2 due to a lack of capability checking and insufficient path validation. This makes it possible for authenticated users with minimal permissions to delete arbitrary files from the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36837 | ThemeGrill Demo Importer 1.3.4 - 1.6.1 - Authorization Bypass to Site Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36837</link><description>The ThemeGrill Demo Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to a missing capability check on the reset_wizard_actions function in versions 1.3.4 through 1.6.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to reset the WordPress database. After which, if there is a user named 'admin', the attacker will become automatically logged in as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36838 | Facebook Chat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Missing Capabilities Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36838</link><description>The Facebook Chat Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on the wp_ajax_update_options function in versions up to, and including, 1.5. This flaw makes it possible for low-level authenticated attackers to connect their own Facebook Messenger account to any site running the vulnerable plugin and engage in chats with site visitors on affected sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36839 | WP Lead Plus X &amp;lt;= 0.99 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36839</link><description>The WP Lead Plus X plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 0.99. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform administrative actions, such as adding pages to the site and/or replacing site content with malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4443 | WordPress Mega Menu &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Arbitrary File Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4443</link><description>The WordPress Mega Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Creation in versions up to, and including, 2.0.6 via the compiler_save AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary PHP files that can be used to execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4444 | Product Filter by WooBeWoo &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4444</link><description>The Product Filter by WooBeWoo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including 1.4.9 due to missing authorization checks on various functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform unauthorized actions such as creating new filters and injecting malicious javascript into a vulnerable site. This was actively exploited at the time of discovery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4445 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.5.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4445</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary Option Updates in versions up to, and including, 4.5.1. This is due to missing capability and nonce checks in the pa_dismiss_admin_notice AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated subscriber+ attackers to change arbitrary options with a restricted value of 1 on vulnerable WordPress sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4446 | Essential Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.6.4 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4446</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to and including 4.6.4 due to missing capability checks and nonce disclosure. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as a subscriber, to perform many unauthorized actions such as changing settings and installing arbitrary plugins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4447 | Essential Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4447</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor  plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to and including 4.6.4 due to a lack of restrictions on who can add a registration form and a custom registration role to an Elementor created page. This makes it possible for attackers with access to the Elementor page builder to create a new registration form that defaults to the user role being set to administrator and subsequently register as an administrative user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4448 | Kaswara Modern VC Addons &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4448</link><description>The Kaswara Modern VC Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient capability checking on various AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform a wide variety of unauthorized actions such as importing data, uploading arbitrary files, deleting arbitrary files, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4449 | ZoomSounds &amp;lt;= 5.96 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4449</link><description>The ZoomSounds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'savepng.php' file in versions up to, and including, 5.96. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4450 | Post Grid &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Contributor+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4450</link><description>The Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via post metadata in versions up to, and including, 2.1.12 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level permissions and above to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4451 | NinjaFirewall &amp;lt;= 4.3.3 - Authenticated PHAR Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4451</link><description>The NinjaFirewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authenticated PHAR Deserialization in versions up to, and including, 4.3.3. This allows authenticated attackers to perform phar deserialization on the server.  This deserialization can allow other plugin or theme exploits if vulnerable software is present (WordPress, and NinjaFirewall).</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4971 | Sassy Social Share &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4971</link><description>The Sassy Social Share plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'urls' parameter called via the 'heateor_sss_sharing_count' AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 3.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4972 | Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 4.7.51 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Data Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4972</link><description>The Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on several REST-API routes related to reporting in versions up to, and including, 4.7.51. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view user data and other sensitive information intended for administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4973 | WordPress Core &amp;lt; 6.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via use of the_meta(); function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4973</link><description>WordPress Core, in versions up to 6.0.2, is vulnerable to Authenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting that can be exploited by users with access to the WordPress post and page editor, typically consisting of Authors, Contributors, and Editors making it possible to inject arbitrary web scripts into posts and pages that execute if the the_meta(); function is called on that page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4974 | Freemius SDK &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Missing Authorization Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4974</link><description>The Freemius SDK, as used by hundreds of WordPress plugin and theme developers, was vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery and Information disclosure due to missing capability checks and nonce protection on the _get_debug_log, _get_db_option, and the _set_db_option functions in versions up to, and including 2.4.2. Any WordPress plugin or theme running a version of Freemius less than 2.4.3 is vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7286 | ACF Quick Edit Fields &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7286</link><description>The plugin ACF Quick Edit Fields for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for attackers without the edit_users capability to access metadata of other users, this includes contributor-level users and above.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7287 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;pt_cancel_subscription&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7287</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized subscription cancellation due to a missing capability check on the pt_cancel_subscription function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to cancel a subscription to the plugin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7288 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;update_profile_preference&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7288</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the update_profile_preference function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to change plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7289 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;paytium_sw_save_api_keys&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7289</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized API key update due to a missing capability check on the paytium_sw_save_api_keys function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to change plugin API keys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7290 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;check_for_verified_profiles&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7290</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the check_for_verified_profiles function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to check profile statuses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7291 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;create_mollie_account&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7291</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the create_mollie_account function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to set up a mollie account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7292 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;paytium_notice_dismiss&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7292</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized notification dismissal due to a missing capability check on the paytium_notice_dismiss function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to dismiss admin notices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7293 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;check_mollie_account_details&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7293</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the check_mollie_account_details function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to verify the existence of a mollie account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7294 | Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp;amp; donations &amp;lt;= 4.3.7 - Missing Authorization in &amp;#x27;create_mollie_profile&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7294</link><description>The Paytium: Mollie payment forms &amp; donations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the create_mollie_profile function in versions up to, and including, 4.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to create a mollie payment profile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8507 | File Manager Pro &amp;lt;= 8.3.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8507</link><description>The File Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'mk_file_folder_manager' ajax action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8746 | File Manager Pro &amp;lt;= 8.3.9 - Unauthenticated Backup File Download and Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8746</link><description>The File Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary backup file downloads and uploads due to missing file type validation via the 'mk_file_folder_manager_shortcode' ajax action in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers, if granted access to the File Manager by an administrator, to download and upload arbitrary backup files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8918 | File Manager Pro &amp;lt;= 8.3.9 - Unauthenticated Limited JavaScript File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8918</link><description>The File Manager Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Limited JavaScript File Upload in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.9. This is due to a lack of proper checks on allowed file types. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers, with permissions granted by an administrator, to upload .css and .js files, which could lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9582 | Accordion Slider &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Authenticted (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9582</link><description>The Accordion Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘html’ attribute of an accordion slider in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: Successful exploitation by Contributor-level users requires an Administrator-level user to provide access to the plugin's admin area via the `Access` plugin setting, which is restricted to administrators by default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 06:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9873 | Community by PeepSo &amp;lt;= 6.4.6.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9873</link><description>The Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles, Premium – Mobile App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URLs in posts, comments, and profiles when Markdown support is enabled in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 05:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9888 | ElementInvader Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9888</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's contact form widget redirect URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 05:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9937 | Woo Manage Fraud Orders &amp;lt;= 6.1.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9937</link><description>The Woo Manage Fraud Orders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 05:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10018 | Improper permission control in the mobile application (com.transsion.aivoiceassistant) can lead to the launch of any unexported component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10018</link><description>Improper permission control in the mobile application (com.transsion.aivoiceassistant) can lead to the launch of any unexported component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 03:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8541 | Discount Rules for WooCommerce – Create Smart WooCommerce Coupons &amp;amp; Discounts, Bulk Discount, BOGO Coupons &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8541</link><description>The Discount Rules for WooCommerce – Create Smart WooCommerce Coupons &amp; Discounts, Bulk Discount, BOGO Coupons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note that this is only exploitable when the 'Leave a Review' notice is present, which occurs after 100 orders are made and disappears after a user dismisses the notice.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8787 | Smart Online Order for Clover &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8787</link><description>The Smart Online Order for Clover plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9104 | UltimateAI &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 - Limited User Password Change due to Improper Empty and Missing Default Value Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9104</link><description>The UltimateAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3. This is due to the improper empty value check and a missing default activated value check in the 'ultimate_ai_change_pass' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the password of the first user, whose account is not yet activated or the first user who activated their account, who are subscribers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9105 | UltimateAI &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9105</link><description>The UltimateAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.8.3. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied in the 'ultimate_ai_register_or_login_with_google' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9305 | AppPresser – Mobile App Framework &amp;lt;= 4.4.4 - Privilege Escalation and Account Takeover via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9305</link><description>The AppPresser – Mobile App Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.4. This is due to the appp_reset_password() and validate_reset_password() functions not having enough controls to prevent a successful brute force attack of the OTP to change a password, or verify that a password reset request came from an authorized user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate and brute force an OTP that makes it possible to change any users passwords, including an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9521 | SEO Manager &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9521</link><description>The SEO Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via post meta in versions up to, and including, 1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9634 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.16.3 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9634</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.3 via deserialization of untrusted input from the give_company_name parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9647 | Kama SpamBlock &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9647</link><description>The Kama SpamBlock plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_POST values in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9649 | WP ULike &amp;lt;= 4.7.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Statistic Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9649</link><description>The WP ULike – The Ultimate Engagement Toolkit for Websites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wp_ulike_delete_history_api() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete engagements via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9652 | Locatoraid Store Locator &amp;lt;= 3.9.47 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9652</link><description>The Locatoraid Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_POST keys in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.47 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9891 | Multiline files upload for contact form 7 &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9891</link><description>The Multiline files upload for contact form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin deactivation due to a missing capability check on the mfcf7_zl_custom_handle_deactivation_plugin_form_submission() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to deactivate the plugin and send a custom reason from the site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 02:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49340 | IBM Watson Studio Local cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49340</link><description>IBM Watson Studio Local 1.2.3 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 01:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>