<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-2202 | Tenda AC8 httpd WifiGuestSet fromSetWifiGusetBasic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2202</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC8 16.03.33.05. Affected is the function fromSetWifiGusetBasic of the file /goform/WifiGuestSet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument shareSpeed results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2203 | Tenda AC8 Embedded Httpd Service fast_setting_wifi_set buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2203</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.33.05. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set of the component Embedded Httpd Service. This manipulation of the argument timeZone causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2210 | D-Link DIR-823X set_filtering sub_4211C8 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2210</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function sub_4211C8 of the file /goform/set_filtering. Such manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2200 | heyewei JFinalCMS API Endpoint save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2200</link><description>A weakness has been identified in heyewei JFinalCMS 5.0.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/admin/save of the component API Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2201 | ZeroWdd studentmanager LeaveController.java addLeave cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2201</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ZeroWdd studentmanager up to 2151560fc0a50ec00426785ec1e01a3763b380d9. This impacts the function addLeave of the file src/main/java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/LeaveController.java. The manipulation of the argument Reason for Leave leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2198 | code-projects Online Reviewer System loaddata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2198</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/loaddata.php. Such manipulation of the argument difficulty_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2199 | code-projects Online Reviewer System user-delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2199</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /reviewer/system/system/admins/manage/users/user-delete.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2196 | code-projects Online Reviewer System exam-update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/exam-update.php. The manipulation of the argument test_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2197 | code-projects Online Reviewer System exam-delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2197</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/exam-delete.php. This manipulation of the argument test_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2194 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 start_proxy_client_email command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2194</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DI-7100G C1 24.04.18D1. This affects the function start_proxy_client_email. Executing a manipulation can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2195 | code-projects Online Reviewer System questions-view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2195</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/questions-view.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2192 | Tenda AC9 formGetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2192</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC9 15.03.06.42_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formGetRebootTimer. Such manipulation of the argument sys.schedulereboot.start_time/sys.schedulereboot.end_time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2193 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 set_jhttpd_info command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2193</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DI-7100G C1 24.04.18D1. Affected by this issue is the function set_jhttpd_info. Performing a manipulation of the argument usb_username results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2190 | itsourcecode School Management System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2190</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/user/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2191 | Tenda AC9 formGetDdosDefenceList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2191</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC9 15.03.06.42_multi. Affected is the function formGetDdosDefenceList. This manipulation of the argument security.ddos.map causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2189 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2189</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/report/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ay leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2188 | UTT 进取 521G formPdbUpConfig sub_446B18 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2188</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 进取 521G 3.1.1-190816. The impacted element is the function sub_446B18 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Executing a manipulation of the argument policyNames can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2186 | Tenda RX3 SetIpMacBind fromSetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2186</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Impacted is the function fromSetIpMacBind of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. Such manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2187 | Tenda RX3 formSetQosBand set_qosMib_list stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. The affected element is the function set_qosMib_list of the file /goform/formSetQosBand. Performing a manipulation of the argument list results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2184 | Great Developers Certificate Generation System csv.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2184</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Great Developers Certificate Generation System up to 97171bb0e5e22e52eacf4e4fa81773e5f3cffb73. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /restructured/csv.php. The manipulation of the argument photo results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2185 | Tenda RX3 MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint setBlackRule set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2185</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. This issue affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument devName/mac causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2182 | UTT 进取 521G setSysAdm doSystem command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2182</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 进取 521G 3.1.1-190816. Affected by this issue is the function doSystem of the file /goform/setSysAdm. Executing a manipulation of the argument passwd1 can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2183 | Great Developers Certificate Generation System csv.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2183</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Great Developers Certificate Generation System up to 97171bb0e5e22e52eacf4e4fa81773e5f3cffb73. This affects an unknown part of the file /restructured/csv.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2179 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2179</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-users.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2180 | Tenda RX3 fast_setting_wifi_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2180</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. Such manipulation of the argument ssid_5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2181 | Tenda RX3 openSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2181</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. Performing a manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2176 | code-projects Contact Management System index.py sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2176</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Contact Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.py. Such manipulation of the argument selecteditem[0] leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2177 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Login session fixiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2177</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Login. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2178 | r-huijts xcode-mcp-server run_lldb index.ts registerXcodeTools command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2178</link><description>A vulnerability was found in r-huijts xcode-mcp-server up to f3419f00117aa9949e326f78cc940166c88f18cb. This affects the function registerXcodeTools of the file src/tools/xcode/index.ts of the component run_lldb. The manipulation of the argument args results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The patch is identified as 11f8d6bacadd153beee649f92a78a9dad761f56f. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2173 | code-projects Online Examination System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2173</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2174 | code-projects Contact Management System CRUD Endpoint improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2174</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Contact Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component CRUD Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authentication. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2175 | D-Link DIR-823X set_upnp sub_420618 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2175</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420618 of the file /goform/set_upnp. This manipulation of the argument upnp_enable causes os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2171 | code-projects Online Student Management System Login accounts.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2171</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Student Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file accounts.php of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument username/password results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2172 | code-projects Online Application System for Admission Login Endpoint index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2172</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Application System for Admission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file enrollment/index.php of the component Login Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2168 | D-Link DWR-M921 formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel sub_419920 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2168</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. This affects the function sub_419920 of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel. This manipulation of the argument fota_url causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2169 | D-Link DWR-M921 formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2169</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. This impacts an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom. Such manipulation of the argument fota_url leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2166 | code-projects Online Reviewer System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2166</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /login/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2167 | Totolink WA300 cstecgi.cgi setAPNetwork os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2167</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Totolink WA300 5.2cu.7112_B20190227. The impacted element is the function setAPNetwork of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument Ipaddr results in os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2163 | D-Link DIR-600 ssdp.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2163</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-600 up to 2.15WWb02. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ssdp.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument HTTP_ST/REMOTE_ADDR/REMOTE_PORT/SERVER_ID leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2164 | detronetdip E-commerce addadhar.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2164</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in detronetdip E-commerce 1.0.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /seller/assets/backend/profile/addadhar.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2165 | detronetdip E-commerce Account Creation Endpoint add_seller.php missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2165</link><description>A weakness has been identified in detronetdip E-commerce 1.0.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Admin/assets/backend/seller/add_seller.php of the component Account Creation Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument email can lead to missing authentication. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2161 | itsourcecode Directory Management System forget-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2161</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Directory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/forget-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2162 | itsourcecode News Portal Project aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2162</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/aboutus.php. This manipulation of the argument pagetitle causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2159 | SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website Registration Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2159</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tourism/classes/Master.php?f=register of the component Registration. Executing a manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/username can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2160 | SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2160</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tourism/classes/Master.php?f=save_package. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2157 | D-Link DIR-823X set_static_route_table sub_4175CC os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2157</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function sub_4175CC of the file /goform/set_static_route_table. Such manipulation of the argument interface/destip/netmask/gateway/metric leads to os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2158 | code-projects Student Web Portal check_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2158</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Student Web Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /check_user.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2156 | code-projects Online Student Management System Announcement Management index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2156</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/announcement/index.php?view=add of the component Announcement Management Module. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2155 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration set_dmz sub_4208A0 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2155</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is the function sub_4208A0 of the file /goform/set_dmz of the component Configuration Handler. The manipulation of the argument dmz_host/dmz_enable results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2154 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System Patient Registration registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2154</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /registration.php of the component Patient Registration Module. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2153 | mwielgoszewski doorman views.py is_safe_url redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2153</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in mwielgoszewski doorman up to 0.6. This issue affects the function is_safe_url of the file doorman/users/views.py. Executing a manipulation of the argument Next can lead to open redirect. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2152 | D-Link DIR-615 Web Configuration adv_routing.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2152</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file adv_routing.php of the component Web Configuration Interface. Performing a manipulation of the argument dest_ip/ submask/ gw results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2151 | D-Link DIR-615 DMZ Host Feature adv_firewall.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2151</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This affects an unknown part of the file adv_firewall.php of the component DMZ Host Feature. Such manipulation of the argument dmz_ipaddr  leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2150 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System checkin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2150</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /checkin.php. This manipulation of the argument patient_id causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2149 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System appointments.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2149</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /appointments.php. The manipulation of the argument patient_id results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2148 | Tenda AC21 Web Management DownloadFlash information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2148</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/DownloadFlash of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2147 | Tenda AC21 Web Management DownloadLog information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2147</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This impacts an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/DownloadLog of the component Web Management Interface. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2146 | guchengwuyue yshopmall co.yixiang.utils.FileUtil updateAvatar unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2146</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in guchengwuyue yshopmall up to 1.9.1. This affects the function updateAvatar of the file /api/users/updateAvatar of the component co.yixiang.utils.FileUtil. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2145 | cym1102 nginxWebUI Web Management check cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2145</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 4.3.7. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /adminPage/conf/check of the component Web Management Interface. Such manipulation of the argument nginxDir leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2143 | D-Link DIR-823X DDNS Service set_ddns os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2143</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/set_ddns of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation of the argument ddnsType/ddnsDomainName/ddnsUserName/ddnsPwd leads to os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2142 | D-Link DIR-823X set_qos sub_420688 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2142</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420688 of the file /goform/set_qos. Executing a manipulation can lead to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2141 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM URL PermissionServiceImpl.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2141</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM up to 11.3.3. This affects an unknown part of the file gateway/src/main/java/com/kakarote/gateway/service/impl/PermissionServiceImpl.java of the component URL Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2140 | Tenda TX9 setMacFilterCfg sub_4223E0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2140</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4223E0 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg. Such manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2139 | Tenda TX9 fast_setting_wifi_set sub_432580 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2139</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_432580 of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2138 | Tenda TX9 SetStaticRouteCfg sub_42D03C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected is the function sub_42D03C of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2137 | Tenda TX3 SetIpMacBind buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda TX3 up to 16.03.13.11_multi. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2136 | projectworlds Online Food Ordering System view-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2136</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectworlds Online Food Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /view-ticket.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2134 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-doctors.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /hms/admin/manage-doctors.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2135 | UTT HiPER 810 formPdbUpConfig sub_43F020 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_43F020 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument policyNames results in command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2132 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2132</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument txtcat results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2133 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2133</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. This manipulation of the argument txtimage causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2130 | BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret search_username index.ts command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2130</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret up to 1.0.12. This affects an unknown part of the file src/index.ts of the component search_username. Executing a manipulation of the argument Username can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.13 is able to mitigate this issue. This patch is called b1ae073c4b3e789ab8de36dc6ca8111ae9399e7a. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2131 | XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server input_text os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2131</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server 0.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function input_text. The manipulation of the argument text leads to os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15027 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15027</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15100 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via jay_panel_ajax_update_profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15100</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_panel_ajax_update_profile' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2129 | D-Link DIR-823X set_ac_status os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/set_ac_status. Performing a manipulation of the argument ac_ipaddr/ac_ipstatus/ap_randtime results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2205 | WeKan Meteor Publication cards.js CardPubSubBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2205</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This affects an unknown part of the file server/publications/cards.js of the component Meteor Publication Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to mitigate this issue. The name of the patch is 0f5a9c38778ca550cbab6c5093470e1e90cb837f. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2206 | WeKan Administrative Repair fixDuplicateLists.js FixDuplicateBleed access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2206</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WeKan up to 8.20. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file server/methods/fixDuplicateLists.js of the component Administrative Repair Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to resolve this issue. The patch is named 4ce181d17249778094f73d21515f7f863f554743. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2207 | WeKan Activity Publication activities.js LinkedBoardActivitiesBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2207</link><description>A weakness has been identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file server/publications/activities.js of the component Activity Publication Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is capable of addressing this issue. This patch is called 91a936e07d2976d4246dfe834281c3aaa87f9503. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2208 | WeKan Rules rules.js RulesBleed authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2208</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in WeKan up to 8.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file server/publications/rules.js of the component Rules Handler. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is recommended to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is a787bcddf33ca28afb13ff5ea9a4cb92dceac005. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2209 | WeKan Custom Translation translationBody.js setCreateTranslation improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2209</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in WeKan up to 8.18. The affected element is the function setCreateTranslation of the file client/components/settings/translationBody.js of the component Custom Translation Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 8.19 is sufficient to fix this issue. The patch is identified as f244a43771f6ebf40218b83b9f46dba6b940d7de. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2120 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration Parameter set_server_settings os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2120</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/set_server_settings of the component Configuration Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument terminal_addr/server_ip/server_port leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2122 | Xiaopi Panel WAF Firewall demo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2122</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Xiaopi Panel up to 20260126. This impacts an unknown function of the file /demo.php of the component WAF Firewall. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2118 | UTT HiPER 810 rehttpd formReleaseConnect sub_4407D4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2118</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_4407D4 of the file /goform/formReleaseConnect of the component rehttpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument Isp_Name can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2117 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_activity.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument activity_id results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:02:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2116 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_expenses.php. Such manipulation of the argument expenses_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 23:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2115 | itsourcecode Society Management System delete_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2115</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete_expenses.php. This manipulation of the argument expenses_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25859 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.20 Migration Functionality Insufficient Permission Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25859</link><description>Wekan versions prior to 8.20 allow non-administrative users to access migration functionality due to insufficient permission checks, potentially resulting in unauthorized migration operations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2114 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2114</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25560 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 LDAP Authentication Filter Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25560</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an LDAP filter injection vulnerability in LDAP authentication. User-supplied username input is incorporated into LDAP search filters and DN-related values without adequate escaping, allowing an attacker to manipulate LDAP queries during authentication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25561 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Attachment Upload Object Relationship Validation Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25561</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization weakness in the attachment upload API. The API does not fully validate that provided identifiers (such as boardId, cardId, swimlaneId, and listId) are consistent and refer to a coherent card/board relationship, enabling attempts to upload attachments with mismatched object relationships.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25562 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Attachments Publication Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25562</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an information disclosure vulnerability in the attachments publication. Attachment metadata can be returned without properly scoping results to boards and cards accessible to the requesting user, potentially exposing attachment metadata to unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25563 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Checklist Creation Cross-Board IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25563</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in checklist creation and related checklist routes. The implementation does not verify that the supplied cardId belongs to the supplied boardId, allowing cross-board ID tampering by manipulating identifiers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25564 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Checklist Deletion IDOR via Missing Relationship Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25564</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in checklist creation and related checklist routes. The implementation does not verify that the supplied cardId belongs to the supplied boardId, allowing cross-board ID tampering by manipulating identifiers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25565 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Read-only Board Roles Can Update Cards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25565</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization vulnerability where certain card update API paths validate only board read access rather than requiring write permission. This can allow users with read-only roles to perform card updates that should require write access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25566 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Cross-board Card Move Without Destination Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25566</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization vulnerability in card move logic. A user can specify a destination board/list/swimlane without adequate authorization checks for the destination and without validating that destination objects belong to the destination board, potentially enabling unauthorized cross-board moves.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25567 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Card Comment Author Spoofing via User-controlled authorId</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25567</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in the card comment creation API. The endpoint accepts an authorId from the request body, allowing an authenticated user to spoof the recorded comment author by supplying another user's identifier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25568 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 allowPrivateOnly Setting Enforcement Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25568</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization logic vulnerability where the instance configuration setting allowPrivateOnly is not sufficiently enforced at board creation time. When allowPrivateOnly is enabled, users can still create public boards due to incomplete server-side enforcement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25857 | Tenda G300-F Command Injection via formSetWanDiag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25857</link><description>Tenda G300-F router firmware versio 16.01.14.2 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the WAN diagnostic functionality (formSetWanDiag). The implementation constructs a shell command that invokes curl and incorporates attacker-controlled input into the command line without adequate neutralization. As a result, a remote attacker with access to the affected management interface can inject additional shell syntax and execute arbitrary commands on the device with the privileges of the management process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25858 | macrozheng mall &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 Unauthenticated Password Reset via OTP Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25858</link><description>macrozheng mall version 1.0.3 and prior contains an authentication vulnerability in the mall-portal password reset workflow that allows an unauthenticated attacker to reset arbitrary user account passwords using only a victim’s telephone number. The password reset flow exposes the one-time password (OTP) directly in the API response and validates password reset requests solely by comparing the provided OTP to a value stored by telephone number, without verifying user identity or ownership of the telephone number. This enables remote account takeover of any user with a known or guessable telephone number.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15564 | Mapnik value.cpp operator divide by zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15564</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Mapnik up to 4.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function mapnik::detail::mod&lt;...&gt;::operator of the file src/value.cpp. The manipulation leads to divide by zero. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2113 | yuan1994 tpadmin WebUploader preview.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2113</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yuan1994 tpadmin up to 1.3.12. This affects an unknown part in the library /public/static/admin/lib/webuploader/0.1.5/server/preview.php of the component WebUploader. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2111 | JeecgBoot Retrieval-Augmented Generation edit path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2111</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /airag/knowledge/doc/edit of the component Retrieval-Augmented Generation Module. Executing a manipulation of the argument filePath can lead to path traversal. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2110 | Tasin1025 SwiftBuy login.php excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2110</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tasin1025 SwiftBuy up to 0f5011372e8d1d7edfd642d57d721c9fadc54ec7. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. Performing a manipulation results in improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2109 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Delete Category undo improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2109</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in jsbroks COCO Annotator up to 0.11.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/undo/ of the component Delete Category Handler. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2108 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Endpoint long_task denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2108</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jsbroks COCO Annotator up to 0.11.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file /api/info/long_task of the component Endpoint. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2107 | yeqifu warehouse Log Info LoginfoController.java batchDeleteLoginfo improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function loadAllLoginfo/deleteLoginfo/batchDeleteLoginfo of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\LoginfoController.java of the component Log Info Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2106 | yeqifu warehouse Notice Management NoticeController.java batchDeleteNotice improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. The impacted element is the function addNotice/updateNotice/deleteNotice/batchDeleteNotice of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\NoticeController.java of the component Notice Management. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2105 | yeqifu warehouse Department Management DeptController.java deleteDept improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2105</link><description>A flaw has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. The affected element is the function addDept/updateDept/deleteDept of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\DeptController.java of the component Department Management. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2090 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2090</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/message/search.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument term can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2089 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2089</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/subject/controller.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2088 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System accepted-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2088</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/accepted-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument delid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2087 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2087</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. This manipulation of the argument user_email causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2086 | UTT HiPER 810G Management formFireWall strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2086</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formFireWall of the component Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument GroupName results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2085 | D-Link DWR-M921 USSD Configuration Endpoint formUSSDSetup sub_419F20 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2085</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. Affected is the function sub_419F20 of the file /boafrm/formUSSDSetup of the component USSD Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ussdValue leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2084 | D-Link DIR-823X set_language os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2084</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/set_language. Executing a manipulation of the argument langSelection can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2083 | code-projects Social Networking Site delete_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2083</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Social Networking Site 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /delete_post.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2082 | D-Link DIR-823X set_mac_clone os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2082</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_mac_clone. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2081 | D-Link DIR-823X set_password os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2081</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_password. This manipulation of the argument http_passwd causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2080 | UTT HiPER 810 formUser setSysAdm command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2080</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. This issue affects the function setSysAdm of the file /goform/formUser. The manipulation of the argument passwd1 leads to command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15476 | The Bucketlister &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Bucket List Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15476</link><description>The The Bucketlister plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the bucketlister_do_admin_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add delete or modify arbitrary bucket list items.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15477 | The Bucketlister &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via `category` and `id` Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15477</link><description>The Bucketlister plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode `category` and `id` attributes in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameters and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0555 | Premmerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;premmerce_wizard_actions&amp;#x27; AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0555</link><description>The Premmerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'premmerce_wizard_actions' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.20. This is due to missing capability checks and insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the `state` parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page (the Premmerce Wizard admin page).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1082 | TITLE ANIMATOR &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1082</link><description>The TITLE ANIMATOR plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings page form handler in `inc/settings-page.php`. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1570 | Simple Bible Verse via Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1570</link><description>The Simple Bible Verse via Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `verse` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1573 | OMIGO &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1573</link><description>The OMIGO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `omigo_donate_button` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1608 | Video Onclick &amp;lt;= 0.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1608</link><description>The Video Onclick plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `youtube` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1611 | Wikiloops Track Player &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1611</link><description>The Wikiloops Track Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `wikiloops` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1613 | Wonka Slide &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1613</link><description>The Wonka Slide plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `list_class` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1634 | Subitem AL Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1634</link><description>The Subitem AL Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1643 | MP-Ukagaka &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1643</link><description>The MP-Ukagaka plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1675 | Advanced Country Blocker &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Unauthenticated Authorization Bypass via Insecure Default Secret Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1675</link><description>The Advanced Country Blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authorization Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to the use of a predictable default value for the secret bypass key created during installation without requiring users to change it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the geolocation blocking mechanism by appending the key to any URL on sites where the administrator has not changed the default value.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2079 | yeqifu warehouse Menu Management MenuController.java deleteMenu improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2079</link><description>A flaw has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This vulnerability affects the function addMenu/updateMenu/deleteMenu of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\MenuController.java of the component Menu Management. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2078 | yeqifu warehouse Permission Management PermissionController.java deletePermission improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2078</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function addPermission/updatePermission/deletePermission of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\PermissionController.java of the component Permission Management. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2077 | yeqifu warehouse Role Management RoleController.java deleteRole improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2077</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected by this issue is the function addRole/updateRole/deleteRole of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\RoleController.java of the component Role Management Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2076 | yeqifu warehouse User Management Endpoint UserController.java deleteUser improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2076</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function addUser/updateUser/deleteUser of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\UserController.java of the component User Management Endpoint. This manipulation causes improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15491 | Post Slides &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Contributor+ Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15491</link><description>The Post Slides WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not validate some shortcode attributes before using them to generate paths passed to include function/s, allowing any authenticated users such as with contributor or higher roles to perform LFI attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12159 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12159</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_raw_content shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12803 | Bold Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_tabs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12803</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin 'bt_bb_tabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13463 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting in Post Grid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13463</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Grid component in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15267 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_accordion_item Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15267</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_accordion_item shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2075 | yeqifu warehouse Role-Permission Binding RoleController.java saveRolePermission access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2075</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected is the function saveRolePermission of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\RoleController.java of the component Role-Permission Binding Handler. The manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2074 | O2OA HTTP POST Request check xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2074</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in O2OA up to 9.0.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /x_program_center/jaxrs/mpweixin/check of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31990 | HCL DevOps Velocity is susceptible to a Denial of Service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31990</link><description>Rate limiting for certain API calls is not being enforced, making HCL Velocity vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) attacks.  An attacker could flood the system with a large number of requests, overwhelming its resources and causing it to become unresponsive to legitimate users.  This vulnerability is fixed in 5.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2073 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2073</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/user/index.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2071 | UTT 进取 520W formP2PLimitConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2071</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formP2PLimitConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument except results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>