<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-2906 | Tenda HG9 Samba Configuration Endpoint formSamba stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2906</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boaform/formSamba of the component Samba Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument sambaCap results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2907 | Tenda HG9 GPON Configuration Endpoint formgponConf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2907</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boaform/formgponConf of the component GPON Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument fmgpon_loid/fmgpon_loid_password causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2908 | Tenda HG9 Loopback Detection Configuration Endpoint formLoopBack stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2908</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda HG9 300001138. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boaform/formLoopBack of the component Loopback Detection Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument Ethtype leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2909 | Tenda HG9 Diagnostic Ping Endpoint formPing stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2909</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda HG9 300001138. This affects an unknown part of the file /boaform/formPing of the component Diagnostic Ping Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument pingAddr results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2905 | Tenda HG9 Wireless Configuration Endpoint formWlanSetup stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2905</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda HG9 300001138. This impacts an unknown function of the file /boaform/formWlanSetup of the component Wireless Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2897 | funadmin Backend index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2897</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file app/backend/view/index/index.html of the component Backend Interface. The manipulation of the argument Value leads to cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2898 | funadmin Backend Endpoint AuthCloudService.php getMember deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2898</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This issue affects the function getMember of the file app/common/service/AuthCloudService.php of the component Backend Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument cloud_account results in deserialization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2903 | skvadrik re2c ast.cc check_and_merge_special_rules null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2903</link><description>A flaw has been found in skvadrik re2c up to 4.4. Impacted is the function check_and_merge_special_rules of the file src/parse/ast.cc. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. Patch name: febeb977936f9519a25d9fbd10ff8256358cdb97. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2904 | UTT HiPER 810G ConfigExceptAli strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2904</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810G 1.7.7-171114. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptAli. Executing a manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 02:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2896 | funadmin Configuration Ajax.php setConfig improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2896</link><description>A weakness has been identified in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. This affects the function setConfig of the file app/backend/controller/Ajax.php of the component Configuration Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2894 | funadmin forget.html getMember information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2894</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getMember of the file app/frontend/view/login/forget.html. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2895 | funadmin Member.php repass password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2895</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in funadmin up to 7.1.0-rc4. Affected by this issue is the function repass of the file app/frontend/controller/Member.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument forget_code/vercode results in weak password recovery. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2889 | CCExtractor mp4.c processmp4 use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2889</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CCExtractor up to 0.96.5. Affected is the function processmp4 in the library src/lib_ccx/mp4.c. Performing a manipulation results in use after free. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.96.6 is able to address this issue. The patch is named fd7271bae238ccb3ae8a71304ea64f0886324925. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 22:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2886 | Tenda A21 SetOnlineDevName set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2886</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. This manipulation of the argument devName causes stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2887 | aardappel lobster idents.h TypeName recursion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2887</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in aardappel lobster up to 2025.4. This impacts the function lobster::TypeName in the library dev/src/lobster/idents.h. Such manipulation leads to uncontrolled recursion. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 2026.1 will fix this issue. The name of the patch is 8ba49f98ccfc9734ef352146806433a41d9f9aa6. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2884 | D-Link DWR-M960 WAN Interface Setting formWanConfigSetup sub_41914C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2884</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. The affected element is the function sub_41914C of the file /boafrm/formWanConfigSetup of the component WAN Interface Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2885 | D-Link DWR-M960 formIpv6Setup sub_469104 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2885</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. The impacted element is the function sub_469104 of the file /boafrm/formIpv6Setup. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2882 | D-Link DWR-M960 formDosCfg sub_46385C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2882</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This issue affects the function sub_46385C of the file /boafrm/formDosCfg. Performing a manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2883 | D-Link DWR-M960 formIpQoS sub_427D74 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2883</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Impacted is the function sub_427D74 of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2881 | D-Link DWR-M960 Advanced Firewall Configuration Endpoint formFirewallAdv sub_425FF8 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2881</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_425FF8 of the file /boafrm/formFirewallAdv of the component Advanced Firewall Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 19:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2877 | Tenda A18 Httpd Service WifiExtraSet strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2877</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda A18 15.13.07.13. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet of the component Httpd Service. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 19:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2874 | Tenda A21 fast_setting_wifi_set form_fast_setting_wifi_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2874</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. Impacted is the function form_fast_setting_wifi_set of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. Executing a manipulation of the argument ssid can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2876 | Tenda A18 setBlackRule parse_macfilter_rule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2876</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda A18 15.13.07.13. This affects the function parse_macfilter_rule of the file /goform/setBlackRule. This manipulation of the argument deviceList causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2873 | Tenda A21 openSchedWifi setSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2873</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This issue affects the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. Performing a manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2872 | Tenda A21 MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint setBlackRule set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2872</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This vulnerability affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument devName/mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2871 | Tenda A21 SetIpMacBind fromSetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2871</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. This affects the function fromSetIpMacBind of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. This manipulation of the argument list causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2869 | janet-lang janet handleattr specials.c janetc_varset out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2869</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function janetc_varset of the file src/core/specials.c of the component handleattr Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 1.41.0 addresses this issue. The identifier of the patch is 2fabc80151a2b8834ee59cda8a70453f848b40e5. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2870 | Tenda A21 formSetQosBand set_qosMib_list stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2870</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda A21 1.0.0.0. Affected by this issue is the function set_qosMib_list of the file /goform/formSetQosBand. The manipulation of the argument list results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2867 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System billaction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2867</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /billaction.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1787 | LearnPress Export Import &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Migrated Course Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1787</link><description>The LearnPress Export Import – WordPress extension for LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'delete_migrated_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete course that have been migrated from Tutor LMS. The Tutor LMS plugin must be installed and activated in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27492 | Lettermint Node.js SDK leaks email properties to unintended recipients when client instance is reused</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27492</link><description>Lettermint Node.js SDK is the official Node.js SDK for Lettermint. In versions 1.5.0 and below, email properties (such as to, subject, html, text, and attachments) are not reset between sends when a single client instance is reused across multiple .send() calls. This can cause properties from a previous send to leak into a subsequent one, potentially delivering content or recipient addresses to unintended parties. Applications sending emails to different recipients in sequence — such as transactional flows like password resets or notifications — are affected. This issue has been fixed in version 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27574 | OneUptime: node:vm sandbox escape in probe allows any project member to achieve RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27574</link><description>OneUptime is a solution for monitoring and managing online services. In versions 9.5.13 and below, custom JavaScript monitor feature uses Node.js's node:vm module (explicitly documented as not a security mechanism) to execute user-supplied code, allowing trivial sandbox escape via a well-known one-liner that grants full access to the underlying process. Because the probe runs with host networking and holds all cluster credentials (ONEUPTIME_SECRET, DATABASE_PASSWORD, REDIS_PASSWORD, CLICKHOUSE_PASSWORD) in its environment variables, and monitor creation is available to the lowest role (ProjectMember) with open registration enabled by default, any anonymous user can achieve full cluster compromise in about 30 seconds. This issue has been fixed in version 10.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27579 | CollabPlatform : CORS Misconfiguration Allows Arbitrary Origin With Credentials Leading to Authenticated Account Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27579</link><description>CollabPlatform is a full-stack, real-time doc collaboration platform. In all versions of CollabPlatform, the Appwrite project used by the application is misconfigured to allow arbitrary origins in CORS responses while also permitting credentialed requests. An attacker-controlled domain can issue authenticated cross-origin requests and read sensitive user account information, including email address, account identifiers, and MFA status. The issue did not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27576 | OpenClaw: ACP prompt-size checks missing in local stdio bridge could reduce responsiveness with very large inputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27576</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, the ACP bridge accepts very large prompt text blocks and can assemble oversized prompt payloads before forwarding them to chat.send. Because ACP runs over local stdio, this mainly affects local ACP clients (for example IDE integrations) that send unusually large inputs. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.19.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27488 | OpenClaw hardened cron webhook delivery against SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27488</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, Cron webhook delivery in src/gateway/server-cron.ts uses fetch() directly, so webhook targets can reach private/metadata/internal endpoints without SSRF policy checks. This issue was fixed in version 2026.2.19.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27486 | OpenClaw: Process Safety - Unvalidated PID Kill via SIGKILL in Process Cleanup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27486</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.13 and below of the OpenClaw CLI, the process cleanup uses system-wide process enumeration and pattern matching to terminate processes without verifying if they are owned by the current OpenClaw process. On shared hosts, unrelated processes can be terminated if they match the pattern. The CLI runner cleanup helpers can kill processes matched by command-line patterns without validating process ownership. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.14.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27487 | OpenClaw: Prevent shell injection in macOS keychain credential write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27487</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.13 and below, when using macOS, the Claude CLI keychain credential refresh path constructed a shell command to write the updated JSON blob into Keychain via security add-generic-password -w .... Because OAuth tokens are user-controlled data, this created an OS command injection risk. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.14.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14339 | weMail &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Form Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14339</link><description>The weMail - Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optin Forms, Email Newsletters, A/B Testing, and Automation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized form deletion in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.7. This is due to the `Forms::permission()` callback only validating the `X-WP-Nonce` header without checking user capabilities. Since the REST nonce is exposed to unauthenticated visitors via the `weMail` JavaScript object on pages with weMail forms, any unauthenticated user can permanently delete all weMail forms by extracting the nonce from the page source and sending a DELETE request to the forms endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27482 | Ray: Dashboard DELETE endpoints allow unauthenticated browser-triggered DoS (Serve shutdown / job deletion)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27482</link><description>Ray is an AI compute engine. In versions 2.53.0 and below, thedashboard HTTP server blocks browser-origin POST/PUT but does not cover DELETE, and key DELETE endpoints are unauthenticated by default. If the dashboard/agent is reachable (e.g., --dashboard-host=0.0.0.0), a web page via DNS rebinding or same-network access can issue DELETE requests that shut down Serve or delete jobs without user interaction. This is a drive-by availability impact. The fix for this vulnerability is to update to Ray 2.54.0 or higher.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27484 | OpenClaw Discord moderation authorization used untrusted sender identity in tool-driven flows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27484</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, the Discord moderation action handling (timeout, kick, ban) uses sender identity from request parameters in tool-driven flows, instead of trusted runtime sender context. In setups where Discord moderation actions are enabled and the bot has the necessary guild permissions, a non-admin user can request moderation actions by spoofing sender identity fields. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27485 | OpenClaw affected by Stored XSS in Control UI via unsanitized assistant name/avatar in inline script injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27485</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. In versions 2026.2.17 and below, skills/skill-creator/scripts/package_skill.py (a local helper script used when authors package skills) previously followed symlinks while building .skill archives. If an author runs this script on a crafted local skill directory containing symlinks to files outside the skill root, the resulting archive can include unintended file contents. If exploited, this vulnerability can lead to potential unintentional disclosure of local files from the packaging machine into a generated .skill artifact, but requires local execution of the packaging script on attacker-controlled skill contents. This issue has been fixed in version 2026.2.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27480 | Static Web Server: Timing-Based Username Enumeration in Basic Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27480</link><description>Static Web Server (SWS) is a production-ready web server suitable for static web files or assets. In versions 2.1.0 through 2.40.1, a timing-based username enumeration vulnerability in Basic Authentication allows attackers to identify valid users by exploiting early responses for invalid usernames, enabling targeted brute-force or credential-stuffing attacks. SWS checks whether a username exists before verifying the password, causing valid usernames to follow a slower code path (e.g., bcrypt hashing) while invalid usernames receive an immediate 401 response. This timing discrepancy allows attackers to enumerate valid accounts by measuring response-time differences. This issue has been fixed in version 2.41.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27479 | Wallos: SSRF via Redirect Bypass in Logo/Icon URL Fetch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27479</link><description>Wallos is an open-source, self-hostable personal subscription tracker. Versions 4.6.0 and below contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the subscription and payment logo/icon upload functionality. The application validates the IP address of the provided URL before making the request, but allows HTTP redirects (CURLOPT_FOLLOWLOCATION = true), enabling an attacker to bypass the IP validation and access internal resources, including cloud instance metadata endpoints. The getLogoFromUrl() function validates the URL by resolving the hostname and checking if the resulting IP is in a private or reserved range using FILTER_FLAG_NO_PRIV_RANGE | FILTER_FLAG_NO_RES_RANGE. However, the subsequent cURL request is configured with CURLOPT_FOLLOWLOCATION = true and CURLOPT_MAXREDIRS = 3, which means the request will follow HTTP redirects without re-validating the destination IP. This issue has been fixed in version 4.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27464 | Metabase: Server-Side Template Injection via Notifications Endpoint Leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27464</link><description>Metabase is an open-source data analytics platform. In versions prior to 0.57.13 and versions 0.58.x through 0.58.6, authenticated users are able to retrieve sensitive information from a Metabase instance, including database access credentials. During testing, it was confirmed that a low-privileged user can extract sensitive information including database credentials, into the email body via template evaluation. This issue has been fixed in versions 0.57.13 and 0.58.7. To workaround this issue, users can disable notifications in their Metabase instance to disallow access to the vulnerable endpoints.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27470 | ZoneMinder: Second-Order SQL Injection in `getNearEvents()` via Stored Event Name and Cause Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27470</link><description>ZoneMinder is a free, open source closed-circuit television software application. In versions 1.36.37 and below and 1.37.61 through 1.38.0, there is a second-order SQL Injection vulnerability in the web/ajax/status.php file within the getNearEvents() function. Event field values (specifically Name and Cause) are stored safely via parameterized queries but are later retrieved and concatenated directly into SQL WHERE clauses without escaping. An authenticated user with Events edit and view permissions can exploit this to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27469 | Isso: Stored XSS via comment website field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27469</link><description>Isso is a lightweight commenting server written in Python and JavaScript. In commits before 0afbfe0691ee237963e8fb0b2ee01c9e55ca2144, there is a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting the website and author comment fields. The website field was HTML-escaped using quote=False, which left single and double quotes unescaped. Since the frontend inserts the website value directly into a single-quoted href attribute via string concatenation, a single quote in the URL breaks out of the attribute context, allowing injection of arbitrary event handlers (e.g. onmouseover, onclick). The same escaping is missing entirely from the user-facing comment edit endpoint (PUT /id/) and the moderation edit endpoint (POST /id//edit/). This issue has been patched in commit 0afbfe0691ee237963e8fb0b2ee01c9e55ca2144. To workaround, nabling comment moderation (moderation = enabled = true in isso.cfg) prevents unauthenticated users from publishing comments, raising the bar for exploitation, but it does not fully mitigate the issue since a moderator activating a malicious comment would still expose visitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2864 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm PictureController.java pictureDelete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2864</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 4288d53bd35757b27f2d070057aefb2c07bdd097. This affects the function pictureDelete of the file PictureController.java. Such manipulation of the argument picName leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. This product is distributed under two entirely different names. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2865 | itsourcecode Agri-Trading Online Shopping System HTTP POST Request productcontroller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Agri-Trading Online Shopping System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file admin/productcontroller.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument Product results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27466 | BigBlueButton: Exposed ClamAV port enables Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27466</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. In versions 3.0.21 and below, the official documentation for "Server Customization" on Support for ClamAV as presentation file scanner contains instructions that leave a BBB server vulnerable for Denial of Service. The flawed command exposes both ports (3310 and 7357) to the internet. A remote attacker can use this to send complex or large documents to clamd and waste server resources, or shutdown the clamd process. The clamd documentation explicitly warns about exposing this port. Enabling ufw (ubuntu firewall) during install does not help, because Docker routes container traffic through the nat table, which is not managed or restricted by ufw. Rules installed by ufw in the filter table have no effect on docker traffic. In addition, the provided example also mounts /var/bigbluebutton with write permissions into the container, which should not be required. Future vulnerabilities in clamd may allow attackers to manipulate files in that folder. Users are unaffected unless they have opted in to follow the extra instructions from BigBlueButton's documentation. This issue has been fixed in version 3.0.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27467 | BigBlueButton: Audio from participants to the server initially unmuted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27467</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. In versions 3.0.19 and below, when first joining a session with the microphone muted, the client sends audio to the server regardless of mute state. Media is discarded at the server side, so it isn't audible to any participants, but this may allow for malicious server operators to access audio data. The behavior is only incorrect between joining the meeting and the first time the user unmutes. This issue has been fixed in version 3.0.20.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27206 | Zumba Json Serializer has a potential PHP Object Injection via Unrestricted @type in unserialize()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27206</link><description>Zumba Json Serializer is a library to serialize PHP variables in JSON format. In versions 3.2.2 and below, the library allows deserialization of PHP objects from JSON using a special @type field. The deserializer instantiates any class specified in the @type field without restriction. When processing untrusted JSON input, this behavior may allow an attacker to instantiate arbitrary classes available in the application. If a vulnerable application passes attacker-controlled JSON into JsonSerializer::unserialize() and contains classes with dangerous magic methods (such as __wakeup() or __destruct()), this may lead to PHP Object Injection and potentially Remote Code Execution (RCE), depending on available gadget chains in the application or its dependencies. This behavior is similar in risk profile to PHP's native unserialize() when used without the allowed_classes restriction. Applications are impacted only if untrusted or attacker-controlled JSON is passed into JsonSerializer::unserialize() and the application or its dependencies contain classes that can be leveraged as a gadget chain. This issue has been fixed in version 3.2.3. If an immediate upgrade isn't feasible, mitigate the vulnerability by never deserializing untrusted JSON with JsonSerializer::unserialize(), validating and sanitizing all JSON input before deserialization, and disabling @type-based object instantiation wherever possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27452 | ASN.1 TypeScript Library: Decoding an INTEGER could leak the underlying ArrayBuffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27452</link><description>ASN.1 TypeScript ESM library, including codecs for Basic Encoding Rules (BER) and Distinguished Encoding Rules (DER). In versions 11.0.5 and below, in some cases, decoding an INTEGER could leak the underlying ArrayBuffer. This issue is expected to be fixed in version 11.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27458 | LinkAce: Stored XSS in Atom Feed via CDATA Escape in List Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27458</link><description>LinkAce is a self-hosted archive to collect website links. Versions 2.4.2 and below have a Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability through the Atom feed endpoint for lists (/lists/feed). An authenticated user can inject a CDATA-breaking payload into a list description that escapes the XML CDATA section, injects a native SVG element into the Atom XML document, and executes arbitrary JavaScript directly in the browser when the feed URL is visited. No RSS reader or additional rendering context is required — the browser's native XML parser processes the injected SVG and fires the onload event handler. This vulnerability exists because the lists feed template outputs list descriptions using Blade's raw syntax ({!! !!}) without sanitization inside a CDATA block. The critical detail is that because the output sits inside , an attacker can inject the sequence ]]&gt; to close the CDATA section prematurely, then inject arbitrary XML/SVG elements that the browser parses and executes natively as part of the Atom document. This issue has been fixed in version 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27471 | ERP: Document access through endpoints due to missing validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27471</link><description>ERP is a free and open source Enterprise Resource Planning tool. In versions up to 15.98.0 and 16.0.0-rc.1 and through 16.6.0, certain endpoints lacked access validation which allowed for unauthorized document access. This issue has been fixed in versions 15.98.1 and 16.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 07:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2861 | Foswiki Changes/Viewfile/Oops information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2861</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Foswiki up to 2.1.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Changes/Viewfile/Oops. The manipulation results in information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.1.11 is sufficient to fix this issue. The patch is identified as 31aeecb58b64/d8ed86b10e46. Upgrading the affected component is recommended.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2863 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm FileServiceImpl.java deleteFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2863</link><description>A flaw has been found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 4288d53bd35757b27f2d070057aefb2c07bdd097. The impacted element is the function deleteFile of the file FileServiceImpl.java. This manipulation causes path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. This product is distributed under two entirely different names. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26045 | Moodle: moodle: improper validation in file restore functionality leading to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26045</link><description>A flaw was identified in Moodle’s backup restore functionality where specially crafted backup files were not properly validated during processing. If a malicious backup file is restored, it could lead to unintended execution of server-side code. Since restore capabilities are typically available to privileged users, exploitation requires authenticated access. Successful exploitation could result in full compromise of the Moodle server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26046 | Moodle: moodle: improper input sanitization in tex filter administration setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26046</link><description>A vulnerability was found in a Moodle TeX filter administrative setting where insufficient sanitization of configuration input could allow command injection. On sites where the TeX filter is enabled and ImageMagick is installed, a maliciously crafted setting value entered by an administrator could result in unintended system command execution. While exploitation requires administrative privileges, successful compromise could affect the entire Moodle server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26047 | Moodle: moodle: uncontrolled resource consumption in tex formula editor leading to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26047</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability was identified in Moodle’s TeX formula editor. When rendering TeX content using mimetex, insufficient execution time limits could allow specially crafted formulas to consume excessive server resources. An authenticated user could abuse this behavior to degrade performance or cause service interruption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27211 | Cloud Hypervisor: Host File Exfiltration via QCOW Backing File Abuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27211</link><description>Cloud Hypervisor is a Virtual Machine Monitor for Cloud workloads. Versions 34.0 through 50.0 arevulnerable to arbitrary host file exfiltration (constrained by process privileges) when using virtio-block devices backed by raw images. A malicious guest can overwrite its disk header with a crafted QCOW2 structure pointing to a sensitive host path. Upon the next VM boot or disk scan, the image format auto-detection parses this header and serves the host file's contents to the guest. Guest-initiated VM reboots are sufficient to trigger a disk scan and do not cause the Cloud Hypervisor process to exit. Therefore, a single VM can perform this attack without needing interaction from the management stack. Successful exploitation requires the backing image to be either writable by the guest or sourced from an untrusted origin. Deployments utilizing only trusted, read-only images are not affected. This issue has been fixed in version 50.1. To workaround, enable land lock sandboxing and restrict process privileges and access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27212 | Swiper has a Prototype Pollution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27212</link><description>Swiper is a free and mobile touch slider with hardware accelerated transitions and native behavior. Versions 6.5.1 through 12.1.1 have a Prototype pollution vulnerability. The vulnerability resides in line 94 of shared/utils.mjs, where the indexOf() function is used to check whether user provided input contain forbidden strings. Despite a previous fix that attempted to mitigate prototype pollution by checking whether user input contained a forbidden key, it is still possible to pollute Object.prototype via a crafted input using Array.prototype. The exploit works across Windows and Linux and on Node and Bun runtimes.  Any application that processes attacker-controlled input using this package may be affected  by the following: Authentication Bypass, Denial of Service and RCE. This issue is fixed in version 12.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27205 | Flask session does not add `Vary: Cookie` header when accessed in some ways</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27205</link><description>Flask is a web server gateway interface (WSGI) web application framework. In versions 3.1.2 and below, when the session object is accessed, Flask should set the Vary: Cookie header., resulting in a Use of Cache Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability. The logic instructs caches not to cache the response, as it may contain information specific to a logged in user. This is handled in most cases, but some forms of access such as the Python in operator were overlooked. The severity and risk depend on the application being hosted behind a caching proxy that doesn't ignore responses with cookies, not setting a Cache-Control header to mark pages as private or non-cacheable, and accessing the session in a way that only touches keys without reading values or mutating the session. The issue has been fixed in version 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27210 | Pannellum has a XSS vulnerability in hot spot attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27210</link><description>Pannellum is a lightweight, free, and open source panorama viewer for the web. In versions 3.5.0 through 2.5.6, the hot spot attributes configuration property allowed any attribute to be set, including HTML event handler attributes, allowing for potential XSS attacks. This affects websites hosting the standalone viewer HTML file and any other use of untrusted JSON config files (bypassing the protections of the escapeHTML parameter). As certain events fire without any additional user interaction, visiting a standalone viewer URL that points to a malicious config file — without additional user interaction — is sufficient to trigger the vulnerability and execute arbitrary JavaScript code, which can, for example, replace the contents of the page with arbitrary content and make it appear to be hosted by the website hosting the standalone viewer HTML file. This issue has been fixed in version 2.5.7. To workaround, setting the Content-Security-Policy header to script-src-attr 'none' will block execution of inline event handlers, mitigating this vulnerability. Don't host pannellum.htm on a domain that shares cookies with user authentication to mitigate XSS risk.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27198 | Formwork Improperly Manages Privileges During User Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27198</link><description>Formwork is a flat file-based Content Management System (CMS). In versions 2.0.0 through 2.3.3, the application fails to properly enforce role-based authorization during account creation. Although the system validates that the specified role exists, it does not verify whether the current user has sufficient privileges to assign highly privileged roles such as admin. As a result, an authenticated user with the editor role can create a new account with administrative privileges, leading to full administrative access and complete compromise of the CMS. This issue has been fixed in version 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27199 | Werkzeug safe_join() allows Windows special device names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27199</link><description>Werkzeug is a comprehensive WSGI web application library. Versions 3.1.5 and below, the safe_join function allows Windows device names as filenames if preceded by other path segments. This was previously reported as GHSA-hgf8-39gv-g3f2, but the added filtering failed to account for the fact that safe_join accepts paths with multiple segments, such as example/NUL. The function send_from_directory uses safe_join to safely serve files at user-specified paths under a directory. If the application is running on Windows, and the requested path ends with a special device name, the file will be opened successfully, but reading will hang indefinitely. This issue has been fixed in version 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27196 | Statamic affected by privilege escalation via stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27196</link><description>Statmatic is a Laravel and Git powered content management system (CMS). Versions 5.73.8 and below in addition to 6.0.0-alpha.1 through 6.3.1 have a Stored XSS vulnerability in html fieldtypes which allows authenticated users with field management permissions to inject malicious JavaScript that executes when viewed by higher-privileged users. This issue has been fixed in 6.3.2 and 5.73.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27197 | Sentry: Improper Authentication on SAML SSO process allows user identity linking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27197</link><description>Sentry is a developer-first error tracking and performance monitoring tool. Versions 21.12.0 through 26.1.0 have a critical vulnerability in its SAML SSO implementation  which allows an attacker to take over any user account by using a malicious SAML Identity Provider and another organization on the same Sentry instance. Self-hosted users are only at risk if the following criteria is met: ore than one organizations are configured (SENTRY_SINGLE_ORGANIZATION = True), or malicious user has existing access and permissions to modify SSO settings for another organization in a multo-organization instance. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0. To workaround this issue, implement user account-based two-factor authentication to prevent an attacker from being able to complete authentication with a victim's user account. Organization administrators cannot do this on a user's behalf, this requires individual users to ensure 2FA has been enabled for their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2860 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm EmployeeController.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2860</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm up to 4288d53bd35757b27f2d070057aefb2c07bdd097. Impacted is an unknown function of the file EmployeeController.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. This product is distributed under two entirely different names. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27193 | Feathers exposes internal headers via unencrypted session cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27193</link><description>Feathersjs is a framework for creating web APIs and real-time applications with TypeScript or JavaScript. In versions 5.0.39 and below, all HTTP request headers are stored in the session cookie, which is signed but not encrypted, exposing internal proxy/gateway headers to clients. The OAuth service stores the complete headers object in the session, then the session is persisted using cookie-session, which base64-encodes the data. While the cookie is signed to prevent tampering, the contents are readable by anyone by simply decoding the base64 value. Under specific deployment configurations (e.g., behind reverse proxies or API gateways), this can lead to exposure of sensitive internal infrastructure details such as API keys, service tokens, and internal IP addresses. This issue has been fixed in version 5.0.40.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27194 | D-Tale affected by Remote Code Execution through the /save-column-filter endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27194</link><description>D-Tale is a visualizer for pandas data structures. Versions prior to 3.20.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution through the /save-column-filter endpoint. Users hosting D-Tale publicly can be vulnerable to remote code execution allowing attackers to run malicious code on the server. This issue has been fixed in version 3.20.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27191 | Feathers: Open Redirect in OAuth callback enables account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27191</link><description>Feathersjs is a framework for creating web APIs and real-time applications with TypeScript or JavaScript. Versions 5.0.39 and below the redirect query parameter is appended to the base origin without validation, allowing attackers to steal access tokens via URL authority injection. This leads to full account takeover, as the attacker obtains the victim's access token and can impersonate them. The application constructs the final redirect URL by concatenating the base origin with the user-supplied redirect parameter. This is exploitable when the origins array is configured and origin values do not end with /. An attacker can supply @attacker.com as the redirect value results in https://target.com@attacker.com#access_token=..., where the browser interprets attacker.com as the host, leading to full account takeover. This issue has been fixed in version 5.0.40.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27192 | Feathers has an origin validation bypass via prefix matching</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27192</link><description>Feathersjs is a framework for creating web APIs and real-time applications with TypeScript or JavaScript. In versions 5.0.39 and below, origin validation uses startsWith() for comparison, allowing attackers to bypass the check by registering a domain that shares a common prefix with an allowed origin.The getAllowedOrigin() function checks if the Referer header starts with any allowed origin, and this comparison is insufficient as it only validates the prefix. This is exploitable when the origins array is configured and an attacker registers a domain starting with an allowed origin string (e.g., https://target.com.attacker.com bypasses https://target.com). On its own, tokens are still redirected to a configured origin. However, in specific scenarios an attacker can initiate the OAuth flow from an unauthorized origin and exfiltrate tokens, achieving full account takeover. This issue has bee fixed in version 5.0.40.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65995 | Apache Airflow: Disclosure of secrets to UI via kwargs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65995</link><description>When a DAG failed during parsing, Airflow’s error-reporting in the UI could include the full kwargs passed to the operators. If those kwargs contained sensitive values (such as secrets), they might be exposed in the UI tracebacks to authenticated users who had permission to view that DAG. 

The issue has been fixed in Airflow 3.1.4 and 2.11.1, and users are strongly advised to upgrade to prevent potential disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27170 | OpenSift: SSRF risk in URL ingestion endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27170</link><description>OpenSift is an AI study tool that sifts through large datasets using semantic search and generative AI. In versions 1.1.2-alpha and below, URL ingest allows overly permissive server-side fetch behavior and can be coerced into requesting unsafe targets. Potential access/probing of private/local network resources from the OpenSift host process when ingesting attacker-controlled URLs. This issue has been fixed in version 1.1.3-alpha. To workaround when using trusted local-only exceptions, use OPENSIFT_ALLOW_PRIVATE_URLS=true with caution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27189 | OpenSift: Race-prone local persistence could cause state corruption/loss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27189</link><description>OpenSift is an AI study tool that sifts through large datasets using semantic search and generative AI. Versions 1.1.2-alpha and below, use non-atomic and insufficiently synchronized local JSON persistence flows, potentially causing concurrent operations to lose updates or corrupt local state across sessions/study/quiz/flashcard/wellness/auth stores. This issue has been fixed in version 1.1.3-alpha.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27169 | OpenSift: Persistent XSS Chat Tool Rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27169</link><description>OpenSift is an AI study tool that sifts through large datasets using semantic search and generative AI. Versions 1.1.2-alpha and below render untrusted user/model content in chat tool UI surfaces using unsafe HTML interpolation patterns, leading to XSS. Stored content can execute JavaScript when later viewed in authenticated sessions. An attacker who can influence stored study/quiz/flashcard content could trigger script execution in a victim’s browser, potentially performing actions as that user in the local app session. This issue has been fixed in version 1.1.3-alpha.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27168 | SAIL: Heap-based Buffer Overflow in Sail-codecs-xwd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27168</link><description>SAIL is a cross-platform library for loading and saving images with support for animation, metadata, and ICC profiles. All versions are vulnerable to Heap-based Buffer Overflow through the XWD parser's use of the bytes_per_line value. The value os read directly from the file as the read size in io-&gt;strict_read(), and is never compared to the actual size of the destination buffer. An attacker can provide an XWD file with an arbitrarily large bytes_per_line, causing a massive write operation beyond the buffer heap allocated for the image pixels. The issue did not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27203 | eBay API MCP Server Affected by Environment Variable Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27203</link><description>eBay API MCP Server is an open source local MCP server providing AI assistants with comprehensive access to eBay's Sell APIs. All versions are vulnerable to Environment Variable Injection through the updateEnvFile function. The ebay_set_user_tokens tool allows updating the .env file with new tokens. The updateEnvFile function in src/auth/oauth.ts blindly appends or replaces values without validating them for newlines or quotes. This allows an attacker to inject arbitrary environment variables into the configuration file. An attacker can inject arbitrary environment variables into the .env file. This could lead to configuration overwrites, Denial of Service, and potential RCE. There was no fix for this issue at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27161 | Unauthenticated Information Disclosure via .htaccess Reliance in Sensitive Directories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27161</link><description>GetSimple CMS is a content management system. All versions of GetSimple CMS rely on .htaccess files to restrict access to sensitive directories such as /data/ and /backups/. If Apache AllowOverride is disabled (common in hardened or shared hosting environments), these protections are silently ignored, allowing unauthenticated attackers to list and download sensitive files including authorization.xml, which contains cryptographic salts and API keys. This issue does not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27202 | GetSimple CMS: Uploaded Files (feature) Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27202</link><description>GetSimple CMS is a content management system. All versions of GetSimple CMS have a flaw in the Uploaded Files feature that allows for arbitrary file reads. This issue has not been fixed at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27134 | Strimzi: All CAs from a custom CA chain consisting of multiple CAs are trusted for mTLS user autentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27134</link><description>Strimzi provides a way to run an Apache Kafka cluster on Kubernetes or OpenShift in various deployment configurations. In versions  0.49.0 through 0.50.0, when using a custom Cluster or Clients CA with a multistage CA chain consisting of multiple CAs, Strimzi incorrectly configures the trusted certificates for mTLS authentication on the internal as well as user-configured listeners. All CAs from the CA chain will be trusted. And users with certificates signed by any of the CAs in the chain will be able to authenticate. This issue affects only users using a custom Cluster or Clients CA with a multistage CA chain consisting of multiple CAs. It does not affect users using the Strimzi-managed Cluster and Clients CAs. It also does not affect users using custom Cluster or Clients CA with only a single CA (i.e., no CA chain with multiple CAs). This issue has been fixed in version 0.50.1. To workaround this issue, instead of providing the full CA chain as the custom CA, users can provide only the single CA that should be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27146 | GetSimple CMS:  Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in File Upload Allows Arbitrary Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27146</link><description>GetSimple CMS is a content management system. All versions of GetSimple CMS do not implement CSRF protection on the administrative file upload endpoint. As a result, an attacker can craft a malicious web page that silently triggers a file upload request from an authenticated victim’s browser. The request is accepted without requiring a CSRF token or origin validation. This allows an attacker to upload arbitrary files to the application without the victim’s knowledge or consent. In order to exploit this vulnerability, the victim must be authenticated to GetSimple CMS (e.g., admin user), and visit an attacker-controlled webpage. This issue does not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27147 | GetSimple CMS: Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via SVG File Upload (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27147</link><description>GetSimple CMS is a content management system. All versions of GetSimple CMS are vulnerable to XSS through SVG file uploads. Authenticated users can upload SVG files via the administrative upload functionality, but they are not properly sanitized or restricted, allowing an attacker to embed malicious JavaScript. When the uploaded SVG file is accessed, the script executes in the browser. This issue does not have a fix at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25158 | Chamilo LMS 1.11.8 Arbitrary File Upload via elfinder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25158</link><description>Chamilo LMS 1.11.8 contains an arbitrary file upload vulnerability that allows authenticated users to upload and execute PHP files through the elfinder filemanager module. Attackers can upload files with image headers in the social myfiles section, rename them to PHP extensions, and execute arbitrary code by accessing the uploaded files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25431 | delpino73 Blue-Smiley-Organizer 1.32 SQL Injection via datetime</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25431</link><description>delpino73 Blue-Smiley-Organizer 1.32 contains an SQL injection vulnerability in the datetime parameter that allows unauthenticated attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can inject SQL code through POST requests to extract sensitive data using boolean-based blind and time-based blind techniques, or write files to the server using INTO OUTFILE statements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25432 | Part-DB 0.4 Authentication Bypass via login.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25432</link><description>Part-DB 0.4 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to login by injecting SQL syntax into authentication parameters. Attackers can submit a single quote followed by 'or' in the login form to bypass credential validation and gain unauthorized access to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25434 | SpotAuditor 5.3.1.0 Denial of Service via Registration Name Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25434</link><description>SpotAuditor 5.3.1.0 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to crash the application by submitting excessive data in the registration name field. Attackers can enter a large string of characters (5000 bytes or more) in the name field during registration to trigger an unhandled exception that crashes the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25435 | Sricam DeviceViewer 3.12.0.1 Local Buffer Overflow DEP Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25435</link><description>Sricam DeviceViewer 3.12.0.1 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the user management add user function that allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code by bypassing data execution prevention. Attackers can inject a malicious payload through the Username field in User Management to trigger a stack-based buffer overflow and execute commands via ROP chain gadgets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25436 | Sricam DeviceViewer 3.12.0.1 Password Change Security Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25436</link><description>Sricam DeviceViewer 3.12.0.1 contains a password change security bypass vulnerability that allows authenticated users to change passwords without proper validation of the old password field. Attackers can inject a large payload into the old password parameter during the change password process to bypass validation and set an arbitrary new password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25437 | Foscam Video Management System 1.1.6.6 Buffer Overflow Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25437</link><description>Foscam Video Management System 1.1.6.6 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the UID field that allows local attackers to crash the application by supplying an excessively long string. Attackers can input a 5000-character buffer into the UID parameter during device addition to trigger an application crash when the Login Check function is invoked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25438 | LabCollector 5.423 SQL Injection via login.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25438</link><description>LabCollector 5.423 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities that allow unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands by injecting malicious code through POST parameters. Attackers can submit crafted SQL payloads in the login parameter of login.php or the user_name parameter of retrieve_password.php to extract sensitive database information without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25441 | thesystem 1.0 Command Injection via run_command endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25441</link><description>thesystem 1.0 contains a command injection vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary system commands by submitting malicious input to the run_command endpoint. Attackers can send POST requests with shell commands in the command parameter to execute arbitrary code on the server without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25447 | OrientDB 3.0.17 Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25447</link><description>OrientDB 3.0.17 GA Community Edition contains cross-site request forgery vulnerabilities that allow attackers to perform unauthorized actions by crafting malicious requests to endpoints like /database/, /command/, and /document/. Attackers can create or delete databases, modify schema classes, manage users, and create functions by sending authenticated requests without token validation, combined with reflected and stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in the web interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25448 | OrientDB 3.0.17 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via User Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25448</link><description>OrientDB 3.0.17 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by creating users with script payloads in the name parameter. Attackers can send POST requests to the document endpoint with JavaScript code in the name field to execute arbitrary scripts when users view the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25449 | OrientDB 3.0.17 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via document endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25449</link><description>OrientDB 3.0.17 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts by submitting crafted JSON payloads to the document endpoint. Attackers can send POST requests to /document/demodb/-1:-1 with script tags in the name parameter to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25451 | phpMoAdmin 1.1.5 Cross-Site Request Forgery via moadmin.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25451</link><description>phpMoAdmin 1.1.5 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to perform unauthorized database operations by crafting malicious requests. Attackers can trick authenticated users into submitting GET requests to moadmin.php with parameters like action, db, and collection to create, drop, or repair databases and collections without user consent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25453 | phpMoAdmin 1.1.5 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via moadmin.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25453</link><description>phpMoAdmin 1.1.5 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by manipulating the newdb parameter. Attackers can craft URLs with JavaScript payloads in the newdb parameter of moadmin.php to execute arbitrary code in users' browsers when they visit the malicious link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25454 | phpMoAdmin 1.1.5 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via collection Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25454</link><description>phpMoAdmin 1.1.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts by manipulating the collection parameter. Attackers can send GET requests to moadmin.php with script payloads in the collection parameter during collection creation to execute arbitrary JavaScript in users' browsers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27119 | Svelte affected by XSS in SSR `&amp;lt;option&amp;gt;` element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27119</link><description>svelte performance oriented web framework. From 5.39.3, &lt;=5.51.4, in certain circumstances, the server-side rendering output of an &lt;option&gt; element does not properly escape its content, potentially allowing HTML injection in the SSR output. Client-side rendering is not affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.51.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27121 | Svelte affected by cross-site scripting via spread attributes in Svelte SSR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27121</link><description>svelte performance oriented web framework. Versions of svelte prior to 5.51.5 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) during server-side rendering. When using spread syntax to render attributes from untrusted data, event handler properties are included in the rendered HTML output. If an application spreads user-controlled or external data as element attributes, an attacker can inject malicious event handlers that execute in victims' browsers. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.51.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27122 | Svelte SSR does not validate dynamic element tag names in `&amp;lt;svelte:element&amp;gt;`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27122</link><description>svelte performance oriented web framework. Prior to 5.51.5, when using  in server-side rendering, the provided tag name is not validated or sanitized before being emitted into the HTML output. If the tag string contains unexpected characters, it can result in HTML injection in the SSR output. Client-side rendering is not affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.51.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27125 | Svelte SSR attribute spreading includes inherited properties from prototype chain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27125</link><description>svelte performance oriented web framework. Prior to 5.51.5, in server-side rendering, attribute spreading on elements (e.g. &lt;div&gt;) enumerates inherited properties from the object's prototype chain rather than only own properties. In environments where Object.prototype has already been polluted — a precondition outside of Svelte's control — this can cause unexpected attributes to appear in SSR output or cause SSR to throw errors. Client-side rendering is not affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.51.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27133 | Strimzi All CAs from CA chain will be trusted in Kafka Connect and Kafka MirrorMaker 2 target clusters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27133</link><description>Strimzi provides a way to run an Apache Kafka cluster on Kubernetes or OpenShift in various deployment configurations. From 0.47.0 to before 0.50.1, when a chain consisting of multiple CA (Certificate Authority) certificates is used in the trusted certificates configuration of a Kafka Connect operand or of the target cluster in the Kafka MirrorMaker 2 operand, all of the certificates that are part of the CA chain will be trusted individually when connecting to the Apache Kafka cluster. Due to this error, the affected operand (Kafka Connect or Kafka MirrorMaker 2) might accept connections to Kafka brokers using server certificates signed by one of the other CAs in the CA chain and not just by the last CA in the chain. This issue is fixed in Strimzi 0.50.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2490 | RustDesk Client for Windows Transfer File Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2490</link><description>RustDesk Client for Windows Transfer File Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of RustDesk Client for Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Transfer File feature. By uploading a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to read arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-27909.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2635 | MLflow Use of Default Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2635</link><description>MLflow Use of Default Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of MLflow. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the basic_auth.ini file. The file contains hard-coded default credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary code in the context of the administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-28256.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 23:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2033 | MLflow Tracking Server Artifact Handler Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2033</link><description>MLflow Tracking Server Artifact Handler Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of MLflow Tracking Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of artifact file paths. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-26649.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2034 | Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2034</link><description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28129.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2035 | Deciso OPNsense diag_backup.php filename Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2035</link><description>Deciso OPNsense diag_backup.php filename Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Deciso OPNsense. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of backup configuration files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-28131.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2036 | GFI Archiver MArc.Store Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2036</link><description>GFI Archiver MArc.Store Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GFI Archiver. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the MArc.Store.Remoting.exe process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-27936.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2037 | GFI Archiver MArc.Core Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2037</link><description>GFI Archiver MArc.Core Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GFI Archiver. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the MArc.Core.Remoting.exe process, which listens on port 8017. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-27935.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2038 | GFI Archiver MArc.Core Missing Authorization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2038</link><description>GFI Archiver MArc.Core Missing Authorization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of GFI Archiver. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the MArc.Core.Remoting.exe process, which listens on port 8017. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-27934.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2039 | GFI Archiver MArc.Store Missing Authorization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2039</link><description>GFI Archiver MArc.Store Missing Authorization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of GFI Archiver. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the MArc.Store.Remoting.exe process, which listens on port 8018. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-28597.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2040 | PDF-XChange Editor TrackerUpdate Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2040</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor TrackerUpdate Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the TrackerUpdate process. The product loads a library from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of a target user. Was ZDI-CAN-27788.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2041 | Nagios Host zabbixagent_configwizard_func Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2041</link><description>Nagios Host zabbixagent_configwizard_func Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Nagios Host. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the zabbixagent_configwizard_func method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-28250.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2042 | Nagios Host monitoringwizard Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2042</link><description>Nagios Host monitoringwizard Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Nagios Host. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the monitoringwizard module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-28245.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2043 | Nagios Host esensors_websensor_configwizard_func Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2043</link><description>Nagios Host esensors_websensor_configwizard_func Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Nagios Host. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the esensors_websensor_configwizard_func method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-28249.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2044 | GIMP PGM File Parsing Uninitialized Memory Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2044</link><description>GIMP PGM File Parsing Uninitialized Memory Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PGM files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28158.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2045 | GIMP XWD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2045</link><description>GIMP XWD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XWD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28265.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2047 | GIMP ICNS File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2047</link><description>GIMP ICNS File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ICNS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28530.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2048 | GIMP XWD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2048</link><description>GIMP XWD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XWD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28591.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2492 | TensorFlow HDF5 Library Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2492</link><description>TensorFlow HDF5 Library Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of TensorFlow. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of plugins. The application loads plugins from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of a target user. Was ZDI-CAN-25480.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0777 | Xmind Attachment Insufficient UI Warning Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0777</link><description>Xmind Attachment Insufficient UI Warning Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Xmind. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of attachments. When opening an attachment, the user interface fails to warn the user of unsafe actions. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of current user. Was ZDI-CAN-26034.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0797 | GIMP ICO File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0797</link><description>GIMP ICO File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ICO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-28599.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27113 | Liquid Prompt arbitrary command injection via crafted Git branch names in gitstatusd backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27113</link><description>Liquid Prompt is an adaptive prompt for Bash and Zsh. Starting in commit cf3441250bb5d8b45f6f8b389fcdf427a99ac28a and prior to commit a4f6b8d8c90b3eaa33d13dfd1093062ab9c4b30c on the master branch, arbitrary command injection can lead to code execution when a user enters a directory in a Git repository containing a crafted branch name. Exploitation requires the LP_ENABLE_GITSTATUSD config option to be enabled (enabled by default), gitstatusd to be installed and started before Liquid Prompt is loaded (not the default), and shell prompt substitution to be active (enabled by default in Bash via "shopt -s promptvars", not enabled by default in Zsh). A branch name containing shell syntax such as "$(...)" or backtick expressions in the default branch or a checked-out branch will be evaluated by the shell when the prompt is rendered. No stable release is affected; only the master branch contains the vulnerable commit. Commit a4f6b8d8c90b3eaa33d13dfd1093062ab9c4b30c contains a fix. As a workaround, set the LP_ENABLE_GITSTATUSD config option to 0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2858 | wren-lang wren Source File wren_compiler.c peekChar out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2858</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in wren-lang wren up to 0.4.0. This affects the function peekChar of the file src/vm/wren_compiler.c of the component Source File Parser. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27111 | Kargo has Missing Authorization Vulnerabilities in Approval &amp;amp; Promotion REST API Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27111</link><description>Kargo manages and automates the promotion of software artifacts. From v1.9.0 to v1.9.2, Kargo's authorization model includes a promote verb -- a non-standard Kubernetes "dolphin verb" -- that gates the ability to advance Freight through a promotion pipeline. This verb exists to separate the ability to manage promotion-related resources from the ability to trigger promotions, enabling fine-grained access control over what is often a sensitive operation. The promote verb is correctly enforced in Kargo's legacy gRPC API. However, three endpoints in the newer REST API omit this check, relying only on standard Kubernetes RBAC for the underlying resource operations (patch on freights/status or create on promotions). This permits users who hold those standard permissions -- but who were deliberately not granted promote -- to bypass the intended authorization boundary. The affected endpoints are /v1beta1/projects/{project}/freight/{freight}/approve, /v1beta1/projects/{project}/stages/{stage}/promotions, and /v1beta1/projects/{project}/stages/{stage}/promotions/downstream. This vulnerability is fixed in v1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27112 | Kargo has an Authorization Bypass Vulnerability in Batch Resource Creation API Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27112</link><description>Kargo manages and automates the promotion of software artifacts. From 1.7.0 to before v1.7.8, v1.8.11, and v1.9.3, the batch resource creation endpoints of both Kargo's legacy gRPC API and newer REST API accept multi-document YAML payloads. Specially crafted payloads can manifest a bug present in the logic of both endpoints to inject arbitrary resources (of specific types only) into the underlying namespace of an existing Project using the API server's own permissions when that behavior was not intended. Critically, an attacker may exploit this as a vector for elevating their own permissions, which can then be leveraged to achieve remote code execution or secret exfiltration. Exfiltrated artifact repository credentials can be leveraged, in turn, to execute further attacks. In some configurations of the Kargo control plane's underlying Kubernetes cluster, elevated permissions may additionally be leveraged to achieve remote code execution or secret exfiltration using kubectl. This can reduce the complexity of the attack, however, worst case scenarios remain entirely achievable even without this. This vulnerability is fixed in v1.7.8, v1.8.11, and v1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27118 | Cache poisoning in @sveltejs/adapter-vercel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27118</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. Versions of @sveltejs/adapter-vercel prior to 6.3.2 are vulnerable to cache poisoning. An internal query parameter intended for Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is accessible on all routes, allowing an attacker to cause sensitive user-specific responses to be cached and served to other users. Successful exploitation requires a victim to visit an attacker-controlled link while authenticated. Existing deployments are protected by Vercel's WAF, but users should upgrade as soon as possible. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27120 | Leaf-kit html escaping does not work on characters that are part of extended grapheme cluster</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27120</link><description>Leafkit is a templating language with Swift-inspired syntax. Prior to 1.4.1, htmlEscaped in leaf-kit will only escape html special characters if the extended grapheme clusters match, which allows bypassing escaping by using an extended grapheme cluster containing both the special html character and some additional characters. In the case of html attributes, this can lead to XSS if there is a leaf variable in the attribute that is user controlled. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27022 | RediSearch Query Injection in @langchain/langgraph-checkpoint-redis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27022</link><description>@langchain/langgraph-checkpoint-redis is the Redis checkpoint and store implementation for LangGraph. A query injection vulnerability exists in the @langchain/langgraph-checkpoint-redis package's filter handling. The RedisSaver and ShallowRedisSaver classes construct RediSearch queries by directly interpolating user-provided filter keys and values without proper escaping. RediSearch has special syntax characters that can modify query behavior, and when user-controlled data contains these characters, the query logic can be manipulated to bypass intended access controls. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27024 | pypdf has a possible infinite loop when processing TreeObject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27024</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to 6.7.1, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to an infinite loop. This requires accessing the children of a TreeObject, for example as part of outlines. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27025 | pypdf has possible long runtimes/large memory usage for large /ToUnicode streams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27025</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to 6.7.1, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to long runtimes and large memory consumption. This requires parsing the /ToUnicode entry of a font with unusually large values, for example during text extraction. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27026 | pypdf possibly has long runtimes for malformed FlateDecode streams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27026</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to 6.7.1, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to long runtimes. This requires a malformed /FlateDecode stream, where the byte-by-byte decompression is used. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25896 | fast-xml-parser has an entity encoding bypass via regex injection in DOCTYPE entity names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25896</link><description>fast-xml-parser allows users to validate XML, parse XML to JS object, or build XML from JS object without C/C++ based libraries and no callback. From 4.1.3to before 5.3.5, a dot (.) in a DOCTYPE entity name is treated as a regex wildcard during entity replacement, allowing an attacker to shadow built-in XML entities (&amp;lt;, &amp;gt;, &amp;amp;, &amp;quot;, &amp;apos;) with arbitrary values. This bypasses entity encoding and leads to XSS when parsed output is rendered. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27020 | Photobooth has a XSS vulnerability in user input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27020</link><description>Photobooth prior to 1.0.1 has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in user input fields. Malicious users could inject scripts through unvalidated form inputs. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2857 | D-Link DWR-M960 Port Forwarding Configuration Endpoint formPortFw sub_423E00 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2857</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this issue is the function sub_423E00 of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component Port Forwarding Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument submit-url causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24892 | openITCOCKPIT has Unsafe Deserialization in openITCOCKPIT Changelog Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24892</link><description>openITCOCKPIT is an open source monitoring tool built for different monitoring engines like Nagios, Naemon and Prometheus. openITCOCKPIT Community Edition 5.3.1 and earlier contains an unsafe PHP deserialization pattern in the processing of changelog entries. Serialized changelog data derived from attacker-influenced application state is unserialized without restricting allowed classes. Although no current application endpoint was found to introduce PHP objects into this data path, the presence of an unrestricted unserialize() call constitutes a latent PHP object injection vulnerability. If future code changes, plugins, or refactors introduce object values into this path, the vulnerability could become immediately exploitable with severe impact, including potential remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27190 | Deno has a Command Injection via Incomplete shell metacharacter blocklist in node:child_process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27190</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime. Prior to 2.6.8, a command injection vulnerability exists in Deno's node:child_process implementation. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62326 | HCL Digital Experience is susceptible to stored cross-site scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62326</link><description>HCL Digital Experience is susceptible to stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in the administrative user interface which would require elevated privileges to exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2855 | D-Link DWR-M960 DDNS Settings formDdns sub_4648F0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2855</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected is the function sub_4648F0 of the file /boafrm/formDdns of the component DDNS Settings Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 20:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34438 | WordPress Shared Files plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34438</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Anssi Laitila Shared Files shared-files.This issue affects Shared Files: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43228 | WordPress SecuPress Free plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43228</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SecuPress SecuPress Free secupress.This issue affects SecuPress Free: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50452 | WordPress Nexter Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50452</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POSIMYTH Nexter Blocks the-plus-addons-for-block-editor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Nexter Blocks: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50555 | WordPress Elementor Website Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.29.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50555</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elementor Elementor Website Builder elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Website Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 3.29.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51915 | WordPress LiteSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51915</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LiteSpeed Technologies LiteSpeed Cache litespeed-cache allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LiteSpeed Cache: from n/a through &lt;= 6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52387 | WordPress  Master Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9.9.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52387</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Liton Arefin Master Addons for Elementor master-addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Master Addons for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.9.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54222 | WordPress Seraphinite Accelerator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.22.15 - Authenticated Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54222</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Seraphinite Solutions Seraphinite Accelerator seraphinite-accelerator allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Seraphinite Accelerator: from n/a through &lt;= 2.22.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56208 | WordPress NewsMash theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.71 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56208</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in desertthemes NewsMash newsmash allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NewsMash: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.71.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52744 | WordPress Inpersttion For Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52744</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in inpersttion Inpersttion For Theme err-our-team allows Code Injection.This issue affects Inpersttion For Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53217 | WordPress AIO WP Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53217</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in staviravn AIO WP Builder all-in-one-wp-builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AIO WP Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53228 | WordPress bbpress Simple Advert Units Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.41 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jezza101 bbpress Simple Advert Units bbpress-simple-advert-units allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects bbpress Simple Advert Units: from n/a through &lt;= 0.41.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53231 | WordPress Easy Taxonomy Images plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdevstudio Easy Taxonomy Images easy-taxonomy-images allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Taxonomy Images: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53233 | WordPress Storyform plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RylanH Storyform storyform allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Storyform: from n/a through &lt;= 0.6.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53237 | WordPress WP Wizard Cloak Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53237</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Soflyy WP Wizard Cloak wp-wizard-cloak allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Wizard Cloak: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60087 | WordPress Extensive VC Addons for WPBakery page builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60087</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Nenad Obradovic Extensive VC Addons for WPBakery page builder extensive-vc-addon allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Extensive VC Addons for WPBakery page builder: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60183 | WordPress Silencesoft RSS Reader Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60183</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in silence Silencesoft RSS Reader external-rss-reader allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Silencesoft RSS Reader: from n/a through &lt;= 0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67547 | WordPress Konte theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67547</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in uixthemes Konte konte allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Konte: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67624 | WordPress Optimize More! – Images plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67624</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arya Dhiratara Optimize More! &amp;#8211; Images optimize-more-images allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Optimize More! &amp;#8211; Images: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67969 | WordPress UPI QR Code Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67969</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in knitpay UPI QR Code Payment Gateway for WooCommerce upi-qr-code-payment-for-woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects UPI QR Code Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67970 | WordPress Schedula plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67970</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in vertim Schedula schedula-smart-appointment-booking allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Schedula: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67971 | WordPress FluentCart plugin &amp;lt; 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67971</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPManageNinja FluentCart fluent-cart allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FluentCart: from n/a through &lt; 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67972 | WordPress Prague plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67972</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fox-themes Prague prague-plugins allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Prague: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67973 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67973</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sunshinephotocart Sunshine Photo Cart sunshine-photo-cart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: from n/a through &lt;= 3.5.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67974 | WordPress WPLegalPages plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67974</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Legal Pages WPLegalPages wplegalpages allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WPLegalPages: from n/a through &lt;= 3.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67975 | WordPress aDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67975</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in aDirectory aDirectory adirectory allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects aDirectory: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67977 | WordPress HAPPY plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67977</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VillaTheme HAPPY happy-helpdesk-support-ticket-system allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HAPPY: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67978 | WordPress Educare plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67978</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FixBD Educare educare allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Educare: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67979 | WordPress WPForms Google Sheet Connector plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67979</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WesternDeal WPForms Google Sheet Connector gsheetconnector-wpforms allows Code Injection.This issue affects WPForms Google Sheet Connector: from n/a through &lt;= 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67980 | WordPress Hara theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.17 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67980</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Hara hara allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Hara: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67981 | WordPress Besa theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67981</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Besa besa allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Besa: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67982 | WordPress Urna theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67982</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Urna urna allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Urna: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67984 | WordPress NPS computy plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67984</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in calliko NPS computy nps-computy allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects NPS computy: from n/a through &lt;= 2.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67987 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master plugin &amp;lt;= 10.3.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ExpressTech Systems Quiz And Survey Master quiz-master-next allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through &lt;= 10.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67988 | WordPress CozyStay theme &amp;lt; 1.9.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67988</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in LoftOcean CozyStay cozystay allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects CozyStay: from n/a through &lt; 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67990 | WordPress GMap Targeting plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67990</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RealMag777 GMap Targeting gmap-targeting allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects GMap Targeting: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67991 | WordPress User Extra Fields plugin &amp;lt;= 16.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67991</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vanquish User Extra Fields wp-user-extra-fields allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects User Extra Fields: from n/a through &lt;= 16.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67992 | WordPress PatioTime theme &amp;lt; 2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67992</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in LoftOcean PatioTime patiotime allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PatioTime: from n/a through &lt; 2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67993 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67993</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Vito Peleg Atarim atarim-visual-collaboration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67994 | WordPress YayCurrency plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67994</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YayCommerce YayCurrency yaycurrency allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects YayCurrency: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67995 | WordPress PatioTime theme &amp;lt; 2.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67995</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in LoftOcean PatioTime patiotime allows Object Injection.This issue affects PatioTime: from n/a through &lt; 2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67996 | WordPress Nestin theme &amp;lt; 1.2.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67996</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Nestin nestin allows Object Injection.This issue affects Nestin: from n/a through &lt; 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67997 | WordPress Travelicious theme &amp;lt; 1.6.7 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67997</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Travelicious travelicious allows Object Injection.This issue affects Travelicious: from n/a through &lt; 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67998 | WordPress Miraculous Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67998</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in kamleshyadav Miraculous Elementor miraculous-el allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Miraculous Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68000 | WordPress Testimonial Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68000</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PickPlugins Testimonial Slider testimonial allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Testimonial Slider: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68002 | WordPress Open User Map plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.16 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68002</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in 100plugins Open User Map open-user-map allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Open User Map: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68005 | WordPress Easy Hotel Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68005</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themewant Easy Hotel Booking easy-hotel allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Hotel Booking: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68021 | WordPress ConveyThis plugin &amp;lt;= 269.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68021</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ConveyThis ConveyThis conveythis-translate allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ConveyThis: from n/a through &lt;= 269.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68022 | WordPress Plugin BlueX for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68022</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in soporteblue Plugin BlueX for WooCommerce bluex-for-woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Plugin BlueX for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68023 | WordPress Addonify – Compare Products For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.17 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68023</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Addonify Addonify &amp;#8211; Compare Products For WooCommerce addonify-compare-products allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Addonify &amp;#8211; Compare Products For WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68024 | WordPress Addonify – WooCommerce Wishlist plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68024</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Addonify Addonify – WooCommerce Wishlist addonify-wishlist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Addonify – WooCommerce Wishlist: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68025 | WordPress Addonify Floating Cart For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.17 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68025</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Addonify Addonify Floating Cart For WooCommerce addonify-floating-cart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Addonify Floating Cart For WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68026 | WordPress LC Wizard plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68026</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Niaj Morshed LC Wizard ghl-wizard allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects LC Wizard: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68028 | WordPress GA4WP: Google Analytics for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68028</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Passionate Brains GA4WP: Google Analytics for WordPress ga-for-wp allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects GA4WP: Google Analytics for WordPress: from n/a through &lt;= 2.10.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68031 | WordPress افزونه پیامک حرفه ای فراز اس ام اس plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68031</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in faraz sms افزونه پیامک حرفه ای فراز اس ام اس farazsms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects افزونه پیامک حرفه ای فراز اس ام اس: from n/a through &lt;= 2.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68032 | WordPress Advanced WC Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19.0 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68032</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Passionate Brains Advanced WC Analytics advance-wc-analytics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced WC Analytics: from n/a through &lt;= 3.19.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68037 | WordPress Export Media URLs plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68037</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Atlas Gondal Export Media URLs export-media-urls allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Export Media URLs: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68042 | WordPress Travelpayouts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68042</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Travelpayouts Travelpayouts travelpayouts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Travelpayouts: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68043 | WordPress LottieFiles plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68043</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LottieFiles LottieFiles lottiefiles allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects LottieFiles: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68048 | WordPress NextMove Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.23.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68048</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in XLPlugins NextMove Lite woo-thank-you-page-nextmove-lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects NextMove Lite: from n/a through &lt;= 2.23.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68050 | WordPress Leadpages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68050</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leadpages Leadpages leadpages allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Leadpages: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68051 | WordPress Shiprocket plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68051</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Shiprocket Shiprocket shiprocket allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Shiprocket: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68069 | WordPress Directorist plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68069</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpWax Directorist directorist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Directorist: from n/a through &lt;= 8.5.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68495 | WordPress JetEngine plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68495</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetEngine jet-engine allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects JetEngine: from n/a through &lt;= 3.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68501 | WordPress Mollie Payments for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68501</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mollie Mollie Payments for WooCommerce mollie-payments-for-woocommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mollie Payments for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 8.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68514 | WordPress Paid Member Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.8 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68514</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Paid Member Subscriptions paid-member-subscriptions allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Paid Member Subscriptions: from n/a through &lt;= 2.16.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68526 | WordPress Modal Popup Box plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68526</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in A WP Life Modal Popup Box modal-popup-box allows Object Injection.This issue affects Modal Popup Box: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68531 | WordPress ModelTheme Addons for WPBakery and Elementor plugin &amp;lt; 1.5.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68531</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in modeltheme ModelTheme Addons for WPBakery and Elementor modeltheme-addons-for-wpbakery allows Object Injection.This issue affects ModelTheme Addons for WPBakery and Elementor: from n/a through &lt; 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68534 | WordPress PDF for WPForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68534</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for WPForms pdf-for-wpforms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PDF for WPForms: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68536 | WordPress Zota theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68536</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Zota zota allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Zota: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68539 | WordPress Fana theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.35 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68539</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Fana fana allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fana: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.35.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68541 | WordPress Ippsum theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68541</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Ippsum ippsum allows Object Injection.This issue affects Ippsum: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68542 | WordPress Checkout Gateway for IRIS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68542</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in vgdevsolutions Checkout Gateway for IRIS checkout-gateway-iris allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Checkout Gateway for IRIS: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68543 | WordPress Diza theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68543</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Diza diza allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Diza: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68545 | WordPress Nika theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68545</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in thembay Nika nika allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Nika: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68549 | WordPress Wiguard theme &amp;lt; 2.0.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68549</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in zozothemes Wiguard wiguard allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Wiguard: from n/a through &lt; 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68552 | WordPress WooCommerce Coming Soon Product with Countdown plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68552</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WebCodingPlace WooCommerce Coming Soon Product with Countdown woo-coming-soon-product allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WooCommerce Coming Soon Product with Countdown: from n/a through &lt;= 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68564 | WordPress Sendy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68564</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sendy Sendy sendy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sendy: from n/a through &lt;= 3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68834 | WordPress Sync Master Sheet – Product Sync with Google Sheet for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68834</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saiful Islam Sync Master Sheet &amp;#8211; Product Sync with Google Sheet for WooCommerce product-sync-master-sheet allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sync Master Sheet &amp;#8211; Product Sync with Google Sheet for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68837 | WordPress ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68837</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ELEXtensions ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System elex-helpdesk-customer-support-ticket-system allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68841 | WordPress TopperPack – Complete Elementor Addons, theme &amp;amp; CPT Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68841</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Themepul TopperPack – Complete Elementor Addons, Theme &amp;amp; CPT Builder topper-pack allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects TopperPack – Complete Elementor Addons, Theme &amp;amp; CPT Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68842 | WordPress Widget Logic Visual plugin &amp;lt;= 1.52 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68842</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in totalbounty Widget Logic Visual widget-logic-visual allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Widget Logic Visual: from n/a through &lt;= 1.52.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68843 | WordPress FeedWordPress Advanced Filters plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68843</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bas Schuiling FeedWordPress Advanced Filters faf allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FeedWordPress Advanced Filters: from n/a through &lt;= 0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68844 | WordPress Membee Login plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68844</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DaleAB Membee Login membees-member-login-widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Membee Login: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68845 | WordPress eDS Responsive Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68845</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in aThemeArt Translations eDS Responsive Menu eds-responsive-menu allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects eDS Responsive Menu: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68846 | WordPress Asynchronous Javascript plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68846</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Paris Holley Asynchronous Javascript asynchronous-javascript allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Asynchronous Javascript: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68847 | WordPress iSape plugin &amp;lt;= 0.72 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68847</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in itex iSape isape allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects iSape: from n/a through &lt;= 0.72.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68848 | WordPress amr cron manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Reflecte dCross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68848</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in anmari amr cron manager amr-cron-manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects amr cron manager: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68852 | WordPress Court Reservation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68852</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webmuehle Court Reservation court-reservation allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Court Reservation: from n/a through &lt;= 1.10.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68853 | WordPress Contact Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 9.1.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68853</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Kleor Contact Manager contact-manager allows Object Injection.This issue affects Contact Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 9.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68854 | WordPress ID Arrays plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - POST-Based Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68854</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in harman79 ID Arrays id-arrays allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects ID Arrays: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68855 | WordPress JobBoard Job listing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68855</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in themeglow JobBoard Job listing job-board-light allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects JobBoard Job listing: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68856 | WordPress Mopinion Feedback Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68856</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in keeswolters Mopinion Feedback Form mopinion-feedback-form allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Mopinion Feedback Form: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68862 | WordPress Woo File Dropzone plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68862</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Murtaza Bhurgri Woo File Dropzone woo-file-dropzone allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Woo File Dropzone: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68863 | WordPress iContact for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68863</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zack Katz iContact for Gravity Forms gravity-forms-icontact allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects iContact for Gravity Forms: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68880 | WordPress Simple Archive Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68880</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in peterwsterling Simple Archive Generator simple-archive-generator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Archive Generator: from n/a through &lt;= 5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68895 | WordPress AhaChat Messenger Marketing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68895</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in ahachat AhaChat Messenger Marketing ahachat-messenger-marketing allows Password Recovery Exploitation.This issue affects AhaChat Messenger Marketing: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69011 | WordPress Cool Tag Cloud plugin &amp;lt;= 2.29 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69011</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPKube Cool Tag Cloud cool-tag-cloud allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cool Tag Cloud: from n/a through &lt;= 2.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69063 | WordPress New User Approve plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69063</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saad Iqbal New User Approve new-user-approve allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects New User Approve: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69294 | WordPress PeakShops theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69294</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in fuelthemes PeakShops peakshops allows Object Injection.This issue affects PeakShops: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69295 | WordPress Coven Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69295</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Coven Core coven-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Coven Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69296 | WordPress Aardvark theme &amp;lt;= 4.6.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69296</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhostPool Aardvark aardvark allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Aardvark: from n/a through &lt;= 4.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69297 | WordPress Aardvark Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69297</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GhostPool Aardvark Plugin aardvark-plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Aardvark Plugin: from n/a through &lt;= 2.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69298 | WordPress Gauge theme &amp;lt;= 6.56.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69298</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GhostPool Gauge gauge allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gauge: from n/a through &lt;= 6.56.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69299 | WordPress Oxygen theme &amp;lt;= 6.0.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69299</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Laborator Oxygen oxygen allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Oxygen: from n/a through &lt;= 6.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69301 | WordPress PhotoMe theme &amp;lt;= 5.6.11 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69301</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods PhotoMe photome allows Object Injection.This issue affects PhotoMe: from n/a through &lt;= 5.6.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69302 | WordPress DesignThemes Core Features plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69302</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in designthemes DesignThemes Core Features designthemes-core-features allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DesignThemes Core Features: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69303 | WordPress ModelTheme Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69303</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in modeltheme ModelTheme Framework modeltheme-framework allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ModelTheme Framework: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69304 | WordPress Allmart plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Allmart allmart-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Allmart: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69305 | WordPress Crete Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Crete Core crete-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Crete Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69306 | WordPress Electio Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Electio Core electio-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Electio Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69307 | WordPress Medinik Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Medinik Core medinik-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Medinik Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69308 | WordPress Nestbyte Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69308</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Nestbyte Core nestbyte-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Nestbyte Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69309 | WordPress Saasplate Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69309</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Saasplate Core saasplate-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Saasplate Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69310 | WordPress Woodly Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69310</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Woodly Core woodly-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Woodly Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69322 | WordPress PeakShops theme &amp;lt; 1.5.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69322</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in fuelthemes PeakShops peakshops allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PeakShops: from n/a through &lt; 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69323 | WordPress Slimstat Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69323</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VeronaLabs Slimstat Analytics wp-slimstat allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Slimstat Analytics: from n/a through &lt;= 5.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69324 | WordPress NEX-Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 9.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Basix NEX-Forms nex-forms-express-wp-form-builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NEX-Forms: from n/a through &lt;= 9.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69325 | WordPress Primer MyData for Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.8 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69325</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in primersoftware Primer MyData for Woocommerce primer-mydata allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Primer MyData for Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69326 | WordPress NEX-Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 9.1.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69326</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Basix NEX-Forms nex-forms-express-wp-form-builder allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects NEX-Forms: from n/a through &lt;= 9.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69328 | WordPress Booking and Rental Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.9 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69328</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in magepeopleteam Booking and Rental Manager booking-and-rental-manager-for-woocommerce allows Object Injection.This issue affects Booking and Rental Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69329 | WordPress Prestige theme &amp;lt; 1.4.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69329</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Jthemes Prestige prestige allows Object Injection.This issue affects Prestige: from n/a through &lt; 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69330 | WordPress Prestige theme &amp;lt; 1.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69330</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jthemes Prestige prestige allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Prestige: from n/a through &lt; 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69337 | WordPress Wolmart Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69337</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in don-themes Wolmart Core wolmart-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Wolmart Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69365 | WordPress Uroan Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69365</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Uroan Core uroan-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Uroan Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69366 | WordPress Emerce Core plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69366</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in TeconceTheme Emerce Core emerce-core allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Emerce Core: from n/a through &lt;= 1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69367 | WordPress Oyster - Photography WordPress Theme theme &amp;lt;= 4.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69367</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GT3themes Oyster - Photography WordPress Theme oyster allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Oyster - Photography WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 4.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69368 | WordPress SOHO - Photography WordPress Theme theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69368</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GT3themes SOHO - Photography WordPress Theme soho allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects SOHO - Photography WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69370 | WordPress Capella theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69370</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods Capella capella allows Object Injection.This issue affects Capella: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69371 | WordPress KindlyCare theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69371</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes KindlyCare kindlycare allows Object Injection.This issue affects KindlyCare: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69372 | WordPress SevenHills theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69372</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes SevenHills sevenhills allows Object Injection.This issue affects SevenHills: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69373 | WordPress VidoRev theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.9.9.9.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69373</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in beeteam368 VidoRev vidorev allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects VidoRev: from n/a through &lt;= 2.9.9.9.9.9.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69374 | WordPress Eleblog – Elementor Blog And Magazine Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69374</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SolverWp Eleblog – Elementor Blog And Magazine Addons ele-blog allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Eleblog – Elementor Blog And Magazine Addons: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69375 | WordPress Portfolio Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69375</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SolverWp Portfolio Builder swp-portfolio allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Portfolio Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69376 | WordPress User Extra Fields plugin &amp;lt;= 17.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69376</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in vanquish User Extra Fields wp-user-extra-fields allows Path Traversal.This issue affects User Extra Fields: from n/a through &lt;= 17.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69377 | WordPress User Extra Fields plugin &amp;lt;= 17.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69377</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in vanquish User Extra Fields wp-user-extra-fields allows Path Traversal.This issue affects User Extra Fields: from n/a through &lt;= 17.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69378 | WordPress Product Filter for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 9.1.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69378</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in XforWooCommerce Product Filter for WooCommerce prdctfltr allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Product Filter for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 9.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69379 | WordPress Upload Files Anywhere plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69379</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in vanquish Upload Files Anywhere wp-upload-files-anywhere allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Upload Files Anywhere: from n/a through &lt;= 2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69380 | WordPress Upload Files Anywhere plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69380</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in vanquish Upload Files Anywhere wp-upload-files-anywhere allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Upload Files Anywhere: from n/a through &lt;= 2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69381 | WordPress WooCommerce Bulk Product Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69381</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in vanquish WooCommerce Bulk Product Editor woocommerce-quick-product-editor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Bulk Product Editor: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69382 | WordPress Themesflat Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69382</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themesflat Themesflat Elementor themesflat-elementor allows Object Injection.This issue affects Themesflat Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69383 | WordPress WP shop plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69383</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Agence web Eoxia - Montpellier WP shop wpshop allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WP shop: from n/a through &lt;= 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69384 | WordPress Timeline Event History plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69384</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdiscover Timeline Event History timeline-event-history allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Timeline Event History: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69385 | WordPress Cartify - WooCommerce Gutenberg WordPress Theme theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69385</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AgniHD Cartify - WooCommerce Gutenberg WordPress Theme cartify allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cartify - WooCommerce Gutenberg WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69386 | WordPress RVCFDI para Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69386</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realvirtualmx RVCFDI para Woocommerce rvcfdi-para-woocommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects RVCFDI para Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 8.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69387 | WordPress Simple Retail Menus plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69387</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in whatwouldjessedo Simple Retail Menus simple-retail-menus allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Simple Retail Menus: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69388 | WordPress Cliengo – Chatbot plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69388</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in cliengo Cliengo – Chatbot cliengo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cliengo – Chatbot: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69389 | WordPress Visitor Maps Extended Referer Field plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69389</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hugh Mungus Visitor Maps Extended Referer Field visitor-maps-extended-referer-field allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Visitor Maps Extended Referer Field: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69390 | WordPress Business Template Blocks for WPBakery (Visual Composer) Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69390</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themebon Business Template Blocks for WPBakery (Visual Composer) Page Builder templates-and-addons-for-wpbakery-page-builder allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Business Template Blocks for WPBakery (Visual Composer) Page Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69391 | WordPress Diamond theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69391</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GT3themes Diamond diamond allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Diamond: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69392 | WordPress iMoney plugin &amp;lt;= 0.36 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69392</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in itex iMoney imoney allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects iMoney: from n/a through &lt;= 0.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69393 | WordPress Exzo theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69393</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jthemes Exzo exzo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Exzo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69394 | WordPress Cnvrse plugin &amp;lt;= 026.02.10.20 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69394</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in cnvrse Cnvrse cnvrse allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cnvrse: from n/a through &lt;= 026.02.10.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69395 | WordPress Gable theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69395</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Gable gable allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Gable: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69396 | WordPress Splendour theme &amp;lt;= 1.23 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69396</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Splendour splendour allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Splendour: from n/a through &lt;= 1.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69397 | WordPress Tint theme &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69397</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Tint tint allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Tint: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69398 | WordPress Plank theme &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69398</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Plank plank allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Plank: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69399 | WordPress Cobble theme &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69399</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Cobble cobble allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Cobble: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69400 | WordPress Yokoo theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.11 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69400</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX Yokoo yokoo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Yokoo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69401 | WordPress WooODT Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Payment Bypass Vulnerability vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69401</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in mdalabar WooODT Lite byconsole-woo-order-delivery-time allows Identity Spoofing.This issue affects WooODT Lite: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69402 | WordPress R&amp;amp;F theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69402</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX R&amp;amp;F rf allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects R&amp;amp;F: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69403 | WordPress Bravis Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69403</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Bravis-Themes Bravis Addons bravis-addons allows Using Malicious Files.This issue affects Bravis Addons: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69404 | WordPress Extreme Store theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69404</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeREX Extreme Store extremestore allows Object Injection.This issue affects Extreme Store: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69405 | WordPress Lorem Ipsum | Books &amp;amp; Media Store theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69405</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeREX Lorem Ipsum | Books &amp; Media Store lorem-ipsum-books-media-store allows Object Injection.This issue affects Lorem Ipsum | Books &amp; Media Store: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69406 | WordPress FreightCo theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69406</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeREX FreightCo freightco allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects FreightCo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69407 | WordPress Struktur theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69407</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Select-Themes Struktur struktur allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Struktur: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69408 | WordPress HealthFirst theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69408</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes HealthFirst healthfirst allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects HealthFirst: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69409 | WordPress PJ | Life &amp;amp; Business Coaching theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69409</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes PJ | Life &amp; Business Coaching pj allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PJ | Life &amp; Business Coaching: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69410 | WordPress Belletrist theme &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69410</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Edge-Themes Belletrist belletrist allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Belletrist: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70831 | A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was found in Smanga 3.2.7 in the /php/path/rescan.php interface. The application fails to proper...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70831</link><description>A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was found in Smanga 3.2.7 in the /php/path/rescan.php interface. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the mediaId parameter before using it in a system shell command. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary operating system commands, leading to complete server compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22341 | WordPress Booked plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22341</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Case-Themes Booked booked allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Booked: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22344 | WordPress FiveStar theme &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22344</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes FiveStar fivestar allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects FiveStar: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22345 | WordPress Image Gallery – Lightbox Gallery, Responsive Photo Gallery, Masonry Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22345</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in A WP Life Image Gallery – Lightbox Gallery, Responsive Photo Gallery, Masonry Gallery new-image-gallery allows Object Injection.This issue affects Image Gallery – Lightbox Gallery, Responsive Photo Gallery, Masonry Gallery: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22346 | WordPress Slider Responsive Slideshow – Image slider, Gallery slideshow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22346</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in A WP Life Slider Responsive Slideshow – Image slider, Gallery slideshow slider-responsive-slideshow allows Object Injection.This issue affects Slider Responsive Slideshow – Image slider, Gallery slideshow: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22350 | WordPress PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22350</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder pdf-for-elementor-forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PDF for Elementor Forms + Drag And Drop Template Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22351 | WordPress WP FullCalendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22351</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Marcus (aka @msykes) WP FullCalendar wp-fullcalendar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP FullCalendar: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22352 | WordPress Persian Woocommerce SMS plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22352</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PersianScript Persian Woocommerce SMS persian-woocommerce-sms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Persian Woocommerce SMS: from n/a through &lt;= 7.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22354 | WordPress Woocommerce Category Banner Management plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22354</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Dotstore Woocommerce Category Banner Management banner-management-for-woocommerce allows Object Injection.This issue affects Woocommerce Category Banner Management: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22356 | WordPress Jetpack CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 6.7.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22356</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Automattic Jetpack CRM zero-bs-crm allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Jetpack CRM: from n/a through &lt;= 6.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22357 | WordPress Link Whisper Free plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22357</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spencer Haws Link Whisper Free link-whisper allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Link Whisper Free: from n/a through &lt;= 0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22361 | WordPress A-Mart theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22361</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes A-Mart a-mart allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects A-Mart: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22362 | WordPress Photolia theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22362</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Photolia photolia allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Photolia: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22363 | WordPress Rhodos theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22363</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Rhodos rhodos allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Rhodos: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22364 | WordPress SevenTrees theme &amp;lt;=1.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22364</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes SevenTrees seventrees allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects SevenTrees: from n/a through &lt;=1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22365 | WordPress Soleng theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22365</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Soleng soleng allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Soleng: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22366 | WordPress Jude theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22366</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Jude jude allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Jude: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22367 | WordPress Coworking theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22367</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Coworking coworking allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Coworking: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22368 | WordPress Redy theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22368</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Redy redy allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Redy: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22369 | WordPress Ironfit theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22369</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Ironfit ironfit allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Ironfit: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22370 | WordPress Marveland theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22370</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axiomthemes Marveland marveland allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Marveland: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22371 | WordPress Gustavo theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22371</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Gustavo gustavo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Gustavo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22372 | WordPress Isida theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22372</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Isida isida allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Isida: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22373 | WordPress Fooddy theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22373</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Fooddy fooddy allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fooddy: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22374 | WordPress Zio Alberto theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22374</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Zio Alberto zioalberto allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Zio Alberto: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22375 | WordPress Impacto Patronus theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22375</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Impacto Patronus impacto-patronus allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Impacto Patronus: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22376 | WordPress Parkivia theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22376</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Parkivia parkivia allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Parkivia: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22377 | WordPress Saveo theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22377</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Saveo saveo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Saveo: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22378 | WordPress Blabber theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22378</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Blabber blabber allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Blabber: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22379 | WordPress Netmix theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22379</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes Netmix netmix allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Netmix: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22380 | WordPress UnlimHost theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22380</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AncoraThemes UnlimHost unlimhost allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects UnlimHost: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22381 | WordPress PawFriends - Pet Shop and Veterinary WordPress Theme theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22381</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes PawFriends - Pet Shop and Veterinary WordPress Theme pawfriends allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PawFriends - Pet Shop and Veterinary WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22383 | WordPress PawFriends - Pet Shop and Veterinary WordPress theme theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22383</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Mikado-Themes PawFriends - Pet Shop and Veterinary WordPress Theme pawfriends allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PawFriends - Pet Shop and Veterinary WordPress Theme: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22384 | WordPress Applay - Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22384</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in leafcolor Applay - Shortcodes applay-shortcodes allows Object Injection.This issue affects Applay - Shortcodes: from n/a through &lt;= 3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24941 | WordPress WP Job Portal plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24941</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpjobportal WP Job Portal wp-job-portal allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through &lt;= 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24943 | WordPress Grand Conference theme &amp;lt;= 5.3.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24943</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGoods Grand Conference grandconference allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Grand Conference: from n/a through &lt;= 5.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24944 | WordPress Subscribe2 plugin &amp;lt;= 10.44 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24944</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in weDevs Subscribe2 subscribe2 allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Subscribe2: from n/a through &lt;= 10.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24946 | WordPress Print Invoice &amp;amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24946</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tychesoftwares Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce woocommerce-delivery-notes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 5.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24948 | WordPress Reflector plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24948</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fox-themes Reflector reflector-plugins allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Reflector: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24949 | WordPress PhotoMe theme &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24949</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGoods PhotoMe photome allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects PhotoMe: from n/a through &lt;= 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24950 | WordPress Authorsy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24950</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in themeplugs Authorsy authorsy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Authorsy: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24953 | WordPress Simple File List plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.15 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24953</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Mitchell Bennis Simple File List simple-file-list allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Simple File List: from n/a through &lt;= 6.1.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24955 | WordPress Whizz Plugins plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24955</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fox-themes Whizz Plugins whizz-plugins allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Whizz Plugins: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24956 | WordPress Download Manager Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24956</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Shahjada Download Manager Addons for Elementor wpdm-elementor allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Download Manager Addons for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24959 | WordPress JS Help Desk plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24959</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in JoomSky JS Help Desk js-support-ticket allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects JS Help Desk: from n/a through &lt;= 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27072 | WordPress PixelYourSite – Your smart PIXEL (TAG) Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 11.2.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27072</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PixelYourSite PixelYourSite – Your smart PIXEL (TAG) Manager pixelyoursite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PixelYourSite – Your smart PIXEL (TAG) Manager: from n/a through &lt;= 11.2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14547 | ECJ-PAKE Integer Underflow Vulnerability in Silicon Labs PSA Crypto and SE Manager APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14547</link><description>An integer underflow vulnerability is present in Silicon Lab’s implementation of PSA Crypto and SE Manager EC-JPAKE APIs during ZKP parsing. Triggering the underflow can lead to a hard fault, causing a temporary denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21627 | Extension - tassos.gr - SQL injection and Unauthenticated File Read in Novarain/Tassos Framework v4.10.14 – v6.0.37 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21627</link><description>The vulnerability was rooted in how the Tassos Framework plugin handled specific AJAX requests through Joomla’s com_ajax entry point. Under certain conditions, internal framework functionality could be invoked without proper restriction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10970 | SQLi in Kolay Software&amp;#x27;s Talentics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10970</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Kolay Software Inc. Talentics allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Talentics: through 20022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2486 | Master Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;ma_el_bh_table_btn_text&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2486</link><description>The Master Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ma_el_bh_table_btn_text' parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21620 | TFTP Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21620</link><description>Relative Path Traversal, Improper Isolation or Compartmentalization vulnerability in erlang otp erlang/otp (tftp_file modules), erlang otp inets (tftp_file modules), erlang otp tftp (tftp_file modules) allows Relative Path Traversal. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/tftp/src/tftp_file.erl, src/tftp_file.Erl.

This issue affects otp: from 17.0, from 07b8f441ca711f9812fad9e9115bab3c3aa92f79; otp: from 5.10 before 7.0; otp: from 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26050 | The installer for ジョブログ集計/分析ソフトウェア RICOHジョブログ集計ツール versions prior to Ver.1.3.7 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26050</link><description>The installer for ジョブログ集計/分析ソフトウェア RICOHジョブログ集計ツール versions prior to Ver.1.3.7 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59819 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Read via filepath parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59819</link><description>This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to read an arbitrary file by changing a filepath parameter into an internal system path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26370 | WordPress Plugin "Survey Maker" versions 5.1.7.7 and prior contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26370</link><description>WordPress Plugin "Survey Maker" versions 5.1.7.7 and prior contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed in the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2825 | rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss Article fix.py fix_html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2825</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss up to 1.4.8. This impacts the function fix_html of the file tools/fix.py of the component Article Module. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2824 | Comfast CF-E7 webmggnt mbox-config sub_441CF4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2824</link><description>A flaw has been found in Comfast CF-E7 2.6.0.9. This affects the function sub_441CF4 of the file /cgi-bin/mbox-config?method=SET&amp;amp;section=ping_config of the component webmggnt. Executing a manipulation of the argument destination can lead to command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2739 | This affects versions of the package bn.js before 5.2.3. Calling maskn(0) on any BN instance corrupts the internal state, causing toString()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2739</link><description>This affects versions of the package bn.js before 5.2.3. Calling maskn(0) on any BN instance corrupts the internal state, causing toString(), divmod(), and other methods to enter an infinite loop, hanging the process indefinitely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2823 | Comfast CF-E7 webmggnt mbox-config sub_41ACCC command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2823</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Comfast CF-E7 2.6.0.9. The impacted element is the function sub_41ACCC of the file /cgi-bin/mbox-config?method=SET&amp;amp;section=ntp_timezone of the component webmggnt. Performing a manipulation of the argument timestr results in command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2822 | JeecgBoot Backend airag_app,1,create_by sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2822</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /jeecgboot/sys/dict/loadDict/airag_app,1,create_by of the component Backend Interface. Such manipulation of the argument keyword leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26991 | LibreNMS vulnerable to Stored Cross-site Scripting through unsanitized /device-groups name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26991</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. In versions 26.1.1 and below, the device group name is not sanitized, allowing attackers with admin privileges to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. When a user adds a device group, an HTTP POST request is sent to the Request-URI "/device-groups". The name of the newly created device group is stored in the value of the name parameter. After the device group is created, the entry is displayed along with relevant buttons such as Rediscover Devices, Edit, and Delete. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26992 | LibreNMS has Stored Cross-Site Scripting via unsanitized /port-groups name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26992</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. In versions 26.1.1 and below, the port group name is not sanitized, allowing attackers with admin privileges to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. When a user adds a port group, an HTTP POST request is sent to the Request-URI "/port-groups". The name of the newly created port group is stored in the value of the name parameter. After the port group is created, the entry is displayed along with relevant buttons such as Edit and Delete. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26993 | Flare has XSS vulnerability in Raw File Preview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26993</link><description>Flare is a Next.js-based, self-hostable file sharing platform that integrates with screenshot tools. Versions 1.7.0 and below allow users to upload files without proper content validation or sanitization. By embedding malicious JavaScript within an SVG (or other active content formats such as HTML or XML), an attacker can achieve script execution in the context of the application's origin when a victim views the file in “raw” mode. This results in a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that can be exploited to exfiltrate user data. This issue has been fixed in version 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26994 | uTLS ServerHellos are accepted without checking TLS 1.3 downgrade canaries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26994</link><description>uTLS is a fork of crypto/tls, created to customize ClientHello for fingerprinting resistance while still using it for the handshake. In versions 1.6.7 and below, uTLS did not implement the TLS 1.3 downgrade protection mechanism specified in RFC 8446 Section 4.1.3 when using a uTLS ClientHello spec. This allowed an active network adversary to downgrade TLS 1.3 connections initiated by a uTLS client to a lower TLS version (e.g., TLS 1.2) by modifying the ClientHello message to exclude the SupportedVersions extension, causing the server to respond with a TLS 1.2 ServerHello (along with a downgrade canary in the ServerHello random field). Because uTLS did not check the downgrade canary in the ServerHello random field, clients would accept the downgraded connection without detecting the attack. This attack could also be used by an active network attacker to fingerprint uTLS connections. This issue has been fixed in version 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26996 | minimatch has a ReDoS via repeated wildcards with non-matching literal in pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26996</link><description>minimatch is a minimal matching utility for converting glob expressions into JavaScript RegExp objects. Versions 10.2.0 and below are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) when a glob pattern contains many consecutive * wildcards followed by a literal character that doesn't appear in the test string. Each * compiles to a separate [^/]*? regex group, and when the match fails, V8's regex engine backtracks exponentially across all possible splits. The time complexity is O(4^N) where N is the number of * characters. With N=15, a single minimatch() call takes ~2 seconds. With N=34, it hangs effectively forever. Any application that passes user-controlled strings to minimatch() as the pattern argument is vulnerable to DoS. This issue has been fixed in version 10.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27017 | uTLS has a Chrome Parrot Fingerprint Vulnerability due to GREASE ECH Cipher Suite Mismatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27017</link><description>uTLS is a fork of crypto/tls, created to customize ClientHello for fingerprinting resistance while still using it for the handshake. Versions 1.6.0 through 1.8.0 contain a fingerprint mismatch with Chrome when using GREASE ECH, related to cipher suite selection. When Chrome selects the preferred cipher suite in the outer ClientHello and for ECH, it does so consistently based on hardware support—for example, if it prefers AES for the outer cipher suite, it also uses AES for ECH. However, the Chrome parrot in uTLS hardcodes AES preference for outer cipher suites but selects the ECH cipher suite randomly between AES and ChaCha20. This creates a 50% chance of selecting ChaCha20 for ECH while using AES for the outer cipher suite, a combination impossible in Chrome. This issue only affects GREASE ECH; in real ECH, Chrome selects the first valid cipher suite when AES is preferred, which uTLS handles correctly. This issue has been fixed in version 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2384 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 6.7.1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2384</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `vc_quizmaker` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.
Note: This vulnerability requires WPBakery Page Builder to be installed and active</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2821 | Fujian Smart Integrated Management Platform System XCamera.ashx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2821</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Fujian Smart Integrated Management Platform System up to 7.5. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Module/CRXT/Controller/XCamera.ashx. This manipulation of the argument ChannelName causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26064 | calibre: Path Traversal Vulnerability Enables Arbitrary File Write and Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26064</link><description>calibre is a cross-platform e-book manager for viewing, converting, editing, and cataloging e-books. Versions 9.2.1 and below contain a Path Traversal vulnerability that allows arbitrary file writes anywhere the user has write permissions. On Windows, this leads to Remote Code Execution by writing a payload to the Startup folder, which executes on next login. Function extract_pictures only checks startswith('Pictures'), and does not sanitize '..' sequences. calibre's own ZipFile.extractall() in utils/zipfile.py does sanitize '..' via _get_targetpath(), but extract_pictures() bypasses this by using manual zf.read() + open(). This issue has been fixed in version 9.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26065 | calibre: Path Traversal can Lead to Arbitrary File Write and Potential Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26065</link><description>calibre is a cross-platform e-book manager for viewing, converting, editing, and cataloging e-books. Versions 9.2.1 and below are vulnerable to Path Traversal through PDB readers (both 132-byte and 202-byte header variants) that allow arbitrary file writes with arbitrary extension and arbitrary content anywhere the user has write permissions. Files are written in 'wb' mode, silently overwriting existing files. This can lead to potential code execution and Denial of Service through file corruption. This issue has been fixed in version 9.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26989 | LibreNMS has Stored XSS in Alert Rule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26989</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Versions 25.12.0 and below are affected by a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Alert Rules workflow. An attacker with administrative privileges can inject malicious scripts that execute in the browser context of any user who accesses the Alert Rules page. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26990 | LibreNMS has Time-Based Blind SQL Injection in address-search.inc.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26990</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Versions 25.12.0 and below have a Time-Based Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in address-search.inc.php via the address parameter. When a crafted subnet prefix is supplied, the prefix value is concatenated directly into an SQL query without proper parameter binding, allowing an attacker to manipulate query logic and infer database information through time-based conditional responses. This vulnerability requires authentication and is exploitable by any authenticated user. This issue has been fixedd in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27016 | LibreNMS has Stored XSS in Custom OID - unit parameter missing strip_tags()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27016</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Versions 24.10.0 through 26.1.1 are vulnerable to Stored XSS via the unit parameter in Custom OID. The Custom OID functionality lacks strip_tags() sanitization while other fields (name, oid, datatype) are sanitized. The unsanitized value is stored in the database and rendered without HTML escaping. This issue is fixed in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2819 | Dromara RuoYi-Vue-Plus Workflow deleteByInstanceIds SaServletFilter authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2819</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Dromara RuoYi-Vue-Plus up to 5.5.3. This vulnerability affects the function SaServletFilter of the file /workflow/instance/deleteByInstanceIds of the component Workflow Module. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2820 | Fujian Smart Integrated Management Platform System XAccessPermissionPlus.ashx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2820</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Fujian Smart Integrated Management Platform System up to 7.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Module/CRXT/Controller/XAccessPermissionPlus.ashx. The manipulation of the argument DeviceIDS results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26960 | node-tar has Arbitrary File Read/Write via Hardlink Target Escape Through Symlink Chain in Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26960</link><description>node-tar is a full-featured Tar for Node.js. When using default options in versions 7.5.7 and below, an attacker-controlled archive can create a hardlink inside the extraction directory that points to a file outside the extraction root, enabling arbitrary file read and write as the extracting user. Severity is high because the primitive bypasses path protections and turns archive extraction into a direct filesystem access primitive. This issue has been fixed in version 7.5.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26977 | Frappe Learning Management System exposes details of unpublished courses to unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26977</link><description>Frappe Learning Management System (LMS) is a learning system that helps users structure their content. In versions 2.44.0 and below, unauthorized users are able to access the details of unpublished courses via API endpoints. A fix for this issue is planned for the 2.45.0 release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26980 | Ghost has a SQL Injection in its Content API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26980</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. Versions 3.24.0 through 6.19.0 allow unauthenticated attackers to perform arbitrary reads from the database. This issue has been fixed in version 6.19.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26987 | LibreNMS affected by reflected XSS via email field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26987</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Versions 25.12.0 and below are vulnerable to  Reflected XSS attacks via email field. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26988 | LibreNMS: SQL Injection in ajax_table.php spreads through a covert data stream</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26988</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring tool. Versions 25.12.0 and below contain an SQL Injection vulnerability in the ajax_table.php endpoint. The application fails to properly sanitize or parameterize user input when processing IPv6 address searches. Specifically, the address parameter is split into an address and a prefix, and the prefix portion is directly concatenated into the SQL query string without validation. This allows an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL commands, potentially leading to unauthorized data access or database manipulation. This issue has been fixed in version 26.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30410 | Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to missing authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30410</link><description>Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to missing authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 39870, Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 39938, Acronis Cyber Protect 15 (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 41800.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30411 | Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to improper authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30411</link><description>Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to improper authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 39938, Acronis Cyber Protect 15 (Linux, Windows) before build 41800.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30412 | Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to improper authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30412</link><description>Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to improper authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 39938, Acronis Cyber Protect 15 (Linux, Windows) before build 41800.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30416 | Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30416</link><description>Sensitive data disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 39938, Acronis Cyber Protect 15 (Linux, Windows) before build 41800.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26967 | PJSIP has a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in its H.264 unpacketizer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26967</link><description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C. In versions 2.16 and below, there is a critical Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in PJSIP's H.264 unpacketizer. The bug occurs when processing malformed SRTP packets, where the unpacketizer reads a 2-byte NAL unit size field without validating that both bytes are within the payload buffer bounds. The vulnerability affects applications that receive video using H.264. A patch is available at https://github.com/pjsip/pjproject/commit/f821c214e52b11bae11e4cd3c7f0864538fb5491.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26974 | Sylde has Improper Control of Generation of Code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26974</link><description>Slyde is a program that creates animated presentations from XML. In versions 0.0.4 and below, Node.js automatically imports **/*.plugin.{js,mjs} files including those from node_modules, so any malicious package with a .plugin.js file can execute arbitrary code when installed or required. All projects using this loading behavior are affected, especially those installing untrusted packages. This issue has been fixed in version 0.0.5. To workaround this issue, users can audit and restrict which packages are installed in node_modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26975 | Music Assistant Server Path Traversal in Playlist Update API Allows Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26975</link><description>Music Assistant is an open-source media library manager that integrates streaming services with connected speakers. Versions 2.6.3 and below allow unauthenticated network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. The music/playlists/update API allows users to bypass the .m3u extension enforcement and write files anywhere on the filesystem, which is exacerbated by the container running as root. This can be exploited to achieve Remote Code Execution by writing a malicious .pth file to the Python site-packages directory, which will execute arbitrary commands when Python loads. This issue has been fixed in version 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26964 | Windmill Exposes Workspace Slack OAuth Client Secrets to Non-Admin Workspace Members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26964</link><description>Windmill is an open-source developer platform for internal code: APIs, background jobs, workflows and UIs. Versions 1.634.6
 and below allow non-admin users to obtain Slack OAuth client secrets, which should only be accessible to workspace administrators. The GET /api/w/{workspace}/workspaces/get_settings endpoint returns the slack_oauth_client_secret to any authenticated workspace member, regardless of their admin status. It is expected behavior for non-admin users see a redacted version of workspace settings, as some of them are necessary for the frontend to behave correctly even for non-admins. However, the Slack configuration should not be visible to non-admins. This is a legacy issue where the setting was stored as a plain value instead of using $variable indirection, and it was never added to the redaction logic. This issue has been fixed in version 1.635.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>