<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:36:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-39935 | jc21 NGINX Proxy Manager before 2.11.3 allows backend/internal/certificate.js OS command injection by an authenticated user (with certificat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39935</link><description>jc21 NGINX Proxy Manager before 2.11.3 allows backend/internal/certificate.js OS command injection by an authenticated user (with certificate management privileges) via untrusted input to the DNS provider configuration. NOTE: this is not part of any NGINX software shipped by F5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6511 | y_project RuoYi Content-Type isJsonRequest cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6511</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in y_project RuoYi up to 4.7.9. Affected by this vulnerability is the function isJsonRequest of the component Content-Type Handler. The manipulation of the argument HttpHeaders.CONTENT_TYPE leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270343.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37471 | WordPress Woffice Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.8 - Site Wide Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37471</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice Core allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Woffice Core: from n/a through 5.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37472 | WordPress Woffice theme &amp;lt;= 5.4.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37472</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Woffice: from n/a through 5.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39934 | Robotmk before 2.0.1 allows a local user to escalate privileges (e.g., to SYSTEM) if automated Python environment setup is enabled, because ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39934</link><description>Robotmk before 2.0.1 allows a local user to escalate privileges (e.g., to SYSTEM) if automated Python environment setup is enabled, because the "shared holotree usage" feature allows any user to edit any Python environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37474 | WordPress Newspack Ads plugin &amp;lt;= 1.47.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37474</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Ads allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Newspack Ads: from n/a through 1.47.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37476 | WordPress Newspack Campaigns plugin &amp;lt;= 2.31.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37476</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Campaigns allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Newspack Campaigns: from n/a through 2.31.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 18:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39930 | The built-in SSH server of Gogs through 0.13.0 allows argument injection in internal/ssh/ssh.go, leading to remote code execution. Authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39930</link><description>The built-in SSH server of Gogs through 0.13.0 allows argument injection in internal/ssh/ssh.go, leading to remote code execution. Authenticated attackers can exploit this by opening an SSH connection and sending a malicious --split-string env request if the built-in SSH server is activated. Windows installations are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39931 | Gogs through 0.13.0 allows deletion of internal files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39931</link><description>Gogs through 0.13.0 allows deletion of internal files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39932 | Gogs through 0.13.0 allows argument injection during the previewing of changes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39932</link><description>Gogs through 0.13.0 allows argument injection during the previewing of changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39933 | Gogs through 0.13.0 allows argument injection during the tagging of a new release.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39933</link><description>Gogs through 0.13.0 allows argument injection during the tagging of a new release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39929 | Exim through 4.97.1 misparses a multiline RFC 2231 header filename, and thus remote attackers can bypass a $mime_filename extension-blocking...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39929</link><description>Exim through 4.97.1 misparses a multiline RFC 2231 header filename, and thus remote attackers can bypass a $mime_filename extension-blocking protection mechanism, and potentially deliver executable attachments to the mailboxes of end users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22277 | VMware Cloud Director Availability contains an HTML injection vulnerability. 
A
 malicious actor with network access to VMware Cloud Directo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22277</link><description>VMware Cloud Director Availability contains an HTML injection vulnerability. 
A
 malicious actor with network access to VMware Cloud Director 
Availability can craft malicious HTML tags to execute within replication
 tasks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39165 | QR/demoapp/qr_image.php in Asial JpGraph Professional through 4.2.6-pro allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a PHP payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39165</link><description>QR/demoapp/qr_image.php in Asial JpGraph Professional through 4.2.6-pro allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a PHP payload in the data parameter in conjunction with a .php file name in the filename parameter. This occurs because an unnecessary QR/demoapp folder.is shipped with the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6506 | Information exposure vulnerability in the MRW plug-in</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6506</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in the MRW plugin, in its 5.4.3 version, affecting the "mrw_log" functionality. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to obtain other customers' order information and access sensitive information such as name and phone number. This vulnerability also allows an attacker to create or overwrite shipping labels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39211 | Kaiten 57.128.8 allows remote attackers to enumerate user accounts via a crafted POST request, because a login response contains a user_emai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39211</link><description>Kaiten 57.128.8 allows remote attackers to enumerate user accounts via a crafted POST request, because a login response contains a user_email field only if the user account exists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6507 | Deep Lake Kaggle command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6507</link><description>Command injection when ingesting a remote Kaggle dataset due to a lack of input sanitization in the ingest_kaggle() API</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5943 | Nested Pages &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5943</link><description>The Nested Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'settingsPage' function and missing santization of the 'tab' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call local php files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 11:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32754 | - Exposure of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32754</link><description>Under certain circumstances, when the controller is in factory reset mode waiting for initial setup, it will broadcast its MAC address, serial number, and firmware version.  Once configured, the controller will no longer broadcast this information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3904 | Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Smart Device Communication Gateway preinstalled on MELIPC Series MI5122-VW firmware versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3904</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Smart Device Communication Gateway preinstalled on MELIPC Series MI5122-VW firmware versions "05" to "07" allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code by saving a malicious file to a specific folder. As a result, the attacker may disclose, tamper with, destroy or delete information in the product, or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 09:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1573 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in the mobile monitoring feature of ICONICS GENESIS64 versions 10.97 to 10.97.2, Mitsubishi Electric G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1573</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in the mobile monitoring feature of ICONICS GENESIS64 versions 10.97 to 10.97.2, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 versions 10.97 to 10.97.2 and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass proper authentication and log in to the system when all of the following conditions are met:  *  Active Directory is used in the security setting.
  *  “Automatic log in” option is enabled in the security setting.
  *  The IcoAnyGlass IIS Application Pool is running under an Active Directory Domain Account.
  *  The IcoAnyGlass IIS Application Pool account is included in GENESIS64TM and MC Works64 Security and has permission to log in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 09:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1574 | Use of Externally-Controlled Input to Select Classes or Code ('Unsafe Reflection') vulnerability in the licensing feature of ICONICS GENESIS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1574</link><description>Use of Externally-Controlled Input to Select Classes or Code ('Unsafe Reflection') vulnerability in the licensing feature of ICONICS GENESIS64 versions 10.97 to 10.97.2, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 versions 10.97 to 10.97.2 and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local attacker to execute a malicious code with administrative privileges by tampering with a specific file that is not protected by the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 09:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1182 | Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1182</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local attacker to execute a malicious code by storing a specially crafted DLL in a specific folder when GENESIS64 and MC Works64 are installed with the Pager agent in the alarm multi-agent notification feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39884 | Apache HTTP Server: source code disclosure with handlers configured via AddType</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39884</link><description>A regression in the core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.60 ignores some use of the legacy content-type based configuration of handlers.   "AddType" and similar configuration, under some circumstances where files are requested indirectly, result in source code disclosure of local content. For example, PHP scripts may be served instead of interpreted.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.61, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6318 | IMGspider &amp;lt;= 2.3.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;upload_img_file&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6318</link><description>The IMGspider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'upload_img_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6319 | IMGspider &amp;lt;= 2.3.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;upload&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6319</link><description>The IMGspider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6434 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.35 - Regular Expressions Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6434</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35. This is due to processing user-supplied input as a regular expression. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to create and query a malicious post title, resulting in slowing server resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5641 | One Click Order Re-Order &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5641</link><description>The One Click Order Re-Order plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ced_ocor_save_general_setting' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the plugin settings, including adding stored cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 07:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2385 | Elementor Addons by Livemesh &amp;lt;= 8.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Limited Local File Inclusion via Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2385</link><description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.7 via several of the plugin's widgets through the 'style' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2926 | Elementor Addons by Livemesh &amp;lt;= 8.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Various Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2926</link><description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3638 | Elementor Addons by Livemesh &amp;lt;= 8.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Marquee Text Widget, Testimonials Widget, and Testimonial Slider Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3638</link><description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Marquee Text Widget, Testimonials Widget, and Testimonial Slider widgets in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3639 | Elementor Addons by Livemesh &amp;lt;= 8.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Posts Grid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3639</link><description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's  Posts Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38471 | Multiple TP-LINK products allow a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to execute arbitrary OS commands by restoring a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38471</link><description>Multiple TP-LINK products allow a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to execute arbitrary OS commands by restoring a crafted backup file. The affected device, with the initial configuration, allows login only from the LAN port or Wi-Fi.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 01:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38344 | A cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in WP Tweet Walls versions prior to 1.0.4. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38344</link><description>A cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in WP Tweet Walls versions prior to 1.0.4. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker allows a user who logs in to the WordPress site where the affected plugin is enabled to access a malicious page. As a result, the user may perform unintended operations on the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 01:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38345 | A cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Sola Testimonials versions prior to 3.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38345</link><description>A cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Sola Testimonials versions prior to 3.0.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker allows a user who logs in to the WordPress site where the affected plugin is enabled to access a malicious page. As a result, the user may perform unintended operations on the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 01:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6284 | Improper IPv4 and IPv6 byte order storage in github.com/google/nftables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6284</link><description>In  https://github.com/google/nftables  IP addresses were encoded in the wrong byte order, resulting in an nftables configuration which does not work as intended (might block or not block the desired addresses).

This issue affects:  https://pkg.go.dev/github.com/google/nftables@v0.1.0 

The bug was fixed in the next released version:  https://pkg.go.dev/github.com/google/nftables@v0.2.0</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6383 | MongoDB C Driver bson_string_append may be vulnerable to a buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6383</link><description>The bson_string_append function in MongoDB C Driver may be vulnerable to a buffer overflow where the function might attempt to allocate too small of buffer and may lead to memory corruption of neighbouring heap memory. This issue affects libbson versions prior to 1.27.1</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 21:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34750 | Apache Tomcat: HTTP/2 excess header handling DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34750</link><description>Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions, Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 stream, Tomcat did not handle some cases of excessive HTTP headers correctly. This led to a miscounting of active HTTP/2 streams which in turn led to the use of an incorrect infinite timeout which allowed connections to remain open which should have been closed.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M20, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.24, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.89.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M21, 10.1.25 or 9.0.90, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39683 | ZITADEL Vulnerable to Session Information Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39683</link><description>ZITADEL is an open-source identity infrastructure tool. ZITADEL provides users the ability to list all user sessions of the current user agent (browser). Starting in version 2.53.0 and prior to versions 2.53.8, 2.54.5, and 2.55.1, due to a missing check, user sessions without that information (e.g. when created though the session service) were incorrectly listed exposing potentially other user's sessions. Versions 2.55.1, 2.54.5, and 2.53.8 contain a fix for the issue. There is no workaround since a patch is already available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36122 | Discourse doesn&amp;#x27;t limit reviewable user serializer payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36122</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, moderators using the review queue to review users may see a users email address even when the Allow moderators to view email addresses setting is disabled. This issue is patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. As possible workarounds, either prevent moderators from accessing the review queue or disable the approve suspect users site setting and the must approve users site setting to prevent users from being added to the review queue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37157 | Discourse vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery via FastImage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37157</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches, a malicious actor could get the FastImage library to redirect requests to an internal Discourse IP. This issue is patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta4 on the `beta` and `tests-passed` branches. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36113 | Discourse missing authorization checks for suspending admins/moderators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36113</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch, version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `beta` branch, and version 3.3.0.beta4-dev on the `tests-passed` branch, a rogue staff user could suspend other staff users preventing them from logging in to the site. The issue is patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch, version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `beta` branch, and version 3.3.0.beta4-dev on the `tests-passed` branch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33870 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. There is path traversal (via a crafted PostScript document) to arbitrary file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33870</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. There is path traversal (via a crafted PostScript document) to arbitrary files if the current directory is in the permitted paths. For example, there can be a transformation of ../../foo to ./../../foo and this will grant access if ./ is permitted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33869 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. Path traversal and command execution can occur (via a crafted PostScript docu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33869</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. Path traversal and command execution can occur (via a crafted PostScript document) because of path reduction in base/gpmisc.c. For example, restrictions on use of %pipe% can be bypassed via the aa/../%pipe%command# output filename.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29507 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 sometimes has a stack-based buffer overflow via the CIDFSubstPath and CIDFSubstFont parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29507</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 sometimes has a stack-based buffer overflow via the CIDFSubstPath and CIDFSubstFont parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33871 | An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. contrib/opvp/gdevopvp.c allows arbitrary code execution via a custom Driver l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33871</link><description>An issue was discovered in Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1. contrib/opvp/gdevopvp.c allows arbitrary code execution via a custom Driver library, exploitable via a crafted PostScript document. This occurs because the Driver parameter for opvp (and oprp) devices can have an arbitrary name for a dynamic library; this library is then loaded.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29510 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1 allows memory corruption, and SAFER sandbox bypass, via format string injection with a uniprint device.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29510</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1 allows memory corruption, and SAFER sandbox bypass, via format string injection with a uniprint device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29511 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1, when Tesseract is used for OCR, has a directory traversal issue that allows arbitrary file reading (and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29511</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.1, when Tesseract is used for OCR, has a directory traversal issue that allows arbitrary file reading (and writing of error messages to arbitrary files) via OCRLanguage. For example, exploitation can use debug_file /tmp/out and user_patterns_file /etc/passwd.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35234 | Discourse vulnerable to stored-dom XSS via Facebook Oneboxes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35234</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users’ browsers by posting a specific URL containing maliciously crafted meta tags. This issue only affects sites with Content Security Polic (CSP) disabled. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. As a workaround, ensure CSP is enabled on the forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29506 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the pdfi_apply_filter() function via a long PDF filter name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29506</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a stack-based buffer overflow in the pdfi_apply_filter() function via a long PDF filter name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29508 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.0.3.0 has a heap-based pointer disclosure (observable in a constructed BaseFont name) in the function pdf_base...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29508</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.0.3.0 has a heap-based pointer disclosure (observable in a constructed BaseFont name) in the function pdf_base_font_alloc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29509 | Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a heap-based overflow when PDFPassword (e.g., for runpdf) has a \000 byte in the middle.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29509</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 10.03.0 has a heap-based overflow when PDFPassword (e.g., for runpdf) has a \000 byte in the middle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52169 | The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains an out-of-bounds read that allows an attacker to read beyond the i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52169</link><description>The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains an out-of-bounds read that allows an attacker to read beyond the intended buffer. The bytes read beyond the intended buffer are presented as a part of a filename listed in the file system image. This has security relevance in some known web-service use cases where untrusted users can upload files and have them extracted by a server-side 7-Zip process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52168 | The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains a heap-based buffer overflow that allows an attacker to overwrite ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52168</link><description>The NtfsHandler.cpp NTFS handler in 7-Zip before 24.01 (for 7zz) contains a heap-based buffer overflow that allows an attacker to overwrite two bytes at multiple offsets beyond the allocated buffer size: buffer+512*i-2, for i=9, i=10, i=11, etc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35227 | Discourse vulnerable to DoS through Onebox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35227</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, Oneboxing against a carefully crafted malicious URL can reduce the availability of a Discourse instance. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. There are no known workarounds available for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5821 | Improper Access Control in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5821</link><description>Improper Access Control in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5887 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5887</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31223 | Fides Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Privacy Center of SERVER_SIDE_FIDES_API_URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31223</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform, and `SERVER_SIDE_FIDES_API_URL` is a server-side configuration environment variable used by the Fides Privacy Center to communicate with the Fides webserver backend. The value of this variable is a URL which typically includes a private IP address, private domain name, and/or port. A vulnerability present starting in version 2.19.0 and prior to version 2.39.2rc0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to make a HTTP GET request from the Privacy Center that discloses the value of this server-side URL. This could result in disclosure of server-side configuration giving an attacker information on server-side ports, private IP addresses, and/or private domain names. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version 2.39.2rc0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3332 | bt: host/smp: DoS caused by null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3332</link><description>A malicious BLE device can send a specific order of packet sequence to cause a DoS attack on the victim BLE device</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39844 | In ZNC before 1.9.1, remote code execution can occur in modtcl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39844</link><description>In ZNC before 1.9.1, remote code execution can occur in modtcl.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39248 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SimpCMS v0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39248</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SimpCMS v0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Title field at /admin.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39220 | BAS-IP AV-01D, AV-01MD, AV-01MFD, AV-01ED, AV-01KD, AV-01BD, AV-01KBD, AV-02D, AV-02IDE, AV-02IDR, AV-02IPD, AV-02FDE, AV-02FDR, AV-03D, AV-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39220</link><description>BAS-IP AV-01D, AV-01MD, AV-01MFD, AV-01ED, AV-01KD, AV-01BD, AV-01KBD, AV-02D, AV-02IDE, AV-02IDR, AV-02IPD, AV-02FDE, AV-02FDR, AV-03D, AV-03BD, AV-04AFD, AV-04ASD, AV-04FD, AV-04SD, AV-05FD, AV-05SD, AA-07BD, AA-07BDI, BA-04BD, BA-04MD, BA-08BD, BA-08MD, BA-12BD, BA-12MD, CR-02BD before firmware v3.9.2 allows authenticated attackers to read SIP account passwords via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6126 | Cockpit: authenticated user can kill any process when enabling pam_env&amp;#x27;s user_readenv option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6126</link><description>A flaw was found in the cockpit package. This flaw allows an authenticated user to kill any process when enabling the pam_env's user_readenv option, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6052 | XSS in SQL check parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6052</link><description>Stored XSS in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p8, 2.2.0p29, 2.1.0p45, and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows users to execute arbitrary scripts by injecting HTML elements</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39223 | An authentication bypass in the SSH service of gost v2.11.5 allows attackers to intercept communications via setting the HostKeyCallback fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39223</link><description>An authentication bypass in the SSH service of gost v2.11.5 allows attackers to intercept communications via setting the HostKeyCallback function to ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32937 | An os command injection vulnerability exists in the CWMP SelfDefinedTimeZone functionality of Grandstream GXP2135 1.0.9.129, 1.0.11.74 and 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32937</link><description>An os command injection vulnerability exists in the CWMP SelfDefinedTimeZone functionality of Grandstream GXP2135 1.0.9.129, 1.0.11.74 and 1.0.11.79. A specially crafted network packet can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a sequence of malicious packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37726 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Micro-Star International Co., Ltd MSI Center v.2.0.36.0 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37726</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Micro-Star International Co., Ltd MSI Center v.2.0.36.0 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Export System Info function in MSI.CentralServer.exe</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6471 | SourceCodester Online Tours &amp;amp; Travels Management sms_setting.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6471</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Tours &amp; Travels Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file sms_setting.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270279.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6470 | playSMS Template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6470</link><description>A vulnerability was found in playSMS 1.4.3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=feature_inboxgroup&amp;amp;op=list of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument Receiver Number with the input {{`id`}} leads to injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270278 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5672 | Red Lion Europe: mbNET.mini vulnerable to OS command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5672</link><description>A high privileged remote attacker can execute arbitrary system commands via GET requests due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6426 | Information exposure vulnerability vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6426</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version, the exploitation of which could allow a local attacker, with user privileges, to access different resources by changing the API value of the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6427 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in MESbook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6427</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in MESbook 20221021.03 version. An unauthenticated remote attacker can use the "message" parameter to inject a payload with dangerous JavaScript code, causing the application to loop requests on itself, which could lead to resource consumption and disable the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6469 | playSMS Template injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6469</link><description>A vulnerability was found in playSMS 1.4.3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php?app=main&amp;amp;inc=feature_firewall&amp;amp;op=firewall_list of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument IP address with the input {{`id`} leads to injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270277 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39353 | RemoteClusterFrame payloads are audit logged in full</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39353</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 and 9.8.0 fail to sanitize the RemoteClusterFrame payloads before audit logging them which allows a high privileged attacker with access to the audit logs to read message contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39361 | Creating posts with user-defined IDs permitted in CreatePost API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39361</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.8.0, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.4, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.2 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 fail to prevent users from specifying a RemoteId for their posts which allows an attacker to specify both a remoteId and the post ID, resulting in creating a post with a user-defined post ID. This can cause some broken functionality in the channel or thread with user-defined posts</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6428 | Limited DoS due to permitting creating users with user-defined IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6428</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.8.0, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.4, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.2, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 fail to prevent specifying a RemoteId when creating a new user which allows an attacker to specify both a remoteId and the user ID, resulting in creating a user with a user-defined user ID. This can cause some broken functionality in User Management such administrative actions against the user not working.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36257 | Lack of permission check when updating the profile picture of a remote user (shared channels enabled)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36257</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 and 9.8.0, when using shared channels with multiple remote servers connected, fail to check that the remote server A requesting the server B to update the profile picture of a user is the remote that actually has the user as a local one . This allows a malicious remote A to change the profile images of users that belong to another remote server C that is connected to the server A.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39807 | Channel IDs of archived/restored channels leaked via webhook events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39807</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5 and 9.8.0 fail to properly sanitize the recipients of a webhook event which allows an attacker monitoring webhook events to retrieve the channel IDs of archived or restored channels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39830 | Timing attack during remote cluster token comparison when shared channels are enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39830</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.0, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.4, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.2 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.5, when shared channels are enabled, fail to use constant time comparison for remote cluster tokens which allows an attacker to retrieve the remote cluster token via a timing attack during remote cluster token comparison.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4482 | The Plus Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 5.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4482</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Countdown' widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'text_days' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6263 | WP Lightbox 2 &amp;lt;= 3.0.6.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6263</link><description>The WP Lightbox 2 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6340 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.35 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6340</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37082 | HAProxy Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link><description>Security check loophole in HAProxy release (in combination with routing release) in Cloud Foundry prior to v40.17.0 potentially allows bypass of mTLS authentication to applications hosted on Cloud Foundry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2040 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Arbitrary Group Joining via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2040</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make users join private groups via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2231 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Subscriber+ Private Group Joining via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2231</link><description>The  allows any authenticated user to join a private group due to a missing authorization check on a function</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2233 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Multiple CSRF on the Group Section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2233</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks. These include declining and accepting group invitations or leaving a group</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2234 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2234</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its Post settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2235 |  Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Bypass Poll Voting Restrictions via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2235</link><description>The Himer WordPress theme before 2.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make users vote on any polls, including those they don't have access to via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2375 | WPQA &amp;lt; 6.1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2375</link><description>The WPQA Builder WordPress plugin before 6.1.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its Slider settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2376 | WPQA &amp;lt; 6.1.1 - Arbitrary Category and Tag Follow/Unfollow via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2376</link><description>The WPQA Builder WordPress plugin before 6.1.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38453 | The Avalara for Salesforce CPQ app before 7.0 for Salesforce allows attackers to read an API key. NOTE: the current version is 11 as of mid-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38453</link><description>The Avalara for Salesforce CPQ app before 7.0 for Salesforce allows attackers to read an API key. NOTE: the current version is 11 as of mid-2024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4543 | Snippet Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 4.1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4543</link><description>The Snippet Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation when adding or editing shortcodes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify shortcodes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 04:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39920 | The TCP protocol in RFC 9293 has a timing side channel that makes it easier for remote attackers to infer the content of one TCP connection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39920</link><description>The TCP protocol in RFC 9293 has a timing side channel that makes it easier for remote attackers to infer the content of one TCP connection from a client system (to any server), when that client system is concurrently obtaining TCP data at a slow rate from an attacker-controlled server, aka the "SnailLoad" issue. For example, the attack can begin by measuring RTTs via the TCP segments whose role is to provide an ACK control bit and an Acknowledgment Number.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32673 | Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Walrus Webassembly runtime engine allows a segmentation fault issue....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32673</link><description>Improper Validation of Array Index vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Walrus Webassembly runtime engine allows a segmentation fault issue.

This issue affects Walrus: before 72c7230f32a0b791355bbdfc78669701024b0956.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 01:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4708 | mySCADA myPRO Use of Hard-coded Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4708</link><description>mySCADA myPRO 

uses a hard-coded password which could allow an attacker to remotely execute code on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 23:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6453 | itsourcecode Farm Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6453</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Farm Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /quarantine.php?id=3. The manipulation of the argument pigno/breed/reason leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270241 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: Original submission mentioned parameter pigno only but the VulDB data analysis team determined two additional parameters to be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24791 | Denial of service due to improper 100-continue handling in net/http</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24791</link><description>The net/http HTTP/1.1 client mishandled the case where a server responds to a request with an "Expect: 100-continue" header with a non-informational (200 or higher) status. This mishandling could leave a client connection in an invalid state, where the next request sent on the connection will fail. An attacker sending a request to a net/http/httputil.ReverseProxy proxy can exploit this mishandling to cause a denial of service by sending "Expect: 100-continue" requests which elicit a non-informational response from the backend. Each such request leaves the proxy with an invalid connection, and causes one subsequent request using that connection to fail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39326 | SkillTree CSRF Vulnerability allows an attacker to modify the Video and Captions of a Skill</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39326</link><description>SkillTree is a micro-learning gamification platform. Prior to version 2.12.6, the endpoint 
`/admin/projects/{projectname}/skills/{skillname}/video` (and probably others) is open to a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. Due to the endpoint being CSRFable e.g POST request, supports a content type that can be exploited (multipart file upload), makes a state change and has no CSRF mitigations in place (samesite flag, CSRF token). It is possible to perform a CSRF attack against a logged in admin account, allowing an attacker that can target a logged in admin of Skills Service to modify the videos, captions, and text of the skill. Version 2.12.6 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39325 | aimeos/ai-controller-frontend doesn&amp;#x27;t reset payment status in basket</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39325</link><description>aimeos/ai-controller-frontend is the  Aimeos frontend controller. Prior to versions 2024.04.2, 2023.10.9, 2022.10.8, 2021.10.8, and 2020.10.15, aimeos/ai-controller-frontend doesn't reset the payment status of a user's basket after the user completes a purchase. Versions 2024.04.2, 2023.10.9, 2022.10.8, 2021.10.8, and 2020.10.15 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39322 | aimeos/ai-admin-jsonadm improper access control vulnerability allows editors to remove required records</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39322</link><description>aimeos/ai-admin-jsonadm is the Aimeos e-commerce JSON API for administrative tasks. In versions prior to 2020.10.13, 2021.10.6, 2022.10.3, 2023.10.4, and 2024.4.2, improper access control allows editors to remove admin group and locale configuration in the Aimeos backend. Versions 2020.10.13, 2021.10.6, 2022.10.3, 2023.10.4, and 2024.4.2 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39324 | aimeos/ai-admin-graphql improper access control vulnerability allows editors to manage own services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39324</link><description>aimeos/ai-admin-graphql is the Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface. Starting in version 2022.04.1 and prior to versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.4.2, improper access control allows a editors to manage own services via GraphQL API which isn't allowed in the JQAdm front end. Versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.4.2 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39315 | Pomerium exposed OAuth2 access and ID tokens in user info endpoint response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39315</link><description>Pomerium is an identity and context-aware access proxy. Prior to version 0.26.1, the Pomerium user info page (at `/.pomerium`) unintentionally included serialized OAuth2 access and ID tokens from the logged-in user's session. These tokens are not intended to be exposed to end users. This issue may be more severe in the presence of a cross-site scripting vulnerability in an upstream application proxied through Pomerium. If an attacker could insert a malicious script onto a web page proxied through Pomerium, that script could access these tokens by making a request to the `/.pomerium` endpoint. Upstream applications that authenticate only the ID token may be vulnerable to user impersonation using a token obtained in this manner. Note that an OAuth2 access token or ID token by itself is not sufficient to hijack a user's Pomerium session. Upstream applications should not be vulnerable to user impersonation via these tokens provided the application verifies the Pomerium JWT for each request, the connection between Pomerium and the application is secured by mTLS, or the connection between Pomerium and the application is otherwise secured at the network layer. The issue is patched in Pomerium v0.26.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6452 | linlinjava litemall AdminGoodscontroller.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6452</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in linlinjava litemall up to 1.8.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file AdminGoodscontroller.java. The manipulation of the argument goodsId/goodsSn/name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270235.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30636 | Limited directory traversal vulnerability on Windows in golang.org/x/crypto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30636</link><description>httpTokenCacheKey uses path.Base to extract the expected HTTP-01 token value to lookup in the DirCache implementation. On Windows, path.Base acts differently to filepath.Base, since Windows uses a different path separator (\ vs. /), allowing a user to provide a relative path, i.e. .well-known/acme-challenge/..\..\asd becomes ..\..\asd. The extracted path is then suffixed with +http-01, joined with the cache directory, and opened. Since the controlled path is suffixed with +http-01 before opening, the impact of this is significantly limited, since it only allows reading arbitrary files on the system if and only if they have this suffix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24531 | Output of &amp;quot;go env&amp;quot; does not sanitize values in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24531</link><description>Command go env is documented as outputting a shell script containing the Go environment. However, go env doesn't sanitize values, so executing its output as a shell script can cause various bad bahaviors, including executing arbitrary commands or inserting new environment variables. This issue is relatively minor because, in general, if an attacker can set arbitrary environment variables on a system, they have better attack vectors than making "go env" print them out.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38537 | Inclusion of Untrusted polyfill.io Code Vulnerability in fides.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38537</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform. `fides.js`, a client-side script used to interact with the consent management features of Fides, used the `polyfill.io` domain in a very limited edge case, when it detected a legacy browser such as IE11 that did not support the fetch standard. Therefore it was possible for users of legacy, pre-2017 browsers who navigate to a page serving `fides.js` to download and execute malicious scripts from the `polyfill.io` domain when the domain was compromised and serving malware. No exploitation of `fides.js` via `polyfill.io` has been identified as of time of publication.

The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.39.1`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. On Thursday, June 27, 2024, Cloudflare and Namecheap intervened at a domain level to ensure `polyfill.io` and its subdomains could not resolve to the compromised service, rendering this vulnerability unexploitable. Prior to the domain level intervention, there were no server-side workarounds and the confidentiality, integrity, and availability impacts of this vulnerability were high. Clients could ensure they were not affected by using a modern browser that supported the fetch standard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25477 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25477</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 leaks driver logs that contain addresses of kernel mode objects, weakening KASLR.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25478 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25478</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 provides read and write access to the PCI configuration space of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25479 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25479</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 allows for the leakage of kernel memory from both the stack and the heap.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25480 | Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25480</link><description>Vulnerability in Realtek RtsPer driver for PCIe Card Reader (RtsPer.sys) before 10.0.22000.21355 and Realtek RtsUer driver for USB Card Reader (RtsUer.sys) before 10.0.22000.31274 allows writing to kernel memory beyond the SystemBuffer of the IRP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39894 | OpenSSH 9.5 through 9.7 before 9.8 sometimes allows timing attacks against echo-off password entry (e.g., for su and Sudo) because of an Obs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39894</link><description>OpenSSH 9.5 through 9.7 before 9.8 sometimes allows timing attacks against echo-off password entry (e.g., for su and Sudo) because of an ObscureKeystrokeTiming logic error. Similarly, other timing attacks against keystroke entry could occur.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39206 | An issue discovered in MSP360 Backup Agent v7.8.5.15 and v7.9.4.84 allows attackers to obtain network share credentials used in a backup due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39206</link><description>An issue discovered in MSP360 Backup Agent v7.8.5.15 and v7.9.4.84 allows attackers to obtain network share credentials used in a backup due to enginesettings.list being encrypted with a hard coded key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39891 | In the Twilio Authy API, accessed by Authy Android before 25.1.0 and Authy iOS before 26.1.0, an unauthenticated endpoint provided access to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39891</link><description>In the Twilio Authy API, accessed by Authy Android before 25.1.0 and Authy iOS before 26.1.0, an unauthenticated endpoint provided access to certain phone-number data. (Authy accounts were not compromised, however.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6381 | MongoDB C Driver bson_strfreev may be susceptible to integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6381</link><description>The bson_strfreev function in the MongoDB C driver library may be susceptible to an integer overflow where the function will try to free memory at a negative offset. This may result in memory corruption. This issue affected libbson versions prior to 1.26.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6382 | Adversarial unsanitized input may cause MongoDB Rust Driver to issue unintended commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6382</link><description>Incorrect handling of certain string inputs may result in MongoDB Rust driver constructing unintended server commands. This may cause unexpected application behavior including data modification. This issue affects MongoDB Rust Driver 2.0 versions prior to 2.8.2</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39323 | aimeos/ai-admin-graphql improper access control vulnerability allows an editor to modify admin account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39323</link><description>aimeos/ai-admin-graphql is the Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface. Starting in version 2022.04.01 and prior to versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.04.6, an improper access control vulnerability allows an editor to modify and take over an admin account in the back end. Versions 2022.10.10, 2023.10.6, and 2024.04.6 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39316 | Rack ReDoS Vulnerability in HTTP Accept Headers Parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39316</link><description>Rack is a modular Ruby web server interface. Starting in version 3.1.0 and prior to version 3.1.5, Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the `Rack::Request::Helpers` module when parsing HTTP Accept headers. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker sending specially crafted `Accept-Encoding` or `Accept-Language` headers, causing the server to spend excessive time processing the request and leading to a Denial of Service (DoS). The fix for CVE-2024-26146 was not applied to the main branch and thus while the issue was fixed for the Rack v3.0 release series, it was not fixed in the v3.1 release series until v3.1.5. Users of versions on the 3.1 branch should upgrade to version 3.1.5 to receive the fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4467 | Qemu: &amp;#x27;qemu-img info&amp;#x27; leads to host file read/write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4467</link><description>A flaw was found in the QEMU disk image utility (qemu-img) 'info' command. A specially crafted image file containing a `json:{}` value describing block devices in QMP could cause the qemu-img process on the host to consume large amounts of memory or CPU time, leading to denial of service or read/write to an existing external file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5865 | Arbitrary File Reading in Centrify PAS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5865</link><description>Vulnerability in Delinea Centrify PAS v. 21.3 and possibly others. The application is prone to the path traversal vulnerability allowing arbitrary files reading outside the web publish directory. Versions 23.1-HF7 and on have the patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5866 | Arbitrary Directory Listing in Centrify PAS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5866</link><description>Vulnerability in Delinea Centrify PAS v. 21.3 and possibly others. The application is prone to the path traversal vulnerability allowing listing of arbitrary directory outside the root directory of the web application. Versions 23.1-HF7 and on have the patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3826 | Broken SAML Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3826</link><description>In versions of Akana in versions prior to and including 2022.1.3 validation is broken when using the SAML Single Sign-On (SSO) functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26314 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 6.0.0 through 16.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26314</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 6.0.0 through 16.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25087 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.7.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25087</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.7.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25088 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25088</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25086 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.2.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25086</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.2.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22105 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22105</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22106 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, or cause a De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22106</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, or cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22103 | Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22103</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22104 | Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22104</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.5.1 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51778 | Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51778</link><description>Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22102 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22102</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.6.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51777 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51777</link><description>Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to cause a Windows blue screen error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51776 | Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51776</link><description>Improper privilege management in Jungo WinDriver 12.1.0 allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4897 | Remote Code Execution in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4897</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui, in its latest version, is vulnerable to remote code execution due to an insecure dependency on llama-cpp-python version llama_cpp_python-0.2.61+cpuavx2-cp311-cp311-manylinux_2_31_x86_64. The vulnerability arises from the application's 'binding_zoo' feature, which allows attackers to upload and interact with a malicious model file hosted on hugging-face, leading to remote code execution. The issue is linked to a known vulnerability in llama-cpp-python, CVE-2024-34359, which has not been patched in lollms-webui as of commit b454f40a. The vulnerability is exploitable through the application's handling of model files in the 'bindings_zoo' feature, specifically when processing gguf format model files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32932 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Reversible User Credential - stored web interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32932</link><description>Under certain circumstances the web interface users credentials may be recovered by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32757 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Linux Credential Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32757</link><description>Under certain circumstances unnecessary user details are provided within system logs</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32756 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Reversible User Credential - Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32756</link><description>Under certain circumstances the Linux users credentials may be recovered by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34122 | T5 Acrobat Vulnerability - Exploitable crash in DecodeTile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34122</link><description>Acrobat for Edge versions 126.0.2592.68 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38519 | yt-dlp file system modification and RCE through improper file-extension sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38519</link><description>`yt-dlp` is a command-line audio/video downloader. Prior to version 2024.07.01, `yt-dlp` does not limit the extensions of downloaded files, which could lead to aribitrary filenames being created in the download folder (and path traversal on Windows). Since `yt-dlp` also reads config from the working directory (and on Windows executables will be executed from the yt-dlp directory) this could lead to arbitrary code being executed. `yt-dlp` version 2024.07.01 fixes this issue by whitelisting the allowed extensions. This might mean some very uncommon extensions might not get downloaded, however it will also limit the possible exploitation surface. In addition to upgrading, have `.%(ext)s` at the end of the output template and make sure the user trusts the websites that they are downloading from. Also, make sure to never download to a directory within PATH or other sensitive locations like one's user directory, `system32`, or other binaries locations. For users who are not able to upgrade, keep the default output template (`-o "%(title)s [%(id)s].%(ext)s`); make sure the extension of the media to download is a common video/audio/sub/... one; try to avoid the generic extractor; and/or use `--ignore-config --config-location ...` to not load config from common locations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32755 | American Dynamics Illustra Essentials Gen 4 - Log Filter Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32755</link><description>Under certain circumstances the web interface will accept characters unrelated to the expected input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36404 | GeoTools Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in evaluating XPath expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36404</link><description>GeoTools is an open source Java library that provides tools for geospatial data. Prior to versions 31.2, 30.4, and 29.6, Remote Code Execution (RCE) is possible if an application uses certain GeoTools functionality to evaluate XPath expressions supplied by user input. Versions 31.2, 30.4, and 29.6 contain a fix for this issue. As a workaround, GeoTools can operate with reduced functionality by removing the `gt-complex` jar from one's application. As an example of the impact, application schema `datastore` would not function without the ability to use XPath expressions to query complex content. Alternatively, one may utilize a drop-in replacement GeoTools jar from SourceForge for versions 31.1, 30.3, 30.2, 29.2, 28.2, 27.5, 27.4, 26.7, 26.4, 25.2, and 24.0. These jars are for download only and are not available from maven central, intended to quickly provide a fix to affected applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39143 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ResidenceCMS 2.10.1 that allows a low-privilege user to create malicious propert...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39143</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ResidenceCMS 2.10.1 that allows a low-privilege user to create malicious property content with HTML inside which acts as a stored XSS payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39119 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via admin/info_deal.php?mudi=rev&amp;nohrefStr=close.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39119</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via admin/info_deal.php?mudi=rev&amp;amp;nohrefStr=close.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6441 | ORIPA LoaderXML.java deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6441</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ORIPA up to 1.72. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file src/main/java/oripa/persistence/doc/loader/LoaderXML.java. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.80 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-270169 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4268 | Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.9 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Blocks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4268</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6088 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated User Registration Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6088</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user registration due to a missing capability check on the 'register' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass disabled user registration to create a new account with the default role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6099 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.1 - Unauthenticated Bypass to User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6099</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated bypass to user registration in versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8.1. This is due to missing checks in the 'check_validate_fields' function in the checkout. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as the default role on the site, even if registration is disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6264 | Post Meta Data Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6264</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘$meta_key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6439 | SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6439</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270167.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6440 | SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6440</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Home Owners Collection Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270168.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6438 | Hitout Carsale OrderController.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6438</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Hitout Carsale 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file OrderController.java. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270166 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 10:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6011 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6011</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘textarea.description’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6012 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Content Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6012</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'embed-create-page' and 'embed-insert-pages' functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary posts and append arbitrary content to existing posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20888 | Improper access control in OneUIHome prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities. User interactio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20888</link><description>Improper access control in OneUIHome prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20889 | Improper authentication in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to pair with devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20889</link><description>Improper authentication in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to pair with devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20890 | Improper input validation in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to trigger abnormal behavior.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20890</link><description>Improper input validation in BLE prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows adjacent attackers to trigger abnormal behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20891 | Improper access control in launchFullscreenIntent of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20891</link><description>Improper access control in launchFullscreenIntent of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20892 | Improper verification of signature in FilterProvider prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute privileged behaviors....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20892</link><description>Improper verification of signature in FilterProvider prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute privileged behaviors. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20893 | Improper input validation in libmediaextractorservice.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20893</link><description>Improper input validation in libmediaextractorservice.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to trigger memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20894 | Improper handling of exceptional conditions in Secure Folder prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20894</link><description>Improper handling of exceptional conditions in Secure Folder prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication under certain condition. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20895 | Improper access control in Dar service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restriction for calling SDP features...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20895</link><description>Improper access control in Dar service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restriction for calling SDP features.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20896 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Configuration message prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20896</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Configuration message prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20897 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in FCM function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20897</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in FCM function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20898 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in SoftphoneClient in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20898</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in SoftphoneClient in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20899 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in RCS function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20899</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in RCS function in IMS service prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20900 | Improper authentication in MTP application prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to enter MTP mode without proper authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20900</link><description>Improper authentication in MTP application prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to enter MTP mode without proper authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20901 | Improper input validation in copying data to buffer cache in libsaped prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20901</link><description>Improper input validation in copying data to buffer cache in libsaped prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34583 | Improper access control in system property prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device identifier.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34583</link><description>Improper access control in system property prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device identifier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34584 | Improper privilege management in SumeNNService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34584</link><description>Improper privilege management in SumeNNService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34585 | Improper access control in launchApp of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34585</link><description>Improper access control in launchApp of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34586 | Improper access control in KnoxCustomManagerService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure Knox privacy policy.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34586</link><description>Improper access control in KnoxCustomManagerService prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure Knox privacy policy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34587 | Improper input validation in parsing application information from RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34587</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing application information from RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34588 | Improper input validation혻in parsing RTCP SR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34588</link><description>Improper input validation혻in parsing RTCP SR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34589 | Improper input validation in parsing RTCP RR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34589</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing RTCP RR packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34590 | Improper input validation혻in parsing an item type from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34590</link><description>Improper input validation혻in parsing an item type from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34591 | Improper input validation in parsing an item data from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34591</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing an item data from RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34592 | Improper input validation in parsing RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger tempor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34592</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing RTCP SDES packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to trigger temporary denial of service. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34593 | Improper input validation in parsing and distributing RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34593</link><description>Improper input validation in parsing and distributing RTCP packet in librtp.so prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34594 | Exposure of sensitive information in proc file system prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to read kernel memory address.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34594</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in proc file system prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to read kernel memory address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34595 | Improper access control in clickAdapterItem of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34595</link><description>Improper access control in clickAdapterItem of SystemUI prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34596 | Improper authentication in SmartThings prior to version 1.8.17 allows remote attackers to bypass the expiration date for members set by the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34596</link><description>Improper authentication in SmartThings prior to version 1.8.17 allows remote attackers to bypass the expiration date for members set by the owner.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34597 | Improper input validation in Samsung Health prior to version 6.27.0.113 allows local attackers to write arbitrary document files to the sand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34597</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Health prior to version 6.27.0.113 allows local attackers to write arbitrary document files to the sandbox of Samsung Health. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34599 | Improper input validation in Tips prior to version 6.2.9.4 in Android 14 allows local attacker to send broadcast with Tips' privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34599</link><description>Improper input validation in Tips prior to version 6.2.9.4 in Android 14 allows local attacker to send broadcast with Tips' privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34600 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.13.0 allows local attackers to copy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34600</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Samsung Flow prior to version 4.9.13.0 allows local attackers to copy image files to external storage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34601 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in GalaxyStore prior to version 4.5.81.0 allows local attackers to launc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34601</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in GalaxyStore prior to version 4.5.81.0 allows local attackers to launch unexported activities of GalaxyStore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4836 | LFI in sites managed by Edito CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4836</link><description>Web services managed by Edito CMS (Content Management System) in versions from 3.5 through 3.25 leak sensitive data as they allow downloading configuration files by an unauthenticated user.
The issue in versions 3.5 - 3.25 was removed in releases which dates from 10th of January 2014. Higher versions were never affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5260 | Sina Extension for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via read_more_text Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5260</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘read_more_text’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31071 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31071</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36243 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36243</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds read and write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36260 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36260</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36278 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36278</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37030 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37030</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37077 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37077</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37185 | Arkcompiler Ets Runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37185</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38857 | Reflected links in visuals facilitate phishing attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38857</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Checkmk before versions 2.3.0p8, 2.2.0p28, 2.1.0p45, and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows attackers to craft malicious links that can facilitate phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41917 | Improper input validation in Kiloview P1/P2 devices allows for remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41917</link><description>Inadequate input validation exposes the system to potential remote code execution (RCE) risks. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by appending shell commands to the Speed-Measurement feature, enabling unauthorized code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41918 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41918</link><description>A vulnerability allows unauthorized access to functionality inadequately constrained by ACLs. Attackers may exploit this to unauthenticated execute commands potentially leading to unauthorized data manipulation, access to privileged functions, or even the execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41919 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41919</link><description>Hardcoded credentials are discovered within the application's source code, creating a potential security risk for unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41920 | Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41920</link><description>The vulnerability allows attackers access to the root account without having to authenticate. Specifically, if the device is configured with the IP address of 10.10.10.10, the root user is automatically logged in.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41921 | Download of Code Without Integrity Check in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41921</link><description>A vulnerability allows attackers to download source code or an executable from a remote location and execute the code without sufficiently verifying the origin and integrity of the code. This vulnerability can allow attackers to modify the firmware before uploading it to the system, thus achieving the modification of the target’s integrity to achieve an insecure state.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41922 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41922</link><description>A 'Cross-site Scripting' (XSS) vulnerability, characterized by improper input neutralization during web page generation, has been discovered. This vulnerability allows for Stored XSS attacks to occur. Multiple areas within the administration interface of the webserver lack adequate input validation, resulting in multiple instances of Stored XSS vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41923 | Weak Password Requirements in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41923</link><description>The user management section of the web application permits the creation of user accounts with excessively weak passwords, including single-character passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41926 | Insufficiently protected credentials in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41926</link><description>The webserver utilizes basic authentication for its user login to the configuration interface. As encryption is disabled on port 80, it enables potential eavesdropping on user traffic, making it possible to intercept their credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41927 | Weak TLS Cipher Suites Supported in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41927</link><description>The server supports at least one cipher suite which is on the NCSC-NL list of cipher suites to be phased out, increasing the risk of cryptographic weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41928 | Remote server offers deprecated TLS protocol in Kiloview P1/P2 devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41928</link><description>The device is observed to accept deprecated TLS protocols, increasing the risk of cryptographic weaknesses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37479 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.1 - Contributor+ Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37479</link><description>Local File Inclusion vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor via "LaStudioKit Progress Bar" widget in New Post, specifically in the "progress_type" attribute.This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3513 | Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title tag attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3513</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks – WordPress Blocks Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the title tag parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5504 | Rife Elementor Extensions &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Writing Effect Headline Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5504</link><description>The Rife Elementor Extensions &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tag' attribute within the plugin's Writing Effect Headline widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5544 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.17 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5544</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the order parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5545 | Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp;amp; Listing &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5545</link><description>The Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp; Listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the stm_edit_delete_user_car function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to unpublish arbitrary posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37126 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37126</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized gain of root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37134 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37134</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37132 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A high privileged attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37132</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37133 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37133</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized gain of root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32853 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.2 contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability. A local low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32853</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.2 contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability. A local low privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32854 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privilege attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32854</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability. A local high privilege attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32852 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.0 contain use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unprivileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32852</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.7.0.0 contain use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unprivileged network malicious attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to data leaks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5219 | Easy Google Maps &amp;lt;= 1.11.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5219</link><description>The Easy Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6172 | Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.7.25 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via unsubscribe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6172</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the db parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.25 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0158 | Dell BIOS contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges may potentially ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0158</link><description>Dell BIOS contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with admin privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to modify a UEFI variable, leading to denial of service and escalation of privileges</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3999 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3999</link><description>The EazyDocs  WordPress plugin before 2.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4627 | Rank Math SEO &amp;lt; 1.0.219 - Authenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4627</link><description>The Rank Math SEO  WordPress plugin before 1.0.219 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow users with access to the General Settings (by default admin, however such access can be given to lower roles via the Role Manager feature of the Rank Math SEO  WordPress plugin before 1.0.219) to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5606 | Quiz And Survey Master &amp;lt; 9.0.2 - Contributor+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5606</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.0.2 is vulnerable does not validate and escape the question_id parameter in the qsm_bulk_delete_question_from_database AJAX action, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by Contributors and above role</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5767 | Sitetweet &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5767</link><description>The sitetweet WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1427 | The Post Grid &amp;lt;= 7.7.1 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via section title tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1427</link><description>The The Post Grid – Shortcode, Gutenberg Blocks and Elementor Addon for Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the section title tag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5349 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5349</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8.1 via the 'map_style' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5419 | Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cf7_redirect_page Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5419</link><description>The Void Contact Form 7 Widget For Elementor Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cf7_redirect_page' attribute within the plugin's Void Contact From 7 widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2819 | File Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2819</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions, Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Common Services: before 11.0.2-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5938 | Boot Store &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5938</link><description>The Boot Store theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4679 | Folder Permission Vulnerability in JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4679</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent for Windows, Hitachi JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent on Windows, Hitachi Job Management Partner1/Extensible SNMP Agent on Windows allows File Manipulation.This issue affects JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent for Windows: from 12-00 before 12-00-01, from 11-00 through 11-00-*; JP1/Extensible SNMP Agent: from 10-10 through 10-10-01, from 10-00 through 10-00-02, from 09-00 through 09-00-04; Job Management Partner1/Extensible SNMP Agent: from 10-10 through 10-10-01, from 10-00 through 10-00-02, from 09-00 through 09-00-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>