<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-25806 | PlaciPy has Missing Authorization Checks on Student Management Endpoints (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25806</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the GET /api/students/:email
PUT /api/students/:email/status, and DELETE /api/students/:email routes in backend/src/routes/student.routes.ts only enforce authentication using authenticateToken but do not enforce authorization. The application does not verify whether the authenticated user owns the student record being accessed, has an administrative / staff role, or is permitted to modify or delete the target student.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25809 | PlaciPy Code Execution Allowed Without Assessment Active State Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25809</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the code evaluation endpoint does not validate the assessment lifecycle state before allowing execution. There is no check to ensure that the assessment has started, is not expired, or the submission window is currently open.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25810 | PlaciPy is Missing Object-Level Authorization in student.submission.routes.ts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25810</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the backend/src/routes/student.submission.routes.ts verify authentication but fails to enforce object-level authorization (ownership checks).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25876 | PlaciPy is Missing Authorization on Assessment Results Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25876</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the backend/src/routes/results.routes.ts verify authentication but fails to enforce object-level authorization (ownership checks). For example, this can be used to return all results for an assessment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25878 | FroshAdminer Adminer UI is accessible without admin session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25878</link><description>FroshAdminer is the Adminer plugin for Shopware Platform. Prior to 2.2.1, the Adminer route (/admin/adminer) was accessible without Shopware admin authentication. The route was configured with auth_required=false and performed no session validation, exposing the Adminer UI to unauthenticated users. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25761 | Command injection via crafted filenames in Super-linter Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25761</link><description>Super-linter is a combination of multiple linters to run as a GitHub Action or standalone. From 6.0.0 to 8.3.0, the Super-linter GitHub Action is vulnerable to command injection via crafted filenames. When this action is used in downstream GitHub Actions workflows, an attacker can submit a pull request that introduces a file whose name contains shell command substitution syntax, such as $(...). In affected Super-linter versions, runtime scripts may execute the embedded command during file discovery processing, enabling arbitrary command execution in the workflow runner context. This can be used to disclose the job’s GITHUB_TOKEN depending on how the workflow configures permissions. This vulnerability is fixed in 8.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25765 | Faraday affected by SSRF via protocol-relative URL host override in build_exclusive_url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25765</link><description>Faraday is an HTTP client library abstraction layer that provides a common interface over many adapters. Prior to 2.14.1, Faraday's build_exclusive_url method (in lib/faraday/connection.rb) uses Ruby's URI#merge to combine the connection's base URL with a user-supplied path. Per RFC 3986, protocol-relative URLs (e.g. //evil.com/path) are treated as network-path references that override the base URL's host/authority component. This means that if any application passes user-controlled input to Faraday's get(), post(), build_url(), or other request methods, an attacker can supply a protocol-relative URL like //attacker.com/endpoint to redirect the request to an arbitrary host, enabling Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25791 | Sliver has a DNS C2 OTP Bypass Allows Unauthenticated Session Flooding and Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25791</link><description>Sliver is a command and control framework that uses a custom Wireguard netstack. Prior to 1.7.0, the DNS C2 listener accepts unauthenticated TOTP bootstrap messages and allocates server-side DNS sessions without validating OTP values, even when EnforceOTP is enabled. Because sessions are stored without a cleanup/expiry path in this flow, an unauthenticated remote actor can repeatedly create sessions and drive memory exhaustion. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25528 | LangSmith Client SDK Affected by Server-Side Request Forgery via Tracing Header Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25528</link><description>LangSmith Client SDKs provide SDK's for interacting with the LangSmith platform. The LangSmith SDK's distributed tracing feature is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery via malicious HTTP headers. An attacker can inject arbitrary api_url values through the baggage header, causing the SDK to exfiltrate sensitive trace data to attacker-controlled endpoints. When using distributed tracing, the SDK parses incoming HTTP headers via RunTree.from_headers() in Python or RunTree.fromHeaders() in Typescript. The baggage header can contain replica configurations including api_url and api_key fields. Prior to the fix, these attacker-controlled values were accepted without validation. When a traced operation completes, the SDK's post() and patch() methods send run data to all configured replica URLs, including any injected by an attacker. This vulnerability is fixed in version 0.6.3 of the Python SDK and  0.4.6 of the JavaScript SDK.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25639 | Axios affected by Denial of Service via __proto__ Key in mergeConfig</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25639</link><description>Axios is a promise based HTTP client for the browser and Node.js. Prior to 1.13.5, the mergeConfig function in axios crashes with a TypeError when processing configuration objects containing __proto__ as an own property. An attacker can trigger this by providing a malicious configuration object created via JSON.parse(), causing complete denial of service. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25740 | Privilege escalation to the `CAP_NET_RAW` capability via the `programs.captive-browser` NixOS module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25740</link><description>captive browser, a dedicated Chrome instance to log into captive portals without messing with DNS settings. In 25.05 and earlier, when programs.captive-browser is enabled, any user of the system can run arbitrary commands with the CAP_NET_RAW capability (binding to privileged ports, spoofing localhost traffic from privileged services...). This vulnerability is fixed in 25.11 and 26.05.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25498 | Craft has a potential authenticated Remote Code Execution via malicious attached Behavior</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25498</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in Craft CMS where the assembleLayoutFromPost() function in src/services/Fields.php fails to sanitize user-supplied configuration data before passing it to Craft::createObject(). This allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious Yii2 behavior configurations that execute arbitrary system commands on the server. This vulnerability represents an unpatched variant of the behavior injection vulnerability addressed in CVE-2025-68455, affecting different endpoints through a separate code path. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25492 | Craft has a save_images_Asset graphql mutation can be abused to exfiltrate AWS credentials of underlying host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25492</link><description>Craft CMS is a content management system. In Craft versions 3.5.0 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the save_images_Asset GraphQL mutation can be abused to fetch internal URLs by providing a domain name that resolves to an internal IP address, bypassing hostname validation. When a non-image file extension such as .txt is allowed, downstream image validation is bypassed, which can allow an authenticated attacker with permission to use save_images_Asset to retrieve sensitive data such as AWS instance metadata credentials from the underlying host. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25493 | Craft has a SSRF in GraphQL Asset Mutation via HTTP Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25493</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the saveAsset GraphQL mutation validates the initial URL hostname and resolved IP against a blocklist, but Guzzle follows HTTP redirects by default. An attacker can bypass all SSRF protections by hosting a redirect that points to cloud metadata endpoints or any internal IP addresses. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25494 | Craft has a SSRF in GraphQL Asset Mutation via Alternative IP Notation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25494</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences.  In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the saveAsset GraphQL mutation uses filter_var(..., FILTER_VALIDATE_IP) to block a specific list of IP addresses. However, alternative IP notations (hexadecimal, mixed) are not recognized by this function, allowing attackers to bypass the blocklist and access cloud metadata services. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25495 | Craft has a SQL Injection in Element Indexes via criteria[orderBy]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25495</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the element-indexes/get-elements endpoint is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the criteria[orderBy] parameter (JSON body). The application fails to sanitize this input before using it in the database query. An attacker with Control Panel access can inject arbitrary SQL into the ORDER BY clause by omitting viewState[order] (or setting both to the same payload). This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25496 | Craft has a stored XSS in Number Prefix &amp;amp; Suffix Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25496</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, a stored XSS vulnerability exists in the Number field type settings. The Prefix and Suffix fields are rendered using the |md|raw Twig filter without proper escaping, allowing script execution when the Number field is displayed on users' profiles. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25497 | Craft has a GraphQL Asset Mutation Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25497</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions from 4.0.0-RC1 to before 4.17.0-beta.1 and 5.9.0-beta.1, there is a Privilege Escalation vulnerability in Craft CMS’s GraphQL API that allows an authenticated user with write access to one asset volume to escalate their privileges and modify/transfer assets belonging to any other volume, including restricted or private volumes to which they should not have access. The saveAsset GraphQL mutation validates authorization against the schema-resolved volume but fetches the target asset by ID without verifying that the asset belongs to the authorized volume. This allows unauthorized cross-volume asset modification and transfer. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.17.0-beta.1 and 5.9.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2246 | AprilRobotics apriltag apriltag.c apriltag_detector_detect memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2246</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in AprilRobotics apriltag up to 3.4.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function apriltag_detector_detect of the file apriltag.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The identifier of the patch is cfac2f5ce1ffe2de25967eb1ab80bc5d99fc1a61. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14778 | Keycloak: incorrect ownership checks in /uma-policy/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14778</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. A significant Broken Access Control vulnerability exists in the UserManagedPermissionService (UMA Protection API). When updating or deleting a UMA policy associated with multiple resources, the authorization check only verifies the caller's ownership against the first resource in the policy's list. This allows a user (Owner A) who owns one resource (RA) to update a shared policy and modify authorization rules for other resources (e.g., RB) in that same policy, even if those other resources are owned by a different user (Owner B). This constitutes a horizontal privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1486 | Org.keycloak.protocol.oidc.grants: disabled identity providers are still accepted for jwt authorization grant</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1486</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. A vulnerability exists in the jwt-authorization-grant flow where the server fails to verify if an Identity Provider (IdP) is enabled before issuing tokens. The issuer lookup mechanism (lookupIdentityProviderFromIssuer) retrieves the IdP configuration but does not filter for isEnabled=false. If an administrator disables an IdP (e.g., due to a compromise or offboarding), an entity possessing that IdP's signing key can still generate valid JWT assertions that Keycloak accepts, resulting in the issuance of valid access tokens.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1529 | Org.keycloak.services.resources.organizations: keycloak: unauthorized organization registration via improper invitation token validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1529</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by modifying the organization ID and target email within a legitimate invitation token's JSON Web Token (JWT) payload. This lack of cryptographic signature verification allows the attacker to successfully self-register into an unauthorized organization, leading to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24900 | MarkUs has a submission-view IDOR exposes all student submissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24900</link><description>MarkUs is a web application for the submission and grading of student assignments. Prior to 2.9.1, the courses/&lt;:course_id&gt;/assignments/&lt;:assignment_id&gt;/submissions/html_content accepted a select_file_id parameter to serve SubmissionFile objects containing a record of files submitted by students. This parameter was not correctly scoped to the requesting user, allowing users access arbitrary submission file contents by id. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25057 | Zip Slip in MarkUs config upload allowing RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25057</link><description>MarkUs is a web application for the submission and grading of student assignments. Prior to 2.9.1, instructors are able to upload a zip file to create an assignment from an exported configuration (courses/&lt;:course_id&gt;/assignments/upload_config_files). The uploaded zip file entry names are used to create paths to write files to disk without checking these paths. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25230 | FileRise affected by HTML Injection using color property in file tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25230</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web file manager / WebDAV server. Prior to 3.3.0, an HTML Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated user to modify the DOM and add e.g. form elements that call certain endpoints or link elements that redirect the user on active interaction. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25231 | FileRise affected by an Unauthenticated File Read Due to Insufficient Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25231</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web file manager / WebDAV server. Versions prior to 3.3.0, the application contains an unauthenticated file read vulnerability due to the lack of access control on the /uploads directory. Files uploaded to this directory can be accessed directly by any user who knows or can guess the file path, without requiring authentication. As a result, sensitive data could be exposed, and privacy may be breached. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25478 | Litestar has a CORS origin allowlist bypass due to unescaped regex metacharacters in allowed origins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25478</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.20.0, CORSConfig.allowed_origins_regex is constructed using a regex built from configured allowlist values and used with fullmatch() for validation. Because metacharacters are not escaped, a malicious origin can match unexpectedly. The check relies on allowed_origins_regex.fullmatch(origin). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25479 | Litestar has an AllowedHosts validation bypass due to unescaped regex metacharacters in configured host patterns</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25479</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.20.0, in litestar.middleware.allowed_hosts, allowlist entries are compiled into regex patterns in a way that allows regex metacharacters to retain special meaning (e.g., . matches any character). This enables a bypass where an attacker supplies a host that matches the regex but is not the intended literal hostname. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25480 | FileStore key canonicalization collisions allow response cache mixup/poisoning (ASCII ord + Unicode NFKD)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25480</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.20.0, FileStore maps cache keys to filenames using Unicode NFKD normalization and ord() substitution without separators, creating key collisions. When FileStore is used as response-cache backend, an unauthenticated remote attacker can trigger cache key collisions via crafted paths, causing one URL to serve cached responses of another (cache poisoning/mixup). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25491 | Craft has a Stored XSS in Entry Types Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25491</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. From 5.0.0-RC1 to 5.8.21, Craft has a stored XSS via Entry Type names. The name is not sanitized when displayed in the Entry Types list. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25598 | Bypassing Logging of Outbound Connections Using sendto, sendmsg, and sendmmsg in Harden-Runner (Community Tier)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25598</link><description>Harden-Runner is a CI/CD security agent that works like an EDR for GitHub Actions runners. Prior to 2.14.2, a security vulnerability has been identified in the Harden-Runner GitHub Action (Community Tier) that allows outbound network connections to evade audit logging. Specifically, outbound traffic using the sendto, sendmsg, and sendmmsg socket system calls can bypass detection and logging when using egress-policy: audit. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2245 | CCExtractor MPEG-TS File ts_tables.c parse_PMT out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2245</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CCExtractor up to 183. This affects the function parse_PAT/parse_PMT in the library src/lib_ccx/ts_tables.c of the component MPEG-TS File Parser. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The name of the patch is fd7271bae238ccb3ae8a71304ea64f0886324925. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23948 | FreeRDP has a NULL Pointer Dereference in rdp_write_logon_info_v2()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23948</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability in rdp_write_logon_info_v2() allows a malicious RDP server to crash FreeRDP proxy by sending a specially crafted LogonInfoV2 PDU with cbDomain=0 or cbUserName=0. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24491 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in video_timer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24491</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, video_timer can send client notifications after the control channel is closed, dereferencing a freed callback and triggering a use after free. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24675 | FreeRDP has a Heap-use-after-free in urb_select_interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24675</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, urb_select_interface can free the device's MS config on error but later code still dereferences it, leading to a use after free in libusb_udev_select_interface. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24676 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in audio_format_compatible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24676</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, AUDIN format renegotiation frees the active format list while the capture thread continues using audin-&gt;format, leading to a use after free in audio_format_compatible. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24677 | FreeRDP has a heap-buffer-overflow in ecam_encoder_compress_h264</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24677</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, ecam_encoder_compress_h264 trusts server-controlled dimensions and does not validate the source buffer size, leading to an out-of-bounds read in sws_scale. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24678 | FreeRDP has a Heap-use-after-free in cam_v4l_stream_capture_thread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24678</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, A capture thread sends sample responses using a freed channel callback after a device channel close, leading to a use after free in ecam_channel_write. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24679 | FreeRDP has a heap-buffer-overflow in urb_select_interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24679</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, The URBDRC client uses server-supplied interface numbers as array indices without bounds checks, causing an out-of-bounds read in libusb_udev_select_interface. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24680 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in update_pointer_new(SDL)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24680</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, sdl_Pointer_New frees data on failure, then pointer_free calls sdl_Pointer_Free and frees it again, triggering ASan UAF. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24681 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in urb_bulk_transfer_cb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24681</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, aAsynchronous bulk transfer completions can use a freed channel callback after URBDRC channel close, leading to a use after free in urb_write_completion. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24682 | FreeRDP has a Heap-buffer-overflow in audio_formats_free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24682</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, audin_server_recv_formats frees an incorrect number of audio formats on parse failure (i + i), leading to out-of-bounds access in audio_formats_free. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24683 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in ainput_send_input_event</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24683</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. ainput_send_input_event caches channel_callback in a local variable and later uses it without synchronization; a concurrent channel close can free or reinitialize the callback, leading to a use after free. Prior to 3.22.0, This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24684 | FreeRDP has a Heap-use-after-free in play_thread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24684</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, the RDPSND async playback thread can process queued PDUs after the channel is closed and internal state is freed, leading to a use after free in rdpsnd_treat_wave. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24777 | OpenProject has Improper Access Control on User Management allows user managers to lock admin accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24777</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to 17.0.2, users with the Manage Users permission can lock and unlock users. This functionality should only be possible for users of the application, but they were not supposed to be able to lock application administrators. Due to a missing permission check this logic was not enforced. The problem was fixed in OpenProject 17.0.2The problem was fixed in OpenProject 17.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66630 | Fiber insecurely fallsback in utils.UUIDv4() / utils.UUID() — predictable / zero‑UUID on crypto/rand failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66630</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. Before 2.52.11, on Go versions prior to 1.24, the underlying crypto/rand implementation can return an error if secure randomness cannot be obtained. Because no error is returned by the Fiber v2 UUID functions, application code may unknowingly rely on predictable, repeated, or low-entropy identifiers in security-critical pathways. This is especially impactful because many Fiber v2 middleware components (session middleware, CSRF, rate limiting, request-ID generation, etc.) default to using utils.UUIDv4(). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.52.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21419 | Dell Display and Peripheral Manager (Windows) versions prior to 2.2 contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21419</link><description>Dell Display and Peripheral Manager (Windows) versions prior to 2.2 contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in the Installer and Service. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2242 | janet-lang janet specials.c janetc_if out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2242</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. This impacts the function janetc_if of the file src/core/specials.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called c43e06672cd9dacf2122c99f362120a17c34b391. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7432 | DPA countermeasures not reseeded under certain conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7432</link><description>DPA countermeasures in Silicon Labs' Series 2 devices are not reseeded under certain conditions. 

This may allow an attacker to eventually extract secret keys through a DPA attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2241 | janet-lang janet os.c os_strftime out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2241</link><description>A vulnerability was found in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. This affects the function os_strftime of the file src/core/os.c. Performing a manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named 0f285855f0e34f9183956be5f16e045f54626bff. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2240 | janet-lang janet compile.c janetc_pop_funcdef out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2240</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. The impacted element is the function janetc_pop_funcdef of the file src/core/compile.c. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 4dd08a4cdef5b1c42d9a2c19fc24412e97ef51d5. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24095 | Missing Permission Check on Analyze Configuration Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24095</link><description>Improper permission enforcement in Checkmk versions 2.4.0 before 2.4.0p21, 2.3.0 before 2.3.0p43, and 2.2.0 (EOL) allows users with the "Use WATO" permission to access the "Analyze configuration" page by directly navigating to its URL, bypassing the intended "Access analyze configuration" permission check. If these users also have the "Make changes, perform actions" permission, they can perform unauthorized actions such as disabling checks or acknowledging results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14831 | Gnutls: gnutls: denial of service via excessive resource consumption during certificate verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14831</link><description>A flaw was found in GnuTLS. This vulnerability allows a denial of service (DoS) by excessive CPU (Central Processing Unit) and memory consumption via specially crafted malicious certificates containing a large number of name constraints and subject alternative names (SANs).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59023 | Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59023</link><description>Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59024 | Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59024</link><description>Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63354 | Hitron HI3120 v7.2.4.5.2b1 allows stored XSS via the Parental Control option when creating a new filter. The device fails to properly handle...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63354</link><description>Hitron HI3120 v7.2.4.5.2b1 allows stored XSS via the Parental Control option when creating a new filter. The device fails to properly handle inputs, allowing an attacker to inject and execute JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24027 | Crafted zones can lead to increased incoming network traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24027</link><description>Crafted zones can lead to increased incoming network traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0398 | Crafted zones can lead to increased resource usage and crafted CNAME chains can lead to cache poisoning in Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0398</link><description>Crafted zones can lead to increased resource usage and crafted CNAME chains can lead to cache poisoning in Recursor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10465 | Unrestricted File Upload in Birtech Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Sensaway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10465</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Birtech Information Technologies Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Sensaway allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Sensaway: through 09022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10464 | Cleartext password storage in Birtech Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Sensaway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10464</link><description>Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Birtech Information Technologies Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Senseway allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Senseway: through 09022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10463 | Improper Authentication in Birtech Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Sensaway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10463</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Birtech Information Technologies Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Senseway allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Senseway: through 09022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7708 | Sensitive Data Exposure in Atlas Software&amp;#x27;s k12net</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7708</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Atlas Educational Software Industry Ltd. Co. K12net allows Communication Channel Manipulation.This issue affects k12net: through 09022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1959 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1959</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes, via the 

'descripción'

parameter in the '/loggrodemo/jbrain/MaestraCuentasBancarias' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1960 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1960</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes, via the 'Facebook' parameter in '/loggrodemo/jbrain/ConsultaTerceros' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6830 | SQLi in Xpoda Türkiye Information Technology&amp;#x27;s Xpoda Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6830</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Xpoda Türkiye Information Technology Inc. Xpoda Studio allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Xpoda Studio: through 09022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0632 | Fluent Forms Pro Add On Pack &amp;lt;= 6.1.12 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;saveDataSource&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0632</link><description>The Fluent Forms Pro Add On Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.12 via the 'saveDataSource' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22922 | Apache Airflow: Airflow externalLogUrl Permission Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22922</link><description>Apache Airflow versions 3.1.0 through 3.1.6 contain an authorization flaw that can allow an authenticated user with custom permissions limited to task access to view task logs without having task log access. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache Airflow 3.1.7 or later, which resolves this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24098 | Apache Airflow: Assigning single DAG permission leaked all DAGs Import Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24098</link><description>Apache Airflow versions before 3.1.7, has vulnerability that allows authenticated UI users with permission to one or more specific Dags to view import errors generated by other Dags they did not have access to. 

Users are advised to upgrade to 3.1.7 or later, which resolves this issue</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25846 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.119033 access tokens could be exposed in Mailbox logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25846</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.119033 access tokens could be exposed in Mailbox logs</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25847 | In JetBrains PyCharm before 2025.3.2 a DOM-based XSS on Jupyter viewer page was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25847</link><description>In JetBrains PyCharm before 2025.3.2 a DOM-based XSS on Jupyter viewer page was possible</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25848 | In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.119807 authentication bypass allowing administrative actions was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25848</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.119807 authentication bypass allowing administrative actions was possible</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2227 | D-Link DCS-931L setSystemAdmin doSystem command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-931L up to 1.13.0. Impacted is the function doSystem of the file /setSystemAdmin. Performing a manipulation of the argument AdminID results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23903 | Apache Shiro: Auth bypass when accessing static files only on case-insensitive filesystems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23903</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Alternate Name vulnerability in Apache Shiro.

This issue affects Apache Shiro: before 2.0.7.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.7, which fixes the issue.

The issue only effects static files. If static files are served from a case-insensitive filesystem,
such as default macOS setup, static files may be accessed by varying the case of the filename in the request.
If only lower-case (common default) filters are present in Shiro, they may be bypassed this way.

Shiro 2.0.7 and later has a new parameters to remediate this issue
shiro.ini: filterChainResolver.caseInsensitive = true
application.propertie: shiro.caseInsensitive=true

Shiro 3.0.0 and later (upcoming) makes this the default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2226 | DouPHP ZIP File file.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2226</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DouPHP up to 1.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/file.php of the component ZIP File Handler. Such manipulation of the argument sql_filename leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25905 | Lack of isolation in mcp-run-python leads to MCP server takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25905</link><description>The Python code being run by 'runPython' or 'runPythonAsync' is not isolated from the rest of the JS code, allowing any Python code to use the Pyodide APIs to modify the JS environment. This may result in an attacker hijacking the MCP server - for malicious purposes including MCP tool shadowing. Note - the "mcp-run-python" project is archived and unlikely to receive a fix.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2225 | itsourcecode News Portal Project Administrator Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2225</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Administrator Login. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7799 | Reflected XSS in Zirve Information Technologies&amp;#x27; e-Taxpayer Accounting Website</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7799</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zirve Information Technologies Inc. E-Taxpayer Accounting Website allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects e-Taxpayer Accounting Website: through 07082025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25916 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.13 and 1.6 before 1.6.13, when "Block remote images" is used, does not block SVG feImage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25916</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.13 and 1.6 before 1.6.13, when "Block remote images" is used, does not block SVG feImage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2223 | code-projects Online Reviewer System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2223</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/system/students/assessments/pretest/take/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22903 | Stack Overflow via SESSIONID Cookie in lighttpd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22903</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can send a crafted HTTP request containing an overly long SESSIONID cookie. This can trigger a stack buffer overflow in the modified lighttpd server, causing it to crash and potentially enabling remote code execution due to missing stack protections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22904 | Stack Overflow via Oversized Cookie Fields in lighttpd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22904</link><description>Improper length handling when parsing multiple cookie fields (including TRACKID) allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to send oversized cookie values and trigger a stack buffer overflow, resulting in a denial‑of‑service condition and possible remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22905 | Authentication Bypass via URI Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22905</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can bypass authentication by exploiting insufficient URI validation and using path traversal sequences (e.g., /js/../cgi-bin/post.cgi), gaining unauthorized access to protected CGI endpoints and configuration downloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22906 | Hardcoded Key Allows Credential Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22906</link><description>User credentials are stored using AES‑ECB encryption with a hardcoded key. An unauthenticated remote attacker obtaining the configuration file can decrypt and recover plaintext usernames and passwords, especially when combined with the authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2222 | code-projects Online Reviewer System btn_functions.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2222</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/system/admins/manage/users/btn_functions.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument firstname can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2234 | HGiga｜C&amp;amp;Cm@il - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2234</link><description>C&amp;amp;Cm@il developed by HGiga  has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read and modify any user's mail content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2235 | HGiga｜C&amp;amp;Cm@il - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2235</link><description>C&amp;amp;Cm@il developed by HGiga has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2236 | HGiga｜C&amp;amp;Cm@il - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2236</link><description>C&amp;amp;Cm@il developed by HGiga  has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24466 | Products provided by Oki Electric Industry Co., Ltd. and its OEM products (Ricoh Co., Ltd., Murata Machinery, Ltd.) register Windows service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24466</link><description>Products provided by Oki Electric Industry Co., Ltd. and its OEM products (Ricoh Co., Ltd., Murata Machinery, Ltd.) register Windows services with unquoted file paths. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2221 | code-projects Online Reviewer System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2221</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login/index.php of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0870 | GIGABYTE｜MacroHub - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0870</link><description>MacroHub developed by GIGABYTE has a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. Due to the MacroHub application launching external applications with improper privileges, allowing authenticated local attackers to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1868 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine in GitLab AI Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1868</link><description>GitLab has remediated a vulnerability in the Duo Workflow Service component of GitLab AI Gateway affecting all versions of the AI Gateway from 18.1.6, 18.2.6, 18.3.1 to 18.6.1, 18.7.0, and 18.8.0 in which AI Gateway was vulnerable to insecure template expansion of user supplied data via crafted Duo Agent Platform Flow definitions. This vulnerability could be used to cause Denial of Service or gain code execution on the Gateway. This has been fixed in versions 18.6.2, 18.7.1, and 18.8.1 of the GitLab AI Gateway.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2220 | code-projects Online Reviewer System btn_functions.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2220</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/btn_functions.php. Such manipulation of the argument difficulty_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22613 | The server identity check mechanism for firmware upgrade performed via command shell is insecurely implemented potentially allowing an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22613</link><description>The server identity check mechanism for firmware upgrade performed via command shell is insecurely implemented potentially allowing an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-middle attack. This security issue has been fixed in the latest firmware version of Eaton 

Network M3

 which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2218 | D-Link DCS-933L alphapd setSystemAdmin command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2218</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DCS-933L up to 1.14.11. This affects an unknown function of the file /setSystemAdmin of the component alphapd. This manipulation of the argument AdminID causes command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2216 | rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss tools.py download_export_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2216</link><description>A flaw has been found in rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss up to 1.4.8. Impacted is the function download_export_file of the file apis/tools.py. Executing a manipulation of the argument filename can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2217 | itsourcecode Event Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2217</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1615 | All versions of the package jsonpath are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection via unsafe evaluation of user-supplied JSON Path expressions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1615</link><description>All versions of the package jsonpath are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection via unsafe evaluation of user-supplied JSON Path expressions. The library relies on the static-eval module to process JSON Path input, which is not designed to handle untrusted data safely. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by supplying a malicious JSON Path expression that, when evaluated, executes arbitrary JavaScript code, leading to Remote Code Execution in Node.js environments or Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in browser contexts. This affects all methods that evaluate JSON Paths against objects, including .query, .nodes, .paths, .value, .parent, and .apply.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2215 | rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss JWT auth.py default key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2215</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss up to 1.4.8. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file core/auth.py of the component JWT Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument SECRET_KEY results in use of default cryptographic key. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66594 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.

Detailed messages are displayed on the error
page. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66594</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.

Detailed messages are displayed on the error
page. This information could be exploited by an attacker for other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66595 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product is
vulnerable to Cross-Site Request ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product is
vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). When a user accesses a link
crafted by an attacker, the user’s account could be compromised.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66596 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate request h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66596</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate request headers. When an attacker inserts an invalid host
header, users could be redirected to malicious sites.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66597 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
weak cryptographic algorith...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66597</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
weak cryptographic algorithms, potentially allowing an attacker to decrypt
communications with the web server.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66598 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
old SSL/TLS versions, poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66598</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
old SSL/TLS versions, potentially allowing an attacker to decrypt
communications with the web server.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2213 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminAddAlbum.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2213</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddAlbum.php. The manipulation of the argument txtimage results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2214 | code-projects for Plugin AdminAddAlbum.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2214</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects for Plugin 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddAlbum.php. This manipulation of the argument txtalbum causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66599 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Physical paths could
be displayed on web pages. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66599</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Physical paths could
be displayed on web pages. This information could be exploited by an attacker
for other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66600 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product lacks
HSTS (HTTP Strict Transport Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66600</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product lacks
HSTS (HTTP Strict Transport Security) configuration. When an attacker performs
a Man in the middle (MITM) attack, communications with the web server could be
sniffed.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66601 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
specify MIME types. When an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66601</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
specify MIME types. When an attacker performs a content sniffing attack,
malicious scripts could be executed.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66602 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
access by IP address. When...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66602</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
access by IP address. When a worm that randomly searches for IP addresses
intrudes into the network, it could potentially be attacked by the worm.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66603 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
the OPTIONS method. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66603</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
the OPTIONS method. An attacker could potentially use this information to carry
out other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66604 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The library version
could be displayed on the web...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66604</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The library version
could be displayed on the web page. This information could be exploited by an
attacker for other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66605 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Since there are input
fields on this webpage with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66605</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Since there are input
fields on this webpage with the autocomplete attribute enabled, the input
content could be saved in the browser the user is using.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66606 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly encode URLs. An at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66606</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly encode URLs. An attacker could tamper with web pages or execute
malicious scripts.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66607 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The response header
contains an insecure setting....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66607</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The response header
contains an insecure setting. Users could be redirected to malicious sites by
an attacker.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66608 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate URLs. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66608</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate URLs. An attacker could send specially crafted requests to
steal files from the web server.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2211 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminDeleteCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2211</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminDeleteCategory.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2212 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminEditCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2212</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminEditCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2202 | Tenda AC8 httpd WifiGuestSet fromSetWifiGusetBasic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2202</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC8 16.03.33.05. Affected is the function fromSetWifiGusetBasic of the file /goform/WifiGuestSet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument shareSpeed results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2203 | Tenda AC8 Embedded Httpd Service fast_setting_wifi_set buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2203</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.33.05. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set of the component Embedded Httpd Service. This manipulation of the argument timeZone causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2210 | D-Link DIR-823X set_filtering sub_4211C8 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2210</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function sub_4211C8 of the file /goform/set_filtering. Such manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2200 | heyewei JFinalCMS API Endpoint save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2200</link><description>A weakness has been identified in heyewei JFinalCMS 5.0.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/admin/save of the component API Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2201 | ZeroWdd studentmanager LeaveController.java addLeave cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2201</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ZeroWdd studentmanager up to 2151560fc0a50ec00426785ec1e01a3763b380d9. This impacts the function addLeave of the file src/main/java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/LeaveController.java. The manipulation of the argument Reason for Leave leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2198 | code-projects Online Reviewer System loaddata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2198</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/loaddata.php. Such manipulation of the argument difficulty_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2199 | code-projects Online Reviewer System user-delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2199</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /reviewer/system/system/admins/manage/users/user-delete.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2196 | code-projects Online Reviewer System exam-update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/exam-update.php. The manipulation of the argument test_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2197 | code-projects Online Reviewer System exam-delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2197</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/exam-delete.php. This manipulation of the argument test_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2194 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 start_proxy_client_email command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2194</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DI-7100G C1 24.04.18D1. This affects the function start_proxy_client_email. Executing a manipulation can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2195 | code-projects Online Reviewer System questions-view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2195</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/questions-view.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2192 | Tenda AC9 formGetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2192</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC9 15.03.06.42_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formGetRebootTimer. Such manipulation of the argument sys.schedulereboot.start_time/sys.schedulereboot.end_time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2193 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 set_jhttpd_info command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2193</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DI-7100G C1 24.04.18D1. Affected by this issue is the function set_jhttpd_info. Performing a manipulation of the argument usb_username results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2190 | itsourcecode School Management System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2190</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/user/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2191 | Tenda AC9 formGetDdosDefenceList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2191</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC9 15.03.06.42_multi. Affected is the function formGetDdosDefenceList. This manipulation of the argument security.ddos.map causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2189 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2189</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/report/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ay leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2188 | UTT 进取 521G formPdbUpConfig sub_446B18 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2188</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 进取 521G 3.1.1-190816. The impacted element is the function sub_446B18 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Executing a manipulation of the argument policyNames can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2186 | Tenda RX3 SetIpMacBind fromSetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2186</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Impacted is the function fromSetIpMacBind of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. Such manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2187 | Tenda RX3 formSetQosBand set_qosMib_list stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. The affected element is the function set_qosMib_list of the file /goform/formSetQosBand. Performing a manipulation of the argument list results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2184 | Great Developers Certificate Generation System csv.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2184</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Great Developers Certificate Generation System up to 97171bb0e5e22e52eacf4e4fa81773e5f3cffb73. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /restructured/csv.php. The manipulation of the argument photo results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2185 | Tenda RX3 MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint setBlackRule set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2185</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. This issue affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument devName/mac causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2182 | UTT 进取 521G setSysAdm doSystem command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2182</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 进取 521G 3.1.1-190816. Affected by this issue is the function doSystem of the file /goform/setSysAdm. Executing a manipulation of the argument passwd1 can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2183 | Great Developers Certificate Generation System csv.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2183</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Great Developers Certificate Generation System up to 97171bb0e5e22e52eacf4e4fa81773e5f3cffb73. This affects an unknown part of the file /restructured/csv.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2179 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2179</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-users.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2180 | Tenda RX3 fast_setting_wifi_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2180</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. Such manipulation of the argument ssid_5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2181 | Tenda RX3 openSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2181</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. Performing a manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2176 | code-projects Contact Management System index.py sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2176</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Contact Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.py. Such manipulation of the argument selecteditem[0] leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2177 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Login session fixiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2177</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Login. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2178 | r-huijts xcode-mcp-server run_lldb index.ts registerXcodeTools command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2178</link><description>A vulnerability was found in r-huijts xcode-mcp-server up to f3419f00117aa9949e326f78cc940166c88f18cb. This affects the function registerXcodeTools of the file src/tools/xcode/index.ts of the component run_lldb. The manipulation of the argument args results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The patch is identified as 11f8d6bacadd153beee649f92a78a9dad761f56f. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2173 | code-projects Online Examination System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2173</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2174 | code-projects Contact Management System CRUD Endpoint improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2174</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Contact Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component CRUD Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authentication. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2175 | D-Link DIR-823X set_upnp sub_420618 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2175</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420618 of the file /goform/set_upnp. This manipulation of the argument upnp_enable causes os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2171 | code-projects Online Student Management System Login accounts.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2171</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Student Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file accounts.php of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument username/password results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2172 | code-projects Online Application System for Admission Login Endpoint index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2172</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Application System for Admission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file enrollment/index.php of the component Login Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2168 | D-Link DWR-M921 formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel sub_419920 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2168</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. This affects the function sub_419920 of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel. This manipulation of the argument fota_url causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2169 | D-Link DWR-M921 formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2169</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. This impacts an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom. Such manipulation of the argument fota_url leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2166 | code-projects Online Reviewer System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2166</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /login/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2167 | Totolink WA300 cstecgi.cgi setAPNetwork os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2167</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Totolink WA300 5.2cu.7112_B20190227. The impacted element is the function setAPNetwork of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument Ipaddr results in os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2163 | D-Link DIR-600 ssdp.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2163</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-600 up to 2.15WWb02. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ssdp.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument HTTP_ST/REMOTE_ADDR/REMOTE_PORT/SERVER_ID leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2164 | detronetdip E-commerce addadhar.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2164</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in detronetdip E-commerce 1.0.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /seller/assets/backend/profile/addadhar.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2165 | detronetdip E-commerce Account Creation Endpoint add_seller.php missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2165</link><description>A weakness has been identified in detronetdip E-commerce 1.0.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Admin/assets/backend/seller/add_seller.php of the component Account Creation Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument email can lead to missing authentication. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2161 | itsourcecode Directory Management System forget-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2161</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Directory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/forget-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2162 | itsourcecode News Portal Project aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2162</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/aboutus.php. This manipulation of the argument pagetitle causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2159 | SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website Registration Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2159</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tourism/classes/Master.php?f=register of the component Registration. Executing a manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/username can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2160 | SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2160</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tourism/classes/Master.php?f=save_package. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2157 | D-Link DIR-823X set_static_route_table sub_4175CC os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2157</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function sub_4175CC of the file /goform/set_static_route_table. Such manipulation of the argument interface/destip/netmask/gateway/metric leads to os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2158 | code-projects Student Web Portal check_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2158</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Student Web Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /check_user.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2156 | code-projects Online Student Management System Announcement Management index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2156</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/announcement/index.php?view=add of the component Announcement Management Module. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2155 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration set_dmz sub_4208A0 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2155</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is the function sub_4208A0 of the file /goform/set_dmz of the component Configuration Handler. The manipulation of the argument dmz_host/dmz_enable results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2154 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System Patient Registration registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2154</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /registration.php of the component Patient Registration Module. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2153 | mwielgoszewski doorman views.py is_safe_url redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2153</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in mwielgoszewski doorman up to 0.6. This issue affects the function is_safe_url of the file doorman/users/views.py. Executing a manipulation of the argument Next can lead to open redirect. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2152 | D-Link DIR-615 Web Configuration adv_routing.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2152</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file adv_routing.php of the component Web Configuration Interface. Performing a manipulation of the argument dest_ip/ submask/ gw results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2151 | D-Link DIR-615 DMZ Host Feature adv_firewall.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2151</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This affects an unknown part of the file adv_firewall.php of the component DMZ Host Feature. Such manipulation of the argument dmz_ipaddr  leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2150 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System checkin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2150</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /checkin.php. This manipulation of the argument patient_id causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2149 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System appointments.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2149</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /appointments.php. The manipulation of the argument patient_id results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2148 | Tenda AC21 Web Management DownloadFlash information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2148</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/DownloadFlash of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2147 | Tenda AC21 Web Management DownloadLog information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2147</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This impacts an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/DownloadLog of the component Web Management Interface. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2146 | guchengwuyue yshopmall co.yixiang.utils.FileUtil updateAvatar unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2146</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in guchengwuyue yshopmall up to 1.9.1. This affects the function updateAvatar of the file /api/users/updateAvatar of the component co.yixiang.utils.FileUtil. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2145 | cym1102 nginxWebUI Web Management check cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2145</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 4.3.7. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /adminPage/conf/check of the component Web Management Interface. Such manipulation of the argument nginxDir leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2143 | D-Link DIR-823X DDNS Service set_ddns os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2143</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/set_ddns of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation of the argument ddnsType/ddnsDomainName/ddnsUserName/ddnsPwd leads to os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2142 | D-Link DIR-823X set_qos sub_420688 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2142</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420688 of the file /goform/set_qos. Executing a manipulation can lead to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2141 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM URL PermissionServiceImpl.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2141</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM up to 11.3.3. This affects an unknown part of the file gateway/src/main/java/com/kakarote/gateway/service/impl/PermissionServiceImpl.java of the component URL Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2140 | Tenda TX9 setMacFilterCfg sub_4223E0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2140</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4223E0 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg. Such manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2139 | Tenda TX9 fast_setting_wifi_set sub_432580 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2139</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_432580 of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2138 | Tenda TX9 SetStaticRouteCfg sub_42D03C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected is the function sub_42D03C of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2137 | Tenda TX3 SetIpMacBind buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda TX3 up to 16.03.13.11_multi. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2136 | projectworlds Online Food Ordering System view-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2136</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectworlds Online Food Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /view-ticket.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2134 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-doctors.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /hms/admin/manage-doctors.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2135 | UTT HiPER 810 formPdbUpConfig sub_43F020 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_43F020 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument policyNames results in command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2132 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2132</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument txtcat results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2133 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2133</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. This manipulation of the argument txtimage causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2130 | BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret search_username index.ts command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2130</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret up to 1.0.12. This affects an unknown part of the file src/index.ts of the component search_username. Executing a manipulation of the argument Username can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.13 is able to mitigate this issue. This patch is called b1ae073c4b3e789ab8de36dc6ca8111ae9399e7a. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2131 | XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server input_text os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2131</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server 0.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function input_text. The manipulation of the argument text leads to os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15027 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15027</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15100 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via jay_panel_ajax_update_profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15100</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_panel_ajax_update_profile' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2129 | D-Link DIR-823X set_ac_status os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/set_ac_status. Performing a manipulation of the argument ac_ipaddr/ac_ipstatus/ap_randtime results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2205 | WeKan Meteor Publication cards.js CardPubSubBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2205</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This affects an unknown part of the file server/publications/cards.js of the component Meteor Publication Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to mitigate this issue. The name of the patch is 0f5a9c38778ca550cbab6c5093470e1e90cb837f. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2206 | WeKan Administrative Repair fixDuplicateLists.js FixDuplicateBleed access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2206</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WeKan up to 8.20. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file server/methods/fixDuplicateLists.js of the component Administrative Repair Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to resolve this issue. The patch is named 4ce181d17249778094f73d21515f7f863f554743. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2207 | WeKan Activity Publication activities.js LinkedBoardActivitiesBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2207</link><description>A weakness has been identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file server/publications/activities.js of the component Activity Publication Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is capable of addressing this issue. This patch is called 91a936e07d2976d4246dfe834281c3aaa87f9503. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2208 | WeKan Rules rules.js RulesBleed authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2208</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in WeKan up to 8.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file server/publications/rules.js of the component Rules Handler. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is recommended to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is a787bcddf33ca28afb13ff5ea9a4cb92dceac005. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2209 | WeKan Custom Translation translationBody.js setCreateTranslation improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2209</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in WeKan up to 8.18. The affected element is the function setCreateTranslation of the file client/components/settings/translationBody.js of the component Custom Translation Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 8.19 is sufficient to fix this issue. The patch is identified as f244a43771f6ebf40218b83b9f46dba6b940d7de. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2120 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration Parameter set_server_settings os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2120</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/set_server_settings of the component Configuration Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument terminal_addr/server_ip/server_port leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2122 | Xiaopi Panel WAF Firewall demo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2122</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Xiaopi Panel up to 20260126. This impacts an unknown function of the file /demo.php of the component WAF Firewall. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2118 | UTT HiPER 810 rehttpd formReleaseConnect sub_4407D4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2118</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_4407D4 of the file /goform/formReleaseConnect of the component rehttpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument Isp_Name can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2117 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_activity.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument activity_id results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:02:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2116 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_expenses.php. Such manipulation of the argument expenses_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 23:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2115 | itsourcecode Society Management System delete_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2115</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete_expenses.php. This manipulation of the argument expenses_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25859 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.20 Migration Functionality Insufficient Permission Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25859</link><description>Wekan versions prior to 8.20 allow non-administrative users to access migration functionality due to insufficient permission checks, potentially resulting in unauthorized migration operations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2114 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2114</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25560 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 LDAP Authentication Filter Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25560</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an LDAP filter injection vulnerability in LDAP authentication. User-supplied username input is incorporated into LDAP search filters and DN-related values without adequate escaping, allowing an attacker to manipulate LDAP queries during authentication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25561 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Attachment Upload Object Relationship Validation Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25561</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization weakness in the attachment upload API. The API does not fully validate that provided identifiers (such as boardId, cardId, swimlaneId, and listId) are consistent and refer to a coherent card/board relationship, enabling attempts to upload attachments with mismatched object relationships.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25562 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Attachments Publication Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25562</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an information disclosure vulnerability in the attachments publication. Attachment metadata can be returned without properly scoping results to boards and cards accessible to the requesting user, potentially exposing attachment metadata to unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25563 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Checklist Creation Cross-Board IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25563</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in checklist creation and related checklist routes. The implementation does not verify that the supplied cardId belongs to the supplied boardId, allowing cross-board ID tampering by manipulating identifiers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25564 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Checklist Deletion IDOR via Missing Relationship Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25564</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in checklist creation and related checklist routes. The implementation does not verify that the supplied cardId belongs to the supplied boardId, allowing cross-board ID tampering by manipulating identifiers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25565 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Read-only Board Roles Can Update Cards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25565</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization vulnerability where certain card update API paths validate only board read access rather than requiring write permission. This can allow users with read-only roles to perform card updates that should require write access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25566 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Cross-board Card Move Without Destination Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25566</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization vulnerability in card move logic. A user can specify a destination board/list/swimlane without adequate authorization checks for the destination and without validating that destination objects belong to the destination board, potentially enabling unauthorized cross-board moves.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25567 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Card Comment Author Spoofing via User-controlled authorId</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25567</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in the card comment creation API. The endpoint accepts an authorId from the request body, allowing an authenticated user to spoof the recorded comment author by supplying another user's identifier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25568 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 allowPrivateOnly Setting Enforcement Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25568</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization logic vulnerability where the instance configuration setting allowPrivateOnly is not sufficiently enforced at board creation time. When allowPrivateOnly is enabled, users can still create public boards due to incomplete server-side enforcement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25857 | Tenda G300-F Command Injection via formSetWanDiag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25857</link><description>Tenda G300-F router firmware versio 16.01.14.2 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the WAN diagnostic functionality (formSetWanDiag). The implementation constructs a shell command that invokes curl and incorporates attacker-controlled input into the command line without adequate neutralization. As a result, a remote attacker with access to the affected management interface can inject additional shell syntax and execute arbitrary commands on the device with the privileges of the management process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25858 | macrozheng mall &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 Unauthenticated Password Reset via OTP Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25858</link><description>macrozheng mall version 1.0.3 and prior contains an authentication vulnerability in the mall-portal password reset workflow that allows an unauthenticated attacker to reset arbitrary user account passwords using only a victim’s telephone number. The password reset flow exposes the one-time password (OTP) directly in the API response and validates password reset requests solely by comparing the provided OTP to a value stored by telephone number, without verifying user identity or ownership of the telephone number. This enables remote account takeover of any user with a known or guessable telephone number.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15564 | Mapnik value.cpp operator divide by zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15564</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Mapnik up to 4.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function mapnik::detail::mod&lt;...&gt;::operator of the file src/value.cpp. The manipulation leads to divide by zero. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2113 | yuan1994 tpadmin WebUploader preview.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2113</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yuan1994 tpadmin up to 1.3.12. This affects an unknown part in the library /public/static/admin/lib/webuploader/0.1.5/server/preview.php of the component WebUploader. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2111 | JeecgBoot Retrieval-Augmented Generation edit path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2111</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /airag/knowledge/doc/edit of the component Retrieval-Augmented Generation Module. Executing a manipulation of the argument filePath can lead to path traversal. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2110 | Tasin1025 SwiftBuy login.php excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2110</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tasin1025 SwiftBuy up to 0f5011372e8d1d7edfd642d57d721c9fadc54ec7. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. Performing a manipulation results in improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2109 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Delete Category undo improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2109</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in jsbroks COCO Annotator up to 0.11.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/undo/ of the component Delete Category Handler. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2108 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Endpoint long_task denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2108</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jsbroks COCO Annotator up to 0.11.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file /api/info/long_task of the component Endpoint. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2107 | yeqifu warehouse Log Info LoginfoController.java batchDeleteLoginfo improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function loadAllLoginfo/deleteLoginfo/batchDeleteLoginfo of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\LoginfoController.java of the component Log Info Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2106 | yeqifu warehouse Notice Management NoticeController.java batchDeleteNotice improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. The impacted element is the function addNotice/updateNotice/deleteNotice/batchDeleteNotice of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\NoticeController.java of the component Notice Management. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2105 | yeqifu warehouse Department Management DeptController.java deleteDept improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2105</link><description>A flaw has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. The affected element is the function addDept/updateDept/deleteDept of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\DeptController.java of the component Department Management. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2090 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2090</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/message/search.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument term can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2089 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2089</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/subject/controller.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2088 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System accepted-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2088</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/accepted-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument delid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2087 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2087</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. This manipulation of the argument user_email causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2086 | UTT HiPER 810G Management formFireWall strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2086</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formFireWall of the component Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument GroupName results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2085 | D-Link DWR-M921 USSD Configuration Endpoint formUSSDSetup sub_419F20 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2085</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. Affected is the function sub_419F20 of the file /boafrm/formUSSDSetup of the component USSD Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ussdValue leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2084 | D-Link DIR-823X set_language os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2084</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/set_language. Executing a manipulation of the argument langSelection can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2083 | code-projects Social Networking Site delete_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2083</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Social Networking Site 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /delete_post.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2082 | D-Link DIR-823X set_mac_clone os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2082</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_mac_clone. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2081 | D-Link DIR-823X set_password os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2081</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_password. This manipulation of the argument http_passwd causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2080 | UTT HiPER 810 formUser setSysAdm command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2080</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. This issue affects the function setSysAdm of the file /goform/formUser. The manipulation of the argument passwd1 leads to command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15476 | The Bucketlister &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Bucket List Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15476</link><description>The The Bucketlister plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the bucketlister_do_admin_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add delete or modify arbitrary bucket list items.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15477 | The Bucketlister &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via `category` and `id` Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15477</link><description>The Bucketlister plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode `category` and `id` attributes in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameters and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0555 | Premmerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;premmerce_wizard_actions&amp;#x27; AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0555</link><description>The Premmerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'premmerce_wizard_actions' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.20. This is due to missing capability checks and insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the `state` parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page (the Premmerce Wizard admin page).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1082 | TITLE ANIMATOR &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1082</link><description>The TITLE ANIMATOR plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings page form handler in `inc/settings-page.php`. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1570 | Simple Bible Verse via Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1570</link><description>The Simple Bible Verse via Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `verse` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1573 | OMIGO &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1573</link><description>The OMIGO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `omigo_donate_button` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1608 | Video Onclick &amp;lt;= 0.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1608</link><description>The Video Onclick plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `youtube` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1611 | Wikiloops Track Player &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1611</link><description>The Wikiloops Track Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `wikiloops` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1613 | Wonka Slide &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1613</link><description>The Wonka Slide plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `list_class` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1634 | Subitem AL Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1634</link><description>The Subitem AL Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1643 | MP-Ukagaka &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1643</link><description>The MP-Ukagaka plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1675 | Advanced Country Blocker &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Unauthenticated Authorization Bypass via Insecure Default Secret Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1675</link><description>The Advanced Country Blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authorization Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to the use of a predictable default value for the secret bypass key created during installation without requiring users to change it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the geolocation blocking mechanism by appending the key to any URL on sites where the administrator has not changed the default value.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2079 | yeqifu warehouse Menu Management MenuController.java deleteMenu improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2079</link><description>A flaw has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This vulnerability affects the function addMenu/updateMenu/deleteMenu of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\MenuController.java of the component Menu Management. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2078 | yeqifu warehouse Permission Management PermissionController.java deletePermission improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2078</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function addPermission/updatePermission/deletePermission of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\PermissionController.java of the component Permission Management. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2077 | yeqifu warehouse Role Management RoleController.java deleteRole improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2077</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected by this issue is the function addRole/updateRole/deleteRole of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\RoleController.java of the component Role Management Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2076 | yeqifu warehouse User Management Endpoint UserController.java deleteUser improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2076</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function addUser/updateUser/deleteUser of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\UserController.java of the component User Management Endpoint. This manipulation causes improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15491 | Post Slides &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Contributor+ Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15491</link><description>The Post Slides WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not validate some shortcode attributes before using them to generate paths passed to include function/s, allowing any authenticated users such as with contributor or higher roles to perform LFI attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12159 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12159</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_raw_content shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12803 | Bold Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_tabs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12803</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin 'bt_bb_tabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13463 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting in Post Grid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13463</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Grid component in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15267 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_accordion_item Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15267</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_accordion_item shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2075 | yeqifu warehouse Role-Permission Binding RoleController.java saveRolePermission access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2075</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected is the function saveRolePermission of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\RoleController.java of the component Role-Permission Binding Handler. The manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2074 | O2OA HTTP POST Request check xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2074</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in O2OA up to 9.0.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /x_program_center/jaxrs/mpweixin/check of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31990 | HCL DevOps Velocity is susceptible to a Denial of Service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31990</link><description>Rate limiting for certain API calls is not being enforced, making HCL Velocity vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) attacks.  An attacker could flood the system with a large number of requests, overwhelming its resources and causing it to become unresponsive to legitimate users.  This vulnerability is fixed in 5.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2073 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2073</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/user/index.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2071 | UTT 进取 520W formP2PLimitConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2071</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formP2PLimitConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument except results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>