<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:32:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-8185 | Vault Vulnerable to Denial of Service When Processing Raft Join Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8185</link><description>Vault Community and Vault Enterprise (“Vault”) clusters using Vault’s Integrated Storage backend are vulnerable to a denial-of-service (DoS) attack through memory exhaustion through a Raft cluster join API endpoint . An attacker may send a large volume of requests to the endpoint which may cause Vault to consume excessive system memory resources, potentially leading to a crash of the underlying system and the Vault process itself.

This vulnerability, CVE-2024-8185, is fixed in Vault Community 1.18.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.18.1, 1.17.8, and 1.16.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8553 | Foreman: read-only access to entire db from templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8553</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Foreman's loader macros introduced with report templates. These macros may allow an authenticated user with permissions to view and create templates to read any field from Foreman's database. By using specific strings in the loader macros, users can bypass permissions and access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48910 | DOMPurify vulnerable to tampering by prototype polution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48910</link><description>DOMPurify is a DOM-only, super-fast, uber-tolerant XSS sanitizer for HTML, MathML and SVG. DOMPurify was vulnerable to prototype pollution. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51254 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51254</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the sign_cacertificate function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51259 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51259</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the setup_cacertificate function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42835 | langflow v1.0.12 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the PythonCodeTool component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42835</link><description>langflow v1.0.12 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the PythonCodeTool component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 13:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10454 | Clickjacking vulnerability in Clibo Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10454</link><description>Clickjacking vulnerability in Clibo Manager v1.1.9.12 in the '/public/login' directory, a login panel. This vulnerability occurs due to the absence of an X-Frame-Options server-side header. An attacker could overlay a transparent iframe to perform click hijacking on victims.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 13:06:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8934 | Beckhoff: Local command injection via TwinCAT Package Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8934</link><description>A local user with administrative access rights can enter specialy crafted values for settings at the user interface (UI) of the TwinCAT Package Manager which then causes arbitrary OS commands to be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 13:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43930 | WordPress JobSearch WP Job Board WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43930</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in eyecix JobSearch allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects JobSearch: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43933 | WordPress WPMobile.App plugin &amp;lt;= 11.48 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43933</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPMobile.App allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPMobile.App: from n/a through 11.48.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43383 | Apache Lucene.Net.Replicator: Remote Code Execution in Lucene.Net.Replicator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43383</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Lucene.Net.Replicator.

This issue affects Apache Lucene.NET's Replicator library: from 4.8.0-beta00005 through 4.8.0-beta00016.

An attacker that can intercept traffic between a replication client and server, or control the target replication node URL, can provide a specially-crafted JSON response that is deserialized as an attacker-provided exception type. This can result in remote code execution or other potential unauthorized access.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.8.0-beta00017, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43984 | WordPress Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.13 - CSRF to Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43984</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Podlove Podlove Podcast Publisher allows Code Injection.This issue affects Podlove Podcast Publisher: from n/a through 4.1.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49674 | WordPress  EKC Tournament Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - CSRF to Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49674</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Lukas Huser EKC Tournament Manager allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects EKC Tournament Manager: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49685 | WordPress Custom Twitter Feeds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49685</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Smash Balloon Custom Twitter Feeds (Tweets Widget) allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Custom Twitter Feeds (Tweets Widget): from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30149 | HCL AppScan Source is affected by an expired TLS/SSL certificate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30149</link><description>HCL AppScan Source &lt;= 10.6.0 does not properly validate a TLS/SSL certificate for an executable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 08:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9165 | Gift Cards (Gift Vouchers and Packages) (WooCommerce Supported) &amp;lt;= 4.4.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9165</link><description>The Gift Cards (Gift Vouchers and Packages) (WooCommerce Supported) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 06:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9430 | Get Quote For Woocommerce – Request A Quote For Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Quote PDF and CSV Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9430</link><description>The Get Quote For Woocommerce – Request A Quote For Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of Quote data due to a missing capability check on the ct_tepfw_wp_loaded function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download Quote PDF and CSV documents.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 06:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9434 | WPGlobus Translate Options &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9434</link><description>The WPGlobus Translate Options plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the on__translate_options_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts and update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 06:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9446 | WP Simple Anchors Links &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpanchor Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9446</link><description>The WP Simple Anchors Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpanchor shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 06:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10392 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.89 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10392</link><description>The AI Power: Complete AI Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'handle_image_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.89. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 05:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9700 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.36.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Submission Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9700</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.36.0 via the submit_quizzes() function due to missing validation on the 'entry_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify other user's quiz submissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 05:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21537 | Versions of the package lilconfig from 3.1.0 and before 3.1.1 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution due to the insecure usage of eval i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21537</link><description>Versions of the package lilconfig from 3.1.0 and before 3.1.1 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution due to the insecure usage of eval in the dynamicImport function. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by passing a malicious input through the defaultLoaders function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 05:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9708 | Easy SVG Upload &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9708</link><description>The Easy SVG Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 02:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10544 | Woo Manage Fraud Orders &amp;lt;= 6.1.7 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Log Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10544</link><description>The Woo Manage Fraud Orders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information about users contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 02:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10559 | SourceCodester Airport Booking Management System Passport Number details buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10559</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Airport Booking Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function details of the component Passport Number Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 02:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10561 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System birdsupdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10561</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file birdsupdate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 02:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48311 | Piwigo v14.5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the Edit album function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48311</link><description>Piwigo v14.5.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the Edit album function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 01:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10557 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System updateprofile.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10557</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /file/updateprofile.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 01:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10556 | Codezips Pet Shop Management System birdsadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10556</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Codezips Pet Shop Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file birdsadd.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48307 | JeecgBoot v3.7.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /onlDragDatasetHead/getTotalData.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48307</link><description>JeecgBoot v3.7.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /onlDragDatasetHead/getTotalData.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10086 | Consul Vulnerable To Reflected XSS On Content-Type Error Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10086</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Consul and Consul Enterprise such that the server response did not explicitly set a Content-Type HTTP header, allowing user-provided inputs to be misinterpreted and lead to reflected XSS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 21:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10005 | Consul L7 Intentions Vulnerable To URL Path Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10005</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Consul and Consul Enterprise (“Consul”) such that using URL paths in L7 traffic intentions could bypass HTTP request path-based access rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 21:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10006 | Consul L7 Intentions Vulnerable To Headers Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10006</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Consul and Consul Enterprise (“Consul”) such that using Headers in L7 traffic intentions could bypass HTTP header based access rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 21:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48807 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System v.1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48807</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System v.1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the search parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 21:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51426 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the _transfer function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51426</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the _transfer function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48733 | SQL injection vulnerability in /SASStudio/sasexec/sessions/{sessionID}/sql in SAS Studio 9.4 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48733</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in /SASStudio/sasexec/sessions/{sessionID}/sql in SAS Studio 9.4 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the POST body request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:48:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48734 | *Unrestricted file upload in /SASStudio/SASStudio/sasexec/{sessionID}/{InternalPath} in SAS Studio 9.4 allows remote attacker to upload mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48734</link><description>*Unrestricted file upload in /SASStudio/SASStudio/sasexec/{sessionID}/{InternalPath} in SAS Studio 9.4 allows remote attacker to upload malicious files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51424 | An issue in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Owned.setOwner function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51424</link><description>An issue in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Owned.setOwner function</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51425 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the WaterToken Contract.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51425</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the WaterToken Contract.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51427 | An issue in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the PepeGxng smart contract mint function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51427</link><description>An issue in Ethereum v.1.12.2 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the PepeGxng smart contract mint function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52066 | http.zig commit 76cf5 was discovered to contain a CRLF injection vulnerability via the url parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52066</link><description>http.zig commit 76cf5 was discovered to contain a CRLF injection vulnerability via the url parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48735 | Directory Traversal in /SASStudio/sasexec/sessions/{sessionID}/workspace/{InternalPath} in SAS Studio 9.4 allows remote attacker to access i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48735</link><description>Directory Traversal in /SASStudio/sasexec/sessions/{sessionID}/workspace/{InternalPath} in SAS Studio 9.4 allows remote attacker to access internal files by manipulating default path during file download.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51419 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Shenzhen Interconnection Harbor Network Technology Co., Ltd Ofweek Online Exhibition v.1.0.0 allows a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51419</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Shenzhen Interconnection Harbor Network Technology Co., Ltd Ofweek Online Exhibition v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43382 | Snowflake JDBC driver versions &gt;= 3.2.6 and &lt;= 3.19.1 have an Incorrect Security Setting that can result in data being uploaded to an encryp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43382</link><description>Snowflake JDBC driver versions &gt;= 3.2.6 and &lt;= 3.19.1 have an Incorrect Security Setting that can result in data being uploaded to an encrypted stage without the additional layer of protection provided by client side encryption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48112 | A deserialization vulnerability in the component \controller\Index.php of Thinkphp v6.1.3 to v8.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48112</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability in the component \controller\Index.php of Thinkphp v6.1.3 to v8.0.4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48346 | xtreme1 &lt;= v0.9.1 contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the /api/data/upload path. The vulnerability is triggered t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48346</link><description>xtreme1 &lt;= v0.9.1 contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the /api/data/upload path. The vulnerability is triggered through the fileUrl parameter, which allows an attacker to make arbitrary requests to internal or external systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51242 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in eladmin 2.7 and earlier in ServerDeployController.java. The manipu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51242</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in eladmin 2.7 and earlier in ServerDeployController.java. The manipulation of the HTTP Body ip parameter leads to SSRF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51243 | The eladmin v2.7 and before contains a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability that can control all application deployment servers of this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51243</link><description>The eladmin v2.7 and before contains a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability that can control all application deployment servers of this management system via DeployController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48093 | Unrestricted File Upload in the Discussions tab in Operately v.0.1.0 allows a privileged user to achieve Remote Code Execution via uploading...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48093</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload in the Discussions tab in Operately v.0.1.0 allows a privileged user to achieve Remote Code Execution via uploading and executing malicious files without validating file extensions or content types.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48271 | D-Link DSL6740C v6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to use insecure default credentials for Administrator access, possibly allowing attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48271</link><description>D-Link DSL6740C v6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to use insecure default credentials for Administrator access, possibly allowing attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges on the device via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48272 | D-Link DSL6740C v6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to use an insecure default Wifi password, possibly allowing attackers to connect to the dev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48272</link><description>D-Link DSL6740C v6.TR069.20211230 was discovered to use an insecure default Wifi password, possibly allowing attackers to connect to the device via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10546 | open-scratch Teaching 在线教学平台 URL getDictItemsByTable sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10546</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in open-scratch Teaching 在线教学平台 up to 2.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/sys/ng-alain/getDictItemsByTable/ of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 19:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46531 | phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the searchinputdata parameter a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46531</link><description>phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the searchinputdata parameter at /index.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48202 | icecms &lt;=3.4.7 has a File Upload vulnerability in FileUtils.java,uploadFile.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48202</link><description>icecms &lt;=3.4.7 has a File Upload vulnerability in FileUtils.java,uploadFile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10456 | Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10456</link><description>Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master versions prior to 1.0.12 are affected by a deserialization vulnerability that targets the Device-Gateway, which could allow deserialization of arbitrary .NET objects prior to authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31972 | EnGenius ESR580 A8J-EMR5000 devices allow a remote attacker to conduct stored XSS attacks that could lead to arbitrary JavaScript code execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31972</link><description>EnGenius ESR580 A8J-EMR5000 devices allow a remote attacker to conduct stored XSS attacks that could lead to arbitrary JavaScript code execution (under the context of the user's session) via the Wi-Fi SSID input fields. Web scripts embedded into the vulnerable fields this way are executed immediately when a user logs into the admin page. This affects /admin/wifi/wlan1 and /admin/wifi/wlan_guest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31975 | EnGenius ESR580 devices through 1.1.30 allow a remote attacker to conduct stored XSS attacks via the Wi-Fi SSID parameters. JavaScript embed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31975</link><description>EnGenius ESR580 devices through 1.1.30 allow a remote attacker to conduct stored XSS attacks via the Wi-Fi SSID parameters. JavaScript embedded into a vulnerable field is executed when the user clicks the SSID field's corresponding EDIT button.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36060 | EnGenius EnStation5-AC A8J-ENS500AC 1.0.0 devices allow blind OS command injection via shell metacharacters in the Ping and Speed Test param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36060</link><description>EnGenius EnStation5-AC A8J-ENS500AC 1.0.0 devices allow blind OS command injection via shell metacharacters in the Ping and Speed Test parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37573 | The Talkatone com.talkatone.android application 8.4.6 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone cal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37573</link><description>The Talkatone com.talkatone.android application 8.4.6 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone calls without user interaction by sending a crafted intent via the com.talkatone.vedroid.ui.launcher.OutgoingCallInterceptor component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42041 | The com.videodownload.browser.videodownloader (aka AppTool-Browser-Video All Video Downloader) application 20-30.05.24 for Android allows an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42041</link><description>The com.videodownload.browser.videodownloader (aka AppTool-Browser-Video All Video Downloader) application 20-30.05.24 for Android allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the acr.browser.lightning.DefaultBrowserActivity component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31973 | Hitron CODA-4582 2AHKM-CODA4589 7.2.4.5.1b8 devices allow a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity to conduct stored XSS attacks via the 'Ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31973</link><description>Hitron CODA-4582 2AHKM-CODA4589 7.2.4.5.1b8 devices allow a remote attacker within Wi-Fi proximity to conduct stored XSS attacks via the 'Network Name (SSID)' input fields to the /index.html#wireless_basic page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48214 | KERUI HD 3MP 1080P Tuya Camera 1.0.4 has a command injection vulnerability in the module that connects to the local network via a QR code. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48214</link><description>KERUI HD 3MP 1080P Tuya Camera 1.0.4 has a command injection vulnerability in the module that connects to the local network via a QR code. This vulnerability allows an attacker to create a custom, unauthenticated QR code and abuse one of the parameters, either SSID or PASSWORD, in the JSON data contained within the QR code. By that, the attacker can execute arbitrary code on the camera.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48241 | An issue in radare2 v5.8.0 through v5.9.4 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the __bf_div function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48241</link><description>An issue in radare2 v5.8.0 through v5.9.4 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the __bf_div function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48569 | Proactive Risk Manager version 9.1.1.0 is affected by multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the add/edit form fields, at th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48569</link><description>Proactive Risk Manager version 9.1.1.0 is affected by multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the add/edit form fields, at the urls starting with the subpaths: /ar/config/configuation/ and /ar/config/risk-strategy-control/</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48646 | An Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability exists in Sage 1000 v7.0.0, which allows authorized users to upload files without proper validatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48646</link><description>An Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability exists in Sage 1000 v7.0.0, which allows authorized users to upload files without proper validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious files, such as HTML, scripts, or other executable content, that may be executed on the server, leading to further system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48647 | A file disclosure vulnerability exists in Sage 1000 v7.0.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to retrieve arbitrary files from the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48647</link><description>A file disclosure vulnerability exists in Sage 1000 v7.0.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to retrieve arbitrary files from the server's file system by manipulating the URL parameter in HTTP requests. The attacker can exploit this flaw to access sensitive information, including configuration files that may contain credentials and system settings, which could lead to further compromise of the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48648 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Sage 1000 v 7.0.0. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48648</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Sage 1000 v 7.0.0. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into URLs, which are reflected back by the server in the response without proper sanitization or encoding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9419 | Certain HP Print Products–Potential Remote Code Execution and/or Elevation of Privilege with the HP Smart Universal Printing Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9419</link><description>Client / Server PCs with the HP Smart Universal Printing Driver installed are potentially vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and/or Elevation of Privilege. A client using the HP Smart Universal Printing Driver that sends a print job comprised of a malicious XPS file could potentially lead to Remote Code Execution and/or Elevation of Privilege on the PC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 17:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9110 | Cross-Site Scripting In Privileged Identity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9110</link><description>A medium severity vulnerability has been identified within Privileged Identity which can allow an attacker to perform reflected cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 17:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51258 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51258</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doSSLTunnel function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50344 | I, Librarian has a Stored XSS vulnerability in Supplemental Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50344</link><description>I, Librarian is an open-source version of a PDF managing SaaS. Supplemental Files are allowed to be viewed in the browser, only if they have a white-listed MIME type. Unfortunately, this logic is broken, thus allowing unsafe files containing Javascript to be executed with the application context. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by uploading a supplementary file that contains a malicious code or script. This code will then be executed when the file is loaded in the browser. The vulnerability was fixed in version 5.11.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 15:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50419 | WordPress Greenshift plugin &amp;lt;= 9.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50419</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Wpsoul Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks: from n/a through 9.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 15:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50353 | ICG.AspNetCore.Utilities.CloudStorage&amp;#x27;s Secure Token Durations Different Than Expected</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50353</link><description>ICG.AspNetCore.Utilities.CloudStorage is a collection of cloud storage utilities to assist with the management of files for cloud upload. Users of this library that set a duration for a SAS Uri with a value other than 1 hour may have generated a URL with a duration that is longer, or shorter than desired. Users not implemented SAS Uri's are unaffected. This issue was resolved in version 8.0.0 of the library.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 14:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23309 | The LevelOne WBR-6012 router with firmware R0.40e6 has an authentication bypass vulnerability in its web application due to reliance on clie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23309</link><description>The LevelOne WBR-6012 router with firmware R0.40e6 has an authentication bypass vulnerability in its web application due to reliance on client IP addresses for authentication. Attackers could spoof an IP address to gain unauthorized access without needing a session token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24777 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the Web Application functionality of the LevelOne WBR-6012 R0.40e6. A specially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24777</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the Web Application functionality of the LevelOne WBR-6012 R0.40e6. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to unauthorized access. An attacker can stage a malicious web page to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28052 | The WBR-6012 is a wireless SOHO router. It is a low-cost device which functions as an internet gateway for homes and small offices while aim...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28052</link><description>The WBR-6012 is a wireless SOHO router. It is a low-cost device which functions as an internet gateway for homes and small offices while aiming to be easy to configure and operate. In addition to providing a WiFi access point, the device serves as a 4-port wired router and implements a variety of common SOHO router capabilities such as port forwarding, quality-of-service, web-based administration, a DHCP server, a basic DMZ, and UPnP capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28875 | A security flaw involving hard-coded credentials in LevelOne WBR-6012's web services allows attackers to gain unauthorized access during the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28875</link><description>A security flaw involving hard-coded credentials in LevelOne WBR-6012's web services allows attackers to gain unauthorized access during the first 30 seconds post-boot. Other vulnerabilities can force a reboot, circumventing the initial time restriction for exploitation.The backdoor string can be found at address 0x80100910

    80100910 40 6d 21 74        ds         "@m!t2K1"
             32 4b 31 00
             
It is referenced by the function located at 0x800b78b0 and is used as shown in the pseudocode below:

    if ((SECOND_FROM_BOOT_TIME &lt; 300) &amp;&amp;
        (is_equal = strcmp(password,"@m!t2K1")) {
            return 1;}
            
Where 1 is the return value to admin-level access (0 being fail and 3 being user).</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31151 | A security flaw involving hard-coded credentials in LevelOne WBR-6012's web services allows attackers to gain unauthorized access during the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31151</link><description>A security flaw involving hard-coded credentials in LevelOne WBR-6012's web services allows attackers to gain unauthorized access during the first 30 seconds post-boot. Other vulnerabilities can force a reboot, circumventing the initial time restriction for exploitation.The password string can be found at addresses 0x 803cdd0f and 0x803da3e6:

    803cdd0f 41 72 69 65        ds         "AriesSerenaCairryNativitaMegan"
             73 53 65 72 
             65 6e 61 43
             ...

It is referenced by the function at 0x800b78b0 and simplified in the pseudocode below:

    if (is_equal = strcmp(password,"AriesSerenaCairryNativitaMegan"){
        ret = 3;}

Where 3 is the return value to user-level access (0 being fail and 1 being admin/backdoor).

While there's no legitimate functionality to change this password, once authenticated it is possible manually make a change by taking advantage of TALOS-2024-XXXXX using HTTP POST paramater "Pu" (new user password) in place of "Pa" (new admin password).</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31152 | The LevelOne WBR-6012 router with firmware R0.40e6 is vulnerable to improper resource allocation within its web application, where a series ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31152</link><description>The LevelOne WBR-6012 router with firmware R0.40e6 is vulnerable to improper resource allocation within its web application, where a series of crafted HTTP requests can cause a reboot. This could lead to network service interruptions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32946 | A vulnerability in the LevelOne WBR-6012 router's firmware version R0.40e6 allows sensitive information to be transmitted in cleartext via W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32946</link><description>A vulnerability in the LevelOne WBR-6012 router's firmware version R0.40e6 allows sensitive information to be transmitted in cleartext via Web and FTP services, exposing it to network sniffing attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33603 | The LevelOne WBR-6012 router has an information disclosure vulnerability in its web application, which allows unauthenticated users to acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33603</link><description>The LevelOne WBR-6012 router has an information disclosure vulnerability in its web application, which allows unauthenticated users to access a verbose system log page and obtain sensitive data, such as memory addresses and IP addresses for login attempts. This flaw could lead to session hijacking due to the device's reliance on IP address for authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33623 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Web Application functionality of LevelOne WBR-6012 R0.40e6. A specially crafted HTTP request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33623</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Web Application functionality of LevelOne WBR-6012 R0.40e6. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a reboot. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33626 | The LevelOne WBR-6012 router contains a vulnerability within its web application that allows unauthenticated disclosure of sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33626</link><description>The LevelOne WBR-6012 router contains a vulnerability within its web application that allows unauthenticated disclosure of sensitive information, such as the WiFi WPS PIN, through a hidden page accessible by an HTTP request. Disclosure of this information could enable attackers to connect to the device's WiFi network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33699 | The LevelOne WBR-6012 router's web application has a vulnerability in its firmware version R0.40e6, allowing attackers to change the adminis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33699</link><description>The LevelOne WBR-6012 router's web application has a vulnerability in its firmware version R0.40e6, allowing attackers to change the administrator password and gain higher privileges without the current password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33700 | The LevelOne WBR-6012 router firmware R0.40e6 suffers from an input validation vulnerability within its FTP functionality, enabling attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33700</link><description>The LevelOne WBR-6012 router firmware R0.40e6 suffers from an input validation vulnerability within its FTP functionality, enabling attackers to cause a denial of service through a series of malformed FTP commands. This can lead to device reboots and service disruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51257 | DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51257</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3 allows attackers to inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doCertificate function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51296 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the pi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51296</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the pingtrace function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51298 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51298</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doGRETunnel function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51299 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51299</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the dumpSyslog function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51300 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51300</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the get_rrd function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51301 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51301</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the packet_monitor function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51304 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ld...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51304</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the ldap_search_dn function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10525 | Eclipse Mosquito: Heap Buffer Overflow in my_subscribe_callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10525</link><description>In Eclipse Mosquitto, from version 1.3.2 through 2.0.18, if a malicious broker sends a crafted SUBACK packet with no reason codes, a client using libmosquitto may make out of bounds memory access when acting in its on_subscribe callback. This affects the mosquitto_sub and mosquitto_rr clients.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 11:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3935 | Eclipse Mosquito: Double free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3935</link><description>In Eclipse Mosquito, versions from 2.0.0 through 2.0.18, if a Mosquitto broker is configured to create an outgoing bridge connection, and that bridge connection has an incoming topic configured that makes use of topic remapping, then if the remote connection sends a crafted PUBLISH packet to the broker a double free will occur with a subsequent crash of the broker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 11:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8512 | W3SPEEDSTER &amp;lt;= 7.26 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8512</link><description>The W3SPEEDSTER plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 7.26 via the 'script' parameter of the hookBeforeStartOptimization() function. This is due to the plugin passing user supplied input to eval(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9388 | Black Widgets For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9388</link><description>The Black Widgets For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50504 | WordPress Bulk Change Role plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50504</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Matt Whiteman Bulk Change Role allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Bulk Change Role: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 08:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50506 | WordPress Marketing Automation by AZEXO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.27.80 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50506</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Azexo Marketing Automation by AZEXO allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Marketing Automation by AZEXO: from n/a through 1.27.80.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 08:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50508 | WordPress Woocommerce Product Design plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50508</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Chetan Khandla Woocommerce Product Design allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Woocommerce Product Design: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 08:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50510 | WordPress AR For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50510</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Web and Print Design AR For Woocommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects AR For Woocommerce: from n/a through 6.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 08:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50507 | WordPress DS.DownloadList plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50507</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Daniel Schmitzer DS.DownloadList allows Object Injection.This issue affects DS.DownloadList: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 07:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50511 | WordPress WP donimedia carousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50511</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in David DONISA WP donimedia carousel allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WP donimedia carousel: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 07:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50503 | WordPress User Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50503</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Deryck Oñate User Toolkit allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects User Toolkit: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 07:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50509 | WordPress Woocommerce Product Design plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50509</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Chetan Khandla Woocommerce Product Design allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Woocommerce Product Design: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 07:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50512 | WordPress Posti Shipping plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.2 - Full Path Disclosure (FPD)  vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50512</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Posti Posti Shipping allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Posti Shipping: from n/a through 3.10.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 07:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9632 | Xorg-x11-server: tigervnc: heap-based buffer overflow privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9632</link><description>A flaw was found in the X.org server. Due to improperly tracked allocation size in _XkbSetCompatMap, a local attacker may be able to trigger a buffer overflow condition via a specially crafted payload, leading to denial of service or local privilege escalation in distributions where the X.org server is run with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 07:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10108 | WPAdverts – Classifieds Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via adverts_add Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10108</link><description>The WPAdverts – Classifieds Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's adverts_add shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 06:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10223 | HT Team Member &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via htteamember Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10223</link><description>The WP Team – WordPress Team Member Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's htteamember shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 06:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8444 | Download Manager &amp;lt; 3.3.00 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8444</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.3.00 doesn't sanitize some of it's shortcode parameters, leading to cross site scripting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 06:49:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10399 | Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 5.0.13 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10399</link><description>The Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_search_users function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to obtain usernames and emails of site users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 05:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8871 | Pricing Tables WordPress Plugin – Easy Pricing Tables &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8871</link><description>The Pricing Tables WordPress Plugin – Easy Pricing Tables plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 05:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10507 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10507</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10509 | Codezips Online Institute Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10509</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Online Institute Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8627 | Ultimate TinyMCE &amp;lt;= 5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8627</link><description>The Ultimate TinyMCE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'field' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8792 | Subscribe to Comments &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8792</link><description>The Subscribe to Comments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9885 | Widget or Sidebar Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9885</link><description>The Widget or Sidebar Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sidebar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5816 | Code Explorer &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) External File Reading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5816</link><description>The Code Explorer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary external file reading in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5. This is due to the fact that the plugin does not restrict accessing files to those outside of the WordPress instance, though the intention of the plugin is to only access WordPress related files. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to read files outside of the WordPress instance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10506 | code-projects Blood Bank System B-.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10506</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/blood/update/B-.php. The manipulation of the argument Bloodname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9846 | Enable Shortcodes inside Widgets,Comments and Experts &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9846</link><description>The The Enable Shortcodes inside Widgets,Comments and Experts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9884 | T(-) Countdown &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9884</link><description>The T(-) Countdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tminus' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9886 | WP Baidu Map &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9886</link><description>The WP Baidu Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'baidu_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10505 | wuzhicms block.php edit code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wuzhicms 4.1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function add/edit of the file www/coreframe/app/content/admin/block.php. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Initially two separate issues were created by the researcher for the different function calls. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:07:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10502 | ESAFENET CDG FileDirectoryService.java getOneFileDirectory sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10502</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function getOneFileDirectory of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/fileManagement/FileDirectoryService.java. The manipulation of the argument directoryId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10503 | Klokan MapTiler tileserver-gl URL cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10503</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Klokan MapTiler tileserver-gl 2.3.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component URL Handler. The manipulation of the argument key leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 02:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10500 | ESAFENET CDG HookWhiteListService.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10500</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/HookWhiteListService.java. The manipulation of the argument policyId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10501 | ESAFENET CDG ExamCDGDocService.java findById sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10501</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This affects the function findById of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/document/ExamCDGDocService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51378 | getresetstatus in dns/views.py in CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 1c0c6cb allows remote attackers to bypass authentication and execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51378</link><description>getresetstatus in dns/views.py in CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 1c0c6cb allows remote attackers to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary commands via /ftp/getresetstatus by bypassing secMiddleware (which is only for a POST request) and using shell metacharacters in the statusfile property, as exploited in the wild in October 2024 by PSAUX. Versions through 2.3.6 and (unpatched) 2.3.7 are affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 22:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51567 | upgrademysqlstatus in databases/views.py in CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 5b08cd6 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51567</link><description>upgrademysqlstatus in databases/views.py in CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 5b08cd6 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary commands via /dataBases/upgrademysqlstatus by bypassing secMiddleware (which is only for a POST request) and using shell metacharacters in the statusfile property, as exploited in the wild in October 2024 by PSAUX. Versions through 2.3.6 and (unpatched) 2.3.7 are affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 22:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51568 | CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 2.3.5 allows Command Injection via completePath in the ProcessUtilities.outputExecutioner() sink. There ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51568</link><description>CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before 2.3.5 allows Command Injection via completePath in the ProcessUtilities.outputExecutioner() sink. There is /filemanager/upload (aka File Manager upload) unauthenticated remote code execution via shell metacharacters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 22:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50348 | InstantCMS has a Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50348</link><description>InstantCMS is a free and open source content management system. In photo upload function in the photo album page there is no input validation taking place. Due to this attackers are able to inject the XSS (Cross Site Scripting) payload and execute. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.16.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 22:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10487 | Out of bounds write in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 130.0.6723.92 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10487</link><description>Out of bounds write in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 130.0.6723.92 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10488 | Use after free in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 130.0.6723.92 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10488</link><description>Use after free in WebRTC in Google Chrome prior to 130.0.6723.92 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7992 | Autodesk AutoCAD DWG Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7992</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD and certain AutoCAD-based products, can force a Stack-based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7991 | Autodesk AutoCAD DWG Out-of-Bounds Write Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7991</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD and certain AutoCAD-based products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8896 | Autodesk AutoCAD DXF File Parsing Unitialized Variable Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8896</link><description>A maliciously crafted DXF file when parsed in acdb25.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force to access a variable prior to initialization. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9489 | Autodesk AutoCAD DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9489</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed in ACAD.exe through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9996 | Autodesk AutoCAD DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9996</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed in acdb25.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9997 | Autodesk AutoCAD DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9997</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed in acdb25.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50421 | WordPress PDF Invoices &amp;amp; Packing Slips for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50421</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Overnight WooCommerce PDF Invoices &amp; Packing Slips allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Invoices &amp; Packing Slips: from n/a through 3.8.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8592 | Autodesk AutoCAD CATPART File Parsing Memory Corruption Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8592</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in AcTranslators.exe through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48572 | A User enumeration vulnerability in AquilaCMS 1.409.20 and prior allows unauthenticated attackers to obtain email addresses via the "Add a u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48572</link><description>A User enumeration vulnerability in AquilaCMS 1.409.20 and prior allows unauthenticated attackers to obtain email addresses via the "Add a user" feature. The vulnerability occurs due to insufficiently validated user input being processed as a regular expression, which is then matched against email addresses to find duplicate entries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48573 | A NoSQL injection vulnerability in AquilaCMS 1.409.20 and prior allows unauthenticated attackers to reset user and administrator account pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48573</link><description>A NoSQL injection vulnerability in AquilaCMS 1.409.20 and prior allows unauthenticated attackers to reset user and administrator account passwords via the "Reset password" feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50422 | WordPress Breeze plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50422</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cloudways Breeze allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Breeze: from n/a through 2.1.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50423 | WordPress Templately plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50423</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Templately allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Templately: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10228 | Vagrant VMWare Utility installation files vulnerable to modification by unprivileged user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10228</link><description>The Vagrant VMWare Utility Windows installer targeted a custom location with a non-protected path that could be modified by an unprivileged user, introducing potential for unauthorized file system writes. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-10228, was fixed in Vagrant VMWare Utility 1.0.23</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50424 | WordPress Templately plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50424</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Templately allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Templately: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50425 | WordPress WP Booking System – Booking Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.19.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50425</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Veribo, Roland Murg WP Booking System.This issue affects WP Booking System: from n/a through 2.0.19.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44080 | In Jitsi Meet before 2.0.9779, the functionality to share an image using giphy was implemented in an insecure way, resulting in clients load...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44080</link><description>In Jitsi Meet before 2.0.9779, the functionality to share an image using giphy was implemented in an insecure way, resulting in clients loading GIFs from any arbitrary URL if a message from another participant contains a URL encoded in the expected format.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44081 | In Jitsi Meet before 2.0.9779, the functionality to share a video file was implemented in an insecure way, resulting in clients loading vide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44081</link><description>In Jitsi Meet before 2.0.9779, the functionality to share a video file was implemented in an insecure way, resulting in clients loading videos from an arbitrary URL if a message from another participant contains a URL encoded in the expected format.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48138 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the component /PluXml/core/admin/parametres_edittpl.php of PluXml v5.8.16 and lower allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48138</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the component /PluXml/core/admin/parametres_edittpl.php of PluXml v5.8.16 and lower allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted payload into a template.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50428 | WordPress Multi Step Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.21 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50428</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mondula GmbH Multi Step Form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Multi Step Form: from n/a through 1.7.21.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50454 | WordPress SEOPress plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.1 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50454</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in The SEO Guys at SEOPress SEOPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SEOPress: from n/a through 8.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8588 | Autodesk AutoCAD SLDPRT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8588</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed in odxsw_dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8589 | Autodesk AutoCAD SLDPRT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8589</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed in odxsw_dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8590 | Autodesk AutoCAD 3DM File Parsing Use-After-Free Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8590</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in atf_api.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8591 | Autodesk AutoCAD 3DM File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8591</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in AcTranslators.exe through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8593 | Autodesk AutoCAD CATPART File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8593</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in ASMKERN230A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8594 | Autodesk AutoCAD MODEL File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8594</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Heap-Based Overflow vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8595 | Autodesk AutoCAD MODEL File Parsing Use-After-Free Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8595</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8596 | Autodesk AutoCAD MODEL File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8596</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file when parsed in libodxdll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bound Write vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8597 | Autodesk AutoCAD STEP File Parsing Memory Corruption Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8597</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ASMDATAX230A.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8598 | Autodesk AutoCAD ACTranslators STEP File Parsing Memory Corruption Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8598</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ACTranslators.exe through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8599 | Autodesk AutoCAD ACTranslators STP File Parsing Memory Corruption Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8599</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file when parsed in ACTranslators.exe through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8600 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed in odxsw_dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability.  A mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8600</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed in odxsw_dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9826 | Autodesk AutoCAD ACTranslators 3DM File Parsing Use-After-Free Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9826</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file when parsed in atf_api.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9827 | Autodesk AutoCAD ACTranslators CATPART File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9827</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48206 | A Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in chainer v7.8.1.post1 leads to execution of arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48206</link><description>A Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in chainer v7.8.1.post1 leads to execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:10:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50455 | WordPress SEOPress plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50455</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in The SEO Guys at SEOPress SEOPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SEOPress: from n/a through 8.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50456 | WordPress SEOPress plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50456</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in The SEO Guys at SEOPress SEOPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SEOPress: from n/a through 8.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8587 | Autodesk AutoCAD SLDPRT File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8587</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file when parsed in odxsw_dll.dll through Autodesk AutoCAD can force a Heap Based Buffer Overflow vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48063 | In PyTorch &lt;=2.4.1, the RemoteModule has Deserialization RCE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48063</link><description>In PyTorch &lt;=2.4.1, the RemoteModule has Deserialization RCE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48461 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in TeslaLogger Admin Panel before v.1.59.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the New...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48461</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in TeslaLogger Admin Panel before v.1.59.6 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the New Journey field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 20:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48955 | In NetAdmin 4.0.30319, an attacker can steal a valid session cookie and inject it into another device, granting unauthorized access. This ty...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48955</link><description>In NetAdmin 4.0.30319, an attacker can steal a valid session cookie and inject it into another device, granting unauthorized access. This type of attack is commonly referred to as session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50459 | WordPress AidWP plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50459</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HM Plugin WordPress Stripe Donation and Payment Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WordPress Stripe Donation and Payment Plugin: from n/a through 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50466 | WordPress DarkMySite – Advanced Dark Mode Plugin for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50466</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DarkMySite DarkMySite – Advanced Dark Mode Plugin for WordPress darkmysite allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects DarkMySite – Advanced Dark Mode Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9988 | Crypto &amp;lt;= 2.15 - Authentication Bypass via register</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9988</link><description>The Crypto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.15. This is due to missing validation on the user being supplied in the 'crypto_connect_ajax_process::register' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9989 | Crypto &amp;lt;= 2.15 - Authentication Bypass via log_in</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9989</link><description>The Crypto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.15. This is due a to limited arbitrary method call to 'crypto_connect_ajax_process::log_in' function in the 'crypto_connect_ajax_process' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9990 | Crypto &amp;lt;= 2.15 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9990</link><description>The Crypto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.15. This is due to missing nonce validation in the 'crypto_connect_ajax_process::check' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25219 | Asio C++ Library before 1.13.0 lacks a fallback error code in the case of SSL_ERROR_SYSCALL with no associated error information from the SS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25219</link><description>Asio C++ Library before 1.13.0 lacks a fallback error code in the case of SSL_ERROR_SYSCALL with no associated error information from the SSL library being used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10491 | Preload arbitrary resources by injecting additional `Link` headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10491</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Express response.links function, allowing for arbitrary resource injection in the Link header when unsanitized data is used.

The issue arises from improper sanitization in `Link` header values, which can allow a combination of characters like `,`, `;`, and `` to preload malicious resources.

This vulnerability is especially relevant for dynamic parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8924 | Unauthenticated Blind SQL Injection in Core Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8924</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed a blind SQL injection vulnerability that was identified in the Now Platform. This vulnerability could enable an unauthenticated user to extract unauthorized information. ServiceNow deployed an update to hosted instances, and ServiceNow provided the update to our partners and self-hosted customers. Further, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8923 | Sandbox Escape in Now Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8923</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed an input validation vulnerability that was identified in the Now Platform. This vulnerability could enable an unauthenticated user to remotely execute code within the context of the Now Platform. ServiceNow deployed an update to hosted instances and ServiceNow provided the update to our partners and self-hosted customers. Further, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25566 | Open Redirect in PingAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25566</link><description>An Open-Redirect vulnerability exists in PingAM where well-crafted requests may cause improper validation of redirect URLs. This could allow an attacker to redirect end-users to malicious sites under their control, simplifying phishing attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7985 | FileOrganizer &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7985</link><description>The FileOrganizer – Manage WordPress and Website Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the "fileorganizer_ajax_handler" function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, and permissions granted by an administrator, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. NOTE: The FileOrganizer Pro plugin must be installed and active to allow Subscriber+ users to upload files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10452 | Organization admins can delete pending invites created in an organization they are not part of.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10452</link><description>Organization admins can delete pending invites created in an organization they are not part of.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49768 | Waitress has request processing race condition in HTTP pipelining with invalid first request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49768</link><description>Waitress is a Web Server Gateway Interface server for Python 2 and 3. A remote client may send a request that is exactly recv_bytes (defaults to 8192) long, followed by a secondary request using HTTP pipelining. When request lookahead is disabled (default) we won't read any more requests, and when the first request fails due to a parsing error, we simply close the connection. However when request lookahead is enabled, it is possible to process and receive the first request, start sending the error message back to the client while we read the next request and queue it. This will allow the secondary request to be serviced by the worker thread while the connection should be closed. Waitress 3.0.1 fixes the race condition. As a workaround, disable channel_request_lookahead, this is set to 0 by default disabling this feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50334 | Semicolon Path Injection on API /api;/config</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50334</link><description>Scoold is a Q&amp;amp;A and a knowledge sharing platform for teams. A semicolon path injection vulnerability was found on the /api;/config endpoint. By appending a semicolon in the URL, attackers can bypass authentication and gain unauthorised access to sensitive configuration data. Furthermore, PUT requests on the /api;/config endpoint while setting the Content-Type: application/hocon header allow unauthenticated attackers to file reading via HOCON file inclusion. This allows attackers to retrieve sensitive information such as configuration files from the server, which can be leveraged for further exploitation. The vulnerability has been fixed in Scoold 1.64.0. A workaround would be to disable the Scoold API with scoold.api_enabled = false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49769 | Waitress has a denial of service leading to high CPU usage/resource exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49769</link><description>Waitress is a Web Server Gateway Interface server for Python 2 and 3. When a remote client closes the connection before waitress has had the opportunity to call getpeername() waitress won't correctly clean up the connection leading to the main thread attempting to write to a socket that no longer exists, but not removing it from the list of sockets to attempt to process. This leads to a busy-loop calling the write function. A remote attacker could run waitress out of available sockets with very little resources required. Waitress 3.0.1 contains fixes that remove the race condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48921 | Kyverno&amp;#x27;s PolicyException objects can be created in any namespace by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48921</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. A kyverno ClusterPolicy, ie. "disallow-privileged-containers," can be overridden by the creation of a PolicyException in a random namespace. By design, PolicyExceptions are consumed from any namespace. Administrators may not recognize that this allows users with privileges to non-kyverno namespaces to create exceptions. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10226 | Arconix Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.1.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via box Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10226</link><description>The Arconix Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'box' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9505 | Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via Button Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9505</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51075 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/user-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51075</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/user-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the searchdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51076 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/booking-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51076</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /odms/admin/booking-search.php in PHPGurukul Online DJ Booking Management System 1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchdata" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47640 | WordPress  WP ERP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in weDevs WP ERP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP ERP: from n/a through 1.13.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49632 | WordPress CWD 3D Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coral Web Design CWD 3D Image Gallery allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CWD 3D Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49634 | WordPress BP Member Type Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.01 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rimon Habib BP Member Type Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BP Member Type Manager: from n/a through 1.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49635 | WordPress Banner Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49635</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Manzurul Haque Banner Slider allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Banner Slider: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49636 | WordPress Agile Video Player Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prashant Mavinkurve Agile Video Player Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Agile Video Player Lite: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51180 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/index.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0, which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51180</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/index.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchifsccode" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51181 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/admin/profile.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51181</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /ifscfinder/admin/profile.php in PHPGurukul IFSC Code Finder Project v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via " searchifsccode" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6673 | CSRF Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6673</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the `install_comfyui` endpoint of the `lollms_comfyui.py` file in the parisneo/lollms-webui repository, versions v9.9 to the latest. The endpoint uses the GET method without requiring a client ID, allowing an attacker to trick a victim into installing ComfyUI. If the victim's device does not have sufficient capacity, this can result in a crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7042 | Prompt Injection in langchain-ai/langchainjs Leading to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7042</link><description>A vulnerability in the GraphCypherQAChain class of langchain-ai/langchainjs versions 0.2.5 and all versions with this class allows for prompt injection, leading to SQL injection. This vulnerability permits unauthorized data manipulation, data exfiltration, denial of service (DoS) by deleting all data, breaches in multi-tenant security environments, and data integrity issues. Attackers can create, update, or delete nodes and relationships without proper authorization, extract sensitive data, disrupt services, access data across different tenants, and compromise the integrity of the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7472 | Email Injection Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7472</link><description>lunary-ai/lunary v1.2.26 contains an email injection vulnerability in the Send email verification API (/v1/users/send-verification) and Sign up API (/auth/signup). An unauthenticated attacker can inject data into outgoing emails by bypassing the extractFirstName function using a different whitespace character (e.g., \xa0). This vulnerability can be exploited to conduct phishing attacks, damage the application's brand, cause legal and compliance issues, and result in financial impact due to unauthorized email usage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7774 | Path Traversal in langchain-ai/langchainjs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7774</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the `getFullPath` method of langchain-ai/langchainjs version 0.2.5. This vulnerability allows attackers to save files anywhere in the filesystem, overwrite existing text files, read `.txt` files, and delete files. The vulnerability is exploited through the `setFileContent`, `getParsedFile`, and `mdelete` methods, which do not properly sanitize user input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7783 | Improper Storage of Sensitive Information in Bearer Token in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7783</link><description>mintplex-labs/anything-llm version latest contains a vulnerability where sensitive information, specifically a password, is improperly stored within a JWT (JSON Web Token) used as a bearer token in single user mode. When decoded, the JWT reveals the password in plaintext. This improper storage of sensitive information poses significant security risks, as an attacker who gains access to the JWT can easily decode it and retrieve the password. The issue is fixed in version 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8309 | SQL Injection in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8309</link><description>A vulnerability in the GraphCypherQAChain class of langchain-ai/langchain version 0.2.5 allows for SQL injection through prompt injection. This vulnerability can lead to unauthorized data manipulation, data exfiltration, denial of service (DoS) by deleting all data, breaches in multi-tenant security environments, and data integrity issues. Attackers can create, update, or delete nodes and relationships without proper authorization, extract sensitive data, disrupt services, access data across different tenants, and compromise the integrity of the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41153 | Command injection vulnerability in the Edge Computing UI for the
TRO600 series radios that allows for the execution of arbitrary system comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41153</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in the Edge Computing UI for the
TRO600 series radios that allows for the execution of arbitrary system commands. If exploited, an attacker with write access to the
web UI can execute commands on the device with root privileges,
far more extensive than what the write privilege intends.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41156 | Profile files from TRO600 series radios are extracted in plain-text
and encrypted file formats. Profile files provide potential attackers
va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41156</link><description>Profile files from TRO600 series radios are extracted in plain-text
and encrypted file formats. Profile files provide potential attackers
valuable configuration information about the Tropos network. Profiles
can only be exported by authenticated users with write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49637 | WordPress Bet WC 2018 Russia plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49637</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Foxskav Bet WC 2018 Russia allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Bet WC 2018 Russia: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49638 | WordPress Risk Warning Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ali Azlan Risk Warning Bar allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Risk Warning Bar: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49639 | WordPress Monitor.chat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49639</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Edward Stoever Monitor.Chat allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Monitor.Chat: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49640 | WordPress ACL Floating Cart for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AmaderCode Lab ACL Floating Cart for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ACL Floating Cart for WooCommerce: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5823 | File Overwrite Vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5823</link><description>A file overwrite vulnerability exists in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt versions &lt;= 20240410. This vulnerability allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access to overwrite critical configuration files within the system. Exploiting this vulnerability can lead to unauthorized changes in system behavior or security settings. Additionally, tampering with these configuration files can result in a denial of service (DoS) condition, disrupting normal system operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5982 | Path Traversal in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5982</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the latest version of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt. The vulnerability arises from unsanitized input handling in multiple features, including user upload, directory creation, and template loading. Specifically, the load_chat_history function in modules/models/base_model.py allows arbitrary file uploads, potentially leading to remote code execution (RCE). The get_history_names function in utils.py permits arbitrary directory creation. Additionally, the load_template function in utils.py can be exploited to leak the first column of CSV files. These issues stem from improper sanitization of user inputs concatenated with directory paths using os.path.join.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6581 | Remote Code Execution due to Stored XSS in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6581</link><description>A vulnerability in the discussion image upload function of the Lollms application, version v9.9, allows for the uploading of SVG files. Due to incomplete filtering in the sanitize_svg function, this can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities, which in turn pose a risk of remote code execution. The sanitize_svg function only removes script elements and 'on*' event attributes, but does not account for other potential vectors for XSS within SVG files. This vulnerability can be exploited when authorized users access a malicious URL containing the crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6674 | Data Leak through CORS Misconfiguration in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6674</link><description>A CORS misconfiguration in parisneo/lollms-webui prior to version 10 allows attackers to steal sensitive information such as logs, browser sessions, and settings containing private API keys from other services. This vulnerability can also enable attackers to perform actions on behalf of a user, such as deleting a project or sending a message. The issue impacts the confidentiality and integrity of the information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6868 | Arbitrary File Write in mudler/LocalAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6868</link><description>mudler/LocalAI version 2.17.1 allows for arbitrary file write due to improper handling of automatic archive extraction. When model configurations specify additional files as archives (e.g., .tar), these archives are automatically extracted after downloading. This behavior can be exploited to perform a 'tarslip' attack, allowing files to be written to arbitrary locations on the server, bypassing checks that normally restrict files to the models directory. This vulnerability can lead to remote code execution (RCE) by overwriting backend assets used by the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7010 | Timing Attack in mudler/localai</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7010</link><description>mudler/localai version 2.17.1 is vulnerable to a Timing Attack. This type of side-channel attack allows an attacker to compromise the cryptosystem by analyzing the time taken to execute cryptographic algorithms. Specifically, in the context of password handling, an attacker can determine valid login credentials based on the server's response time, potentially leading to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7473 | IDOR Vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7473</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability exists in the 'Evaluations' function of the 'umgws datasets' section in lunary-ai/lunary versions 1.3.2. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to update other users' prompts by manipulating the 'id' parameter in the request. The issue is fixed in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7474 | IDOR in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7474</link><description>In version 1.3.2 of lunary-ai/lunary, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists. A user can view or delete external users by manipulating the 'id' parameter in the request URL. The application does not perform adequate checks on the 'id' parameter, allowing unauthorized access to external user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7475 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7475</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability in lunary-ai/lunary version 1.3.2 allows an attacker to update the SAML configuration without authorization. This vulnerability can lead to manipulation of authentication processes, fraudulent login requests, and theft of user information. Appropriate access controls should be implemented to ensure that the SAML configuration can only be updated by authorized users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7807 | Denial of Service (DOS) in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7807</link><description>A vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240628 allows for a Denial of Service (DOS) attack. When uploading a file, if an attacker appends a large number of characters to the end of a multipart boundary, the system will continuously process each character, rendering ChuanhuChatGPT inaccessible. This uncontrolled resource consumption can lead to prolonged unavailability of the service, disrupting operations and causing potential data inaccessibility and loss of productivity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7962 | Arbitrary File Read via Insufficient Validation in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7962</link><description>An arbitrary file read vulnerability exists in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240628 due to insufficient validation when loading prompt template files. An attacker can read any file that matches specific criteria using an absolute path. The file must not have a .json extension and, except for the first line, every other line must contain commas. This vulnerability allows reading parts of format-compliant files, including code and log files, which may contain highly sensitive information such as account credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8143 | Unauthorized Access to User Chat History in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8143</link><description>In the latest version (20240628) of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt, an issue exists in the /file endpoint that allows authenticated users to access the chat history of other users. When a user logs in, a directory is created in the history folder with the user's name. By manipulating the /file endpoint, an authenticated user can enumerate and access files in other users' directories, leading to unauthorized access to private chat histories. This vulnerability can be exploited to read any user's private chat history.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10458 | A permission leak could have occurred from a trusted site to an untrusted site via `embed` or `object` elements. This vulnerability affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10458</link><description>A permission leak could have occurred from a trusted site to an untrusted site via `embed` or `object` elements. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.17, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10459 | An attacker could have caused a use-after-free when accessibility was enabled, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10459</link><description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free when accessibility was enabled, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.17, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10460 | The origin of an external protocol handler prompt could have been obscured using a data: URL within an `iframe`. This vulnerability affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10460</link><description>The origin of an external protocol handler prompt could have been obscured using a data: URL within an `iframe`. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10461 | In multipart/x-mixed-replace responses, `Content-Disposition: attachment` in the response header was not respected and did not force a downl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10461</link><description>In multipart/x-mixed-replace responses, `Content-Disposition: attachment` in the response header was not respected and did not force a download, which could allow XSS attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10462 | Truncation of a long URL could have allowed origin spoofing in a permission prompt. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10462</link><description>Truncation of a long URL could have allowed origin spoofing in a permission prompt. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10463 | Video frames could have been leaked between origins in some situations. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10463</link><description>Video frames could have been leaked between origins in some situations. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.17, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10464 | Repeated writes to history interface attributes could have been used to cause a Denial of Service condition in the browser. This was address...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10464</link><description>Repeated writes to history interface attributes could have been used to cause a Denial of Service condition in the browser. This was addressed by introducing rate-limiting to this API. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10465 | A clipboard "paste" button could persist across tabs which allowed a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10465</link><description>A clipboard "paste" button could persist across tabs which allowed a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10466 | By sending a specially crafted push message, a remote server could have hung the parent process, causing the browser to become unresponsive....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10466</link><description>By sending a specially crafted push message, a remote server could have hung the parent process, causing the browser to become unresponsive. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10467 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 131, Firefox ESR 128.3, and Thunderbird 128.3. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10467</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 131, Firefox ESR 128.3, and Thunderbird 128.3. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.4, Thunderbird &lt; 128.4, and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10468 | Potential race conditions in IndexedDB could have caused memory corruption, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10468</link><description>Potential race conditions in IndexedDB could have caused memory corruption, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 132 and Thunderbird &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10474 | Focus was incorrectly allowing internal links to utilize the app scheme used for deeplinking, which could result in links potentially circum...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10474</link><description>Focus was incorrectly allowing internal links to utilize the app scheme used for deeplinking, which could result in links potentially circumventing some URL safety checks This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 132.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49641 | WordPress Tida URL Screenshot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tidaweb Tida URL Screenshot allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tida URL Screenshot: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49643 | WordPress Whitelist plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Abdullah Irfan Whitelist allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Whitelist: from n/a through 3.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49645 | WordPress Affiliate Platform plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ilias Gomatos Affiliate Platform allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Affiliate Platform: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20195 | LUNAD3v AreaLoad request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LUNAD3v AreaLoad up to 1a1103182ed63a06dde63d1712f3262eda19c3ec. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file request.php. The manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 264813c546dba03989ac0fc365f2022bf65e3be2. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49646 | WordPress Code Generate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ioannup Code Generate allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Code Generate: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49647 | WordPress Simple Custom Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Carl Alberto Simple Custom Admin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Custom Admin: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49648 | WordPress SVG Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rafasashi SVG Captcha allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SVG Captcha: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49650 | WordPress BuddyPress Greeting Message plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49650</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in xarbo BuddyPress Greeting Message allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BuddyPress Greeting Message: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49651 | WordPress WooCommerce Maintenance Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Royal WooCommerce Maintenance Mode allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Maintenance Mode: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49654 | WordPress Extra Privacy for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49654</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marian Heddesheimer Extra Privacy for Elementor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Extra Privacy for Elementor: from n/a through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49656 | WordPress DocumentPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Abdullah Irfan DocumentPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DocumentPress: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49659 | WordPress Coub plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49659</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rami Yushuvaev Coub allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Coub: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49660 | WordPress Campus Explorer Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49660</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Campus Explorer Campus Explorer Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Campus Explorer Widget: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49661 | WordPress leenk.me plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49661</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lew Ayotte leenk.Me allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects leenk.Me: from n/a through 2.16.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49662 | WordPress Simple Load More plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webgensis Simple Load More allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Load More: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49663 | WordPress uCAT – Next Story plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elena Zhyvohliad uCAT – Next Story allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects uCAT – Next Story: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10181 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via newsletters_video Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10181</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's newsletters_video shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49664 | WordPress chatplusjp plugin &amp;lt;= 1.02 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects chatplusjp: from n/a through 1.02.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49665 | WordPress  Web Bricks Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Web Bricks Web Bricks Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Web Bricks Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49667 | WordPress Local Business Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NervyThemes Local Business Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Local Business Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10184 | SW Kick Integration - Blocks and Shortcodes for Embedding Kick Streams &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sw-kick-embed Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10184</link><description>The StreamWeasels Kick Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sw-kick-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10185 | StreamWeasels YouTube Integration &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sw-youtube-embed Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10185</link><description>The StreamWeasels YouTube Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sw-youtube-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10233 | SMSAlert - WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sa_subscribe Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10233</link><description>The SMS Alert Order Notifications – WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sa_subscribe shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10266 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.60 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Box Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10266</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Video Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.60 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10360 | Move Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10360</link><description>The Move Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5 via the render function in includes/widgets/accordion/widget.php, includes/widgets/remote-template/widget.php, and other widget.php files. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49670 | WordPress Client Power Tools Portal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49670</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sam Glover Client Power Tools Portal allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Client Power Tools Portal: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49672 | WordPress Google Docs RSVP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49672</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Gifford Cheung, Brian Watanabe, Chongsun Ahn Google Docs RSVP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Google Docs RSVP: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49673 | WordPress LaTeX2HTML plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Van Abel LaTeX2HTML allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LaTeX2HTML: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49678 | WordPress js paper theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jinwen js allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects js paper: from n/a through 2.5.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49679 | WordPress WPKoi Templates for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPKoi WPKoi Templates for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPKoi Templates for Elementor: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49692 | WordPress AffiliateX plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49692</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AffiliateX allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AffiliateX: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50407 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50407</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50409 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50409</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50410 | WordPress Namaste! LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50410</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Namaste! LMS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50550 | WordPress LiteSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50550</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in LiteSpeed Technologies LiteSpeed Cache allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects LiteSpeed Cache: from n/a through 6.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10227 | affiliate-toolkit &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via atkp_product Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10227</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's atkp_product shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10436 | WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10436</link><description>The WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1 via the get_condition_value function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10437 | WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Message Activation/Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10437</link><description>The WPC Smart Messages for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Smar Message activation/deactivation due to a missing capability check on the ajax_enable function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate or deactivate smart messages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9376 | Kata Plus – Addons for Elementor – Widgets, Extensions and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9376</link><description>The Kata Plus – Addons for Elementor – Widgets, Extensions and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22066 | There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in ZTE ZXR10 ZSR V2 intelligent multi service router . An authenticated attacker could use the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22066</link><description>There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in ZTE ZXR10 ZSR V2 intelligent multi service router . An authenticated attacker could use the vulnerability to obtain sensitive information about the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45477 | Apache NiFi: Improper Neutralization of Input in Parameter Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45477</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.27.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field for Parameters in a Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.28.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49642 | WordPress Todo Custom Field plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rafasashi Todo Custom Field allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Todo Custom Field: from n/a through 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50411 | WordPress WP Abstracts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50411</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kevon Adonis WP Abstracts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Abstracts: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50412 | WordPress Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50412</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jules Colle Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 2.4.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50413 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.27.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50413</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in codection Import and export users and customers allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.27.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50414 | WordPress Button contact VR plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50414</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VirusTran Button contact VR allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Button contact VR: from n/a through 4.7.9.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50415 | WordPress Ads.txt &amp;amp; App-ads.txt Manager for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50415</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pagup Ads.Txt &amp; App-ads.Txt Manager for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ads.Txt &amp; App-ads.Txt Manager for WordPress: from n/a through 1.1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50418 | WordPress Time Slot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50418</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Time Slot Booking Time Slot allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Time Slot: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50426 | WordPress Survey Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50426</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Survey Maker team Survey Maker allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Survey Maker: from n/a through 5.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50475 | WordPress Signup Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50475</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Scott Gamon Signup Page allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Signup Page: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50476 | WordPress GRÜN spendino Spendenformular plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50476</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GRÜN Software Group GmbH GRÜN spendino Spendenformular allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GRÜN spendino Spendenformular: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50481 | WordPress Bstone Demo Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50481</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Stack Themes Bstone Demo Importer allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Bstone Demo Importer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10048 | Post Status Notifier Lite and Premium &amp;lt;= 1.11.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10048</link><description>The Post Status Notifier Lite and Premium plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50420 | WordPress aDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50420</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in adirectory aDirectory allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects aDirectory: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50427 | WordPress SurveyJS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.136 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50427</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Devsoft Baltic OÜ SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder.This issue affects SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder: from n/a through 1.9.136.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50473 | WordPress Ajar in5 Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50473</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Ajar Productions Ajar in5 Embed allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Ajar in5 Embed: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50485 | WordPress Exam Matrix plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50485</link><description>: Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Udit Rawat Exam Matrix allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Exam Matrix: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50490 | WordPress PegaPoll plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50490</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Szabolcs Szecsenyi PegaPoll allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects PegaPoll: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9438 | SEUR Oficial &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9438</link><description>The SEUR Oficial plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'change_service' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46872 | Client-Side Path Traversal Leading to CSRF in Playbooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46872</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.10.x &lt;= 9.10.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.1, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to sanitize user inputs in the frontend that are used for redirection which allows for a one-click client-side path traversal that is leading to CSRF in Playbooks</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47401 | DoS via Amplified GraphQL Response in Playbooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47401</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.10.x &lt;= 9.10.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.1 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to prevent detailed error messages from being displayed in Playbooks which allows an attacker to generate a large response and cause an amplified GraphQL response which in turn could cause the application to crash by sending a specially crafted request to Playbooks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10241 | Private channel names leaked with Ctrl+K when ElasticSearch is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10241</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to properly filter the channel data when ElasticSearch is enabled which allows a user to get private channel names by using cmd+K/ctrl+K.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50052 | Arbitrary post deletion via Playbooks /ignore-thread endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50052</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.10.x &lt;= 9.10.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.1, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.9 fail to check that the origin of the message in an integration action matches with the original post metadata which allows an authenticated user to delete an arbitrary post.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50480 | WordPress Marketing Automation by AZEXO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.27.80 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50480</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in azexo Marketing Automation by AZEXO allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Marketing Automation by AZEXO: from n/a through 1.27.80.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50482 | WordPress Woocommerce Product Design plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50482</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Chetan Khandla Woocommerce Product Design allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Woocommerce Product Design: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50484 | WordPress Multi Purpose Mail Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50484</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in mahlamusa Multi Purpose Mail Form allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Multi Purpose Mail Form: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50493 | WordPress Automatic Translation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50493</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in masterhomepage Automatic Translation allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Automatic Translation: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50494 | WordPress Sudan Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50494</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Amin Omer Sudan Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Sudan Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 08:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10312 | Exclusive Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10312</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 via the render function in elements/tabs/tabs.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 07:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10000 | Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.13.3 - Authenticated (Student+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Ask a Question Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10000</link><description>The Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the question's content parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with student-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 05:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10008 | Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.13.3 - Authenticated (Student+) Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10008</link><description>The Masteriyo LMS – eLearning and Online Course Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user profile modification due to missing authorization checks on the /wp-json/masteriyo/v1/users/$id REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with student-level access and above, to modify the roles of arbitrary users. As a result, attackers can escalate their privileges to the Administrator and demote existing administrators to students.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 05:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22065 | ZTE MF258 Pro product has a OS Command injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22065</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in ZTE MF258 Pro product. Due to insufficient validation of Ping Diagnosis interface parameter, an authenticated attacker could use the vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10479 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Theme Management Module admin#themes cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10479</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms up to 2.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin#themes of the component Theme Management Module. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45656 | IBM Flexible Service Processor hard coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45656</link><description>IBM Flexible Service Processor (FSP) FW860.00 through FW860.B3, FW950.00 through FW950.C0, FW1030.00 through FW1030.61, FW1050.00 through FW1050.21, and FW1060.00 through FW1060.10 has static credentials which may allow network users to gain service privileges to the FSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50068 | mm/damon/tests/sysfs-kunit.h: fix memory leak in damon_sysfs_test_add_targets()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50068</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/damon/tests/sysfs-kunit.h: fix memory leak in damon_sysfs_test_add_targets()

The sysfs_target-&gt;regions allocated in damon_sysfs_regions_alloc() is not
freed in damon_sysfs_test_add_targets(), which cause the following memory
leak, free it to fix it.

	unreferenced object 0xffffff80c2a8db80 (size 96):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 187, jiffies 4294894363
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
	    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
	  backtrace (crc 0):
	    [&lt;0000000001e3714d&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;000000008e6835c1&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000001286d9f8&gt;] damon_sysfs_test_add_targets+0x1cc/0x738
	    [&lt;0000000032ef8f77&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;00000000f3edea23&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000adf936cf&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;0000000041bb1628&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50069 | pinctrl: apple: check devm_kasprintf() returned value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50069</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: apple: check devm_kasprintf() returned value

devm_kasprintf() can return a NULL pointer on failure but this returned
value is not checked. Fix this lack and check the returned value.

Found by code review.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50070 | pinctrl: stm32: check devm_kasprintf() returned value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50070</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: stm32: check devm_kasprintf() returned value

devm_kasprintf() can return a NULL pointer on failure but this returned
value is not checked. Fix this lack and check the returned value.

Found by code review.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50071 | pinctrl: nuvoton: fix a double free in ma35_pinctrl_dt_node_to_map_func()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50071</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pinctrl: nuvoton: fix a double free in ma35_pinctrl_dt_node_to_map_func()

'new_map' is allocated using devm_* which takes care of freeing the
allocated data on device removal, call to

	.dt_free_map = pinconf_generic_dt_free_map

double frees the map as pinconf_generic_dt_free_map() calls
pinctrl_utils_free_map().

Fix this by using kcalloc() instead of auto-managed devm_kcalloc().</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50072 | x86/bugs: Use code segment selector for VERW operand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50072</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/bugs: Use code segment selector for VERW operand

Robert Gill reported below #GP in 32-bit mode when dosemu software was
executing vm86() system call:

  general protection fault: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
  CPU: 4 PID: 4610 Comm: dosemu.bin Not tainted 6.6.21-gentoo-x86 #1
  Hardware name: Dell Inc. PowerEdge 1950/0H723K, BIOS 2.7.0 10/30/2010
  EIP: restore_all_switch_stack+0xbe/0xcf
  EAX: 00000000 EBX: 00000000 ECX: 00000000 EDX: 00000000
  ESI: 00000000 EDI: 00000000 EBP: 00000000 ESP: ff8affdc
  DS: 0000 ES: 0000 FS: 0000 GS: 0033 SS: 0068 EFLAGS: 00010046
  CR0: 80050033 CR2: 00c2101c CR3: 04b6d000 CR4: 000406d0
  Call Trace:
   show_regs+0x70/0x78
   die_addr+0x29/0x70
   exc_general_protection+0x13c/0x348
   exc_bounds+0x98/0x98
   handle_exception+0x14d/0x14d
   exc_bounds+0x98/0x98
   restore_all_switch_stack+0xbe/0xcf
   exc_bounds+0x98/0x98
   restore_all_switch_stack+0xbe/0xcf

This only happens in 32-bit mode when VERW based mitigations like MDS/RFDS
are enabled. This is because segment registers with an arbitrary user value
can result in #GP when executing VERW. Intel SDM vol. 2C documents the
following behavior for VERW instruction:

  #GP(0) - If a memory operand effective address is outside the CS, DS, ES,
	   FS, or GS segment limit.

CLEAR_CPU_BUFFERS macro executes VERW instruction before returning to user
space. Use %cs selector to reference VERW operand. This ensures VERW will
not #GP for an arbitrary user %ds.

[ mingo: Fixed the SOB chain. ]</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50073 | tty: n_gsm: Fix use-after-free in gsm_cleanup_mux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50073</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tty: n_gsm: Fix use-after-free in gsm_cleanup_mux

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in gsm_cleanup_mux+0x77b/0x7b0
drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3160 [n_gsm]
Read of size 8 at addr ffff88815fe99c00 by task poc/3379
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 3379 Comm: poc Not tainted 6.11.0+ #56
Hardware name: VMware, Inc. VMware Virtual Platform/440BX
Desktop Reference Platform, BIOS 6.00 11/12/2020
Call Trace:
 
 gsm_cleanup_mux+0x77b/0x7b0 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3160 [n_gsm]
 __pfx_gsm_cleanup_mux+0x10/0x10 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3124 [n_gsm]
 __pfx_sched_clock_cpu+0x10/0x10 kernel/sched/clock.c:389
 update_load_avg+0x1c1/0x27b0 kernel/sched/fair.c:4500
 __pfx_min_vruntime_cb_rotate+0x10/0x10 kernel/sched/fair.c:846
 __rb_insert_augmented+0x492/0xbf0 lib/rbtree.c:161
 gsmld_ioctl+0x395/0x1450 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3408 [n_gsm]
 _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x92/0xf0 arch/x86/include/asm/atomic.h:107
 __pfx_gsmld_ioctl+0x10/0x10 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3822 [n_gsm]
 ktime_get+0x5e/0x140 kernel/time/timekeeping.c:195
 ldsem_down_read+0x94/0x4e0 arch/x86/include/asm/atomic64_64.h:79
 __pfx_ldsem_down_read+0x10/0x10 drivers/tty/tty_ldsem.c:338
 __pfx_do_vfs_ioctl+0x10/0x10 fs/ioctl.c:805
 tty_ioctl+0x643/0x1100 drivers/tty/tty_io.c:2818

Allocated by task 65:
 gsm_data_alloc.constprop.0+0x27/0x190 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:926 [n_gsm]
 gsm_send+0x2c/0x580 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:819 [n_gsm]
 gsm1_receive+0x547/0xad0 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3038 [n_gsm]
 gsmld_receive_buf+0x176/0x280 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3609 [n_gsm]
 tty_ldisc_receive_buf+0x101/0x1e0 drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:391
 tty_port_default_receive_buf+0x61/0xa0 drivers/tty/tty_port.c:39
 flush_to_ldisc+0x1b0/0x750 drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:445
 process_scheduled_works+0x2b0/0x10d0 kernel/workqueue.c:3229
 worker_thread+0x3dc/0x950 kernel/workqueue.c:3391
 kthread+0x2a3/0x370 kernel/kthread.c:389
 ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:257

Freed by task 3367:
 kfree+0x126/0x420 mm/slub.c:4580
 gsm_cleanup_mux+0x36c/0x7b0 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3160 [n_gsm]
 gsmld_ioctl+0x395/0x1450 drivers/tty/n_gsm.c:3408 [n_gsm]
 tty_ioctl+0x643/0x1100 drivers/tty/tty_io.c:2818

[Analysis]
gsm_msg on the tx_ctrl_list or tx_data_list of gsm_mux
can be freed by multi threads through ioctl,which leads
to the occurrence of uaf. Protect it by gsm tx lock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50074 | parport: Proper fix for array out-of-bounds access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50074</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

parport: Proper fix for array out-of-bounds access

The recent fix for array out-of-bounds accesses replaced sprintf()
calls blindly with snprintf().  However, since snprintf() returns the
would-be-printed size, not the actually output size, the length
calculation can still go over the given limit.

Use scnprintf() instead of snprintf(), which returns the actually
output letters, for addressing the potential out-of-bounds access
properly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50075 | xhci: tegra: fix checked USB2 port number</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50075</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xhci: tegra: fix checked USB2 port number

If USB virtualizatoin is enabled, USB2 ports are shared between all
Virtual Functions. The USB2 port number owned by an USB2 root hub in
a Virtual Function may be less than total USB2 phy number supported
by the Tegra XUSB controller.

Using total USB2 phy number as port number to check all PORTSC values
would cause invalid memory access.

[  116.923438] Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address 006c622f7665642f
...
[  117.213640] Call trace:
[  117.216783]  tegra_xusb_enter_elpg+0x23c/0x658
[  117.222021]  tegra_xusb_runtime_suspend+0x40/0x68
[  117.227260]  pm_generic_runtime_suspend+0x30/0x50
[  117.232847]  __rpm_callback+0x84/0x3c0
[  117.237038]  rpm_suspend+0x2dc/0x740
[  117.241229] pm_runtime_work+0xa0/0xb8
[  117.245769]  process_scheduled_works+0x24c/0x478
[  117.251007]  worker_thread+0x23c/0x328
[  117.255547]  kthread+0x104/0x1b0
[  117.259389]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[  117.263582] Code: 54000222 f9461ae8 f8747908 b4ffff48 (f9400100)</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50076 | vt: prevent kernel-infoleak in con_font_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50076</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vt: prevent kernel-infoleak in con_font_get()

font.data may not initialize all memory spaces depending on the implementation
of vc-&gt;vc_sw-&gt;con_font_get. This may cause info-leak, so to prevent this, it
is safest to modify it to initialize the allocated memory space to 0, and it
generally does not affect the overall performance of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50077 | Bluetooth: ISO: Fix multiple init when debugfs is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50077</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: ISO: Fix multiple init when debugfs is disabled

If bt_debugfs is not created successfully, which happens if either
CONFIG_DEBUG_FS or CONFIG_DEBUG_FS_ALLOW_ALL is unset, then iso_init()
returns early and does not set iso_inited to true. This means that a
subsequent call to iso_init() will result in duplicate calls to
proto_register(), bt_sock_register(), etc.

With CONFIG_LIST_HARDENED and CONFIG_BUG_ON_DATA_CORRUPTION enabled, the
duplicate call to proto_register() triggers this BUG():

  list_add double add: new=ffffffffc0b280d0, prev=ffffffffbab56250,
    next=ffffffffc0b280d0.
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:35!
  Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 2 PID: 887 Comm: bluetoothd Not tainted 6.10.11-1-ao-desktop #1
  RIP: 0010:__list_add_valid_or_report+0x9a/0xa0
  ...
    __list_add_valid_or_report+0x9a/0xa0
    proto_register+0x2b5/0x340
    iso_init+0x23/0x150 [bluetooth]
    set_iso_socket_func+0x68/0x1b0 [bluetooth]
    kmem_cache_free+0x308/0x330
    hci_sock_sendmsg+0x990/0x9e0 [bluetooth]
    __sock_sendmsg+0x7b/0x80
    sock_write_iter+0x9a/0x110
    do_iter_readv_writev+0x11d/0x220
    vfs_writev+0x180/0x3e0
    do_writev+0xca/0x100
  ...

This change removes the early return. The check for iso_debugfs being
NULL was unnecessary, it is always NULL when iso_inited is false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50078 | Bluetooth: Call iso_exit() on module unload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50078</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Call iso_exit() on module unload

If iso_init() has been called, iso_exit() must be called on module
unload. Without that, the struct proto that iso_init() registered with
proto_register() becomes invalid, which could cause unpredictable
problems later. In my case, with CONFIG_LIST_HARDENED and
CONFIG_BUG_ON_DATA_CORRUPTION enabled, loading the module again usually
triggers this BUG():

  list_add corruption. next-&gt;prev should be prev (ffffffffb5355fd0),
    but was 0000000000000068. (next=ffffffffc0a010d0).
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:29!
  Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 1 PID: 4159 Comm: modprobe Not tainted 6.10.11-4+bt2-ao-desktop #1
  RIP: 0010:__list_add_valid_or_report+0x61/0xa0
  ...
    __list_add_valid_or_report+0x61/0xa0
    proto_register+0x299/0x320
    hci_sock_init+0x16/0xc0 [bluetooth]
    bt_init+0x68/0xd0 [bluetooth]
    __pfx_bt_init+0x10/0x10 [bluetooth]
    do_one_initcall+0x80/0x2f0
    do_init_module+0x8b/0x230
    __do_sys_init_module+0x15f/0x190
    do_syscall_64+0x68/0x110
  ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50079 | io_uring/sqpoll: ensure task state is TASK_RUNNING when running task_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50079</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/sqpoll: ensure task state is TASK_RUNNING when running task_work

When the sqpoll is exiting and cancels pending work items, it may need
to run task_work. If this happens from within io_uring_cancel_generic(),
then it may be under waiting for the io_uring_task waitqueue. This
results in the below splat from the scheduler, as the ring mutex may be
attempted grabbed while in a TASK_INTERRUPTIBLE state.

Ensure that the task state is set appropriately for that, just like what
is done for the other cases in io_run_task_work().

do not call blocking ops when !TASK_RUNNING; state=1 set at [&lt;0000000029387fd2&gt;] prepare_to_wait+0x88/0x2fc
WARNING: CPU: 6 PID: 59939 at kernel/sched/core.c:8561 __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
Modules linked in:
CPU: 6 UID: 0 PID: 59939 Comm: iou-sqp-59938 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc3-00113-g8d020023b155 #7456
Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
pstate: 61400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO +DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
lr : __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
sp : ffff80008c5e7830
x29: ffff80008c5e7830 x28: ffff0000d93088c0 x27: ffff60001c2d7230
x26: dfff800000000000 x25: ffff0000e16b9180 x24: ffff80008c5e7a50
x23: 1ffff000118bcf4a x22: ffff0000e16b9180 x21: ffff0000e16b9180
x20: 000000000000011b x19: ffff80008310fac0 x18: 1ffff000118bcd90
x17: 30303c5b20746120 x16: 74657320313d6574 x15: 0720072007200720
x14: 0720072007200720 x13: 0720072007200720 x12: ffff600036c64f0b
x11: 1fffe00036c64f0a x10: ffff600036c64f0a x9 : dfff800000000000
x8 : 00009fffc939b0f6 x7 : ffff0001b6327853 x6 : 0000000000000001
x5 : ffff0001b6327850 x4 : ffff600036c64f0b x3 : ffff8000803c35bc
x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffff0000e16b9180
Call trace:
 __might_sleep+0xf4/0x140
 mutex_lock+0x84/0x124
 io_handle_tw_list+0xf4/0x260
 tctx_task_work_run+0x94/0x340
 io_run_task_work+0x1ec/0x3c0
 io_uring_cancel_generic+0x364/0x524
 io_sq_thread+0x820/0x124c
 ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50080 | ublk: don&amp;#x27;t allow user copy for unprivileged device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50080</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ublk: don't allow user copy for unprivileged device

UBLK_F_USER_COPY requires userspace to call write() on ublk char
device for filling request buffer, and unprivileged device can't
be trusted.

So don't allow user copy for unprivileged device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50081 | blk-mq: setup queue -&amp;gt;tag_set before initializing hctx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50081</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-mq: setup queue -&gt;tag_set before initializing hctx

Commit 7b815817aa58 ("blk-mq: add helper for checking if one CPU is mapped to specified hctx")
needs to check queue mapping via tag set in hctx's cpuhp handler.

However, q-&gt;tag_set may not be setup yet when the cpuhp handler is
enabled, then kernel oops is triggered.

Fix the issue by setup queue tag_set before initializing hctx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50082 | blk-rq-qos: fix crash on rq_qos_wait vs. rq_qos_wake_function race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50082</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-rq-qos: fix crash on rq_qos_wait vs. rq_qos_wake_function race

We're seeing crashes from rq_qos_wake_function that look like this:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffafe180a40084
  #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
  PGD 100000067 P4D 100000067 PUD 10027c067 PMD 10115d067 PTE 0
  Oops: Oops: 0002 [#1] PREEMPT SMP PTI
  CPU: 17 UID: 0 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/17 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc3-00013-geca631b8fe80 #11
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.0-0-gd239552ce722-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:_raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x1d/0x40
  Code: 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 90 f3 0f 1e fa 0f 1f 44 00 00 41 54 9c 41 5c fa 65 ff 05 62 97 30 4c 31 c0 ba 01 00 00 00  0f b1 17 75 0a 4c 89 e0 41 5c c3 cc cc cc cc 89 c6 e8 2c 0b 00
  RSP: 0018:ffffafe180580ca0 EFLAGS: 00010046
  RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffafe180a3f7a8 RCX: 0000000000000011
  RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: 0000000000000003 RDI: ffffafe180a40084
  RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 00000000001e7240 R09: 0000000000000011
  R10: 0000000000000028 R11: 0000000000000888 R12: 0000000000000002
  R13: ffffafe180a40084 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000003
  FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff9aaf1f280000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: ffffafe180a40084 CR3: 000000010e428002 CR4: 0000000000770ef0
  DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
  DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
  PKRU: 55555554
  Call Trace:
   
   try_to_wake_up+0x5a/0x6a0
   rq_qos_wake_function+0x71/0x80
   __wake_up_common+0x75/0xa0
   __wake_up+0x36/0x60
   scale_up.part.0+0x50/0x110
   wb_timer_fn+0x227/0x450
   ...

So rq_qos_wake_function() calls wake_up_process(data-&gt;task), which calls
try_to_wake_up(), which faults in raw_spin_lock_irqsave(&amp;amp;p-&gt;pi_lock).

p comes from data-&gt;task, and data comes from the waitqueue entry, which
is stored on the waiter's stack in rq_qos_wait(). Analyzing the core
dump with drgn, I found that the waiter had already woken up and moved
on to a completely unrelated code path, clobbering what was previously
data-&gt;task. Meanwhile, the waker was passing the clobbered garbage in
data-&gt;task to wake_up_process(), leading to the crash.

What's happening is that in between rq_qos_wake_function() deleting the
waitqueue entry and calling wake_up_process(), rq_qos_wait() is finding
that it already got a token and returning. The race looks like this:

rq_qos_wait()                           rq_qos_wake_function()
==============================================================
prepare_to_wait_exclusive()
                                        data-&gt;got_token = true;
                                        list_del_init(&amp;amp;curr-&gt;entry);
if (data.got_token)
        break;
finish_wait(&amp;amp;rqw-&gt;wait, &amp;amp;data.wq);
  ^- returns immediately because
     list_empty_careful(&amp;amp;wq_entry-&gt;entry)
     is true
... return, go do something else ...
                                        wake_up_process(data-&gt;task)
                                          (NO LONGER VALID!)-^

Normally, finish_wait() is supposed to synchronize against the waker.
But, as noted above, it is returning immediately because the waitqueue
entry has already been removed from the waitqueue.

The bug is that rq_qos_wake_function() is accessing the waitqueue entry
AFTER deleting it. Note that autoremove_wake_function() wakes the waiter
and THEN deletes the waitqueue entry, which is the proper order.

Fix it by swapping the order. We also need to use
list_del_init_careful() to match the list_empty_careful() in
finish_wait().</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50083 | tcp: fix mptcp DSS corruption due to large pmtu xmit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50083</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: fix mptcp DSS corruption due to large pmtu xmit

Syzkaller was able to trigger a DSS corruption:

  TCP: request_sock_subflow_v4: Possible SYN flooding on port [::]:20002. Sending cookies.
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 5227 at net/mptcp/protocol.c:695 __mptcp_move_skbs_from_subflow+0x20a9/0x21f0 net/mptcp/protocol.c:695
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 5227 Comm: syz-executor350 Not tainted 6.11.0-syzkaller-08829-gaf9c191ac2a0 #0
  Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 08/06/2024
  RIP: 0010:__mptcp_move_skbs_from_subflow+0x20a9/0x21f0 net/mptcp/protocol.c:695
  Code: 0f b6 dc 31 ff 89 de e8 b5 dd ea f5 89 d8 48 81 c4 50 01 00 00 5b 41 5c 41 5d 41 5e 41 5f 5d c3 cc cc cc cc e8 98 da ea f5 90 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 90 e9 47 ff ff ff e8 8a da ea f5 90 0f 0b 90 e9 99 e0 ff ff
  RSP: 0018:ffffc90000006db8 EFLAGS: 00010246
  RAX: ffffffff8ba9df18 RBX: 00000000000055f0 RCX: ffff888030023c00
  RDX: 0000000000000100 RSI: 00000000000081e5 RDI: 00000000000055f0
  RBP: 1ffff110062bf1ae R08: ffffffff8ba9cf12 R09: 1ffff110062bf1b8
  R10: dffffc0000000000 R11: ffffed10062bf1b9 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: dffffc0000000000 R14: 00000000700cec61 R15: 00000000000081e5
  FS:  000055556679c380(0000) GS:ffff8880b8600000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: 0000000020287000 CR3: 0000000077892000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
  DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
  DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
  Call Trace:
   
   move_skbs_to_msk net/mptcp/protocol.c:811 [inline]
   mptcp_data_ready+0x29c/0xa90 net/mptcp/protocol.c:854
   subflow_data_ready+0x34a/0x920 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1490
   tcp_data_queue+0x20fd/0x76c0 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:5283
   tcp_rcv_established+0xfba/0x2020 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:6237
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x96d/0xc70 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:1915
   tcp_v4_rcv+0x2dc0/0x37f0 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:2350
   ip_protocol_deliver_rcu+0x22e/0x440 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:205
   ip_local_deliver_finish+0x341/0x5f0 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:233
   NF_HOOK+0x3a4/0x450 include/linux/netfilter.h:314
   NF_HOOK+0x3a4/0x450 include/linux/netfilter.h:314
   __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5662 [inline]
   __netif_receive_skb+0x2bf/0x650 net/core/dev.c:5775
   process_backlog+0x662/0x15b0 net/core/dev.c:6107
   __napi_poll+0xcb/0x490 net/core/dev.c:6771
   napi_poll net/core/dev.c:6840 [inline]
   net_rx_action+0x89b/0x1240 net/core/dev.c:6962
   handle_softirqs+0x2c5/0x980 kernel/softirq.c:554
   do_softirq+0x11b/0x1e0 kernel/softirq.c:455
   
   
   __local_bh_enable_ip+0x1bb/0x200 kernel/softirq.c:382
   local_bh_enable include/linux/bottom_half.h:33 [inline]
   rcu_read_unlock_bh include/linux/rcupdate.h:919 [inline]
   __dev_queue_xmit+0x1764/0x3e80 net/core/dev.c:4451
   dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3094 [inline]
   neigh_hh_output include/net/neighbour.h:526 [inline]
   neigh_output include/net/neighbour.h:540 [inline]
   ip_finish_output2+0xd41/0x1390 net/ipv4/ip_output.c:236
   ip_local_out net/ipv4/ip_output.c:130 [inline]
   __ip_queue_xmit+0x118c/0x1b80 net/ipv4/ip_output.c:536
   __tcp_transmit_skb+0x2544/0x3b30 net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:1466
   tcp_transmit_skb net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:1484 [inline]
   tcp_mtu_probe net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:2547 [inline]
   tcp_write_xmit+0x641d/0x6bf0 net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:2752
   __tcp_push_pending_frames+0x9b/0x360 net/ipv4/tcp_output.c:3015
   tcp_push_pending_frames include/net/tcp.h:2107 [inline]
   tcp_data_snd_check net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:5714 [inline]
   tcp_rcv_established+0x1026/0x2020 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:6239
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x96d/0xc70 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:1915
   sk_backlog_rcv include/net/sock.h:1113 [inline]
   __release_sock+0x214/0x350 net/core/sock.c:3072
   release_sock+0x61/0x1f0 net/core/sock.c:3626
   mptcp_push_
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50084 | net: microchip: vcap api: Fix memory leaks in vcap_api_encode_rule_test()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50084</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: microchip: vcap api: Fix memory leaks in vcap_api_encode_rule_test()

Commit a3c1e45156ad ("net: microchip: vcap: Fix use-after-free error in
kunit test") fixed the use-after-free error, but introduced below
memory leaks by removing necessary vcap_free_rule(), add it to fix it.

	unreferenced object 0xffffff80ca58b700 (size 192):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898264
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    00 12 7a 00 05 00 00 00 0a 00 00 00 64 00 00 00  ..z.........d...
	    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 04 0b cc 80 ff ff ff  ................
	  backtrace (crc 9c09c3fe):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;0000000040a01b8d&gt;] vcap_alloc_rule+0x3cc/0x9c4
	    [&lt;000000003fe86110&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x1ac/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0400 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898265
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    80 04 0b cc 80 ff ff ff 18 b7 58 ca 80 ff ff ff  ..........X.....
	    39 00 00 00 02 00 00 00 06 05 04 03 02 01 ff ff  9...............
	  backtrace (crc daf014e9):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000000ff63fd4&gt;] vcap_rule_add_key+0x2cc/0x528
	    [&lt;00000000dfdb1e81&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x224/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0700 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898265
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    80 07 0b cc 80 ff ff ff 28 b7 58 ca 80 ff ff ff  ........(.X.....
	    3c 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 01 2f 03 b3 ec ff ff ff  &lt;......../......
	  backtrace (crc 8d877792):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000006eadfab7&gt;] vcap_rule_add_action+0x2d0/0x52c
	    [&lt;00000000323475d1&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x4d4/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0900 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898266
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    80 09 0b cc 80 ff ff ff 80 06 0b cc 80 ff ff ff  ................
	    7d 00 00 00 01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 ff 00 00 00  }...............
	  backtrace (crc 34181e56):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000000ff63fd4&gt;] vcap_rule_add_key+0x2cc/0x528
	    [&lt;00000000991e3564&gt;] vcap_val_rule+0xcf0/0x13e8
	    [&lt;00000000fc9868e5&gt;] vcap_api_encode_rule_test+0x678/0x16b0
	    [&lt;00000000b3595fc4&gt;] kunit_try_run_case+0x13c/0x3ac
	    [&lt;0000000010f5d2bf&gt;] kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x80/0xec
	    [&lt;00000000c5d82c9a&gt;] kthread+0x2e8/0x374
	    [&lt;00000000f4287308&gt;] ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
	unreferenced object 0xffffff80cc0b0980 (size 64):
	  comm "kunit_try_catch", pid 1215, jiffies 4294898266
	  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
	    18 b7 58 ca 80 ff ff ff 00 09 0b cc 80 ff ff ff  ..X.............
	    67 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 01 01 74 88 c0 ff ff ff  g.........t.....
	  backtrace (crc 275fd9be):
	    [&lt;0000000052a0be73&gt;] kmemleak_alloc+0x34/0x40
	    [&lt;0000000043605459&gt;] __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x26c/0x2f4
	    [&lt;000000000ff63fd4&gt;] vcap_rule_add_key+0x2cc/0x528
	    [&lt;000000001396a1a2&gt;] test_add_de
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50085 | mptcp: pm: fix UaF read in mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50085</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: fix UaF read in mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow

Syzkaller reported this splat:

  ==================================================================
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow+0xb44/0xcc0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:881
  Read of size 4 at addr ffff8880569ac858 by task syz.1.2799/14662

  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 14662 Comm: syz.1.2799 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc2-syzkaller-00307-g36c254515dc6 #0
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2~bpo12+1 04/01/2014
  Call Trace:
   
   __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
   dump_stack_lvl+0x116/0x1f0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
   print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:377 [inline]
   print_report+0xc3/0x620 mm/kasan/report.c:488
   kasan_report+0xd9/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:601
   mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow+0xb44/0xcc0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:881
   mptcp_pm_nl_rm_subflow_received net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:914 [inline]
   mptcp_nl_remove_id_zero_address+0x305/0x4a0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:1572
   mptcp_pm_nl_del_addr_doit+0x5c9/0x770 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:1603
   genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x202/0x2f0 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1115
   genl_family_rcv_msg net/netlink/genetlink.c:1195 [inline]
   genl_rcv_msg+0x565/0x800 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1210
   netlink_rcv_skb+0x165/0x410 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2551
   genl_rcv+0x28/0x40 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1219
   netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1331 [inline]
   netlink_unicast+0x53c/0x7f0 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1357
   netlink_sendmsg+0x8b8/0xd70 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1901
   sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:729 [inline]
   __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:744 [inline]
   ____sys_sendmsg+0x9ae/0xb40 net/socket.c:2607
   ___sys_sendmsg+0x135/0x1e0 net/socket.c:2661
   __sys_sendmsg+0x117/0x1f0 net/socket.c:2690
   do_syscall_32_irqs_on arch/x86/entry/common.c:165 [inline]
   __do_fast_syscall_32+0x73/0x120 arch/x86/entry/common.c:386
   do_fast_syscall_32+0x32/0x80 arch/x86/entry/common.c:411
   entry_SYSENTER_compat_after_hwframe+0x84/0x8e
  RIP: 0023:0xf7fe4579
  Code: b8 01 10 06 03 74 b4 01 10 07 03 74 b0 01 10 08 03 74 d8 01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 51 52 55 89 e5 0f 34 cd 80 &lt;5d&gt; 5a 59 c3 90 90 90 90 8d b4 26 00 00 00 00 8d b4 26 00 00 00 00
  RSP: 002b:00000000f574556c EFLAGS: 00000296 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000172
  RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 000000000000000b RCX: 0000000020000140
  RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: 0000000000000000
  RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000296 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 0000000000000000
   

  Allocated by task 5387:
   kasan_save_stack+0x33/0x60 mm/kasan/common.c:47
   kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30 mm/kasan/common.c:68
   poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:377 [inline]
   __kasan_kmalloc+0xaa/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:394
   kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:878 [inline]
   kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1014 [inline]
   subflow_create_ctx+0x87/0x2a0 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1803
   subflow_ulp_init+0xc3/0x4d0 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1956
   __tcp_set_ulp net/ipv4/tcp_ulp.c:146 [inline]
   tcp_set_ulp+0x326/0x7f0 net/ipv4/tcp_ulp.c:167
   mptcp_subflow_create_socket+0x4ae/0x10a0 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1764
   __mptcp_subflow_connect+0x3cc/0x1490 net/mptcp/subflow.c:1592
   mptcp_pm_create_subflow_or_signal_addr+0xbda/0x23a0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:642
   mptcp_pm_nl_fully_established net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:650 [inline]
   mptcp_pm_nl_work+0x3a1/0x4f0 net/mptcp/pm_netlink.c:943
   mptcp_worker+0x15a/0x1240 net/mptcp/protocol.c:2777
   process_one_work+0x958/0x1b30 kernel/workqueue.c:3229
   process_scheduled_works kernel/workqueue.c:3310 [inline]
   worker_thread+0x6c8/0xf00 kernel/workqueue.c:3391
   kthread+0x2c1/0x3a0 kernel/kthread.c:389
   ret_from_fork+0x45/0x80 arch/x86/ke
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50086 | ksmbd: fix user-after-free from session log off</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50086</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix user-after-free from session log off

There is racy issue between smb2 session log off and smb2 session setup.
It will cause user-after-free from session log off.
This add session_lock when setting SMB2_SESSION_EXPIRED and referece
count to session struct not to free session while it is being used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50087 | btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free on read_alloc_one_name() error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50087</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free on read_alloc_one_name() error

The function read_alloc_one_name() does not initialize the name field of
the passed fscrypt_str struct if kmalloc fails to allocate the
corresponding buffer.  Thus, it is not guaranteed that
fscrypt_str.name is initialized when freeing it.

This is a follow-up to the linked patch that fixes the remaining
instances of the bug introduced by commit e43eec81c516 ("btrfs: use
struct qstr instead of name and namelen pairs").</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50088 | btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free in add_inode_ref()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50088</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix uninitialized pointer free in add_inode_ref()

The add_inode_ref() function does not initialize the "name" struct when
it is declared.  If any of the following calls to "read_one_inode()
returns NULL,

	dir = read_one_inode(root, parent_objectid);
	if (!dir) {
		ret = -ENOENT;
		goto out;
	}

	inode = read_one_inode(root, inode_objectid);
	if (!inode) {
		ret = -EIO;
		goto out;
	}

then "name.name" would be freed on "out" before being initialized.

out:
	...
	kfree(name.name);

This issue was reported by Coverity with CID 1526744.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10477 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Permission Management Page admin#permissions cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10477</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms up to 2.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin#permissions of the component Permission Management Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10478 | LinZhaoguan pb-cms Edit Article edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10478</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in LinZhaoguan pb-cms up to 2.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin#article/edit?id=2 of the component Edit Article Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>