<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:47:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-32658 | FreeRDP ExtractRunLengthRegular* out of bound read </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32658</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32482 | Tillitis TKey Signer possible RAM disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32482</link><description>The Tillitis TKey signer device application is an ed25519 signing tool. A vulnerability has been found that makes it possible to disclose portions of the TKey’s data in RAM over the USB interface. To exploit the vulnerability an attacker needs to use a custom client application and to touch the TKey. No secret is disclosed. All client applications integrating tkey-device-signer should upgrade to version 1.0.0 to receive a fix. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31208 | Synapse&amp;#x27;s V2 state resolution weakness allows DoS from remote room members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31208</link><description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver. A remote Matrix user with malicious intent, sharing a room with Synapse instances before 1.105.1, can dispatch specially crafted events to exploit a weakness in the V2 state resolution algorithm. This can induce high CPU consumption and accumulate excessive data in the database of such instances, resulting in a denial of service. Servers in private federations, or those that do not federate, are not affected. Server administrators should upgrade to 1.105.1 or later. Some workarounds are available. One can ban the malicious users or ACL block servers from the rooms and/or leave the room and purge the room using the admin API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21972 | An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21972</link><description>An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed shader to potentially achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21979 | An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21979</link><description>An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed shader to potentially achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32258 | The network server of fceux 2.7.0 has a path traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to overwrite any files on the server without authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32258</link><description>The network server of fceux 2.7.0 has a path traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to overwrite any files on the server without authentication by fake ROM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31804 | An unquoted service path vulnerability in Terratec DMX_6Fire USB v.1.23.0.02 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Program....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31804</link><description>An unquoted service path vulnerability in Terratec DMX_6Fire USB v.1.23.0.02 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Program.exe component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33211 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PPPOEPassword parameter in ip/g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33211</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PPPOEPassword parameter in ip/goform/QuickIndex.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33212 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the funcpara1 parameter in ip/gofor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33212</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the funcpara1 parameter in ip/goform/setcfm.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33213 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/go...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33213</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/goform/RouteStatic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33214 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter in ip/goform/R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33214</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter in ip/goform/RouteStatic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33215 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/go...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33215</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/goform/addressNat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33217 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter in ip/goform/add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33217</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter in ip/goform/addressNat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28130 | An incorrect type conversion vulnerability exists in the DVPSSoftcopyVOI_PList::createFromImage functionality of OFFIS DCMTK 3.6.8. A specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28130</link><description>An incorrect type conversion vulnerability exists in the DVPSSoftcopyVOI_PList::createFromImage functionality of OFFIS DCMTK 3.6.8. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32679 | WordPress Shared Files plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32679</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shared Files PRO Shared Files.This issue affects Shared Files: from n/a through 1.7.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2477 | The wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Alternative Text' field of an uploaded image in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2477</link><description>The wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Alternative Text' field of an uploaded image in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28627 | An issue in Flipsnack v.18/03/2024 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reader.gz.js file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28627</link><description>An issue in Flipsnack v.18/03/2024 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reader.gz.js file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26922 | drm/amdgpu: validate the parameters of bo mapping operations more clearly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26922</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: validate the parameters of bo mapping operations more clearly

Verify the parameters of
amdgpu_vm_bo_(map/replace_map/clearing_mappings) in one common place.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30800 | PX4 Autopilot v.1.14 allows an attacker to fly the drone into no-fly zones by breaching the geofence using flaws in the function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30800</link><description>PX4 Autopilot v.1.14 allows an attacker to fly the drone into no-fly zones by breaching the geofence using flaws in the function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47731 | IBM QRadar Suite Software cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47731</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.19.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  272203.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3911 | Welotec: Clickjacking Vulnerability in WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3911</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can deceive users into performing unintended actions due to improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3491 | The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "How To" and "F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3491</link><description>The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "How To" and "FAQ" Blocks in all versions up to, and including, 1.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3665 | The Rank Math SEO with AI SEO Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's HowTo and FAQ widgets...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3665</link><description>The Rank Math SEO with AI SEO Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's HowTo and FAQ widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.216 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3732 | The GeoDirectory – WordPress Business Directory Plugin, or Classified Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3732</link><description>The GeoDirectory – WordPress Business Directory Plugin, or Classified Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gd_single_tabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.48 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3185 | Rapid7 Insight Agent Sensitive Key Exposed To Local Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3185</link><description>A key used in logging.json does not follow the least privilege principle by default and is exposed to local users in the Rapid7 Platform.  This allows an attacker with local access to a machine with the logging.json file to use that key to authenticate to the platform with high privileges.  This was fixed in the Rapid7 platform starting 3 April 2024 via the introduction of a restricted role and the removal of automatic API key generation on installation of an agent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0900 | The Elespare – Build Your Blog, News &amp; Magazine Websites with Expert-Designed Template Kits. One Click Import: No Coding Skills Required! pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0900</link><description>The Elespare – Build Your Blog, News &amp; Magazine Websites with Expert-Designed Template Kits. One Click Import: No Coding Skills Required! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post creation due to a missing capability check on the elespare_create_post() function hooked via AJAX in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3664 | The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3664</link><description>The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the set_thumbnail and delete_thumbnail functions in all versions up to, and including, 13.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to delete thumbnails and add thumbnails to posts they did not author.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48184 | QuickJS before 7414e5f has a quickjs.h JS_FreeValueRT use-after-free because of incorrect garbage collection of async functions with closure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48184</link><description>QuickJS before 7414e5f has a quickjs.h JS_FreeValueRT use-after-free because of incorrect garbage collection of async functions with closures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48183 | QuickJS before c4cdd61 has a build_for_in_iterator NULL pointer dereference because of an erroneous lexical scope of "this" with eval.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48183</link><description>QuickJS before c4cdd61 has a build_for_in_iterator NULL pointer dereference because of an erroneous lexical scope of "this" with eval.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4031 | MEVO WEBCAM APP Windows Unquoted Service Path Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4031</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in Logitech MEVO WEBCAM APP on Windows allows Local Execution of Code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6833 | Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6833</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Administrator allows local users to gain sensitive information.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Administrator: before 11.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2493 | Session Hijacking Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2493</link><description>Session Hijacking vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.1-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2798 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget container...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2798</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget containers in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.971 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2799 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Grid &amp; Advanced Tex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2799</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Grid &amp; Advanced Text widget HTML tags in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.96 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3889 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Advanced Accordi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3889</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Advanced Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.971 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'accordion_title_tag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21511 | Versions of the package mysql2 before 3.9.7 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection due to improper sanitization of the timezone paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21511</link><description>Versions of the package mysql2 before 3.9.7 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection due to improper sanitization of the timezone parameter in the readCodeFor function by calling a native MySQL Server date/time function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28890 | Forminator prior to 1.29.0 contains an unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28890</link><description>Forminator prior to 1.29.0 contains an unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain sensitive information by accessing files on the server, alter the site that uses the plugin, and cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31077 | Forminator prior to 1.29.3 contains a SQL injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote authenticated attacker with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31077</link><description>Forminator prior to 1.29.3 contains a SQL injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege may obtain and alter any information in the database and cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31857 | Forminator prior to 1.15.4 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31857</link><description>Forminator prior to 1.15.4 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain user information etc. and alter the page contents on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1241 | Watchdog Antivirus v1.6.415 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1241</link><description>Watchdog Antivirus v1.6.415 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002014 IOCTL code of the wsdk-driver.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2760 | Bkav Home v7816, build 2403161130 - Kernel Memory Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2760</link><description>Bkav Home v7816, build 2403161130 is vulnerable to a Memory Information Leak vulnerability by triggering the 0x222240 IOCTL code of the BkavSDFlt.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3293 | The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the rtmedia_gallery shortcod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3293</link><description>The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the rtmedia_gallery shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.18 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 02:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3177 | Bypassing mountable secrets policy imposed by the ServiceAccount admission plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3177</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where users may be able to launch containers that bypass the mountable secrets policy enforced by the ServiceAccount admission plugin when using containers, init containers, and ephemeral containers with the envFrom field populated. The policy ensures pods running with a service account may only reference secrets specified in the service account’s secrets field. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if the ServiceAccount admission plugin and the kubernetes.io/enforce-mountable-secrets annotation are used together with containers, init containers, and ephemeral containers with the envFrom field populated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 23:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32657 | Hydra has persistent XSS vulnerability serving HTML build outputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32657</link><description>Hydra is a Continuous Integration service for Nix based projects. Attackers can execute arbitrary code in the browser context of Hydra and execute authenticated HTTP requests. The abused feature allows Nix builds to specify files that Hydra serves to clients. One use of this functionality is serving NixOS `.iso` files. The issue is only with html files served by Hydra. The issue has been patched on https://hydra.nixos.org around 2024-04-21 14:30 UTC. The nixpkgs package were fixed in unstable and 23.11. Users with custom Hydra packages can apply the fix commit to their local installations. The vulnerability is only triggered when opening HTML build artifacts, so not opening them until the vulnerability is fixed works around the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32480 | LibreNMS&amp;#x27;s Time-Based Blind SQL injection leads to database extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32480</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. Versions prior to 24.4.0 are vulnerable to SQL injection. The `order` parameter is obtained from `$request`. After performing a string check, the value is directly incorporated into an SQL statement and concatenated, resulting in a SQL injection vulnerability. An attacker may extract a whole database this way. Version 24.4.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32653 | Insufficient input filtering of &amp;quot;package name&amp;quot; allows command execution in the device with shell privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32653</link><description>jadx is a  Dex to Java decompiler. Prior to version 1.5.0,  the package name is not filtered before concatenation. This can be exploited to inject arbitrary code into the package name. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute commands with shell privileges. Version 1.5.0 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32656 | Ant Media Server vulnerable to local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32656</link><description>Ant Media Server is live streaming engine software. A local privilege escalation vulnerability in present in versions 2.6.0 through 2.8.2 allows any unprivileged operating system user account to escalate privileges to the root user account on the system. This vulnerability arises from Ant Media Server running with Java Management Extensions (JMX) enabled and authentication disabled on localhost on port 5599/TCP. This vulnerability is nearly identical to the local privilege escalation vulnerability CVE-2023-26269 identified in Apache James. Any unprivileged operating system user can connect to the JMX service running on port 5599/TCP on localhost and leverage the MLet Bean within JMX to load a remote MBean from an attacker-controlled server. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code within the Java process run by Ant Media Server and execute code within the context of the `antmedia` service account on the system. Version 2.9.0 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, one may remove certain parameters from the `antmedia.service` file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32479 | LibreNMS&amp;#x27;s Improper Sanitization on Service template name leads to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32479</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. Prior to version 24.4.0, there is improper sanitization on the `Service` template name, which can lead to stored Cross-site Scripting. Version 24.4.0 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32461 | LibreNMS vulnerable to time-based SQL injection that leads to database extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32461</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. A SQL injection vulnerability in POST /search/search=packages in LibreNMS prior to version 24.4.0 allows a user with global read privileges to execute SQL commands via the package parameter. With this vulnerability, an attacker can exploit a SQL injection time based vulnerability to extract all data from the database, such as administrator credentials. Version 24.4.0 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32460 | FreeRDP Out-Of-Bounds Read in interleaved_decompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32460</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based based clients using `/bpp:32` legacy `GDI` drawing path with a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, use modern drawing paths (e.g. `/rfx` or `/gfx` options). The workaround requires server side support.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31036 | A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the read_byte function in NanoMQ v.0.21.7 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via transmis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31036</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the read_byte function in NanoMQ v.0.21.7 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via transmission of crafted hexstreams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32459 | FreeRDP Out-Of-Bounds Read in ncrush_decompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32459</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients and servers that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29368 | An issue discovered in moziloCMS v2.0 allows attackers to bypass file upload restrictions and run arbitrary code by changing the file extens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29368</link><description>An issue discovered in moziloCMS v2.0 allows attackers to bypass file upload restrictions and run arbitrary code by changing the file extension after upload via crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27574 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Trainme Academy version Ichin v.1.3.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27574</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Trainme Academy version Ichin v.1.3.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the informacion, idcurso, and tit parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32394 | An issue in ruijie.com/cn RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S_07150910 and RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32394</link><description>An issue in ruijie.com/cn RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S_07150910 and RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S_07150910 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32458 | FreeRDP Out-Of-Bounds Read in planar_skip_plane_rle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32458</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, use `/gfx` or `/rfx` modes (on by default, require server side support).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32040 | FreeRDP vulnerable to integer underflow in nsc_rle_decode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32040</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 and have connections to servers using the `NSC` codec are vulnerable to integer underflow. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, do not use the NSC codec (e.g. use `-nsc`).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32041 | FreeRDP OutOfBound Read in zgfx_decompress_segment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32041</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, deactivate `/gfx` (on by default, set `/bpp` or `/rfx` options instead.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32039 | FreeRDP Integer overflow &amp;amp; OutOfBound Write in clear_decompress_residual_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32039</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients using a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to integer overflow and out-of-bounds write. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, do not use `/gfx` options (e.g. deactivate with `/bpp:32` or `/rfx` as it is on by default).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4040 | VFS Sandbox Escape in CrushFTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4040</link><description>VFS Sandbox Escape in CrushFTP in all versions before 10.7.1 and 11.1.0 on all platforms allows remote attackers with low privileges to read files from the filesystem outside of VFS Sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32238 | H3C ER8300G2-X is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The password for the router's management system can be accessed via the management...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32238</link><description>H3C ER8300G2-X is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The password for the router's management system can be accessed via the management system page login interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32399 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in RaidenMAILD Mail Server v.4.9.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32399</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in RaidenMAILD Mail Server v.4.9.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /webeditor/ component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32405 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted payload t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32405</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted payload to the Answer field of InlineMultiQuestion parameter on Exam function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32407 | An issue in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Page Sandbox feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32407</link><description>An issue in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Page Sandbox feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29376 | Sylius 1.12.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "Province" field in Address Book.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29376</link><description>Sylius 1.12.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "Province" field in Address Book.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31545 | Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/?page=user/manage_user&amp;id=6.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31545</link><description>Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/?page=user/manage_user&amp;amp;id=6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46897 | An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5. The CapsuleIFWUSmm driver does not check the return value from a me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46897</link><description>An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5. The CapsuleIFWUSmm driver does not check the return value from a method or function. This can prevent it from detecting unexpected states and conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31666 | An issue in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the edit_addon_post.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31666</link><description>An issue in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the edit_addon_post.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28436 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in D-Link DAP products DAP-2230, DAP-2310, DAP-2330, DAP-2360, DAP-2553, DAP-2590, DAP-2690, DAP-2695, DA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28436</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in D-Link DAP products DAP-2230, DAP-2310, DAP-2330, DAP-2360, DAP-2553, DAP-2590, DAP-2690, DAP-2695, DAP-3520, DAP-3662 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the reload parameter in the session_login.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38290 | Certain software builds for the BLU View 2 and Sharp Rouvo V Android devices contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38290</link><description>Certain software builds for the BLU View 2 and Sharp Rouvo V Android devices contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.evenwell.fqc (versionCode='9020801', versionName='9.0208.01' ; versionCode='9020913', versionName='9.0209.13' ; versionCode='9021203', versionName='9.0212.03') that allows local third-party apps to execute arbitrary shell commands in its context (system user) due to inadequate access control. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.evenwell.fqc app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The vulnerability allows local apps to access sensitive functionality that is generally restricted to pre-installed apps, such as programmatically performing the following actions: granting arbitrary permissions (which can be used to obtain sensitive user data), installing arbitrary apps, video recording the screen, wiping the device (removing the user's apps and data), injecting arbitrary input events, calling emergency phone numbers, disabling apps, accessing notifications, and much more. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: BLU View 2 (BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1672046950:user/release-keys, BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1663816427:user/release-keys, BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1656476696:user/release-keys, BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1647856638:user/release-keys) and Sharp Rouvo V (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_460:user/release-keys and SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys). This malicious app starts an exported activity named com.evenwell.fqc/.activity.ClickTest, crashes the com.evenwell.fqc app by sending an empty Intent (i.e., having not extras) to the com.evenwell.fqc/.FQCBroadcastReceiver receiver component, and then it sends command arbitrary shell commands to the com.evenwell.fqc/.FQCService service component which executes them with "system" privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38291 | An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to ro.boot.wifimacaddr, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38291</link><description>An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to ro.boot.wifimacaddr, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Various software builds for the following TCL devices (30Z and 10L) and Motorola devices (Moto G Pure and Moto G Power) leak the Wi-Fi MAC address to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL A3X (TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAAZ:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB3:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB7:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABA:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABM:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABP:user/release-keys, and TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABS:user/release-keys); TCL 10L (TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:10/QKQ1.200329.002/3CJ0:user/release-keys and TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:11/RKQ1.210107.001/8BIC:user/release-keys); Motorola Moto G Pure (motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-2/74844:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-7/5cde8:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-10/d67faa:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-13/b4a29:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RH32.20-42-10/1c2540:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-13-2-1/6368dd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_a/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-50-2/20fec:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-138/103bd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-138-2/e5502:user/release-keys, and motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-10-14-2/5e0b0:user/release-keys); and Motorola Moto G Power (motorola/tonga_g/tonga:11/RRQ31.Q3-68-16-2/e5877:user/release-keys and motorola/tonga_g/tonga:12/S3RQS32.20-42-10-6/f876d3:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "ro.boot.wifimacaddr" system property to indirectly obtain the Wi-Fi MAC address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38292 | Certain software builds for the TCL 20XE Android device contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com.tct.gcs.hiddenmen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38292</link><description>Certain software builds for the TCL 20XE Android device contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com.tct.gcs.hiddenmenuproxy (versionCode='2', versionName='v11.0.1.0.0201.0') that allows local third-party apps to programmatically perform a factory reset due to inadequate access control. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.tct.gcs.hiddenmenuproxy app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable build are as follows: TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB7I-0:user/release-keys and TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB83-0:user/release-keys. This malicious app sends a broadcast intent to the exported com.tct.gcs.hiddenmenuproxy/.rtn.FactoryResetReceiver receiver component, which initiates a programmatic factory reset.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38293 | Certain software builds for the Nokia C200 and Nokia C100 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38293</link><description>Certain software builds for the Nokia C200 and Nokia C100 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com.tracfone.tfstatus (versionCode='31', versionName='12') that allows local third-party apps to execute arbitrary AT commands in its context (radio user) via AT command injection due to inadequate access control and inadequate input filtering. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.tracfone.tfstatus app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: Nokia C200 (Nokia/Drake_02US/DRK:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_080:user/release-keys and Nokia/Drake_02US/DRK:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_040:user/release-keys) and Nokia C100 (Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_270:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_190:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_130:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_110:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_080:user/release-keys, and Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_050:user/release-keys). This malicious app sends a broadcast Intent to the receiver component named com.tracfone.tfstatus/.TFStatus. This broadcast receiver extracts a string from the Intent and uses it as an extra when it starts the com.tracfone.tfstatus/.TFStatusActivity activity component which uses the externally controlled string as an input to execute an AT command. There are two different injection techniques to successfully inject arbitrary AT commands to execute.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38294 | Certain software builds for the Itel Vision 3 Turbo Android device contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.transsi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38294</link><description>Certain software builds for the Itel Vision 3 Turbo Android device contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.transsion.autotest.factory (versionCode='7', versionName='1.8.0(220310_1027)') that allows local third-party apps to execute arbitrary shell commands in its context (system user) due to inadequate access control. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.transsion.autotest.factory app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The vulnerability allows local apps to access sensitive functionality that is generally restricted to pre-installed apps, such as programmatically performing the following actions: granting arbitrary permissions (which can be used to obtain sensitive user data), installing arbitrary apps, video recording the screen, wiping the device (removing the user's apps and data), injecting arbitrary input events, calling emergency phone numbers, disabling apps, accessing notifications, and much more. The confirmed vulnerable software build fingerprints for the Itel Vision 3 Turbo device are as follows: Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V92-20230105:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V86-20221118:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V78-20221101:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V64-20220803:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V61-20220721:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V58-20220712:user/release-keys, and Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V051-20220613:user/release-keys. This malicious app sends a broadcast Intent to the receiver component named com.transsion.autotest.factory/.broadcast.CommandReceiver with the path to a shell script that it creates in its scoped storage directory. Then the com.transsion.autotest.factory app will execute the shell script with "system" privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38295 | Certain software builds for the TCL 30Z and TCL 10 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app that relies on a missing permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38295</link><description>Certain software builds for the TCL 30Z and TCL 10 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app that relies on a missing permission that provides no protection at runtime. The missing permission is required as an access permission by components in various pre-installed apps. On the TCL 30Z device, the vulnerable app has a package name of com.tcl.screenrecorder (versionCode='1221092802', versionName='v5.2120.02.12008.1.T' ; versionCode='1221092805', versionName='v5.2120.02.12008.2.T'). On the TCL 10L device, the vulnerable app has a package name of com.tcl.sos (versionCode='2020102827', versionName='v3.2014.12.1012.B'). When a third-party app declares and requests the missing permission, it can interact with certain service components in the aforementioned apps (that execute with "system" privileges) to perform arbitrary files reads/writes in its context. An app exploiting this vulnerability only needs to declare and request the single missing permission and no user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL 10L (TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:11/RKQ1.210107.001/8BIC:user/release-keys) and TCL 30Z (TCL/4188R/Jetta_ATT:12/SP1A.210812.016/LV8E:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU5P:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU61:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU66:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU68:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6P:user/release-keys, and TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6X:user/release-keys). This malicious app declares the missing permission named com.tct.smart.switchphone.permission.SWITCH_DATA as a normal permission, requests the missing permission, and uses it to interact with the com.tct.smart.switchdata.DataService service component that is declared in vulnerable apps that execute with "system" privileges to perform arbitrary file reads/writes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38296 | Various software builds for the following TCL 30Z and TCL A3X devices leak the ICCID to a system property that can be accessed by any local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38296</link><description>Various software builds for the following TCL 30Z and TCL A3X devices leak the ICCID to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL 30Z (TCL/4188R/Jetta_ATT:12/SP1A.210812.016/LV8E:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU5P:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU61:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU66:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU68:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6P:user/release-keys, and TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6X:user/release-keys) and TCL A3X (TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAAZ:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB3:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB7:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABA:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABM:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABP:user/release-keys, and TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABS:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "persist.sys.tctPowerIccid" system property to indirectly obtain the ICCID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38297 | An issue was discovered in a third-party com.factory.mmigroup component, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Certain soft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38297</link><description>An issue was discovered in a third-party com.factory.mmigroup component, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Certain software builds for various Android devices contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.factory.mmigroup (versionCode='3', versionName='2.1) that allows local third-party apps to perform various actions, due to inadequate access control, in its context (system user), but the functionalities exposed depend on the specific device. The following capabilities are exposed to zero-permission, third-party apps on the following devices: arbitrary AT command execution via AT command injection (T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, and Boost Mobile Celero 5G); programmatic factory reset (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, Realme C25Y, and Lenovo Tab M8 HD), leaking IMEI (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, and Realme C25Y); leaking serial number (Samsung Galaxy A03s, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, Realme C25Y, and Lenovo Tab M8 HD); powering off the device (Realme C25Y, Samsung Galaxy A03S, and T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G); and programmatically enabling/disabling airplane mode (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, and Realme C25Y); and enabling Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, and GPS (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, and Realme C25Y). No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerabilities in the com.factory.mmigroup app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: Boost Mobile Celero 5G (Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V067:user/release-keys, Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V064:user/release-keys, Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V061:user/release-keys, and Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V052:user/release-keys); Samsung Galaxy A03S (samsung/a03sutfn/a03su:13/TP1A.220624.014/S134DLUDU6CWB6:user/release-keys and samsung/a03sutfn/a03su:12/SP1A.210812.016/S134DLUDS5BWA1:user/release-keys); Lenovo Tab M8 HD (Lenovo/LenovoTB-8505F/8505F:10/QP1A.190711.020/S300637_220706_BMP:user/release-keys and Lenovo/LenovoTB-8505F/8505F:10/QP1A.190711.020/S300448_220114_BMP:user/release-keys); T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G (T-Mobile/Augusta/Augusta:12/SP1A.210812.016/SW_S98121AA1_V070:user/release-keys and T-Mobile/Augusta/Augusta:12/SP1A.210812.016/SW_S98121AA1_V066:user/release-keys); T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G (T-Mobile/Sprout/Sprout:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98115AA1_V077:user/release-keys and T-Mobile/Sprout/Sprout:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98115AA1_V060:user/release-keys); and Realme C25Y (realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1675861640000:user/release-keys, realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1664031768000:user/release-keys, realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1652814687000:user/release-keys, and realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1635785712000:user/release-keys). This malicious app sends a broadcast Intent to com.factory.mmigroup/.MMIGroupReceiver. This causes the com.factory.mmigroup app to dynamically register for various action strings. The malicious app can then send these strings, allowing it to perform various behaviors that the com.factory.mmigroup app exposes. The actual behaviors exposed by the com.factory.mmigroup app depend on device model and chipset. The com.factory.mmigroup app executes as the "system" user, allowing it to interact with the baseband processor and perform various other sensitive actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38298 | Various software builds for the following TCL devices (30Z, A3X, 20XE, 10L) leak the device IMEI to a system property that can be accessed b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38298</link><description>Various software builds for the following TCL devices (30Z, A3X, 20XE, 10L) leak the device IMEI to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL 30Z (TCL/4188R/Jetta_ATT:12/SP1A.210812.016/LV8E:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU5P:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU61:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU66:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU68:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6P:user/release-keys, and TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6X:user/release-keys); TCL A3X (TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAAZ:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB3:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB7:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABA:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABM:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABP:user/release-keys, and TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABS:user/release-keys); TCL 20XE (TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB7I-0:user/release-keys and TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB83-0:user/release-keys); and TCL 10L (TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:10/QKQ1.200329.002/3CJ0:user/release-keys and TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:11/RKQ1.210107.001/8BIC:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "gsm.device.imei0" system property to indirectly obtain the device IMEI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38299 | Various software builds for the AT&amp;T Calypso, Nokia C100, Nokia C200, and BLU View 3 devices leak the device IMEI to a system property that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38299</link><description>Various software builds for the AT&amp;amp;T Calypso, Nokia C100, Nokia C200, and BLU View 3 devices leak the device IMEI to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: AT&amp;amp;T Calypso (ATT/U318AA/U318AA:10/QP1A.190711.020/1632369780:user/release-keys); Nokia C100 (Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_190:user/release-keys and Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_270:user/release-keys); Nokia C200 (Nokia/Drake_02US/DRK:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_080:user/release-keys); and BLU View 3 (BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1628014629:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1632535579:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1637325978:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1650073052:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1657087912:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1666316280:user/release-keys, and BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1672371162:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "persist.sys.imei1" system property to indirectly obtain the device IMEI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38300 | A certain software build for the Orbic Maui device (Orbic/RC545L/RC545L:10/ORB545L_V1.4.2_BVZPP/230106:user/release-keys) leaks the IMEI and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38300</link><description>A certain software build for the Orbic Maui device (Orbic/RC545L/RC545L:10/ORB545L_V1.4.2_BVZPP/230106:user/release-keys) leaks the IMEI and the ICCID to system properties that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in this instance they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. This malicious app reads from the "persist.sys.verizon_test_plan_imei" system property to indirectly obtain the IMEI and reads the "persist.sys.verizon_test_plan_iccid" system property to obtain the ICCID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38301 | An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to vendor.gsm.serial, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Vari...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38301</link><description>An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to vendor.gsm.serial, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Various software builds for the BLU View 2, Boost Mobile Celero 5G, Sharp Rouvo V, Motorola Moto G Pure, Motorola Moto G Power, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, and T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G devices leak the device serial number to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: BLU View 2 (BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1672046950:user/release-keys); Boost Mobile Celero 5G (Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V067:user/release-keys); Sharp Rouvo V (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys); Motorola Moto G Pure (motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-2/74844:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-7/5cde8:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-10/d67faa:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-13/b4a29:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RH32.20-42-10/1c2540:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-13-2-1/6368dd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_a/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-50-2/20fec:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-138/103bd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-138-2/e5502:user/release-keys, and motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-10-14-2/5e0b0:user/release-keys); Motorola Moto G Power (motorola/tonga_g/tonga:11/RRQ31.Q3-68-16-2/e5877:user/release-keys and motorola/tonga_g/tonga:12/S3RQS32.20-42-10-6/f876d3:user/release-keys); T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G (T-Mobile/Augusta/Augusta:12/SP1A.210812.016/SW_S98121AA1_V070:user/release-keys); and T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G (T-Mobile/Sprout/Sprout:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98115AA1_V077:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "vendor.gsm.serial" system property to indirectly obtain the device serial number.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38302 | A certain software build for the Sharp Rouvo V device (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys) leak...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38302</link><description>A certain software build for the Sharp Rouvo V device (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys) leaks the Wi-Fi MAC address and the Bluetooth MAC address to system properties that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in this instance they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. This malicious app reads from the "ro.boot.wifi_mac" system property to indirectly obtain the Wi-Fi MAC address and reads the "ro.boot.bt_mac" system property to obtain the Bluetooth MAC address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-35503 | Improper verification of a user input in Open Source MANO v7-v12 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code within the LCM m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35503</link><description>Improper verification of a user input in Open Source MANO v7-v12 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code within the LCM module container via a Virtual Network Function (VNF) descriptor. An attacker may be able execute code to change the normal execution of the OSM components, retrieve confidential information, or gain access other parts of a Telco Operator infrastructure other than OSM itself.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28699 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in pdf2json v0.70 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the GString::copy() and ImgOutputDev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28699</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in pdf2json v0.70 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the GString::copy() and ImgOutputDev::ImgOutputDev function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34560 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34560</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the History parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34561 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34561</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the video description parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34562 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34562</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the status box.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27347 | Apache HugeGraph-Hubble: SSRF in Hubble connection page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27347</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Hubble.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Hubble: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27348 | Apache HugeGraph-Server: Command execution in gremlin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27348</link><description>RCE-Remote Command Execution vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0 in Java8 &amp; Java11

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0 with Java11 &amp; enable the Auth system, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27349 | Apache HugeGraph-Server: Bypass whitelist in Auth mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27349</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32368 | Insecure Permission vulnerability in Agasta Sanketlife 2.0 Pocket 12-Lead ECG Monitor FW Version 3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32368</link><description>Insecure Permission vulnerability in Agasta Sanketlife 2.0 Pocket 12-Lead ECG Monitor FW Version 3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3645 | The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Counter widget in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3645</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Counter widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'title_html_tag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22813 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to overwrite the hardcoded IP address in the device memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22813</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to overwrite the hardcoded IP address in the device memory, disrupting network connectivity between the router and the controller.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22815 | An issue in the communication protocol of Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22815</link><description>An issue in the communication protocol of Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29661 | A File Upload vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29661</link><description>A File Upload vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22807 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to erase a critical sector of the flash memory, causing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22807</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to erase a critical sector of the flash memory, causing the machine to lose network connectivity and suffer from firmware corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22808 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22808</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the communication between the PathPilot controller and the CNC router via overwriting the card's name in the device memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22809 | Incorrect access control in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to access the G code's shared folder and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22809</link><description>Incorrect access control in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to access the G code's shared folder and view sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22811 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22811</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the communication between the PathPilot controller and the CNC router via overwriting the Hostmot2 configuration cookie in the device memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4026 | Cross-Site Scripting in the Holded application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4026</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Holded application. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to store a JavaScript payload within all editable parameters within the 'General' and 'Team ID' functionalities, which could result in a session takeover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22856 | A SQL injection vulnerability via the Save Favorite Search function in Axefinance Axe Credit Portal &gt;= v.3.0 allows authenticated attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22856</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability via the Save Favorite Search function in Axefinance Axe Credit Portal &gt;= v.3.0 allows authenticated attackers to execute unintended queries and disclose sensitive information from DB tables via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28717 | An issue in OpenStack Storlets yoga-eom allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the gateway.py component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28717</link><description>An issue in OpenStack Storlets yoga-eom allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the gateway.py component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32681 | WordPress Prime Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32681</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 3.13.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32682 | WordPress Prime Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32682</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 3.13.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32684 | WordPress WP Ultimate Review plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Broken Access Control on Review vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32684</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpmet Wp Ultimate Review.This issue affects Wp Ultimate Review: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32687 | WordPress WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32687</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPClever WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce.This issue affects WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32688 | WordPress MyRewards plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Long Watch Studio MyRewards.This issue affects MyRewards: from n/a through 5.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32691 | WordPress Active Products Tables for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32691</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in realmag777 Active Products Tables for WooCommerce.This issue affects Active Products Tables for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32693 | WordPress Automatic plugin &amp;lt; 3.93.0 - Multiple Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32693</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ValvePress Automatic.This issue affects Automatic: from n/a before 3.93.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32697 | WordPress HelloAsso plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HelloAsso allows Stored XSS.This issue affects HelloAsso: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32698 | WordPress Happy Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32698</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leevio Happy Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Happy Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 3.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32694 | WordPress 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.62 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative interactive media 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 3.62.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32695 | WordPress Language Switcher for Transposh plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marco Gasi Language Switcher for Transposh allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Language Switcher for Transposh: from n/a through 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32696 | WordPress AI Infographic Maker OpenAI plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in QuantumCloud Infographic Maker – iList allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Infographic Maker – iList: from n/a through 4.6.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32690 | WordPress RSS Feed Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32690</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood RSS Feed Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects RSS Feed Widget: from n/a through 2.9.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7252 | Tickera &amp;lt; 3.5.2.5 - Ticket leakage through IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7252</link><description>The Tickera  WordPress plugin before 3.5.2.5 does not prevent users from leaking other users' tickets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25101 | l2c2technologies Koha opac-MARCdetail.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25101</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in l2c2technologies Koha up to 20180108. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/koha/opac-MARCdetail.pl. The manipulation of the argument biblionumber with the input 2"&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier of the patch is 950fc8e101886821879066b33e389a47fb0a9782. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-261677 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28722 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Innovaphone myPBX v.14r1, v.13r3, v.12r2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28722</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Innovaphone myPBX v.14r1, v.13r3, v.12r2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the query parameter to the /CMD0/xml_modes.xml endpoint</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32418 | An issue in flusity CMS v2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_addon.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32418</link><description>An issue in flusity CMS v2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_addon.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30799 | An issue in PX4 Autopilot v1.14 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via the Breach R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30799</link><description>An issue in PX4 Autopilot v1.14 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via the Breach Return Point function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10132 | Thimo Grauerholz WP-Spreadplugin spreadplugin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10132</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Thimo Grauerholz WP-Spreadplugin up to 3.8.6.1 on WordPress. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file spreadplugin.php. The manipulation of the argument Spreadplugin leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.8.6.6 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is a9b9afc641854698e80aa5dd9ababfc8e0e57d69. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261676.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29733 | Apache Airflow FTP Provider: FTP_TLS instance with unverified SSL context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29733</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in Apache Airflow FTP Provider.

The FTP hook lacks complete certificate validation in FTP_TLS connections, which can potentially be leveraged. Implementing proper certificate validation by passing context=ssl.create_default_context() during FTP_TLS instantiation is used as mitigation to validate the certificates properly.

This issue affects Apache Airflow FTP Provider: before 3.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29217 | Apache Answer: XSS vulnerability when changing personal website</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29217</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: before 1.3.0.

XSS attack when user changes personal website. A logged-in user, when modifying their personal website, can input malicious code in the website to create such an attack.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.3.0], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4022 | Keenetic KN-1010/KN-1410/KN-1711/KN-1810/KN-1910 Version Data version.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4022</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keenetic KN-1010, KN-1410, KN-1711, KN-1810 and KN-1910 up to 4.1.2.15. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /version.js of the component Version Data Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 10:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4021 | Keenetic KN-1010/KN-1410/KN-1711/KN-1810/KN-1910 Configuration Setting ndmComponents.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4021</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keenetic KN-1010, KN-1410, KN-1711, KN-1810 and KN-1910 up to 4.1.2.15. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ndmComponents.js of the component Configuration Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261673 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 10:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>