<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 06:53:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11355 | UTT 1250GW aspChangeChannel strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11355</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT 1250GW up to v2v3.2.2-200710. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/aspChangeChannel. The manipulation of the argument pvid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 06:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10162 | OrderConvo &amp;lt; 14 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10162</link><description>The Admin and Customer Messages After Order for WooCommerce: OrderConvo WordPress plugin before 14 does not validate the path of files to be downloaded, which could allow unauthenticated attacker to read/download arbitrary files via a path traversal attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 06:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11354 | code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System addslideexec.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11354</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/addslideexec.php. Executing manipulation of the argument image can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 06:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11353 | code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System addgalleryexec.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11353</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/addgalleryexec.php. Performing manipulation of the argument image results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 05:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11352 | code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System addexec.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11352</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/addexec.php. Such manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 05:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11362 | Versions of the package pdfmake before 0.3.0-beta.17 are vulnerable to Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling via repeatedly r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11362</link><description>Versions of the package pdfmake before 0.3.0-beta.17 are vulnerable to Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling via repeatedly redirect URL in file embedding. An attacker can cause the application to crash or become unresponsive by providing crafted input that triggers this condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 05:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11351 | code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System editpicexec.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11351</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/editpicexec.php. This manipulation of the argument image causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 04:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11350 | Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11350</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 04:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11349 | Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System search-visitor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11349</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /search-visitor.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 03:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11347 | code-projects Student Crud Operation Add Student Page/Edit Student add.php move_uploaded_file unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Crud Operation up to 3.3. This vulnerability affects the function move_uploaded_file of the file add.php of the component Add Student Page/Edit Student Page. Performing manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 03:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11348 | Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11348</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 03:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34251 | Tesla Telematics Control Unit (TCU) &amp;lt; v2025.14 Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34251</link><description>Tesla Telematics Control Unit (TCU) firmware prior to v2025.14 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability. The TCU runs the Android Debug Bridge (adbd) as root and, despite a “lockdown” check that disables adb shell, still permits adb push/pull and adb forward. Because adbd is privileged and the device’s USB port is exposed externally, an attacker with physical access can write an arbitrary file to a writable location and then overwrite the kernel’s uevent_helper or /proc/sys/kernel/hotplug entries via ADB, causing the script to be executed with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 23:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61774 | PyVista has Dependency Confusion Vulnerability in that leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61774</link><description>PyVista provides 3D plotting and mesh analysis through an interface for the Visualization Toolkit (VTK). Version 0.46.3 of the PyVista Project is vulnerable to remote code execution via dependency confusion. Two pieces of code use`--extra-index-url`. But when `--extra-index-url` is used, pip always checks for the PyPI index first, and then the external index. One package listed in the code is not published in PyPI. If an attacker publishes a package with higher version in PyPI, the malicious code from the attacker controlled package may be pulled, leading to remote code execution and a supply chain attack. As of time of publication, a patched version is unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43824 | The Profile widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43824</link><description>The Profile widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions uses a user’s name in the “Content-Disposition” header, which allows remote authenticated users to change the file extension when a vCard file is downloaded.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 22:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61768 | Kuno CMS Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via Unsafe SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61768</link><description>KUNO CMS is a fully deployable full-stack blog application. In versions prior to 1.3.15, an SSRF (Server-Side Request Forgery) vulnerability exists in the Media module of the Kuno CMS administrative panel. A logged-in administrator can upload a specially crafted SVG file containing an external image reference, causing the server to initiate an outgoing connection to an arbitrary external URL. This can lead to information disclosure or internal network probing. Version 1.3.15 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 22:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59450 | The YoSmart YoLink Smart Hub firmware 0382 is unencrypted, and data extracted from it can be used to determine network access credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59450</link><description>The YoSmart YoLink Smart Hub firmware 0382 is unencrypted, and data extracted from it can be used to determine network access credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59451 | The YoSmart YoLink application through 2025-10-02 has session tokens with unexpectedly long lifetimes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59451</link><description>The YoSmart YoLink application through 2025-10-02 has session tokens with unexpectedly long lifetimes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59452 | The YoSmart YoLink API through 2025-10-02 uses an endpoint URL that is derived from a device's MAC address along with an MD5 hash of non-sec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59452</link><description>The YoSmart YoLink API through 2025-10-02 uses an endpoint URL that is derived from a device's MAC address along with an MD5 hash of non-secret information, such as a key that begins with cf50.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59448 | Components of the YoSmart YoLink ecosystem through 2025-10-02 leverage unencrypted MQTT to communicate over the internet. An attacker with t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59448</link><description>Components of the YoSmart YoLink ecosystem through 2025-10-02 leverage unencrypted MQTT to communicate over the internet. An attacker with the ability to monitor network traffic could therefore obtain sensitive information or tamper with the traffic to control affected devices. This affects YoLink Hub 0382, YoLink Mobile Application 1.40.41, and YoLink MQTT Broker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59449 | The YoSmart YoLink MQTT broker through 2025-10-02 does not enforce sufficient authorization controls to prevent cross-account attacks, allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59449</link><description>The YoSmart YoLink MQTT broker through 2025-10-02 does not enforce sufficient authorization controls to prevent cross-account attacks, allowing an attacker to remotely operate affected devices if the attacker obtains the associated device IDs. Because YoLink device IDs are predictable, an attacker can exploit this to gain full control over any other YoLink user's devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59447 | The YoSmart YoLink Smart Hub device 0382 exposes a UART debug interface. An attacker with direct physical access can leverage this interface...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59447</link><description>The YoSmart YoLink Smart Hub device 0382 exposes a UART debug interface. An attacker with direct physical access can leverage this interface to read a boot log, which includes network access credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11346 | ILIAS Base64 Decoding unserialize deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11346</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ILIAS up to 8.23/9.13/10.1. This affects the function unserialize of the component Base64 Decoding Handler. Such manipulation of the argument f_settings leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.24, 9.14 and 10.2 is able to mitigate this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11345 | ILIAS Test Import unserialize deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11345</link><description>A flaw has been found in ILIAS up to 8.23/9.13/10.1. Affected by this issue is the function unserialize of the component Test Import. This manipulation causes deserialization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.24, 9.14 and 10.2 can resolve this issue. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11344 | ILIAS Certificate Import Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11344</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ILIAS up to 8.23/9.13/10.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Certificate Import Handler. The manipulation results in Remote Code Execution. The attack may be performed from remote. Upgrading to version 8.24, 9.14 and 10.2 addresses this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61984 | ssh in OpenSSH before 10.1 allows control characters in usernames that originate from certain possibly untrusted sources, potentially leadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61984</link><description>ssh in OpenSSH before 10.1 allows control characters in usernames that originate from certain possibly untrusted sources, potentially leading to code execution when a ProxyCommand is used. The untrusted sources are the command line and %-sequence expansion of a configuration file. (A configuration file that provides a complete literal username is not categorized as an untrusted source.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61985 | ssh in OpenSSH before 10.1 allows the '\0' character in an ssh:// URI, potentially leading to code execution when a ProxyCommand is used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61985</link><description>ssh in OpenSSH before 10.1 allows the '\0' character in an ssh:// URI, potentially leading to code execution when a ProxyCommand is used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11343 | code-projects Student Crud Operation delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11343</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Student Crud Operation 3.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file delete.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57515 | A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Uniclare Student Portal v2. This flaw allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57515</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Uniclare Student Portal v2. This flaw allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands via vulnerable input fields, enabling the execution of time-delay functions to infer database responses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6985 | XXE Vulnerability in langchain-ai/langchain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6985</link><description>The HTMLSectionSplitter class in langchain-text-splitters version 0.3.8 is vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) attacks due to unsafe XSLT parsing. This vulnerability arises because the class allows the use of arbitrary XSLT stylesheets, which are parsed using lxml.etree.parse() and lxml.etree.XSLT() without any hardening measures. In lxml versions up to 4.9.x, external entities are resolved by default, allowing attackers to read arbitrary local files or perform outbound HTTP(S) fetches. In lxml versions 5.0 and above, while entity expansion is disabled, the XSLT document() function can still read any URI unless XSLTAccessControl is applied. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to gain read-only access to any file the LangChain process can reach, including sensitive files such as SSH keys, environment files, source code, or cloud metadata. No authentication, special privileges, or user interaction are required, and the issue is exploitable in default deployments that enable custom XSLT.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28129 | Phpgurukul Hostel Management System 2.1 is vulnerable to clickjacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28129</link><description>Phpgurukul Hostel Management System 2.1 is vulnerable to clickjacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11342 | code-projects Online Course Registration edit-course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11342</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Course Registration 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-course.php. Executing manipulation of the argument coursecode can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56382 | A stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Customer Management Module of LionCoders SalePro POS 5.4.8. An authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56382</link><description>A stored Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Customer Management Module of LionCoders SalePro POS 5.4.8. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the 'Customer Name' parameter when creating or editing customer profiles. This malicious input is improperly sanitized before storage and subsequent rendering, leading to script execution in the browsers of users who view the affected customer details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11341 | Jinher OA type xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11341</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Jinher OA up to 2.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /c6/Jhsoft.Web.module/eformaspx/WebDesign.aspx/?type=SystemUserInfo&amp;amp;style=1. Performing manipulation results in xml external entity reference. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60956 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60956</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service, gain escalated privileges, and gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60957 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60957</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service, gain escalated privileges, and gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60958 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60958</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60959 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60959</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60960 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60960</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service, gain escalated privileges, and gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60961 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60961</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to gain sensitive information, and possibly other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60962 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60962</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to gain sensitive information, and possibly other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60963 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60963</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service, gain escalated privileges, and gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60964 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60964</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service, gain escalated privileges, gain sensitive information, and possibly other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60965 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60965</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0071-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service, gain escalated privileges, gain sensitive information, and possibly other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60967 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0076-000 Ver 4.00 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60967</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0076-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60969 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0076-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60969</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in EndRun Technologies Sonoma D12 Network Time Server (GPS) F/W 6010-0076-000 Ver 4.00 allows attackers to gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36354 | IBM Security Verify Access command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36354</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.9.0 and 11.0.0.0 through 11.0.1.0 



could allow an unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary commands with lower user privileges on the system due to improper validation of user supplied input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36355 | IBM Security Verify Access code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36355</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.9.0 and 11.0.0.0 through 11.0.1.0 

could allow a locally authenticated user to execute malicious scripts from outside of its control sphere.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36356 | IBM Security Verify Access privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36356</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.9.0 and 11.0.0.0 through 11.0.1.0 could allow a locally authenticated user to escalate their privileges to root due to execution with more privileges than required.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61778 | Akka.Remote TLS did not properly implement certificate-based authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61778</link><description>Akka.NET is a .NET port of the Akka project from the Scala / Java community. In all versions of Akka.Remote from v1.2.0 to v1.5.51, TLS could be enabled via our `akka.remote.dot-netty.tcp` transport and this would correctly enforce private key validation on the server-side of inbound connections. Akka.Remote, however, never asked the outbound-connecting client to present ITS certificate - therefore it's possible for untrusted parties to connect to a private key'd Akka.NET cluster and begin communicating with it without any certificate. The issue here is that for certificate-based authentication to work properly, ensuring that all members of the Akka.Remote network are secured with the same private key, Akka.Remote needed to implement mutual TLS. This was not the case before Akka.NET v1.5.52. Those who run Akka.NET inside a private network that they fully control or who were never using TLS in the first place are now affected by the bug. However, those who use TLS to secure their networks must upgrade to Akka.NET V1.5.52 or later. One patch forces "fail fast" semantics if TLS is enabled but the private key is missing or invalid. Previous versions would only check that once connection attempts occurred. The second patch, a critical fix, enforces mutual TLS (mTLS) by default, so both parties must be keyed using the same certificate. As a workaround, avoid exposing the application publicly to avoid the vulnerability having a practical impact on one's application. However, upgrading to version 1.5.52 is still recommended by the maintainers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61777 | FlagForge Allows Unauthenticated Badge Template API Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61777</link><description>Flag Forge is a Capture The Flag (CTF) platform. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to version 2.3.2, the `/api/admin/badge-templates` (GET) and `/api/admin/badge-templates/create` (POST) endpoints previously allowed access without authentication or authorization. This could have enabled unauthorized users to retrieve all badge templates and sensitive metadata (createdBy, createdAt, updatedAt) and/or create arbitrary badge templates in the database. This could lead to data exposure, database pollution, or abuse of the badge system. The issue has been fixed in FlagForge v2.3.2. GET, POST, UPDATE, and DELETE endpoints now require authentication. Authorization checks ensure only admins can access and modify badge templates. No reliable workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10363 | Unauthenticated RCE via .NET Deserialization in Topal Finance Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10363</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Topal Solutions AG Topal Finanzbuchhaltung on Windows allows Remote Code Execution.This issue affects at least Topal Finanzbuchhaltung: 10.1.5.20 and is fixed in version 11.2.12.00</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11339 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 jhttpd hi_block.asp sub_4BD4F8 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11339</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DI-7100G C1 up to 20250928. This issue affects the function sub_4BD4F8 of the file /webchat/hi_block.asp of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument popupId leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0038 | In AMD Zynq UltraScale+ devices, the lack of address validation when executing CSU runtime services through the PMU Firmware can allow acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0038</link><description>In AMD Zynq UltraScale+ devices, the lack of address validation when executing CSU runtime services through the PMU Firmware can allow access to isolated or protected memory spaces resulting in the loss of integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57247 | The BATBToken smart contract (address 0xfbf1388408670c02f0dbbb74251d8ded1d63b7a2, Compiler Version v0.8.26+commit.8a97fa7a) contains incorre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57247</link><description>The BATBToken smart contract (address 0xfbf1388408670c02f0dbbb74251d8ded1d63b7a2, Compiler Version v0.8.26+commit.8a97fa7a) contains incorrect access control implementation in whitelist management functions. The setColdWhiteList() and setSpecialAddress() functions in the base ERC20 contract are declared as public without proper access control modifiers, allowing any user to bypass transfer restrictions and manipulate special address settings. This enables unauthorized users to circumvent cold time transfer restrictions and potentially disrupt dividend distribution mechanisms, leading to privilege escalation and violation of the contract's intended tokenomics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61766 | Bucket vulnerable to infinite recursion when querying a bucket using the != operator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61766</link><description>Bucket is a MediaWiki extension to store and retrieve structured data on articles. Prior to version 1.0.0, infinite recursion can occur if a user queries a bucket using the `!=` comparator. This will result in PHP's call stack limit exceeding, and/or increased memory consumption, potentially leading to a denial of service. Version 1.0.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61769 | Emlog vulnerable to stored XSS in file upload functionality in emlog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61769</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in emlog up to and including version 2.5.22 allows authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the file upload functionality. As an authenticated user it is possible to upload .svg file that contains JavaScript code that is later being executed. Commit 052f9c4226b2c0014bcd857fec47677340b185b1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11338 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 jhttpd login.cgi sub_4C0990 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11338</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DI-7100G C1 up to 20250928. This vulnerability affects the function sub_4C0990 of the file /webchat/login.cgi of the component jhttpd. Executing manipulation of the argument openid can lead to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61765 | python-socketio vulnerable to arbitrary Python code execution (RCE) through malicious pickle deserialization in certain multi-server deployments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61765</link><description>python-socketio is a Python implementation of the Socket.IO realtime client and server. A remote code execution vulnerability in python-socketio versions prior to 5.14.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Python code through malicious pickle deserialization in multi-server deployments on which the attacker previously gained access to the message queue that the servers use for internal communications. When Socket.IO servers are configured to use a message queue backend such as Redis for inter-server communication, messages sent between the servers are encoded using the `pickle` Python module. When a server receives one of these messages through the message queue, it assumes it is trusted and immediately deserializes it. The vulnerability stems from deserialization of messages using Python's `pickle.loads()` function. Having previously obtained access to the message queue, the attacker can send a python-socketio server a crafted pickle payload that executes arbitrary code during deserialization via Python's `__reduce__` method. This vulnerability only affects deployments with a compromised message queue. The attack can lead to the attacker executing random code in the context of, and with the privileges of a Socket.IO server process. Single-server systems that do not use a message queue, and multi-server systems with a secure message queue are not vulnerable. In addition to making sure standard security practices are followed in the deployment of the message queue, users of the python-socketio package can upgrade to version 5.14.0 or newer, which remove the `pickle` module and use the much safer JSON encoding for inter-server messaging.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61687 | FlowiseAI/Flosise has File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61687</link><description>Flowise is a drag &amp; drop user interface to build a customized large language model flow. A file upload vulnerability in version 3.0.7 of FlowiseAI allows authenticated users to upload arbitrary files without proper validation. This enables attackers to persistently store malicious Node.js web shells on the server, potentially leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The system fails to validate file extensions, MIME types, or file content during uploads. As a result, malicious scripts such as Node.js-based web shells can be uploaded and stored persistently on the server. These shells expose HTTP endpoints capable of executing arbitrary commands if triggered. The uploaded shell does not automatically execute, but its presence allows future exploitation via administrator error or chained vulnerabilities. This presents a high-severity threat to system integrity and confidentiality. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61224 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DokuWiki 2025-05-14a 'Librarian'[56.1] allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the q pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61224</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DokuWiki 2025-05-14a 'Librarian'[56.1] allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the q parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59159 | SillyTavern Web Interface Vulnerable to DNS Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59159</link><description>SillyTavern is a locally installed user interface that allows users to interact with text generation large language models, image generation engines, and text-to-speech voice models. In versions prior to 1.13.4, the web user interface for SillyTavern is susceptible to DNS rebinding, allowing attackers to perform actions like install malicious extensions, read chats, inject arbitrary HTML for phishing attacks, etc. The vulnerability has been patched in the version 1.13.4 by introducing a server configuration setting that enables a validation of host names in inbound HTTP requests according to the provided list of allowed hosts: `hostWhitelist.enabled` in config.yaml file or `SILLYTAVERN_HOSTWHITELIST_ENABLED` environment variable. While the setting is disabled by default to honor a wide variety of existing user configurations and maintain backwards compatibility, existing and new users are encouraged to review their server configurations and apply necessary changes to their setup, especially if hosting over the local network while not using SSL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59152 | X-Forwarded-For Header Spoofing Bypasses Litestar Rate Limiting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59152</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. In version 2.17.0, rate limits can be completely bypassed by manipulating the X-Forwarded-For header. This renders IP-based rate limiting ineffective against determined attackers. Litestar's RateLimitMiddleware uses `cache_key_from_request()` to generate cache keys for rate limiting. When an X-Forwarded-For header is present, the middleware trusts it unconditionally and uses its value as part of the client identifier. Since clients can set arbitrary X-Forwarded-For values, each different spoofed IP creates a separate rate limit bucket. An attacker can rotate through different header values to avoid hitting any single bucket's limit. This affects any Litestar application using RateLimitMiddleware with default settings, which likely includes most applications that implement rate limiting. Version 2.18.0 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52472 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to HQL injection via wiki and space search REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52472</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Starting in version 4.3-milestone-1 and prior to versions 16.10.9, 17.4.2, and 17.5.0, the REST search URL is vulnerable to HQL injection via the `orderField` parameter. The specified value is added twice in the query, though, once in the field list for the select and once in the order clause, so it's not that easy to exploit. The part of the query between the two fields can be enclosed in single quotes to effectively remove them, but the query still needs to remain valid with the query two times in it. This has been patched in versions 17.5.0, 17.4.2, and 16.10.9. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49886 | IBM Transformation Extender Advanced code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49886</link><description>IBM Standards Processing Engine 10.0.1.10 could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by an unsafe java deserialization. By sending specially crafted input, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49594 | XWiki OIDC Authenticator vulnerable to creation of token for any user with just `view` right</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49594</link><description>XWiki OIDC has various tools to manipulate OpenID Connect protocol in XWiki. Starting in version 2.17.1 and prior to version 2.18.2, anyone with VIEW access to a user profile can create a token for that user. If that XWiki instance is configured to allow token authentication, it allows authentication with any user (since users are very commonly viewable, at least to other registered users). Version 2.18.2 contains a patch. As a workaround, disable token access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61197 | An issue in Orban Optimod 5950, Optimod 5950HD, Optimod 5750, Optimod 5750HD, Optimod Trio Optimod version 1.0.0.33 - System version 2.5.26 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61197</link><description>An issue in Orban Optimod 5950, Optimod 5950HD, Optimod 5750, Optimod 5750HD, Optimod Trio Optimod version 1.0.0.33 - System version 2.5.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the application stores user privilege/role information in client-side browser storage</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61198 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Optimod 5950 - Optimod 5950HD - Optimod 5750 - Optimod 5750HD - Optimod Trio - Optimod ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61198</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Optimod 5950 - Optimod 5950HD - Optimod 5750 - Optimod 5750HD - Optimod Trio - Optimod version 1.0.0.33 - System version 2.5.26, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by including a malicious payload into the logs which would be returned in logs rendered in the UI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11337 | Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform download.do;othersusrlogout.do path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11337</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform up to 2.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /aloneReport/index.do/../../aloneReport/download.do;othersusrlogout.do. Performing manipulation of the argument fileName results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11336 | Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform download.do;otherlogout.do path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11336</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform up to 2.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /stAlarmConfigure/index.do/../../aloneReport/download.do;otherlogout.do. Such manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11335 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 jhttpd msp_info.htm sub_46409C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11335</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DI-7100G C1 up to 20250928. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_46409C of the file /msp_info.htm?flag=qos of the component jhttpd. This manipulation of the argument iface causes command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11334 | Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System visitor-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11334</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /visitor-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11333 | langleyfcu Online Banking System Add Customer customer_add_action.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11333</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in langleyfcu Online Banking System up to 57437e6400ce0ae240e692c24e6346b8d0c17d7a. This impacts an unknown function of the file /customer_add_action.php of the component Add Customer Page. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11332 | CmsEasy URL view.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11332</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in CmsEasy up to 7.7.7. This affects an unknown function in the library lib/inc/view.php of the component URL Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument PHP_SELF can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11331 | IdeaCMS Website Name Config.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IdeaCMS up to 1.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file app/common/logic/admin/Config.php of the component Website Name Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument 网站名称 results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11330 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System sales-reports-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11330</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/sales-reports-detail.php. Such manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0607 | HTML Injection in Logo Software&amp;#x27;s Logo Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0607</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Logo Software Inc. Logo Cloud allows Phishing.This issue affects Logo Cloud: before 2.57.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0608 | Open Redirect in Logo Software&amp;#x27;s Logo Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0608</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Logo Software Inc. Logo Cloud allows Phishing, Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Logo Cloud: before 2025.R6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0609 | XSS in Logo Software&amp;#x27;s Logo Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0609</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Logo Software Inc. Logo Cloud allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Logo Cloud: before 1.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0606 | IDOR in Logo Software&amp;#x27;s Logo Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0606</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Logo Software Inc. Logo Cloud allows Forceful Browsing, Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Logo Cloud: before 0.67.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11329 | code-projects Online Course Registration manage-students.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11329</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Course Registration 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-students.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11328 | Tenda AC18 SetDDNSCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11328</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19(6318). This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SetDDNSCfg. The manipulation of the argument ddnsEn results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11327 | Tenda AC18 SetUpnpCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11327</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19(6318). This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/SetUpnpCfg. The manipulation of the argument upnpEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59728 | Heap-buffer-overflow write in FFmpeg MDASH resolve_content_path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59728</link><description>When calculating the content path in handling of MPEG-DASH manifests, there's an out-of-bounds NUL-byte write one byte past the end of the buffer.When we call xmlNodeGetContent below [0], it returns a buffer precisely allocated to match the string length, using strdup internally. If this buffer is not an empty string, it is assigned to root_url at [1].If the last (non-NUL) byte in this buffer is not '/' then we append '/' in-place at [2]. This will write two bytes into the buffer, starting at the last valid byte in the buffer, writing the NUL byte beyond the end of the allocated buffer.
We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59729 | Heap-buffer-overflow read in FFmpeg DHAV get_duration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59729</link><description>When parsing the header for a DHAV file, there's an integer underflow in offset calculation that leads to reading the duration from before the start of the allocated buffer.

If we load a DHAV file that is larger than MAX_DURATION_BUFFER_SIZE bytes (0x100000) for example 0x101000 bytes, then at [0] we have size = 0x101000. At [1] we have end_buffer_size = 0x100000, and at [2] we have end_buffer_pos = 0x1000.

The loop then scans backwards through the buffer looking for the dhav tag; when it is found, we'll calculate end_pos based on a 32-bit offset read from the buffer.

There is subsequently a check [3] that end_pos is within the section of the file that has been copied into end_buffer, but it only correctly handles the cases where end_pos is before the start of the file or after the section copied into end_buffer, and not the case where end_pos is within the the file, but before the section copied into end_buffer. If we provide such an offset, (end_pos - end_buffer_pos) can underflow, resulting in the subsequent access at [4] occurring before the beginning of the allocation.

We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59730 | Heap-buffer-overflow write in FFmpeg SANM decoding due to lack of bounds-checking in old_codec48</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59730</link><description>When decoding a frame for a SANM file (ANIM v0 variant), the decoded data can be larger than the buffer allocated for it.

Frames encoded with codec 48 can specify their resolution (width x height). A buffer of appropriate size is allocated depending on the resolution.

This codec can encode the frame contents using a run-length encoding algorithm. There are no checks that the decoded frame fits in the allocated buffer, leading to a heap-buffer-overflow.

process_frame_obj initializes the buffers based on the frame resolution:



We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59731 | Heap-buffer-overflow write in FFmpeg EXR dwa_uncompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59731</link><description>When decoding an OpenEXR file that uses DWAA or DWAB compression, the specified raw length of run-length-encoded data is not checked when using it to calculate the output data.

We read rle_raw_size from the input file at [0], we decompress and decode into the buffer td-&gt;rle_raw_data of size rle_raw_size at [1], and then at [2] we will access entries in this buffer up to (td-&gt;xsize - 1) * (td-&gt;ysize - 1) + rle_raw_size / 2, which may exceed rle_raw_size.




We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59732 | Heap-buffer-overflow write in FFmpeg EXR dwa_uncompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59732</link><description>When decoding an OpenEXR file that uses DWAA or DWAB compression, there's an implicit assumption that the height and width are divisible by 8.

If the height or width of the image is not divisible by 8, the copy loops at [0] and [1] will continue to write until the next multiple of 8.

The buffer td-&gt;uncompressed_data is allocated in decode_block based on the precise height and width of the image, so the "rounded-up" multiple of 8 in the copy loop can exceed the buffer bounds, and the write block starting at [2] can corrupt following heap memory.



We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59733 | Heap-buffer-overflow write in FFmpeg EXR dwa_uncompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59733</link><description>When decoding an OpenEXR file that uses DWAA or DWAB compression, there's an implicit assumption that all image channels have the same pixel type (and size), and that if there are four channels, the first four are "B", "G", "R" and "A". The channel parsing code can be found in decode_header. The buffer td-&gt;uncompressed_data is allocated in decode_block based on the xsize, ysize and computed current_channel_offset.

The function dwa_uncompress then assumes at [5] that if there are 4 channels, these are "B", "G", "R" and "A", and in the calculations at [6] and [7] that all channels are of the same type, which matches the type of the main color channels.

If we set the main color channels to a 4-byte type and add duplicate or unknown channels of the 2-byte EXR_HALF type, then the addition at [7] will increment the pointer by 4-bytes * xsize * nb_channels, which will exceed the allocated buffer.





We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59734 | Heap-buffer-overflow write in FFmpeg SANM process_ftch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59734</link><description>It is possible to cause an use-after-free write in SANM decoding with a carefully crafted animation using subversion &lt;2.

When a STOR chunk is present, a subsequent FOBJ chunk will be saved in ctx-&gt;stored_frame. Stored frames can later be referenced by FTCH chunks. For files using subversion &lt; 2, the undecoded frame is stored, and decoded again when the FTCH chunks are parsed. However, in process_frame_obj if the frame has an invalid size, there’s an early return, with a value of 0. 

This causes the code in decode_frame to still store the raw frame buffer into ctx-&gt;stored_frame. Leaving ctx-&gt;has_dimensions set to false.

A subsequent chunk with type FTCH would call process_ftch and decode that frame obj again, adding to the top/left values and calling process_frame_obj again.
Given that we never set ctx-&gt;have_dimensions before, this time we set the dimensions, calling init_buffers, which can reallocate the buffer in ctx-&gt;stored_frame, freeing the previous one. However, the GetByteContext object gb still holds a reference to the old buffer.




Finally, when the code tries to decode the frame, codecs that accept a GetByteContext as a parameter will trigger a use-after-free read when using gb.

GetByteContext is only used for reading bytes, so at most one could read invalid data. There are no heap allocations between the free and when the object is accessed. However, upon returning to process_ftch, the code restores the original values for top/left in stored_frame, writing 4 bytes to the freed data at offset 6, potentially corrupting the allocator’s metadata.

This issue can be triggered just by probing whether a file has the sanm format.







We recommend upgrading to version 8.0 or beyond.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11326 | Tenda AC18 WifiMacFilterSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11326</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19(6318). This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/WifiMacFilterSet. Executing manipulation of the argument wifi_chkHz can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11325 | Tenda AC18 fast_setting_pppoe_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11325</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19(6318). Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/fast_setting_pppoe_set. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58579 | Username Disclosure Through Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58579</link><description>Due to a lack of authentication, it is possible for an unauthenticated user to request data from this endpoint, making the application vulnerable for user enumeration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58584 | Plain Text Transmission of Username and Password in the URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58584</link><description>In the HTTP request, the username and password are transferred directly in the URL as parameters. However, URLs can be stored in various systems such as server logs, browser histories or proxy servers. As a result, there is a high risk that this sensitive data will be disclosed unintentionally.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58585 | Sensitive Information Disclosure Through Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58585</link><description>Multiple endpoints with sensitive information do not require authentication, making the application susceptible to information gathering.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58586 | User Enumeration by excessive error output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58586</link><description>For failed login attempts, the application returns different error messages depending on whether the login failed due to an incorrect password or a non-existing username. This allows an attacker to guess usernames until they find an existing one.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58587 | Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58587</link><description>The application does not implement sufficient measures to prevent multiple failed authentication attempts within a short time frame, making it possible for an attacker to guess user credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58589 | Information Disclosure Through Stacktrace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58589</link><description>When an error occurs in the application a full stacktrace is provided to the user. The stacktrace lists class and method names as well as other internal information. An attacker thus receives information about the technology used and the structure of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58590 | Path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58590</link><description>It's possible to brute force folders and files, what can be used by an attacker to steal sensitve information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58591 | Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58591</link><description>A remote, unauthorized attacker can brute force folders and files and read them like private keys or configurations, making the application vulnerable for gathering sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58578 | Unlimited user creation by authorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58578</link><description>A user with the appropriate authorization can create any number of user accounts via an API endpoint using a POST request. There are no quotas, checking mechanisms or restrictions to limit the creation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58580 | Injection via log file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58580</link><description>An API  endpoint  allows  arbitrary  log  entries  to  be  created  via  POST request.  Without sufficient  validation  of the  input data, an attacker  can create manipulated log entries and thus falsify or dilute logs, for example.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58581 | Information Disclosure Through Stacktrace-/MQTT/Config/changeAll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58581</link><description>When an error occurs in the application a full stacktrace is  provided to the user. The stacktrace lists class and method names as well as other internal information. An attacker can thus obtain information about the technology used and the structure of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58582 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption via log file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58582</link><description>If a user tries to login but the provided credentials are incorrect a log is created. The data for this POST requests is not validated and it’s possible to send giant payloads which are then logged.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58583 | User Enumeration with prefilled information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58583</link><description>The  application  provides  access  to  a  login  protected  H2  database for  caching  purposes. The username is prefilled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9914 | Authentication bypass with local user database</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9914</link><description>The credentials of the users stored in the system's local database can be used for the log in, making it possible for an attacker to gain unauthorized access. This could potentially affect the confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11324 | Tenda AC18 setNotUpgrade stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11324</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19(6318). Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/setNotUpgrade. Such manipulation of the argument newVersion leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9913 | Cross Site Scripting: Session Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9913</link><description>JavaScript can be ran inside the address bar via the dashboard "Open in new Tab" Button, making the application vulnerable to session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11323 | UTT 1250GW formUserStatusRemark strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11323</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 1250GW up to v2v3.2.2-200710. Affected is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formUserStatusRemark. This manipulation of the argument Username causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9703 | Ultimate Addons for Elementor Lite &amp;lt; 2.5.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9703</link><description>The Ultimate Addons for Elementor (Formerly Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder) WordPress plugin before 2.5.0 does not sanitize SVG file contents when uploaded through the xmlrpc.php endpoint using base64 encode, leading to a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9710 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt; 2.5.3 - Unauthenticated Stored-XSS via Comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9710</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery WordPress plugin before 2.5.3 does not properly handle HTML tag attributes modifications, potentially allowing unauthenticated attackers to abuse the functionality to include event handlers and conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11322 | Mangati NovoSGA User Creation new weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11322</link><description>A flaw has been found in Mangati NovoSGA up to 2.2.12. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /novosga.users/new of the component User Creation Page. Executing manipulation of the argument Senha/Confirmação da senha can lead to weak password requirements. The attack can be launched remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 05:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57781 | The installers of DENSO TEN drive recorder viewer contain an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57781</link><description>The installers of DENSO TEN drive recorder viewer contain an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with the privilege of the user invoking the installer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 05:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11321 | zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education WrongBookController.java authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11321</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education up to 1.0.4. The affected element is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/com/education/api/controller/student/WrongBookController.java. Performing manipulation of the argument subjectId results in authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 05:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11320 | zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education UploadController.java uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11320</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in zhuimengshaonian wisdom-education up to 1.0.4. Impacted is the function uploadFile of the file src/main/java/com/education/core/controller/UploadController.java. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11319 | nahiduddinahammed Hospital-Management-System-Website delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11319</link><description>A weakness has been identified in nahiduddinahammed Hospital-Management-System-Website up to e6562429e14b2f88bd2139cae16e87b965024097. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /delete.php. This manipulation of the argument ai causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 04:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11318 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 uploadWxFile.do unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11318</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file uploadWxFile.do. The manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 03:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11317 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findSingConfigPage.do findRolePage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11317</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. This affects the function findRolePage of the file findSingConfigPage.do. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11316 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findCategoryPage.do findCategoryPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11316</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function findCategoryPage of the file findCategoryPage.do. Executing manipulation of the argument tenantId can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11315 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findUserPage.do findUserPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11315</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function findUserPage of the file findUserPage.do. Performing manipulation of the argument sort results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11313 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findRolePage.do findRolePage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11313</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. This impacts the function findRolePage of the file findRolePage.do. This manipulation of the argument sort causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11314 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findSingConfigPage.do findRolePage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11314</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. Affected is the function findRolePage of the file findSingConfigPage.do. Such manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29192 | Flowise before 3.0.5 allows XSS via a FORM element and an INPUT element when an admin views the chat log.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29192</link><description>Flowise before 3.0.5 allows XSS via a FORM element and an INPUT element when an admin views the chat log.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50538 | Flowise before 3.0.5 allows XSS via an IFRAME element when an admin views the chat log.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50538</link><description>Flowise before 3.0.5 allows XSS via an IFRAME element when an admin views the chat log.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11312 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findModulePage.do findModulePage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11312</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. This affects the function findModulePage of the file findModulePage.do. The manipulation of the argument sort results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11311 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findTenantPage.do findTenantPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11311</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. The impacted element is the function findTenantPage of the file findTenantPage.do. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11310 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findFileServerPage.do findFileServerPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11310</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. The affected element is the function findFileServerPage of the file findFileServerPage.do. Executing manipulation of the argument sort can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 23:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11309 | Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 findDeptPage.do doFilter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11309</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tipray 厦门天锐科技股份有限公司 Data Leakage Prevention System 天锐数据泄露防护系统 1.0. Impacted is the function doFilter of the file findDeptPage.do. Performing manipulation of the argument sort results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 23:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11308 | Vanderlande Baggage 360 messages cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11308</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Vanderlande Baggage 360 7.0.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api-addons/v1/messages. Such manipulation of the argument Message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 22:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11306 | qianfox FoxCMS Search cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11306</link><description>A vulnerability was found in qianfox FoxCMS up to 1.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php/Search of the component Search Page. The manipulation of the argument keyword results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 22:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11305 | UTT HiPER 840G formTaskEdit strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11305</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT HiPER 840G up to 3.1.1-190328. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formTaskEdit. The manipulation of the argument txtMin2 leads to buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11304 | CodeCanyon/ui-lib Mentor LMS API cross-domain policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11304</link><description>A flaw has been found in CodeCanyon/ui-lib Mentor LMS up to 1.1.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component API. Executing manipulation can lead to permissive cross-domain policy with untrusted domains. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11303 | Belkin F9K1015 mp command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11303</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/mp. Performing manipulation of the argument command results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11302 | Belkin F9K1015 formWpsStart buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11302</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/formWpsStart. Such manipulation of the argument pinCode leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11301 | Belkin F9K1015 formWlanSetupWPS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11301</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/formWlanSetupWPS. This manipulation of the argument webpage causes buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11300 | Belkin F9K1015 formWlanMP buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11300</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/formWlanMP. The manipulation of the argument ateFunc results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11299 | Belkin F9K1015 formWanTcpipSetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11299</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/formWanTcpipSetup. The manipulation of the argument pppUserName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11298 | Belkin F9K1015 formSetWanStatic command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11298</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/formSetWanStatic. Executing manipulation of the argument m_wan_ipaddr can lead to command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11297 | Belkin F9K1015 formSetLanguage buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/formSetLanguage. Performing manipulation of the argument webpage results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11296 | Belkin F9K1015 formPPTPSetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11296</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/formPPTPSetup. Such manipulation of the argument pptpUserName leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11295 | Belkin F9K1015 formPPPoESetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11295</link><description>A flaw has been found in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/formPPPoESetup. This manipulation of the argument pppUserName causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11294 | Belkin F9K1015 formL2TPSetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11294</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/formL2TPSetup. The manipulation of the argument L2TPUserName results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11293 | Belkin F9K1015 formConnectionSetting buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11293</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/formConnectionSetting. The manipulation of the argument max_Conn leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11292 | Belkin F9K1015 formBSSetSitesurvey command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11292</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Belkin F9K1015 1.00.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/formBSSetSitesurvey. Executing manipulation of the argument wan_ipaddr can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11291 | ixmaps website2017 HTTP GET Request map.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11291</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in ixmaps website2017 up to 0c71cffa0162186bc057a76766bc97e9f5a3a2d0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /map.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument trid results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11290 | CRMEB JWT HMAC Secret hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11290</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CRMEB up to 5.6.1. This affects an unknown function of the component JWT HMAC Secret Handler. Such manipulation of the argument secret with the input default leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 11:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11289 | westboy CicadasCMS Template Management TemplateFileServiceImpl.java save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11289</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in westboy CicadasCMS up to 2431154dac8d0735e04f1fd2a3c3556668fc8dab. The impacted element is the function Save of the file src/main/java/com/zhiliao/common/template/TemplateFileServiceImpl.java of the component Template Management Page. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8917 | Path Traversal Leading to Remote Code Execution in allegroai/clearml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8917</link><description>A vulnerability in allegroai/clearml version v2.0.1 allows for path traversal due to improper handling of symbolic and hard links in the `safe_extract` function. This flaw can lead to arbitrary file writes outside the intended directory, potentially resulting in remote code execution if critical files are overwritten.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8406 | Path Traversal in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8406</link><description>ZenML version 0.83.1 is affected by a path traversal vulnerability in the `PathMaterializer` class. The `load` function uses `is_path_within_directory` to validate files during `data.tar.gz` extraction, which fails to effectively detect symbolic and hard links. This vulnerability can lead to arbitrary file writes, potentially resulting in arbitrary command execution if critical files are overwritten.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 09:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11288 | CRMEB GET Parameter product sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11288</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CRMEB up to 5.6. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adminapi/product/product of the component GET Parameter Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument cate_id results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 07:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11287 | samanhappy MCPHub sseService.ts handleSseConnectionfunction improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11287</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in samanhappy MCPHub up to 0.9.10. This vulnerability affects the function handleSseConnectionfunction of the file src/services/sseService.ts. Such manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 07:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11286 | samanhappy MCPHub MCPRouter Service serverController.ts server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11286</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in samanhappy MCPHub up to 0.9.10. This affects an unknown part of the file src/controllers/serverController.ts of the component MCPRouter Service. This manipulation of the argument baseUrl causes server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11285 | samanhappy MCPHub serverController.ts os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11285</link><description>A vulnerability was found in samanhappy MCPHub up to 0.9.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file src/controllers/serverController.ts. The manipulation of the argument command/args results in os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11284 | Zytec Dalian Zhuoyun Technology Central Authentication Service HTTP Header git hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11284</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Zytec Dalian Zhuoyun Technology Central Authentication Service 3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php/auth/Ops/git of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Authorization leads to use of hard-coded password. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11283 | Frappe LMS Course cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11283</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Frappe LMS 2.35.0. This affects an unknown function of the component Course Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument Description can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was informed early about a total of four security issues and confirmed that those have been fixed. However, the release notes on GitHub do not mention them.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11282 | Frappe LMS Incomplete Fix CVE-2025-55006 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11282</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Frappe LMS 2.34.x/2.35.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Incomplete Fix CVE-2025-55006. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The affected component should be upgraded. The vendor was informed early about a total of four security issues and confirmed that those have been fixed. However, the release notes on GitHub do not mention them.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 04:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11281 | Frappe LMS Unpublished Course courses access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11281</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Frappe LMS 2.35.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /courses/ of the component Unpublished Course Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. You should upgrade the affected component. The vendor was informed early about a total of four security issues and confirmed that those have been fixed. However, the release notes on GitHub do not mention them.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 04:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11280 | Frappe LMS Assignment Picture files direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11280</link><description>A flaw has been found in Frappe LMS 2.35.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /files/ of the component Assignment Picture Handler. This manipulation causes direct request. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was informed early about a total of four security issues and confirmed that those have been fixed. However, the release notes on GitHub do not mention them.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 03:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61882 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61882</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 03:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11279 | Axosoft Scrum and Bug Tracking Add Work Item csv injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11279</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Axosoft Scrum and Bug Tracking 22.1.1.11545. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Add Work Item Page. The manipulation of the argument Title results in csv injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 03:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11278 | AllStarLink Supermon AllMon2 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11278</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in AllStarLink Supermon up to 6.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component AllMon2. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 02:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11277 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp Q3DLoader.cpp InternReadFile heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11277</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 6.0.2. This affects the function Q3DImporter::InternReadFile of the file assimp/code/AssetLib/Q3D/Q3DLoader.cpp. Executing manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 02:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11276 | Rebuild Comment/Guestbook cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11276</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Rebuild up to 4.1.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Comment/Guestbook. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 4.1.4 can resolve this issue. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. According to the researcher the vendor has confirmed the flaw and fix in a private issue response.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11275 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp OpenDDLParserUtils.h getNextSeparator heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11275</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 6.0.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ODDLParser::getNextSeparator in the library assimp/contrib/openddlparser/include/openddlparser/OpenDDLParserUtils.h. Such manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11274 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp Q3DLoader.cpp InternReadFile allocation of resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11274</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 6.0.2. Affected is the function Q3DImporter::InternReadFile of the file assimp/code/AssetLib/Q3D/Q3DLoader.cpp. This manipulation causes allocation of resources. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 01:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>