<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:26:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-20570 | Insufficient verification of data authenticity in
the configuration state machine may allow a local attacker to potentially load
arbitrary b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20570</link><description>Insufficient verification of data authenticity in
the configuration state machine may allow a local attacker to potentially load
arbitrary bitstreams.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26562 | In Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15 and 9.0, a closed account (with 2FA and generated passwords) can send e-mail messages when configured f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26562</link><description>In Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15 and 9.0, a closed account (with 2FA and generated passwords) can send e-mail messages when configured for Imap/smtp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45206 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. Through the help document endpoint in webmail, an attacker can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45206</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. Through the help document endpoint in webmail, an attacker can inject JavaScript or HTML code that leads to cross-site scripting (XSS). (Adding an adequate message to avoid malicious code will mitigate this issue.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45207 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. An attacker can send a PDF document through mail that contains ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45207</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. An attacker can send a PDF document through mail that contains malicious JavaScript. While previewing this file in webmail in the Chrome browser, the stored XSS payload is executed. (This has been mitigated by sanitising the JavaScript code present in a PDF document.)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48432 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. XSS, with resultant session stealing, can occur via JavaScript ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48432</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 8.8.15, 9.0, and 10.0. XSS, with resultant session stealing, can occur via JavaScript code in a link (for a webmail redirection endpoint) within en email message, e.g., if a victim clicks on that link within Zimbra webmail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22923 | SQL injection vulnerability in adv radius v.2.2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22923</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in adv radius v.2.2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1140 | Twister Antivirus v8.17 - Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1140</link><description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability by triggering the 0x801120B8 IOCTL code of the filmfd.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23439 | Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 - Arbitrary Memory Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23439</link><description>Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 is vulnerable to an Arbitrary Memory Read vulnerability by triggering the 0x22201B, 0x22201F, 0x222023, 0x222027 ,0x22202B, 0x22202F, 0x22203F, 0x222057 and 0x22205B IOCTL codes of the Vba32m64.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23440 | Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 - Arbitrary Memory Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23440</link><description>Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 is vulnerable to an Arbitrary Memory Read vulnerability. The 0x22200B IOCTL code of the Vba32m64.sys driver allows to read up to 0x802 of memory from ar arbitrary user-supplied pointer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1096 | Twister Antivirus v8.17 - Elevation of Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1096</link><description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 allows Elevation of Privileges on the computer where it's installed by triggering the 0x80112067, 0x801120CB and 0x801120CC IOCTL codes of the fildds.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:06:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1163 | Path Traversal in mbloch/mapshaper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1163</link><description>Path Traversal in GitHub repository mbloch/mapshaper prior to 0.6.44.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4408 | Parsing large DNS messages may cause excessive CPU load</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4408</link><description>The DNS message parsing code in `named` includes a section whose computational complexity is overly high. It does not cause problems for typical DNS traffic, but crafted queries and responses may cause excessive CPU load on the affected `named` instance by exploiting this flaw. This issue affects both authoritative servers and recursive resolvers.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.16.45, 9.18.0 through 9.18.21, 9.19.0 through 9.19.19, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5517 | Querying RFC 1918 reverse zones may cause an assertion failure when &amp;quot;nxdomain-redirect&amp;quot; is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5517</link><description>A flaw in query-handling code can cause `named` to exit prematurely with an assertion failure when:

  - `nxdomain-redirect &lt;domain&gt;;` is configured, and
  - the resolver receives a PTR query for an RFC 1918 address that would normally result in an authoritative NXDOMAIN response.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.12.0 through 9.16.45, 9.18.0 through 9.18.21, 9.19.0 through 9.19.19, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5679 | Enabling both DNS64 and serve-stale may cause an assertion failure during recursive resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5679</link><description>A bad interaction between DNS64 and serve-stale may cause `named` to crash with an assertion failure during recursive resolution, when both of these features are enabled.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.12 through 9.16.45, 9.18.0 through 9.18.21, 9.19.0 through 9.19.19, 9.16.12-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5680 | Cleaning an ECS-enabled cache may cause excessive CPU load</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5680</link><description>If a resolver cache has a very large number of ECS records stored for the same name, the process of cleaning the cache database node for this name can significantly impair query performance. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.21-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6516 | Specific recursive query patterns may lead to an out-of-memory condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6516</link><description>To keep its cache database efficient, `named` running as a recursive resolver occasionally attempts to clean up the database. It uses several methods, including some that are asynchronous: a small chunk of memory pointing to the cache element that can be cleaned up is first allocated and then queued for later processing. It was discovered that if the resolver is continuously processing query patterns triggering this type of cache-database maintenance, `named` may not be able to handle the cleanup events in a timely manner. This in turn enables the list of queued cleanup events to grow infinitely large over time, allowing the configured `max-cache-size` limit to be significantly exceeded.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.0 through 9.16.45 and 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.45-S1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24781 | Hima: Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in multiple products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24781</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability to DoS the affected devices through excessive traffic on a single ethernet port.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24782 | HIMA: Origin Validation Error in multiple products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24782</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can send a ping request from one network to another through an error in the origin verification even though the ports are separated by VLAN.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1309 | Resource Consumption Identified in NTP before 4.2.4p8 and 4.2.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1309</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Honeywell Niagara Framework on Windows, Linux, QNX allows Content Spoofing.This issue affects Niagara Framework: before Niagara AX 3.8.1, before Niagara 4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6072 | A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix Central Management (CM) prior to 9.1.3.97129 allows a remote authenticated attacker to craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6072</link><description>A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix Central Management (CM) prior to 9.1.3.97129 allows a remote authenticated attacker to craft CM dashboard internal requests causing arbitrary content to be injected into the response when accessing the CM dashboard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1157 | The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button URL in all versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1157</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1159 | The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1159</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1160 | The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon Link in all versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1160</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon Link in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48363 | A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48363</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Route Control V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V18 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V19 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.4 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.5 (All versions &lt; V7.5 SP2 Update 15), SIMATIC WinCC V8.0 (All versions &lt; V8.0 SP4). The implementation of the RPC (Remote Procedure call) &#13;
communication protocol in the affected products do not &#13;
properly handle certain unorganized RPC messages. An &#13;
attacker could use this vulnerability to cause a denial of service &#13;
condition in the RPC server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48364 | A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48364</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OpenPCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Route Control V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V18 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V19 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.4 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.5 (All versions &lt; V7.5 SP2 Update 15), SIMATIC WinCC V8.0 (All versions &lt; V8.0 SP4). The implementation of the RPC (Remote Procedure call) communication protocol in the affected products do not properly handle certain malformed RPC messages. An attacker could use this vulnerability to cause a denial of service condition in the RPC server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49125 | A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.263), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.252), Parasolid V36...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49125</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.263), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.252), Parasolid V36.0 (All versions &lt; V36.0.198). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted files containing XT format. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50236 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The affected product is vulnerable due to weak file and folder permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50236</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The affected product is vulnerable due to weak file and folder permissions in the installation path. An attacker with local access could exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51440 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 343-1 (6GK7343-1EX30-0XE0) (All versions), SIMATIC CP 343-1 Lean (6GK7343-1CX10-0XE0) (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51440</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 343-1 (6GK7343-1EX30-0XE0) (All versions), SIMATIC CP 343-1 Lean (6GK7343-1CX10-0XE0) (All versions), SIPLUS NET CP 343-1 (6AG1343-1EX30-7XE0) (All versions), SIPLUS NET CP 343-1 Lean (6AG1343-1CX10-2XE0) (All versions). Affected products incorrectly validate TCP sequence numbers. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to create a denial of service condition by injecting spoofed TCP RST packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22042 | A vulnerability has been identified in Unicam FX (All versions). The windows installer agent used in affected product contains incorrect use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22042</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Unicam FX (All versions). The windows installer agent used in affected product contains incorrect use of privileged APIs that trigger the Windows Console Host (conhost.exe) as a child process with SYSTEM privileges. This could be exploited by an attacker to perform a local privilege escalation attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22043 | A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.251), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.170). The affected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22043</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Parasolid V35.0 (All versions &lt; V35.0.251), Parasolid V35.1 (All versions &lt; V35.1.170). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted XT files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23795 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23795</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted WRL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23796 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23796</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected application is vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23797 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23797</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain a stack overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23798 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23798</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain a stack overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23799 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23799</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23800 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23800</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23801 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23801</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23802 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23802</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted SPP files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23803 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23803</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0007). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted SPP file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23804 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23804</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2201 (All versions &lt; V2201.0012), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0006). The affected applications contain a stack overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PSOBJ files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23810 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application is vulnerable to SQL injection. This co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23810</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application is vulnerable to SQL injection. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the server database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23811 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application allows users to upload arbitrary files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23811</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application allows users to upload arbitrary files via TFTP. This could allow an attacker to upload malicious firmware images or other files, that could potentially lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23812 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application incorrectly neutralizes special element...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23812</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V2.0 SP1). The affected application incorrectly neutralizes special elements when creating a report which could lead to command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23813 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The REST API endpoints of doorsconnector of the affected product lacks p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23813</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion ALM (All versions). The REST API endpoints of doorsconnector of the affected product lacks proper authentication. An unauthenticated attacker could access the endpoints, and potentially execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23816 | A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence Perpetual Large (9DE5110-8CA13-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23816</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Location Intelligence Perpetual Large (9DE5110-8CA13-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence Perpetual Medium (9DE5110-8CA12-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence Perpetual Non-Prod (9DE5110-8CA10-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence Perpetual Small (9DE5110-8CA11-1AX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Large (9DE5110-8CA13-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Medium (9DE5110-8CA12-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Non-Prod (9DE5110-8CA10-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3), Location Intelligence SUS Small (9DE5110-8CA11-1BX0) (All versions &lt; V4.3). Affected products use a hard-coded secret value for the computation of a Keyed-Hash Message Authentication Code. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain full administrative access to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24920 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24920</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted Catia MODEL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-21710)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24921 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24921</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted Catia MODEL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-21712)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24922 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24922</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted Catia MODEL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-21715)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24923 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000), Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0001). The affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24923</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2401.0000), Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0001). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted Catia MODEL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-22055)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24924 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24924</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application contains an out of bounds write past the end of an allocated buffer while parsing a specially crafted Catia MODEL file. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-22059)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24925 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to uninitialized ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24925</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2306.0000). The affected application is vulnerable to uninitialized pointer access while parsing specially crafted Catia MODEL files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-22060)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22445 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain an OS command injection vulnerability. A remote high privileged at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22445</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain an OS command injection vulnerability. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to a system take over by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22454 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain a weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten passwords. A remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22454</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version 19.15 and prior versions, contain a weak password recovery mechanism for forgotten passwords. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access to the application with privileges of the compromised account. The attacker could retrieve the reset password token without authorization and then perform the password change</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6815 | Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-R Series Safety CPU R08/16/32/120SFCPU all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6815</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-R Series Safety CPU R08/16/32/120SFCPU all versions and MELSEC iQ-R Series SIL2 Process CPU R08/16/32/120PSFCPU all versions allows a remote authenticated attacker who has logged into the product as a non-administrator user to disclose the credentials (user ID and password) of a user with a lower access level than the attacker by sending a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 06:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25914 | WordPress SMTP Mail Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25914</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Photoboxone SMTP Mail.This issue affects SMTP Mail: from n/a through 1.3.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 05:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21491 | Versions of the package svix before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to an issue in the verify function where signatures o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21491</link><description>Versions of the package svix before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to an issue in the verify function where signatures of different lengths are incorrectly compared. An attacker can bypass signature verification by providing a shorter signature that matches the beginning of the actual signature.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;The attacker would need to know a victim uses the Rust library for verification,no easy way to automatically check that; and uses webhooks by a service that uses Svix, and then figure out a way to craft a malicious payload that will actually include all of the correct identifiers needed to trick the receivers to cause actual issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 05:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48623 | The Cpanel::JSON::XS package before 4.33 for Perl performs out-of-bounds accesses in a way that allows attackers to obtain sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48623</link><description>The Cpanel::JSON::XS package before 4.33 for Perl performs out-of-bounds accesses in a way that allows attackers to obtain sensitive information or cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52431 | The Plack::Middleware::XSRFBlock package before 0.0.19 for Perl allows attackers to bypass a CSRF protection mechanism via an empty form val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52431</link><description>The Plack::Middleware::XSRFBlock package before 0.0.19 for Perl allows attackers to bypass a CSRF protection mechanism via an empty form value and an empty cookie (if signed cookies are disabled).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22024 | An XML external entity or XXE vulnerability in the SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x), Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x) and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22024</link><description>An XML external entity or XXE vulnerability in the SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x), Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x) and ZTA gateways which allows an attacker to access certain restricted resources without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22129 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Companion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22129</link><description>SAP Companion - version &lt;3.1.38, has a URL with parameter that could be vulnerable to XSS attack. The attacker could send a malicious link to a user that would possibly allow an attacker to retrieve the sensitive information and cause minor impact on the integrity of the web application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24741 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Master Data Governance Material</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24741</link><description>SAP Master Data Governance for Material Data - versions 618, 619, 620, 621, 622, 800, 801, 802, 803, 804, does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to read some sensitive information but no impact to integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25643 | Missing authorization check in SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Requests)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25643</link><description>The SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Request) - version 605, does not perform the necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user which may result in an escalation of privileges. It is possible to manipulate the URLs of data requests to access information that the user should not have access to. There is no impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47218 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47218</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50358 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50358</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QTS 4.3.6.2665 build 20240131 and later
QTS 4.3.4.2675 build 20240131 and later
QTS 4.3.3.2644 build 20240131 and later
QTS 4.2.6 build 20240131 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24742 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24742</link><description>SAP CRM WebClient UI - version S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to integrity of the application data after successful exploitation. There is no impact on confidentiality and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24743 | XXE vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Guided Procedures)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24743</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures) - version 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious request with a crafted XML file over the network, which when parsed will enable him to access sensitive files and data but not modify them. There are expansion limits in place so that availability is not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25642 | Improper Certificate Validation in SAP Cloud Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25642</link><description>Due to improper validation of certificate in SAP Cloud Connector - version 2.0, attacker can impersonate the genuine servers to interact with SCC breaking the mutual authentication. Hence, the attacker can intercept the request to view/modify sensitive information. There is no impact on the availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24740 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP (SAP Kernel)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24740</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP) - versions KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.93, KERNEL 7.94, KRNL64UC 7.53, under certain conditions, allows an attacker to access information which could otherwise be restricted with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22130 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP CRM WebClient UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22130</link><description>Print preview option in SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, S4FND 108, WEBCUIF 700, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 730, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the appliaction data after successful exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22131 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP ABA (Application Basis)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22131</link><description>In SAP ABA (Application Basis) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75I, an attacker authenticated as a user with a remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface. This allows the attacker to use the interface to invoke an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user/business data and can make the entire system unavailable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22132 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP IDES Systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22132</link><description>SAP IDES ECC-systems contain code that permits the execution of arbitrary program code of user's choice.An attacker can therefore control the behaviour of the system by executing malicious code which can potentially escalate privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24739 | Missing authorization check in SAP BAM (Bank Account Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24739</link><description>SAP Bank Account Management (BAM) allows an authenticated user with restricted access to use functions which can result in escalation of privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22128 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Business Client for HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22128</link><description>SAP NWBC for HTML - versions SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, SAP_UI 758, SAP_BASIS 700, SAP_BASIS 701, SAP_BASIS 702, SAP_BASIS 731, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can inject malicious javascript to cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the application data after successful exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22126 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (User Admin Application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22126</link><description>The User Admin application of SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, insufficiently validates and improperly encodes the incoming URL parameters before including them into the redirect URL. This results in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and mild impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:04:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49339 | Ellucian Banner 9.17 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) via a modified bannerId to the /StudentSelfService/ssb/studentCard/retri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49339</link><description>Ellucian Banner 9.17 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) via a modified bannerId to the /StudentSelfService/ssb/studentCard/retrieveData endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42374 | An issue in mystenlabs Sui Blockchain before v.1.6.3 allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42374</link><description>An issue in mystenlabs Sui Blockchain before v.1.6.3 allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a crafted compressed script to the Sui node component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52059 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payloa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52059</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Description text field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52060 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to arbitrarily edit user profile information via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52060</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Gestsup v3.2.46 allows attackers to arbitrarily edit user profile information via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25407 | SteVe v3.6.0 was discovered to use predictable transaction ID's when receiving a StartTransaction request. This vulnerability can allow atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25407</link><description>SteVe v3.6.0 was discovered to use predictable transaction ID's when receiving a StartTransaction request. This vulnerability can allow attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by using the predicted transaction ID's to terminate other transactions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28018 | HCL Connections s vulnerable to possible denial of service for certain users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28018</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by improper validation on certain requests. Using a specially-crafted request an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause denial of service for affected users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1454 | Opensc: memory use after free in authentic driver when updating token info</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1454</link><description>The use-after-free vulnerability was found in the AuthentIC driver in OpenSC packages, occuring in the card enrolment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrols or modifies cards. An attacker must have physical access to the computer system and requires a crafted USB device or smart card to present the system with specially crafted responses to the APDUs, which are considered high complexity and low severity. This manipulation can allow for compromised card management operations during enrolment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52430 | The caddy-security plugin 1.1.20 for Caddy allows reflected XSS via a GET request to a URL that contains an XSS payload and begins with eith...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52430</link><description>The caddy-security plugin 1.1.20 for Caddy allows reflected XSS via a GET request to a URL that contains an XSS payload and begins with either a /admin or /settings/mfa/delete/ substring.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24826 | Out-of-bounds read in QuickTimeVideo::NikonTagsDecoder in Exiv2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24826</link><description>Exiv2 is a command-line utility and C++ library for reading, writing, deleting, and modifying the metadata of image files. An out-of-bounds read was found in Exiv2 version v0.28.1. The vulnerable function, `QuickTimeVideo::NikonTagsDecoder`, was new in v0.28.0, so Exiv2 versions before v0.28 are _not_ affected. The out-of-bounds read is triggered when Exiv2 is used to read the metadata of a crafted video file. In most cases this out of bounds read will result in a crash. This bug is fixed in version v0.28.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25112 | Denial of service due to unbounded recursion in QuickTimeVideo::multipleEntriesDecoder in Exiv2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25112</link><description>Exiv2 is a command-line utility and C++ library for reading, writing, deleting, and modifying the metadata of image files. A denial-of-service was found in Exiv2 version v0.28.1: an unbounded recursion can cause Exiv2 to crash by exhausting the stack. The vulnerable function, `QuickTimeVideo::multipleEntriesDecoder`, was new in v0.28.0, so Exiv2 versions before v0.28 are _not_ affected. The denial-of-service is triggered when Exiv2 is used to read the metadata of a crafted video file. This bug is fixed in version v0.28.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23762 | Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Content Manager feature in Gambio 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via upload of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23762</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Content Manager feature in Gambio 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via upload of crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23763 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Gambio through 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via crafted GET request using modifiers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23763</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Gambio through 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via crafted GET request using modifiers[attribute][] parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23761 | Server Side Template Injection in Gambio 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted smarty email template.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23761</link><description>Server Side Template Injection in Gambio 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted smarty email template.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23760 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Gambio 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via error-handler.log.json and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23760</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Gambio 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via error-handler.log.json and legacy-error-handler.log.txt under the webroot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23759 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in Gambio through 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via "search" parameter of the Parcelshopf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23759</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data in Gambio through 4.9.2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via "search" parameter of the Parcelshopfinder/AddAddressBookEntry" function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24337 | CSV Injection vulnerability in '/members/moremember.pl' and '/admin/aqbudgets.pl' endpoints in Koha Library Management System version 23.05....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24337</link><description>CSV Injection vulnerability in '/members/moremember.pl' and '/admin/aqbudgets.pl' endpoints in Koha Library Management System version 23.05.05 and earlier allows attackers to to inject DDE commands into csv exports via the 'Budget' and 'Patrons Member' components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1250 | Improper Privilege Management in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1250</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. When a user is assigned a custom role with manage_group_access_tokens permission, they may be able to create group access tokens with Owner privileges, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:48:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1459 | Undertow: directory traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1459</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in Undertow. This issue may allow a remote attacker to append a specially-crafted sequence to an HTTP request for an application deployed to JBoss EAP, which may permit access to privileged or restricted files and directories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23833 | OpenRefine JDBC Attack Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23833</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source power tool for working with messy data and improving it. A jdbc attack vulnerability exists in OpenRefine(version&lt;=3.7.7) where an attacker may construct a JDBC query which may read files on the host filesystem. Due to the newer MySQL driver library in the latest version of OpenRefine (8.0.30), there is no associated deserialization utilization point, so original code execution cannot be achieved, but attackers can use this vulnerability to read sensitive files on the target server. This issue has been addressed in version 3.7.8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25108 | Insufficient authorization allowing elevated access to resources in pixelfed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25108</link><description>Pixelfed is an open source photo sharing platform. When processing requests authorization was improperly and insufficiently checked, allowing attackers to access far more functionality than users intended, including to the administrative and moderator functionality of the Pixelfed server. This vulnerability affects every version of Pixelfed between v0.10.4 and v0.11.9, inclusive. A proof of concept of this vulnerability exists. This vulnerability affects every local user of a Pixelfed server, and can potentially affect the servers' ability to federate. Some user interaction is required to setup the conditions to be able to exercise the vulnerability, but the attacker could conduct this attack time-delayed manner, where user interaction is not actively required. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 0.11.11. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25110 | Azure IoT Platform Device SDK Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25110</link><description>The UAMQP is a general purpose C library for AMQP 1.0. During a call to open_get_offered_capabilities, a memory allocation may fail causing a use-after-free issue and if a client called it during connection communication it may cause a remote code execution. Users are advised to update the submodule with commit `30865c9c`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4437 | dbartholomae lambda-middleware frameguard JSON Mime-Type JsonDeserializer.ts redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4437</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in dbartholomae lambda-middleware frameguard up to 1.0.4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file packages/json-deserializer/src/JsonDeserializer.ts of the component JSON Mime-Type Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. Upgrading to version 1.1.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as f689404d830cbc1edd6a1018d3334ff5f44dc6a6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-253406 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-22506 | IBM Robotic Process Automation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22506</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation 21.0.2 contains a vulnerability that could allow user ids may be exposed across tenants.  IBM X-Force ID:  227293.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34309 | IBM CICS TX information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34309</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard and Advanced 11.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  229440.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22221 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains SQL Injection vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22221</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains SQL Injection vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22222 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_udoctor utility. An authenticated malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22222</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_udoctor utility. An authenticated malicious user with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22223 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_cbr utility. An authenticated malicious use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22223</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_cbr utility. An authenticated malicious user with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22226 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain a path traversal vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacker could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22226</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain a path traversal vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to gain unauthorized write access to the files stored on the server filesystem, with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22225 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22225</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22224 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_nas utility. An authenticated attacker could po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22224</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_nas utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, escaping the restricted shell and execute arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22230 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Cross-site scripting vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22230</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Cross-site scripting vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, stealing session information, masquerading as the affected user or carry out any actions that this user could perform, or to generally control the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22228 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cifssupport utility. An authenticated attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22228</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cifssupport utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, escaping the restricted shell and execute arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0164 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0164</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22227 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_dc utility. An authenticated attacker could pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22227</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_dc utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability execute commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0165 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_acldb_dump utility. An authenticated attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0165</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_acldb_dump utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0166 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_tcpdump utility. An authenticated attacker coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0166</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_tcpdump utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0167 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in the svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0167</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in the svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to overwrite arbitrary files on the file system with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0168 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Command Injection Vulnerability in svc_oscheck utility. An authenticated attacker could potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0168</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Command Injection Vulnerability in svc_oscheck utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to inject arbitrary operating system commands. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34311 | IBM CICS TX session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34311</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard and Advanced 11.1 could allow a user with physical access to the web browser to gain access to the user's session due to insufficiently protected credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  229446.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0169 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0169</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading users to download and execute malicious software crafted by this product's feature to compromise their systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0170 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cava utility. An authenticated attacker could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0170</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cava utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, escaping the restricted shell and execute arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34310 | IBM CICS TX information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34310</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard and Advanced 11.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  229441.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38714 | IBM DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38714</link><description>IBM DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.6 to 4.5.2 stores sensitive credential information that can be read by a privileged user.  IBM X-Force ID:  235060.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6036 | Web3 – Crypto wallet Login &amp;amp; NFT token gating &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6036</link><description>The Web3 WordPress plugin before 3.0.0 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass due to incorrect authentication checking in the login flow in functions 'handle_auth_request' and 'hadle_login_request'. This makes it possible for non authenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6081 | Chart.js for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2023.2 - Editor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting in New Chart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6081</link><description>The chartjs WordPress plugin through 2023.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6082 | Chart.js for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2023.2 - Editor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6082</link><description>The chartjs WordPress plugin through 2023.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6294 | popup-builder &amp;lt; 4.2.6 - Admin+ SSRF &amp;amp; File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6294</link><description>The Popup Builder WordPress plugin before 4.2.6 does not validate a parameter before making a request to it, which could allow users with the administrator role to perform SSRF attack in Multisite WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6499 | lasTunes &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6499</link><description>The lasTunes WordPress plugin through 3.6.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6501 | Splashscreen &amp;lt;= 0.20 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6501</link><description>The Splashscreen WordPress plugin through 0.20 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6591 | Popup Box Pro &amp;lt; 20.9.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6591</link><description>The Popup Box WordPress plugin before 20.9.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7233 | GigPress &amp;lt;= 2.3.29 - Admin+ Stored Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7233</link><description>The GigPress WordPress plugin through 2.3.29 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0248 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.4.0 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Posts Deletion and Document Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0248</link><description>The EazyDocs WordPress plugin before 2.4.0 re-introduced CVE-2023-6029 (https://wpscan.com/vulnerability/7a0aaf85-8130-4fd7-8f09-f8edc929597e/) in 2.3.8, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to delete arbitrary posts, as well as add and delete documents/sections. The issue was partially fixed in 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0250 | Analytics Insights for Google Analytics 4 &amp;lt; 6.3 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0250</link><description>The Analytics Insights for Google Analytics 4 (AIWP) WordPress plugin before 6.3 is vulnerable to Open Redirect due to insufficient validation on the redirect oauth2callback.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0420 | MapPress Maps for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.88.15 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0420</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin before 2.88.15 does not sanitize and escape the map title when outputting it back in the admin dashboard, allowing Contributors and above roles to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0421 | MapPress Maps for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.88.16 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Private/Draft Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0421</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin before 2.88.16 does not ensure that posts to be retrieve via an AJAX action is a public map, allowing unauthenticated users to read arbitrary private and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0566 | Smart Manager &amp;lt; 8.28.0 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0566</link><description>The Smart Manager WordPress plugin before 8.28.0 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25360 | A hidden interface in Motorola CX2L Router firmware v1.0.1 leaks information regarding the SystemWizardStatus component via sending a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25360</link><description>A hidden interface in Motorola CX2L Router firmware v1.0.1 leaks information regarding the SystemWizardStatus component via sending a crafted request to device_web_ip.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6681 | Jwcrypto: denail of service  via specifically crafted jwe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6681</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JWCrypto. This flaw allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) attack and possible password brute-force and dictionary attacks to be more resource-intensive. This issue can result in a large amount of computational consumption, causing a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 14:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1062 | 389-ds-base: a heap overflow leading to denail-of-servce while writing a value larger than 256 chars (in log_entry_attr)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1062</link><description>A heap overflow flaw was found in 389-ds-base. This issue leads to a denial of service when writing a value larger than 256 chars in log_entry_attr.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 13:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1439 | Inadequate access control vulnerability in Moodle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1439</link><description>Inadequate access control in Moodle LMS. This vulnerability could allow a local user with a student role to create arbitrary events intended for users with higher roles. It could also allow the attacker to add events to the calendar of all users without their prior consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 10:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24875 | WordPress Link Library Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24875</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library.This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.5.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24884 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Connector Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24884</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ARI Soft Contact Form 7 Connector.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Connector: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24887 | WordPress Contest Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 21.2.8.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24887</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Contest Gallery Photos and Files Contest Gallery – Contact Form, Upload Form, Social Share and Voting Plugin for WordPress.This issue affects Photos and Files Contest Gallery – Contact Form, Upload Form, Social Share and Voting Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 21.2.8.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24929 | WordPress WP Contact Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24929</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ryan Duff, Peter Westwood WP Contact Form.This issue affects WP Contact Form: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24935 | WordPress Basic Log Viewer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24935</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WpSimpleTools Basic Log Viewer.This issue affects Basic Log Viewer: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46615 | WordPress KD Coming Soon Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46615</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Kalli Dan. KD Coming Soon.This issue affects KD Coming Soon: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41703 | User ID references at mentions in document comments were not correctly sanitized. Script code could be injected to a users session when work...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41703</link><description>User ID references at mentions in document comments were not correctly sanitized. Script code could be injected to a users session when working with a malicious document. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. User-defined content like comments and mentions are now filtered to avoid potentially malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41704 | Processing of CID references at E-Mail can be abused to inject malicious script code that passes the sanitization engine. Malicious script c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41704</link><description>Processing of CID references at E-Mail can be abused to inject malicious script code that passes the sanitization engine. Malicious script code could be injected to a users sessions when interacting with E-Mails. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. CID handing has been improved and resulting content is checked for malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41705 | Processing of user-defined DAV user-agent strings is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41705</link><description>Processing of user-defined DAV user-agent strings is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of DAV user-agents now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41706 | Processing time of drive search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. Av...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41706</link><description>Processing time of drive search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing of user-defined drive search expressions is not limited No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41707 | Processing of user-defined mail search expressions is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41707</link><description>Processing of user-defined mail search expressions is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of mail search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached.&#13;
 No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41708 | References to the "app loader" functionality could contain redirects to unexpected locations. Attackers could forge app references that bypa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41708</link><description>References to the "app loader" functionality could contain redirects to unexpected locations. Attackers could forge app references that bypass existing safeguards to inject malicious script code. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. References to apps are now controlled more strict to avoid relative references. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23512 | WordPress ProductX – Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23512</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in wpxpo ProductX – WooCommerce Builder &amp; Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks.This issue affects ProductX – WooCommerce Builder &amp; Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23513 | WordPress PropertyHive Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23513</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PropertyHive.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24796 | WordPress Event Manager for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24796</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MagePeople Team Event Manager and Tickets Selling Plugin for WooCommerce – WpEvently – WordPress Plugin.This issue affects Event Manager and Tickets Selling Plugin for WooCommerce – WpEvently – WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24797 | WordPress ERE Recently Viewed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24797</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in G5Theme ERE Recently Viewed – Essential Real Estate Add-On.This issue affects ERE Recently Viewed – Essential Real Estate Add-On: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24926 | WordPress Brooklyn Theme &amp;lt;= 4.9.7.6 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24926</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in UnitedThemes Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme.This issue affects Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme: from n/a through 4.9.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25100 | WordPress Coupon Referral Program Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25100</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WP Swings Coupon Referral Program.This issue affects Coupon Referral Program: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47526 | WordPress Chartify Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47526</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chart Builder Team Chartify – WordPress Chart Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Chartify – WordPress Chart Plugin: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50875 | WordPress Sensei LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.17.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic Sensei LMS – Online Courses, Quizzes, &amp; Learning allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sensei LMS – Online Courses, Quizzes, &amp; Learning: from n/a through 4.17.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51370 | WordPress WP Chat App Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51370</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NinjaTeam WP Chat App allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Chat App: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51403 | WordPress Restaurant Reservations Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51403</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nicdark Restaurant Reservations allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Restaurant Reservations: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24889 | WordPress All 404 Pages Redirect to Homepage Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Geek Code Lab All 404 Pages Redirect to Homepage allows Stored XSS.This issue affects All 404 Pages Redirect to Homepage: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24927 | WordPress Brooklyn Theme &amp;lt;= 4.9.7.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24927</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UnitedThemes Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme: from n/a through 4.9.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24928 | WordPress Content Cards Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Arunas Liuiza Content Cards allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Content Cards: from n/a through 0.9.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24930 | WordPress Buttons Shortcode and Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24930</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OTWthemes.Com Buttons Shortcode and Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Buttons Shortcode and Widget: from n/a through 1.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24931 | WordPress Before After Image Slider WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24931</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in swadeshswain Before After Image Slider WP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Before After Image Slider WP: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24932 | WordPress VK Poster Group Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24932</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Djo VK Poster Group allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects VK Poster Group: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24933 | WordPress Honeypot for WP Comment Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24933</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prasidhda Malla Honeypot for WP Comment allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Honeypot for WP Comment: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25744 | In the Linux kernel before 6.6.7, an untrusted VMM can trigger int80 syscall handling at any given point. This is related to arch/x86/coco/t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25744</link><description>In the Linux kernel before 6.6.7, an untrusted VMM can trigger int80 syscall handling at any given point. This is related to arch/x86/coco/tdx/tdx.c and arch/x86/mm/mem_encrypt_amd.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 04:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52429 | dm_table_create in drivers/md/dm-table.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to (in alloc_targets) allocate more than INT_MAX byte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52429</link><description>dm_table_create in drivers/md/dm-table.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to (in alloc_targets) allocate more than INT_MAX bytes, and crash, because of a missing check for struct dm_ioctl.target_count.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25739 | create_empty_lvol in drivers/mtd/ubi/vtbl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to allocate zero bytes, and crash, because of a mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25739</link><description>create_empty_lvol in drivers/mtd/ubi/vtbl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to allocate zero bytes, and crash, because of a missing check for ubi-&gt;leb_size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25740 | A memory leak flaw was found in the UBI driver in drivers/mtd/ubi/attach.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 for UBI_IOCATT, because kobj-&gt;n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25740</link><description>A memory leak flaw was found in the UBI driver in drivers/mtd/ubi/attach.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 for UBI_IOCATT, because kobj-&gt;name is not released.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25741 | printer_write in drivers/usb/gadget/function/f_printer.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 does not properly call usb_ep_queue, which might ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25741</link><description>printer_write in drivers/usb/gadget/function/f_printer.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 does not properly call usb_ep_queue, which might allow attackers to cause a denial of service or have unspecified other impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1433 | KDE Plasma Workspace Theme File eventpluginsmanager.cpp enabledPlugins path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1433</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in KDE Plasma Workspace up to 5.93.0. This affects the function EventPluginsManager::enabledPlugins of the file components/calendar/eventpluginsmanager.cpp of the component Theme File Handler. The manipulation of the argument pluginId leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The patch is named 6cdf42916369ebf4ad5bd876c4dfa0170d7b2f01. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253407. NOTE: This requires write access to user's home or the installation of third party global themes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 23:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25728 | ExpressVPN before 12.73.0 on Windows, when split tunneling is used, sends DNS requests according to the Windows configuration (e.g., sends t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25728</link><description>ExpressVPN before 12.73.0 on Windows, when split tunneling is used, sends DNS requests according to the Windows configuration (e.g., sends them to DNS servers operated by the user's ISP instead of to the ExpressVPN DNS servers), which may allow remote attackers to obtain sensitive information about websites visited by VPN users.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25417 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/add_translation.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25417</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/add_translation.php.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25418 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_menu.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25418</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_menu.php.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25419 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_menu.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25419</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_menu.php.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1151 | Kernel: stack overflow problem in open vswitch kernel module leading to dos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1151</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in the Open vSwitch sub-component in the Linux Kernel. The flaw occurs when a recursive operation of code push recursively calls into the code block. The OVS module does not validate the stack depth, pushing too many frames and causing a stack overflow. As a result, this can lead to a crash or other related issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21875 | DoS attack when broadcasting billboard messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21875</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Badge leading to a denial of service attack.Team Hacker Hotel Badge 2024 on risc-v (billboard modules) allows Flooding.This issue affects Hacker Hotel Badge 2024: from 0.1.0 through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 08:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25722 | qanything_kernel/connector/database/mysql/mysql_client.py in qanything.ai QAnything before 1.2.0 allows SQL Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25722</link><description>qanything_kernel/connector/database/mysql/mysql_client.py in qanything.ai QAnything before 1.2.0 allows SQL Injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52428 | In Connect2id Nimbus JOSE+JWT before 9.37.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service (resource consumption) via a large JWE p2c header val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52428</link><description>In Connect2id Nimbus JOSE+JWT before 9.37.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service (resource consumption) via a large JWE p2c header value (aka iteration count) for the PasswordBasedDecrypter (PBKDF2) component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 04:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25718 | In the Samly package before 1.4.0 for Elixir, Samly.State.Store.get_assertion/3 can return an expired session, which interferes with access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25718</link><description>In the Samly package before 1.4.0 for Elixir, Samly.State.Store.get_assertion/3 can return an expired session, which interferes with access control because Samly.AuthHandler uses a cached session and does not replace it, even after expiry.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 04:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52427 | In OpenDDS through 3.27, there is a segmentation fault for a DataWriter with a large value of resource_limits.max_samples. NOTE: the vendor'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52427</link><description>In OpenDDS through 3.27, there is a segmentation fault for a DataWriter with a large value of resource_limits.max_samples. NOTE: the vendor's position is that the product is not designed to handle a max_samples value that is too large for the amount of memory on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 04:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1432 | DeepFaceLab main.py apply_xseg deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1432</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function apply_xseg of the file main.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253391. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 03:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1431 | Netgear R7000 Web Management Interface debuginfo.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1431</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /debuginfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25714 | In Rhonabwy through 1.1.13, HMAC signature verification uses a strcmp function that is vulnerable to side-channel attacks, because it stops ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25714</link><description>In Rhonabwy through 1.1.13, HMAC signature verification uses a strcmp function that is vulnerable to side-channel attacks, because it stops the comparison when the first difference is spotted in the two signatures. (The fix uses gnutls_memcmp, which has constant-time execution.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25715 | Glewlwyd SSO server 2.x through 2.7.6 allows open redirection via redirect_uri.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25715</link><description>Glewlwyd SSO server 2.x through 2.7.6 allows open redirection via redirect_uri.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25713 | yyjson through 0.8.0 has a double free, leading to remote code execution in some cases, because the pool_free function lacks loop checks. (p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25713</link><description>yyjson through 0.8.0 has a double free, leading to remote code execution in some cases, because the pool_free function lacks loop checks. (pool_free is part of the pool series allocator, along with pool_malloc and pool_realloc.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25712 | http-swagger before 1.2.6 allows XSS via PUT requests, because a file that has been uploaded (via httpSwagger.WrapHandler and *webdav.memFil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25712</link><description>http-swagger before 1.2.6 allows XSS via PUT requests, because a file that has been uploaded (via httpSwagger.WrapHandler and *webdav.memFile) can subsequently be accessed via a GET request. NOTE: this is independently fixable with respect to CVE-2022-24863, because (if a solution continued to allow PUT requests) large files could have been blocked without blocking JavaScript, or JavaScript could have been blocked without blocking large files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25711 | diffoscope before 256 allows directory traversal via an embedded filename in a GPG file. Contents of any file, such as ../.ssh/id_rsa, may b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25711</link><description>diffoscope before 256 allows directory traversal via an embedded filename in a GPG file. Contents of any file, such as ../.ssh/id_rsa, may be disclosed to an attacker. This occurs because the value of the gpg --use-embedded-filenames option is trusted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1430 | Netgear R7000 Web Management Interface currentsetting.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1430</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /currentsetting.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253381 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23724 | Ghost through 5.76.0 allows stored XSS, and resultant privilege escalation in which a contributor can take over any account, via an SVG prof...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23724</link><description>Ghost through 5.76.0 allows stored XSS, and resultant privilege escalation in which a contributor can take over any account, via an SVG profile picture that contains JavaScript code to interact with the API on localhost TCP port 3001. NOTE: The discoverer reports that "The vendor does not view this as a valid vector."</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>