<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-39840 | Factorio before 1.1.101 allows a crafted server to execute arbitrary code on clients via a custom map that leverages the ability of certain ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39840</link><description>Factorio before 1.1.101 allows a crafted server to execute arbitrary code on clients via a custom map that leverages the ability of certain Lua base module functions to execute bytecode and generate fake objects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2386 | WordPress Plugin for Google Maps – WP MAPS &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2386</link><description>The WordPress Plugin for Google Maps – WP MAPS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the 'put_wpgm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25943 | iDRAC9, versions prior to 7.00.00.172 for 14th Generation and 7.10.50.00 for 15th and 16th Generations, contains a session hijacking vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25943</link><description>iDRAC9, versions prior to 7.00.00.172 for 14th Generation and 7.10.50.00 for 15th and 16th Generations, contains a session hijacking vulnerability in IPMI. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution on the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4017 | Goya &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.7 - Unauthenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4017</link><description>The Goya theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘attra-color’,  'attra-size', and 'product-cata' parameters in versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 11:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5819 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features &amp;lt;= 3.2.45 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Data Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5819</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML data attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.45 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 09:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5666 | Extensions for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5666</link><description>The Extensions for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the EE Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5790 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.11.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Gradient Heading Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5790</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ attribute within the plugin's Gradient Heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6363 | Stock Ticker &amp;lt;= 3.24.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via stock_ticker Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6363</link><description>The Stock Ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's stock_ticker shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5192 | Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp;amp; One Click Upsells &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5192</link><description>The Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp; One Click Upsells plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘mimes’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5598 | Advanced File Manager &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Directory Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5598</link><description>The Advanced File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.4 via the 'fma_local_file_system' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including backups or other sensitive information if the files have been moved to the built-in Trash folder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5889 | Events Manager &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5889</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘country’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5942 | Page and Post Clone &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5942</link><description>The Page and Post Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.0 via the 'content_clone' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to clone and read private posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6265 | UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp;amp; Members Directory plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;uwp_sort_by&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6265</link><description>The UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp; Members Directory plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘uwp_sort_by’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6405 | Floating Social Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6405</link><description>The Floating Social Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the floating_social_buttons_option() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugins settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25211 | parseWildcardRules in Gin-Gonic CORS middleware before 1.6.0 mishandles a wildcard at the end of an origin string, e.g., https://example.com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25211</link><description>parseWildcardRules in Gin-Gonic CORS middleware before 1.6.0 mishandles a wildcard at the end of an origin string, e.g., https://example.community/* is allowed when the intention is that only https://example.com/* should be allowed, and http://localhost.example.com/* is allowed when the intention is that only http://localhost/* should be allowed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 23:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37371 | In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can cause invalid memory reads during GSS message token handling by sending message ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37371</link><description>In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can cause invalid memory reads during GSS message token handling by sending message tokens with invalid length fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37370 | In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can modify the plaintext Extra Count field of a confidential GSS krb5 wrap token, ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37370</link><description>In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can modify the plaintext Extra Count field of a confidential GSS krb5 wrap token, causing the unwrapped token to appear truncated to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39828 | R74n Sandboxels 1.9 through 1.9.5 allows XSS via a message in a modified saved-game file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39828</link><description>R74n Sandboxels 1.9 through 1.9.5 allows XSS via a message in a modified saved-game file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38532 | TEST_KEY used in example dcp_tool reference implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38532</link><description>The NXP Data Co-Processor (DCP) is a built-in hardware module for specific NXP SoCs¹ that implements a dedicated AES cryptographic engine for encryption/decryption operations. The dcp_tool reference implementation included in the repository selected the test key, regardless of its `-t` argument. This issue has been patched in commit 26a7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38533 | ZKsync Era invalid stack addressing conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38533</link><description>ZKsync Era is a layer 2 rollup that uses zero-knowledge proofs to scale Ethereum. There is possible invalid stack access due to the addresses used to access the stack not properly being converted to cells. This issue has been patched in version 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38525 | dd-trace-cpp malformed unicode header values may cause crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38525</link><description>dd-trace-cpp is the Datadog distributed tracing for C++. When the library fails to extract trace context due to malformed unicode, it logs the list of audited headers and their values using the `nlohmann` JSON library. However, due to the way the JSON library is invoked, it throws an uncaught exception, which results in a crash. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29040 | Fapi Verify Quote: Does not detect if quote was not generated by TPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29040</link><description>This repository hosts source code implementing the Trusted Computing Group's (TCG) TPM2 Software Stack (TSS). The JSON Quote Info returned by Fapi_Quote has to be deserialized by Fapi_VerifyQuote to the TPM Structure `TPMS_ATTEST`. For the field `TPM2_GENERATED magic` of this structure any number can be used in the JSON structure. The verifier can receive a state which does not represent the actual, possibly malicious state of the device under test. The malicious device might get access to data it shouldn't, or can use services it shouldn't be able to. This 
issue has been patched in version 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39302 | Some bbb-record-core files installed with wrong file permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39302</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom designed to help teachers teach and learners learn. An attacker may be able to exploit the overly elevated file permissions in the `/usr/local/bigbluebutton/core/vendor/bundle/ruby/2.7.0/gems/resque-2.6.0` directory with the goal of privilege escalation, potentially exposing sensitive information on the server. This issue has been patched in version(s) 2.6.18, 2.7.8 and 3.0.0-alpha.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39307 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via crafted ebooks in Kavita</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39307</link><description>Kavita is a cross platform reading server. Opening an ebook with malicious scripts inside leads to code execution inside the browsing context. Kavita doesn't sanitize or sandbox the contents of epubs, allowing scripts inside ebooks to execute. This vulnerability was patched in version 0.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38518 | bbb-web API additional parameters considered</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38518</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom designed to help teachers teach and learners learn. An attacker with a valid join link to a meeting can trick BigBlueButton into generating a signed join link with additional parameters. One of those parameters may be "role=moderator", allowing an attacker to join a meeting as moderator using a join link that was originally created for viewer access. This vulnerability has been patched in version(s) 2.6.18, 2.7.8 and 3.0.0-alpha.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3995 | Command Injection in Helix Sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3995</link><description>In Helix ALM versions prior to 2024.2.0, a local command injection was identified.  Reported by Bryan Riggins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38528 | Unlimited number of NTS-KE connections can crash ntpd-rs server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38528</link><description>nptd-rs is a tool for synchronizing your computer's clock, implementing the NTP and NTS protocols. There is a missing limit for accepted NTS-KE connections. This allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to crash ntpd-rs when an NTS-KE server is configured. Non NTS-KE server configurations, such as the default ntpd-rs configuration, are unaffected. This vulnerability has been patched in version 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5827 | Arbitrary File Write by Prompt Injection via DuckDB SQL in vanna-ai/vanna</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5827</link><description>Vanna v0.3.4 is vulnerable to SQL injection in its DuckDB integration exposed to its Flask Web APIs. Attackers can inject malicious SQL training data and generate corresponding queries to write arbitrary files on the victim's file system, such as backdoor.php with contents ``. This can lead to command execution or the creation of backdoors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5712 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5712</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27540 | A potential Time-of-Check to Time-of Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability has been identified in the HP BIOS for certain HP PC products, which might a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27540</link><description>A potential Time-of-Check to Time-of Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability has been identified in the HP BIOS for certain HP PC products, which might allow arbitrary code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure. HP is releasing BIOS updates to mitigate the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38383 | IBM Cloud Pak for Security information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38383</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security (CP4S) 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Software Suite 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.21.0 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  233673.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25041 | IBM Cognos Analytics cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25041</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, and 12.0.2 is potentially vulnerable to cross site scripting (XSS). A remote attacker could execute malicious commands due to improper validation of column headings in Cognos Assistant.  IBM X-Force ID:  282780.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25053 | IBM Cognos Analytics improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25053</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, and 12.0.2 is vulnerable to improper certificate validation when using the IBM Planning Analytics Data Source Connection. This could allow an attacker to spoof a trusted entity by interfering in the communication path between IBM Planning Analytics server and IBM Cognos Analytics server.  IBM X-Force ID:  283364.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38322 | IBM Storage Defender information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38322</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.4 agent username and password error response discrepancy exposes product to brute force enumeration.  IBM X-Force ID:  294869.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25031 | IBM Storage Defender information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25031</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.4 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow an attacker on the network to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  281678.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27628 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DCMTK v.3.6.8 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the EctEnhancedCT method component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27628</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DCMTK v.3.6.8 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the EctEnhancedCT method component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27629 | An issue in dc2niix before v.1.0.20240202 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the generated file name is not properly esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27629</link><description>An issue in dc2niix before v.1.0.20240202 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the generated file name is not properly escaped and injected into a system call when certain types of compression are used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35116 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35116</link><description>IBM MQ 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, 9.2 LTS, 9.3 LTS, and 9.3 CD is vulnerable to a denial of service attack caused by an error applying configuration changes.  IBM X-Force ID:  290335.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35156 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35156</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  292766.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38514 | NextChat Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38514</link><description>NextChat is a cross-platform ChatGPT/Gemini UI. There is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a lack of validation of the `endpoint` GET parameter on the WebDav API endpoint. This SSRF can be used to perform arbitrary HTTPS request from the vulnerable instance (MKCOL, PUT and GET methods supported), or to target NextChat users and make them execute arbitrary JavaScript code in their browser. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.12.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38374 | Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference in org.cyclonedx:cyclonedx-core-java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38374</link><description>The CycloneDX core module provides a model representation of the SBOM along with utilities to assist in creating, validating, and parsing SBOMs. Before deserializing CycloneDX Bill of Materials in XML format, _cyclonedx-core-java_ leverages XPath expressions to determine the schema version of the BOM. The `DocumentBuilderFactory` used to evaluate XPath expressions was not configured securely, making the library vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) injection. This vulnerability has been fixed in cyclonedx-core-java version 9.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38371 | Insufficient access control for OAuth2 Device Code flow in authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38371</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Access restrictions assigned to an application were not checked when using the OAuth2 Device code flow. This could potentially allow users without the correct authorization to get OAuth tokens for an application and access it. This issue has been patched in version(s) 2024.6.0, 2024.2.4 and 2024.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31912 | IBM MQ privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31912</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could allow an authenticated user to escalate their privileges under certain configurations due to incorrect privilege assignment.  IBM X-Force ID:  289894.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35155 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35155</link><description>IBM MQ Console 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could disclose could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  292765.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31919 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31919</link><description>IBM MQ 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, 9.2 LTS, 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD, in certain configurations, is vulnerable to a denial of service attack caused by an error processing messages when an API Exit using MQBUFMH is used.  IBM X-Force ID:  290259.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37905 | Improper Access Control and Incorrect Authorization in github.com/goauthentik/authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37905</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider that emphasizes flexibility and versatility. Authentik API-Access-Token mechanism can be exploited to gain admin user privileges. A successful exploit of the issue will result in a user gaining full admin access to the Authentik application, including resetting user passwords and more. This issue has been patched in version(s) 2024.2.4, 2024.4.2 and 2024.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38522 | CSP bypass in Hush Line</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38522</link><description>Hush Line is a free and open-source, anonymous-tip-line-as-a-service for organizations or individuals. The CSP policy applied on the `tips.hushline.app` website and bundled by default in this repository is trivial to bypass. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6402 | Tenda A301 SetOnlineDevName fromSetWirelessRepeat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6402</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda A301 15.13.08.12. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269947. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6403 | Tenda A301 SetOnlineDevName formWifiBasicSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6403</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda A301 15.13.08.12. Affected by this issue is the function formWifiBasicSet of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269948. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29039 | Missing check in tpm2_checkquote allows attackers to misrepresent the TPM state</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29039</link><description>tpm2 is the source repository for the Trusted Platform Module (TPM2.0) tools. This vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate tpm2_checkquote outputs by altering the TPML_PCR_SELECTION in the PCR input file.  As a result, digest values are incorrectly mapped to PCR slots and banks, providing a misleading picture of the TPM state. This issue has been patched in version 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35139 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35139</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information from the container due to incorrect default permissions.  IBM X-Force ID:  292415.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35137 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35137</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to possibly elevate their privileges due to sensitive configuration information being exposed.   IBM X-Force ID:  292413.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38521 | Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in hushline inbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38521</link><description>Hush Line is a free and open-source, anonymous-tip-line-as-a-service for organizations or individuals. There is a stored XSS in the Inbox. The input is displayed using the `safe` Jinja2 attribute, and thus not sanitized upon display. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29038 | tpm2 does not detect if quote was not generated by TPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29038</link><description>tpm2-tools is the source repository for the Trusted Platform Module (TPM2.0) tools. A malicious attacker can generate arbitrary quote data which is not detected by `tpm2 checkquote`. This issue was patched in version 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38531 | Nix sandbox escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38531</link><description>Nix is a package manager for Linux and other Unix systems that makes package management reliable and reproducible. A build process has access to and can change the permissions of the build directory. After creating a setuid binary in a globally accessible location, a malicious local user can assume the permissions of a Nix daemon worker and hijack all future builds. This issue was patched in version(s) 2.23.1, 2.22.2, 2.21.3, 2.20.7, 2.19.5 and 2.18.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3801 | XSS in S@M CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3801</link><description>Sites managed in S@M CMS (Concept Intermedia) might be vulnerable to Reflected XSS via including scripts in one of GET header parameters. 
Only a part of observed services is vulnerable, but since vendor has not investigated the root problem, it is hard to determine when the issue appears.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3816 | SQLi in S@M CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3816</link><description>Sites managed in S@M CMS (Concept Intermedia) might be vulnerable to a blind SQL Injection executed using the search bar. 
Only a part of observed services is vulnerable, but since vendor has not investigated the root problem, it is hard to determine when the issue appears.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37741 | OpenPLC 3 through 9cd8f1b allows XSS via an SVG document as a profile picture.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37741</link><description>OpenPLC 3 through 9cd8f1b allows XSS via an SVG document as a profile picture.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39704 | Soft Circle French-Bread Melty Blood: Actress Again: Current Code through 1.07 Rev. 1.4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39704</link><description>Soft Circle French-Bread Melty Blood: Actress Again: Current Code through 1.07 Rev. 1.4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on a client's machine via a crafted packet on TCP port 46318.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3800 | XSS in S@M CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3800</link><description>Sites managed in S@M CMS (Concept Intermedia) might be vulnerable to Reflected XSS via including scripts in requested file names. 
Only a part of observed services is vulnerable, but since vendor has not investigated the root problem, it is hard to determine when the issue appears.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5735 | Full Path Disclosure in AdmirorFrames Joomla! Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5735</link><description>Full Path Disclosure vulnerability in AdmirorFrames Joomla! extension in afHelper.php script allows an unauthorised attacker to retrieve location of web root folder.This issue affects AdmirorFrames: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5736 | SSRF in AdmirorFrames Joomla! Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5736</link><description>Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in AdmirorFrames Joomla! extension in afGdStream.php script allows to access local files or server pages available only from localhost.  This issue affects AdmirorFrames: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5737 | HTML Injection in AdmirorFrames Joomla! Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5737</link><description>Script afGdStream.php in AdmirorFrames Joomla! extension doesn’t specify a content type and as a result default (text/html) is used. An attacker may embed HTML tags directly in image data which is rendered by a webpage as HTML. This issue affects AdmirorFrames: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5424 | Gallery Blocks with Lightbox. Image Gallery, (HTML5 video , YouTube, Vimeo) Video Gallery and Lightbox for native gallery &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via galleryID and className Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5424</link><description>The Gallery Blocks with Lightbox. Image Gallery, (HTML5 video , YouTube, Vimeo) Video Gallery and Lightbox for native gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘galleryID’ and 'className' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5662 | Ultimate Post Kit Addons For Elementor – (Post Grid, Post Carousel, Post Slider, Category List, Post Tabs, Timeline, Post Ticker, Tag Cloud) &amp;lt;= 3.11.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Count (Static) Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5662</link><description>The Ultimate Post Kit Addons For Elementor – (Post Grid, Post Carousel, Post Slider, Category List, Post Tabs, Timeline, Post Ticker, Tag Cloud) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the Social Count (Static) widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5922 | Scylla lite &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5922</link><description>The Scylla lite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5925 | Theron Lite &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5925</link><description>The Theron Lite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30135 | Sensitive Information Disclosure vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30135</link><description>HCL DRYiCE AEX is potentially impacted by disclosure of sensitive information in the mobile application when a snapshot is taken.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2795 | SEO SIMPLE PACK &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2795</link><description>The SEO SIMPLE PACK plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 via META description. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract limited information about password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39350 | A vulnerability regarding authentication bypass by spoofing is found in the RTSP functionality. This allows man-in-the-middle attackers to o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39350</link><description>A vulnerability regarding authentication bypass by spoofing is found in the RTSP functionality. This allows man-in-the-middle attackers to obtain privileges without consent via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5788 | Silesia &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5788</link><description>The Silesia theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ attribute within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5796 | Infinite &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via project_url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5796</link><description>The Infinite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘project_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6288 | Conversios.io - All-in-one Google Analytics, Pixels and Product Feed Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 7.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6288</link><description>The Conversios – Google Analytics 4 (GA4), Meta Pixel &amp; more Via Google Tag Manager For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tiktok_user_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30111 | Missing Root Detection vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30111</link><description>HCL DRYiCE AEX product is impacted by Missing
Root Detection vulnerability in the mobile application. The  mobile app can be installed in the rooted
device due to which malicious users can gain unauthorized access to the rooted
devices, compromising security and potentially leading to data breaches or
other malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30110 | Lack of input validation vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30110</link><description>HCL DRYiCE
AEX product is impacted by lack of input validation vulnerability in a particular web application. A malicious script can be injected into a system which
can cause the system to behave in unexpected ways.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39347 | Incorrect default permissions vulnerability in firewall functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1.3.1-9346-8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39347</link><description>Incorrect default permissions vulnerability in firewall functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1.3.1-9346-8 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to access highly sensitive intranet resources via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39348 | Download of code without integrity check vulnerability in AirPrint functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39348</link><description>Download of code without integrity check vulnerability in AirPrint functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1.3.1-9346-8 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47802 | A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the IP bloc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47802</link><description>A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the IP block functionality. This allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47803 | A vulnerability regarding improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') is found in the Language Settings f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47803</link><description>A vulnerability regarding improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') is found in the Language Settings functionality. This allows remote attackers to read specific files containing non-sensitive information via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39349 | A vulnerability regarding buffer copy without checking size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') is found in the libjansson component and it...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39349</link><description>A vulnerability regarding buffer copy without checking size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') is found in the libjansson component and it does not affect the upstream library. This allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39351 | A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the NTP con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39351</link><description>A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the NTP configuration. This allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39352 | A vulnerability regarding incorrect authorization is found in the firmware upgrade functionality. This allows remote authenticated users wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39352</link><description>A vulnerability regarding incorrect authorization is found in the firmware upgrade functionality. This allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to bypass firmware integrity check via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5570 | Simple Photoswipe &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5570</link><description>The Simple Photoswipe WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not have authorisation check when updating its settings, which could allow any authenticated users, such as subscriber to update them</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5727 | Widget4Call &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5727</link><description>The Widget4Call WordPress plugin through 1.0.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5728 | Animated AL List &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5728</link><description>The Animated AL List WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5729 | Simple AL Slider &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5729</link><description>The Simple AL Slider WordPress plugin through 1.2.10 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5730 | Pagerank Tools &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5730</link><description>The Pagerank tools WordPress plugin through 1.1.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30109 | Lack of Clickjacking Protection vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30109</link><description>HCL DRYiCE AEX is impacted by a lack of clickjacking protection in the AEX web application.  An attacker can use multiple transparent or opaque layers to trick a user into clicking on a button or link on another page than the one intended.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 05:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37282 | It was identified that under certain specific preconditions, an API key that was originally created with a specific privileges could be subs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37282</link><description>It was identified that under certain specific preconditions, an API key that was originally created with a specific privileges could be subsequently used to create new API keys that have elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6296 | Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.13.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6296</link><description>The Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘data-caption’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5863 | Easy Image Collage &amp;lt;= 1.13.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Data Clearance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5863</link><description>The Easy Image Collage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_image_collage() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to erase all of the content in arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5864 | Easy Affiliate Links &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5864</link><description>The Easy Affiliate Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the eafl_reset_settings AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37137 | Dell Key Trust Platform, v3.0.6 and prior, contains Use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A local priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37137</link><description>Dell Key Trust Platform, v3.0.6 and prior, contains Use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A local privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privileged information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39708 | An issue was discovered in the Agent in Delinea Privilege Manager (formerly Thycotic Privilege Manager) before 12.0.1096 on Windows. Sometim...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39708</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Agent in Delinea Privilege Manager (formerly Thycotic Privilege Manager) before 12.0.1096 on Windows. Sometimes, a non-administrator user can copy a crafted DLL file to a temporary directory (used by .NET Shadow Copies) such that privilege escalation can occur if the core agent service loads that file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6071 | PTC Creo Elements/Direct License Server Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6071</link><description>PTC Creo Elements/Direct License Server exposes a web interface which can be used by unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 23:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-20022 | In the Linux kernel before 4.8, usb_parse_endpoint in drivers/usb/core/config.c does not validate the wMaxPacketSize field of an endpoint de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-20022</link><description>In the Linux kernel before 4.8, usb_parse_endpoint in drivers/usb/core/config.c does not validate the wMaxPacketSize field of an endpoint descriptor. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the supplier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39705 | NLTK through 3.8.1 allows remote code execution if untrusted packages have pickled Python code, and the integrated data package download fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39705</link><description>NLTK through 3.8.1 allows remote code execution if untrusted packages have pickled Python code, and the integrated data package download functionality is used. This affects, for example, averaged_perceptron_tagger and punkt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36059 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Kalkitech ASE ASE61850 IEDSmart upto and including version 2.3.5 allows attackers to read/write arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36059</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Kalkitech ASE ASE61850 IEDSmart upto and including version 2.3.5 allows attackers to read/write arbitrary files via the IEC61850 File Transfer protocol.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52892 | In phpseclib before 1.0.22, 2.x before 2.0.46, and 3.x before 3.0.33, some characters in Subject Alternative Name fields in TLS certificates...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52892</link><description>In phpseclib before 1.0.22, 2.x before 2.0.46, and 3.x before 3.0.33, some characters in Subject Alternative Name fields in TLS certificates are incorrectly allowed to have a special meaning in regular expressions (such as a + wildcard), leading to name confusion in X.509 certificate host verification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4395 | Lack of Client Validation in Jamf Compliance Editor&amp;#x27;s Helper Service May Result in Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4395</link><description>The XPC service within the audit functionality of Jamf Compliance Editor before version 1.3.1 on macOS can lead to local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5642 | Buffer overread when using an empty list with SSLContext.set_npn_protocols()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5642</link><description>CPython 3.9 and earlier doesn't disallow configuring an empty list ("[]") for SSLContext.set_npn_protocols() which is an invalid value for the underlying OpenSSL API. This results in a buffer over-read when NPN is used (see CVE-2024-5535 for OpenSSL). This vulnerability is of low severity due to NPN being not widely used and specifying an empty list likely being uncommon in-practice (typically a protocol name would be configured).</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22272 | VMware Cloud Director contains an Improper Privilege Management vulnerability. 


An authenticated tenant administrator for a
 given organiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22272</link><description>VMware Cloud Director contains an Improper Privilege Management vulnerability. 


An authenticated tenant administrator for a
 given organization within VMware Cloud Director may be able to 
accidentally disable their organization leading to a Denial of Service 
for active sessions within their own organization's scope.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22276 | VMware Cloud Director Object Storage Extension contains an Insertion of Sensitive Information vulnerability.


A malicious actor with adjace...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22276</link><description>VMware Cloud Director Object Storage Extension contains an Insertion of Sensitive Information vulnerability.


A malicious actor with adjacent access to 
web/proxy server logging may be able to obtain sensitive information 
from URLs that are logged.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36074 | Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the Endpoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36074</link><description>Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the Endpoint Protector and Unify agent in the way that the EasyLock dependency is acquired from the server. An attacker with administrative access to the Endpoint Protector or Unify server can cause a client to acquire and execute a malicious file resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36075 | Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36075</link><description>Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the application configuration component of the Endpoint Protector and Unify agent which allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to manipulate the configuration of either their own or another client endpoint resulting in the bypass of certain configuration options. Manipulation of the application configuration can result in local policy bypass and in some scenarios remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22260 | VMware Workspace One UEM update addresses an information exposure vulnerability. 
A malicious actor with network access to the Workspace One...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22260</link><description>VMware Workspace One UEM update addresses an information exposure vulnerability. 
A malicious actor with network access to the Workspace One UEM may be 
able to perform an attack resulting in an information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2973 | Session Smart Router(SSR): API Authentication can be bypassed in redundant routers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2973</link><description>An Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Juniper Networks Session Smart Router or conductor running with a redundant peer allows a network based attacker to bypass authentication and take full control of the device.
Only routers or conductors that are running in high-availability redundant configurations are affected by this vulnerability.




No other Juniper Networks products or platforms are affected by this issue.





This issue affects:

Session Smart Router: 



  *  All versions before 5.6.15, 
  *  from 6.0 before 6.1.9-lts, 
  *  from 6.2 before 6.2.5-sts.



Session Smart Conductor: 



  *  All versions before 5.6.15, 
  *  from 6.0 before 6.1.9-lts, 
  *  from 6.2 before 6.2.5-sts. 



WAN Assurance Router: 



  *  6.0 versions before 6.1.9-lts, 
  *  6.2 versions before 6.2.5-sts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36072 | Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the loggin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36072</link><description>Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the logging component of the Endpoint Protector and Unify server application which allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to send a malicious request, resulting in the ability to execute system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36073 | Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the shadow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36073</link><description>Netwrix CoSoSys Endpoint Protector through 5.9.3 and CoSoSys Unify through 7.0.6 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the shadowing component of the Endpoint Protector and Unify agent which allows an attacker with administrative access to the Endpoint Protector or Unify server to overwrite sensitive configuration and subsequently execute system commands with SYSTEM/root privileges on a chosen client endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36755 | D-Link DIR-1950 up to v1.11B03 does not validate SSL certificates when requesting the latest firmware version and downloading URL. This can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36755</link><description>D-Link DIR-1950 up to v1.11B03 does not validate SSL certificates when requesting the latest firmware version and downloading URL. This can allow attackers to downgrade the firmware version or change the downloading URL via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39132 | A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in DumpTS v0.1.0-nightly allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the function VerifyComma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39132</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in DumpTS v0.1.0-nightly allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the function VerifyCommandLine() at /src/DumpTS.cpp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39134 | A Stack Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zziplibv 0.13.77 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the __zzip_fetch_disk_trailer() ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39134</link><description>A Stack Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zziplibv 0.13.77 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the __zzip_fetch_disk_trailer() function at /zzip/zip.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39209 | luci-app-sms-tool v1.9-6 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the score parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39209</link><description>luci-app-sms-tool v1.9-6 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the score parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31802 | DESIGNA ABACUS v.18 and before allows an attacker to bypass the payment process via a crafted QR code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31802</link><description>DESIGNA ABACUS v.18 and before allows an attacker to bypass the payment process via a crafted QR code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39130 | A NULL Pointer Dereference discovered in DumpTS v0.1.0-nightly allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the function DumpOneStream(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39130</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference discovered in DumpTS v0.1.0-nightly allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the function DumpOneStream() at /src/DumpStream.cpp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39133 | Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zziplib v0.13.77 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the __zzip_parse_root_directory() f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39133</link><description>Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in zziplib v0.13.77 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the __zzip_parse_root_directory() function at /zzip/zip.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39207 | lua-shmem v1.0-1 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the shmem_write function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39207</link><description>lua-shmem v1.0-1 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the shmem_write function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39208 | luci-app-lucky v2.8.3 was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39208</link><description>luci-app-lucky v2.8.3 was discovered to contain hardcoded credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39129 | Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DumpTS v0.1.0-nightly allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the function PushTSBuf() at /s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39129</link><description>Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DumpTS v0.1.0-nightly allows attackers to cause a denial of service via the function PushTSBuf() at /src/PayloadBuf.cpp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38523 | Hush Line OTP issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38523</link><description>Hush Line is a free and open-source, anonymous-tip-line-as-a-service for organizations or individuals. The TOTP authentication flow has multiple issues that weakens its one-time nature. Specifically, the lack of 2FA for changing security settings allows attacker with CSRF or XSS primitives to change such settings without user interaction and credentials are required. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6127 | BC Security Empire Path Traversal RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6127</link><description>BC Security Empire before 5.9.3 is vulnerable to a path traversal issue that can lead to remote code execution. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability over HTTP by acting as a normal agent, completing all cryptographic handshakes, and then triggering an upload of payload data containing a malicious path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2882 | Missing Authorization in SDG Technologies PnPSCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2882</link><description>SDG Technologies PnPSCADA allows a remote attacker to attach various entities without requiring system authentication. This breach could potentially lead to unauthorized control, data manipulation, and access to sensitive information within the SCADA system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3331 | Spotfire: NTLM token leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3331</link><description>Vulnerability in Spotfire Spotfire Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, Spotfire Spotfire Statistics Services, Spotfire Spotfire Analyst, Spotfire Spotfire Desktop, Spotfire Spotfire Server allows The impact of this vulnerability depends on the privileges of the user running the affected software..This issue affects Spotfire Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: from 1.12.7 through 1.20.0; Spotfire Statistics Services: from 12.0.7 through 12.3.1, from 14.0.0 through 14.3.0; Spotfire Analyst: from 12.0.9 through 12.5.0, from 14.0.0 through 14.3.0; Spotfire Desktop: from 14.0 through 14.3.0; Spotfire Server: from 12.0.10 through 12.5.0, from 14.0.0 through 14.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5755 | Email Validation Bypass in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5755</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary versions &lt;=v1.2.11, an attacker can bypass email validation by using a dot character ('.') in the email address. This allows the creation of multiple accounts with essentially the same email address (e.g., 'attacker123@gmail.com' and 'attacker.123@gmail.com'), leading to incorrect synchronization and potential security issues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5822 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in gaizhenbiao/ChuanhuChatGPT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5822</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the upload processing interface of gaizhenbiao/ChuanhuChatGPT versions &lt;= ChuanhuChatGPT-20240410-git.zip. This vulnerability allows attackers to send crafted requests from the vulnerable server to internal or external resources, potentially bypassing security controls and accessing sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5824 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5824</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in the `/set_personality_config` endpoint of parisneo/lollms version 9.4.0 allows an attacker to overwrite the `configs/config.yaml` file. This can lead to remote code execution by changing server configuration properties such as `force_accept_remote_access` and `turn_on_code_validation`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5885 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in stangirard/quivr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5885</link><description>stangirard/quivr version 0.0.236 contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The application does not provide sufficient controls when crawling a website, allowing an attacker to access applications on the local network. This vulnerability could allow a malicious user to gain access to internal servers, the AWS metadata endpoint, and capture Supabase data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5933 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5933</link><description>A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the chat functionality of parisneo/lollms-webui in the latest version. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts via chat messages, which are then executed in the context of the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5935 | CSRF Vulnerability in imartinez/privategpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5935</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in version 0.5.0 of imartinez/privategpt allows an attacker to delete all uploaded files on the server. This can lead to data loss and service disruption for the application's users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5936 | Open Redirect in imartinez/privategpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5936</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability exists in imartinez/privategpt version 0.5.0 due to improper handling of the 'file' parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to redirect users to a URL specified by user-controlled input without proper validation or sanitization. The impact of this vulnerability includes potential phishing attacks, malware distribution, and credential theft.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5980 | Arbitrary File Write via /v1/runs API endpoint in lightning-ai/pytorch-lightning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5980</link><description>A vulnerability in the /v1/runs API endpoint of lightning-ai/pytorch-lightning v2.2.4 allows attackers to exploit path traversal when extracting tar.gz files. When the LightningApp is running with the plugin_server, attackers can deploy malicious tar.gz plugins that embed arbitrary files with path traversal vulnerabilities. This can result in arbitrary files being written to any directory in the victim's local file system, potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6085 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6085</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the XTTS server included in the lollms package, version v9.6. This vulnerability arises from the ability to perform an unauthenticated root folder settings change. Although the read file endpoint is protected against path traversals, this protection can be bypassed by changing the root folder to '/'. This allows attackers to read arbitrary files on the system. Additionally, the output folders can be changed to write arbitrary audio files to any location on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6086 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6086</link><description>In version 1.2.7 of lunary-ai/lunary, any authenticated user, regardless of their role, can change the name of an organization due to improper access control. The function checkAccess() is not implemented, allowing users with the lowest privileges, such as the 'Prompt Editor' role, to modify organization attributes without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6139 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6139</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of the parisneo/lollms package version v9.6. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write audio files to arbitrary locations on the system and enumerate file paths. The issue arises from improper validation of user-provided file paths in the `tts_to_file` endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3330 | Spotfire Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3330</link><description>Vulnerability in Spotfire Spotfire Analyst, Spotfire Spotfire Server, Spotfire Spotfire for AWS Marketplace allows In the case of the installed Windows client: Successful execution of this vulnerability will result in an attacker being able to run arbitrary code.This requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker., In the case of the Web player (Business Author): Successful execution of this vulnerability via the Web Player, will result in the attacker being able to run arbitrary code as the account running the Web player process, In the case of Automation Services: Successful execution of this vulnerability will result in an attacker being able to run arbitrary code via Automation Services..This issue affects Spotfire Analyst: from 12.0.9 through 12.5.0, from 14.0 through 14.0.2; Spotfire Server: from 12.0.10 through 12.5.0, from 14.0 through 14.0.3, from 14.2.0 through 14.3.0; Spotfire for AWS Marketplace: from 14.0 before 14.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5710 | Improper Access Control in Team Management in berriai/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5710</link><description>berriai/litellm version 1.34.34 is vulnerable to improper access control in its team management functionality. This vulnerability allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions such as creating, updating, viewing, deleting, blocking, and unblocking any teams, as well as adding or deleting any member to or from any teams. The vulnerability stems from insufficient access control checks in various team management endpoints, enabling attackers to exploit these functionalities without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5714 | Improper Access Control in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5714</link><description>In lunary-ai/lunary version 1.2.4, an improper access control vulnerability allows members with team management permissions to manipulate project identifiers in requests, enabling them to invite users to projects in other organizations, change members to projects in other organizations with escalated privileges, and change members from other organizations to their own or other projects, also with escalated privileges. This vulnerability is due to the backend's failure to validate project identifiers against the current user's organization ID and projects belonging to it, as well as a misconfiguration in attribute naming (`org_id` should be `orgId`) that prevents proper user organization validation. As a result, attackers can cause inconsistencies on the platform for affected users and organizations, including unauthorized privilege escalation. The issue is present in the backend API endpoints for user invitation and modification, specifically in the handling of project IDs in requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5751 | Remote Code Execution in BerriAI/litellm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5751</link><description>BerriAI/litellm version v1.35.8 contains a vulnerability where an attacker can achieve remote code execution. The vulnerability exists in the `add_deployment` function, which decodes and decrypts environment variables from base64 and assigns them to `os.environ`. An attacker can exploit this by sending a malicious payload to the `/config/update` endpoint, which is then processed and executed by the server when the `get_secret` function is triggered. This requires the server to use Google KMS and a database to store a model.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5820 | Missing Authorization in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5820</link><description>Missing Authorization in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5826 | Remote Code Execution via Prompt Injection in vanna-ai/vanna</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5826</link><description>In the latest version of vanna-ai/vanna, the `vanna.ask` function is vulnerable to remote code execution due to prompt injection. The root cause is the lack of a sandbox when executing LLM-generated code, allowing an attacker to manipulate the code executed by the `exec` function in `src/vanna/base/base.py`. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker to achieve remote code execution on the app backend server, potentially gaining full control of the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5979 | Denial of Service via Invalid Argument in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5979</link><description>In h2oai/h2o-3 version 3.46.0, the `run_tool` command in the `rapids` component allows the `main` function of any class under the `water.tools` namespace to be called. One such class, `MojoConvertTool`, crashes the server when invoked with an invalid argument, causing a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6038 | ReDoS Vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6038</link><description>A Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the latest version of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt. The vulnerability is located in the filter_history function within the utils.py module. This function takes a user-provided keyword and attempts to match it against chat history filenames using a regular expression search. Due to the lack of sanitization or validation of the keyword parameter, an attacker can inject a specially crafted regular expression, leading to a denial of service condition. This can cause severe degradation of service performance and potential system unavailability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6090 | Path Traversal Vulnerability in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6090</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240410, allowing any user to delete other users' chat histories. This vulnerability can also be exploited to delete any files ending in `.json` on the target system, leading to a denial of service as users are unable to authenticate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6250 | Absolute Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6250</link><description>An absolute path traversal vulnerability exists in parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6, specifically in the `open_file` endpoint of `lollms_advanced.py`. The `sanitize_path` function with `allow_absolute_path=True` allows an attacker to access arbitrary files and directories on a Windows system. This vulnerability can be exploited to read any file and list arbitrary directories on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3017 | Denial of service in multi-protocol gateway - Zigbee + Thread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3017</link><description>In a 

Silicon Labs  multi-protocol gateway, a corrupt pointer to buffered data on a multi-protocol radio co-processor (RCP) causes the OpenThread Border Router(OTBR) application task running on the host platform to crash, allowing an attacker to cause a temporary denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4578 | Privilege escalation in Arista Wireless Access Points</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4578</link><description>This Advisory describes an issue that impacts Arista Wireless Access Points. Any entity with the ability to authenticate via SSH to an affected AP as the “config” user is able to cause a privilege escalation via spawning a bash shell. The SSH CLI session does not require high permissions to exploit this vulnerability, but the config password is required to establish the session. The spawned shell is able to obtain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30997 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30997</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to obtain root access due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  254638.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30998 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30998</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to obtain root access due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  254649.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38368 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38368</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could disclose sensitive information to a local user to do improper permission controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  261195.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38370 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38370</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1, under certain configurations, could allow a user on the network to install malicious packages.  IBM X-Force ID:  261197.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3043 | Zigbee co-ordinator realignment packet may lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3043</link><description>An unauthenticated IEEE 802.15.4 'co-ordinator realignment' packet can be used to force Zigbee nodes to change their network identifier (pan ID), leading to a denial of service. This packet type is not useful in production and should be used only for PHY qualification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38371 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38371</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  261198.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42014 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42014</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.2.0.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  265511.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31916 | IBM OpenBMC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31916</link><description>IBM OpenBMC FW1050.00 through FW1050.10 BMCWeb HTTPS server component could disclose sensitive URI content to an unauthorized actor that bypasses authentication channels.  IBM X-ForceID:  290026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42011 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition tapjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42011</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.1 and 6.2 does not restrict or incorrectly restricts frame objects or UI layers that belong to another application or domain, which can lead to user confusion about which interface the user is interacting with.  IBM X-Force ID:  265508.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24792 | Panic when parsing invalid palette-color images in golang.org/x/image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24792</link><description>Parsing a corrupt or malicious image with invalid color indices can cause a panic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35260 | Microsoft Dataverse Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35260</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5334 | External Control of File Name or Path in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5334</link><description>External Control of File Name or Path in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5547 | Relative Path Traversal in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5547</link><description>Relative Path Traversal in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5548 | Path Traversal in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5548</link><description>Path Traversal in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35153 | IBM WebSphere Application Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35153</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  292640.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39374 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39374</link><description>TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitters are vulnerable to an attacker exploiting a hidden admin account that can be accessed through the use of hard-coded credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39375 | Use of Client-Side Authentication in TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39375</link><description>TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitters are vulnerable to an attacker bypassing authentication and gaining administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39376 | Improper Access Control In TELSAT MarKoni FM Transmitter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39376</link><description>TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitters are vulnerable to users gaining unauthorized access to sensitive information or performing actions beyond their designated permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28820 | Buffer overflow in the extract_openvpn_cr function in openvpn-cr.c in openvpn-auth-ldap (aka the Three Rings Auth-LDAP plugin for OpenVPN) 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28820</link><description>Buffer overflow in the extract_openvpn_cr function in openvpn-cr.c in openvpn-auth-ldap (aka the Three Rings Auth-LDAP plugin for OpenVPN) 2.0.4 allows attackers with a valid LDAP username and who can control the challenge/response password field to pass a string with more than 14 colons into this field and cause a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39373 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command in TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39373</link><description>TELSAT marKoni FM Transmitters are vulnerable to a command injection vulnerability through the manipulation of settings and could allow an attacker to gain unauthorized access to the system with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30430 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30430</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information from trace logs.  IBM X-Force ID:  252183.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31883 | IBM Security Verify Access denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31883</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1, under certain configurations, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service due to asymmetric resource consumption.   IBM X-Force ID:  287615.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6388 | Marco Trevisan discovered that the Ubuntu Advantage Desktop Daemon, before version 1.12, leaks the Pro token to unprivileged users by passin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6388</link><description>Marco Trevisan discovered that the Ubuntu Advantage Desktop Daemon, before version 1.12, leaks the Pro token to unprivileged users by passing the token as an argument in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39669 | In the Console in Soffid IAM before 3.5.39, necessary checks were not applied to some Java objects. A malicious agent could possibly execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39669</link><description>In the Console in Soffid IAM before 3.5.39, necessary checks were not applied to some Java objects. A malicious agent could possibly execute arbitrary code in the Sync Server and compromise security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39153 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/info_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;dataType=news&amp;dat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39153</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/info_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;amp;dataType=news&amp;amp;dataTypeCN.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39154 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/keyWord_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;dataType=word&amp;...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39154</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/keyWord_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;amp;dataType=word&amp;amp;dataTypeCN.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39155 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/ipRecord_deal.php?mudi=add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39155</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/ipRecord_deal.php?mudi=add.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39156 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/keyWord_deal.php?mudi=add.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39156</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/keyWord_deal.php?mudi=add.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39157 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/ipRecord_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;dataType=&amp;dat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39157</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/ipRecord_deal.php?mudi=del&amp;amp;dataType=&amp;amp;dataID=1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39158 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/userSys_deal.php?mudi=infoSet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39158</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/userSys_deal.php?mudi=infoSet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6374 | lahirudanushka School Management System Subject Page subject.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6374</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /subject.php of the component Subject Page. The manipulation of the argument Subject Title/Sybillus Details leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269807.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1153 | Improper Access Control in Talya Informatics&amp;#x27; Travel APPS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1153</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Talya Informatics Travel APPS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Travel APPS: before v17.0.68.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1107 | IDOR in Talya Informatics&amp;#x27; Travel APPS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1107</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Talya Informatics Travel APPS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Travel APPS: before v17.0.68.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6372 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System customeradd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6372</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file customeradd.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269805 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6373 | itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System addproduct.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6373</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Online Food Ordering System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /addproduct.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269806 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6371 | itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6371</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file controller.php. The manipulation of the argument rmtype_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269804.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6369 | LabVantage LIMS POST Request cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6369</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. Affected is an unknown function of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;sdcid=LV_ReagentLot of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mode leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269802 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6370 | LabVantage LIMS POST Request cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6370</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /labvantage/rc?command=file&amp;amp;file=WEB-OPAL/pagetypes/bulletins/sendbulletin.jsp of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument bulletinbody leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269803.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6367 | LabVantage LIMS POST Request cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /labvantage/rc?command=file&amp;amp;file=WEB-CORE/elements/files/filesembedded.jsp of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument sdcid/keyid1/keyid2/keyid3 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269800. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6368 | LabVantage LIMS POST Request cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument param1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269801 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6262 | Portfolio Gallery – Image Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6262</link><description>The Portfolio Gallery – Image Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'PFG' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5535 | SSL_select_next_proto buffer overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5535</link><description>Issue summary: Calling the OpenSSL API function SSL_select_next_proto with an
empty supported client protocols buffer may cause a crash or memory contents to
be sent to the peer.

Impact summary: A buffer overread can have a range of potential consequences
such as unexpected application beahviour or a crash. In particular this issue
could result in up to 255 bytes of arbitrary private data from memory being sent
to the peer leading to a loss of confidentiality. However, only applications
that directly call the SSL_select_next_proto function with a 0 length list of
supported client protocols are affected by this issue. This would normally never
be a valid scenario and is typically not under attacker control but may occur by
accident in the case of a configuration or programming error in the calling
application.

The OpenSSL API function SSL_select_next_proto is typically used by TLS
applications that support ALPN (Application Layer Protocol Negotiation) or NPN
(Next Protocol Negotiation). NPN is older, was never standardised and
is deprecated in favour of ALPN. We believe that ALPN is significantly more
widely deployed than NPN. The SSL_select_next_proto function accepts a list of
protocols from the server and a list of protocols from the client and returns
the first protocol that appears in the server list that also appears in the
client list. In the case of no overlap between the two lists it returns the
first item in the client list. In either case it will signal whether an overlap
between the two lists was found. In the case where SSL_select_next_proto is
called with a zero length client list it fails to notice this condition and
returns the memory immediately following the client list pointer (and reports
that there was no overlap in the lists).

This function is typically called from a server side application callback for
ALPN or a client side application callback for NPN. In the case of ALPN the list
of protocols supplied by the client is guaranteed by libssl to never be zero in
length. The list of server protocols comes from the application and should never
normally be expected to be of zero length. In this case if the
SSL_select_next_proto function has been called as expected (with the list
supplied by the client passed in the client/client_len parameters), then the
application will not be vulnerable to this issue. If the application has
accidentally been configured with a zero length server list, and has
accidentally passed that zero length server list in the client/client_len
parameters, and has additionally failed to correctly handle a "no overlap"
response (which would normally result in a handshake failure in ALPN) then it
will be vulnerable to this problem.

In the case of NPN, the protocol permits the client to opportunistically select
a protocol when there is no overlap. OpenSSL returns the first client protocol
in the no overlap case in support of this. The list of client protocols comes
from the application and should never normally be expected to be of zero length.
However if the SSL_select_next_proto function is accidentally called with a
client_len of 0 then an invalid memory pointer will be returned instead. If the
application uses this output as the opportunistic protocol then the loss of
confidentiality will occur.

This issue has been assessed as Low severity because applications are most
likely to be vulnerable if they are using NPN instead of ALPN - but NPN is not
widely used. It also requires an application configuration or programming error.
Finally, this issue would not typically be under attacker control making active
exploitation unlikely.

The FIPS modules in 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue.

Due to the low severity of this issue we are not issuing new releases of
OpenSSL at this time. The fix will be included in the next releases when they
become available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0949 | Improper Access Control in Talya Informatics&amp;#x27; Elektraweb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0949</link><description>Improper Access Control, Missing Authorization, Incorrect Authorization, Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource, Missing Authentication, Weak Authentication, Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints vulnerability in Talya Informatics Elektraweb allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels, Manipulating Web Input to File System Calls, Embedding Scripts within Scripts, Malicious Logic Insertion, Modification of Windows Service Configuration, Malicious Root Certificate, Intent Spoof, WebView Exposure, Data Injected During Configuration, Incomplete Data Deletion in a Multi-Tenant Environment, Install New Service, Modify Existing Service, Install Rootkit, Replace File Extension Handlers, Replace Trusted Executable, Modify Shared File, Add Malicious File to Shared Webroot, Run Software at Logon, Disable Security Software.This issue affects Elektraweb: before v17.0.68.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 09:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7270 | Local Privilege Escalation via MSI installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7270</link><description>An issue was discovered in SoftMaker Office 2024 / NX before revision 1214 and SoftMaker FreeOffice 2014 before revision 1215. FreeOffice 2021 is also affected, but won't be fixed.





The SoftMaker Office and FreeOffice MSI installer files were found to
 produce a visible conhost.exe window running as the SYSTEM user when 
using the repair function of msiexec.exe. This allows a local, 
low-privileged attacker to use a chain of actions, to open a fully 
functional cmd.exe with the privileges of the SYSTEM user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0947 | Cookies Manipulation in Talya Informatics&amp;#x27; Elektraweb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0947</link><description>Reliance on Cookies without Validation and Integrity Checking vulnerability in Talya Informatics Elektraweb allows Session Credential Falsification through Manipulation, Accessing/Intercepting/Modifying HTTP Cookies, Manipulating Opaque Client-based Data Tokens.This issue affects Elektraweb: before v17.0.68.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4983 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.6.0- Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4983</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘video_color’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 08:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5601 | Create by Mediavine &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Schema Meta Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5601</link><description>The Create by Mediavine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Schema Meta shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 07:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22231 | Syndic cache directory creation is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22231</link><description>Syndic cache directory creation is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack in salt project which can lead a malicious attacker to create an arbitrary directory on a Salt master.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 07:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22232 | Specially crafted url can be created which leads to a directory traversal in the salt file server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22232</link><description>A specially crafted url can be created which leads to a directory traversal in the salt file server.
A malicious user can read an arbitrary file from a Salt master’s filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 07:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1330 | Kadence Blocks Pro &amp;lt; 2.3.8 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Option Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1330</link><description>The kadence-blocks-pro WordPress plugin before 2.3.8 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role using some of its shortcode's functionalities to leak arbitrary options from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3111 | H5P &amp;lt; 1.15.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3111</link><description>The Interactive Content  WordPress plugin before 1.15.8 does not validate uploads which could allow a Contributors and above to update malicious SVG files, leading to Stored Cross-Site Scripting issues</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4664 | WP Chat App &amp;lt; 3.6.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4664</link><description>The WP Chat App WordPress plugin before 3.6.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admins to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4704 |  Contact Form 7 &amp;lt; 5.9.5 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4704</link><description>The Contact Form 7 WordPress plugin before 5.9.5 has an open redirect that allows an attacker to utilize a false URL and redirect to the URL of their choosing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6283 | DethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URL Parameter of the De Gallery Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6283</link><description>The DethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL parameter of the De Gallery widget in all versions up to and including 2.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user clicks on the injected link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 04:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4569 | Elementor Addon Elements &amp;lt;= 1.13.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4569</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.13.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 04:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4570 | Elementor Addon Elements &amp;lt;= 1.13.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4570</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.13.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 04:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5289 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features &amp;lt;= 3.2.42 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Google Maps Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5289</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Google Maps widget parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.42 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6054 | Auto Featured Image &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6054</link><description>The Auto Featured Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'create_post_attachment_from_url' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>