<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-23525 | 1panel App Store vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23525</link><description>1Panel is an open-source, web-based control panel for Linux server management. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the 1Panel App Store when viewing application details. Malicious scripts can execute in the context of the user’s browser, potentially compromising session data or sensitive system interfaces. All versions of 1Panel up to and including v1.10.33-lts and v2.0.16 are affected. An attacker could publish a malicious application that, when loaded by users (locally or remotely), can execute arbitrary scripts. This may result in theft of user cookies, unauthorized access to system functions, or other actions that compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system. The vulnerability is caused by insufficient sanitization of content rendered by the MdEditor component with the `previewOnly` attribute enabled. Specifically, the App Store renders application README content without proper XSS protection, allowing script execution during content rendering; and similar issues exist in system upgrade-related components, which can be fixed by implementing proper XSS sanitization in the MdEditor component. These vulnerabilities can be mitigated by applying proper XSS protection and sanitization when rendering content in the MdEditor component. Safe versions with a patch incorporated are v1.10.34-lts and v2.0.17.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1126 | lwj flow SVG File FormResource.java uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1126</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in lwj flow up to a3d2fe8133db9d3b50fda4f66f68634640344641. This affects the function uploadFile of the file \flow-master\flow-front-rest\src\main\java\com\dragon\flow\web\resource\flow\FormResource.java of the component SVG File Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1125 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifidog_settings sub_412E7C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1125</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is the function sub_412E7C of the file /goform/set_wifidog_settings. Executing a manipulation of the argument wd_enable can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0863 | Sandbox escape in n8n Python task runner allows for arbitrary code execution on the underlying host.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0863</link><description>Using string formatting and exception handling, an attacker may bypass n8n's python-task-executor sandbox restrictions and run arbitrary unrestricted Python code in the underlying operating system.

The vulnerability can be exploited via the Code block by an authenticated user with basic permissions and can lead to a full n8n instance takeover on instances operating under "Internal" execution mode.

If the instance is operating under the  "External" execution mode (ex. n8n's official Docker image) - arbitrary code execution occurs inside a Sidecar container and not the main node, which significantly reduces the vulnerability impact.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1124 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter work_report.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1124</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /worksheet/work_report.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1123 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter work_mod.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1123</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /worksheet/work_mod.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1122 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter work_info.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1122</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /worksheet/work_info.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1121 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter del_workplan.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1121</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /worksheet/del_workplan.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1120 | Yonyou KSOA HTTP GET Parameter del_work.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1120</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Yonyou KSOA 9.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /worksheet/del_work.jsp of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1119 | itsourcecode Society Management System delete_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1119</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_activity.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument activity_id can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1118 | itsourcecode Society Management System add_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1118</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/add_activity.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Title results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15537 | Mapnik dbfile.cpp string_value heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15537</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Mapnik up to 4.2.0. This issue affects the function mapnik::dbf_file::string_value of the file plugins/input/shape/dbfile.cpp. Such manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15536 | BYVoid OpenCC MaxMatchSegmentation.cpp MaxMatchSegmentation heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15536</link><description>A weakness has been identified in BYVoid OpenCC up to 1.1.9. This vulnerability affects the function opencc::MaxMatchSegmentation of the file src/MaxMatchSegmentation.cpp. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. The attack is restricted to local execution. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Patch name: 345c9a50ab07018f1b4439776bad78a0d40778ec. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15535 | nicbarker clay clay.h Clay__MeasureTextCached null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15535</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in nicbarker clay up to 0.14. This affects the function Clay__MeasureTextCached in the library clay.h. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack is only possible with local access. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15534 | raysan5 raylib rtext.c LoadFontData integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15534</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in raysan5 raylib up to 909f040. Affected by this issue is the function LoadFontData of the file src/rtext.c. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is 5a3391fdce046bc5473e52afbd835dd2dc127146. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1112 | Sanluan PublicCMS Trade Address Deletion Endpoint TradeAddressController.java delete improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1112</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 5.202506.d. Affected is the function delete of the file publiccms-trade/src/main/java/com/publiccms/controller/web/trade/TradeAddressController.java of the component Trade Address Deletion Endpoint. Performing a manipulation of the argument ids results in improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1111 | Sanluan PublicCMS Task Template Management TaskTemplateAdminController.java save path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1111</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 5.202506.d. This impacts the function Save of the file com/publiccms/controller/admin/sys/TaskTemplateAdminController.java of the component Task Template Management Handler. Such manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15533 | raysan5 raylib rtext.c GenImageFontAtlas heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15533</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in raysan5 raylib up to 909f040. Affected by this vulnerability is the function GenImageFontAtlas of the file src/rtext.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called 5a3391fdce046bc5473e52afbd835dd2dc127146. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1110 | cijliu librtsp rtsp_parse_method buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1110</link><description>A flaw has been found in cijliu librtsp up to 2ec1a81ad65280568a0c7c16420d7c10fde13b04. This affects the function rtsp_parse_method. This manipulation causes buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 04:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1109 | cijliu librtsp rtsp_parse_request buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1109</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in cijliu librtsp up to 2ec1a81ad65280568a0c7c16420d7c10fde13b04. The impacted element is the function rtsp_parse_request. The manipulation results in buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 03:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1108 | cijliu librtsp rtsp_rely_dumps buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1108</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in cijliu librtsp up to 2ec1a81ad65280568a0c7c16420d7c10fde13b04. The affected element is the function rtsp_rely_dumps. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 03:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1106 | Chamilo LMS Legal Consent SocialController.php deleteLegal improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1106</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Chamilo LMS up to 2.0.0 Beta 1. This issue affects the function deleteLegal of the file src/CoreBundle/Controller/SocialController.php of the component Legal Consent Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument userId results in improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1107 | EyouCMS Member Avatar Diyajax.php check_userinfo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1107</link><description>A weakness has been identified in EyouCMS up to 1.7.1/5.0. Impacted is the function check_userinfo of the file Diyajax.php of the component Member Avatar Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument viewfile can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1105 | EasyCMS UserAction.class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1105</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in EasyCMS up to 1.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /UserAction.class.php. Such manipulation of the argument _order leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1066 | kalcaddle kodbox Compression zip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1066</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.61.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /?explorer/index/zip of the component Compression Handler. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1064 | bastillion-io Bastillion System Management SystemKtrl.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in bastillion-io Bastillion up to 4.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/main/java/io/bastillion/manage/control/SystemKtrl.java of the component System Management Module. Performing a manipulation results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1063 | bastillion-io Bastillion Public Key Management System AuthKeysKtrl.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1063</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in bastillion-io Bastillion up to 4.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main/java/io/bastillion/manage/control/AuthKeysKtrl.java of the component Public Key Management System. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1062 | xiweicheng TMS HtmlUtil.java summary server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1062</link><description>A flaw has been found in xiweicheng TMS up to 2.28.0. This affects the function Summary of the file src/main/java/com/lhjz/portal/util/HtmlUtil.java. This manipulation of the argument url causes server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1061 | xiweicheng TMS FileController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1061</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in xiweicheng TMS up to 2.28.0. Affected by this issue is the function Upload of the file src/main/java/com/lhjz/portal/controller/FileController.java. The manipulation of the argument filename results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1059 | FeMiner wms chkuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1059</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FeMiner wms up to 9cad1f1b179a98b9547fd003c23b07c7594775fa. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/chkuser.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1050 | risesoft-y9 Digital-Infrastructure REST Authenticate Endpoint Y9PlatformUtil.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1050</link><description>A flaw has been found in risesoft-y9 Digital-Infrastructure up to 9.6.7. This affects an unknown function of the file source-code/src/main/java/net/risesoft/util/Y9PlatformUtil.java of the component REST Authenticate Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1049 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1049</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl. Such manipulation of the argument TicketID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1048 | LigeroSmart index.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1048</link><description>A weakness has been identified in LigeroSmart up to 6.1.26. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /otrs/index.pl?Action=AgentTicketZoom. This manipulation of the argument TicketID causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15532 | Open5GS Timer resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15532</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Timer Handler. The manipulation results in resource consumption. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is identified as c7c131f8d2cb1195ada5e0e691b6868ebcd8a845. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15531 | Open5GS context.c sgwc_bearer_add assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15531</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This vulnerability affects the function sgwc_bearer_add of the file src/sgwc/context.c. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15530 | Open5GS s11-handler.c assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15530</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This affects the function sgwc_s11_handle_create_indirect_data_forwarding_tunnel_request of the file /src/sgwc/s11-handler.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to reachable assertion. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The issue report is flagged as already-fixed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10484 | Registration &amp;amp; Login with Mobile Phone Number for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10484</link><description>The Registration &amp; Login with Mobile Phone Number for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity prior to authenticating them via the fma_lwp_set_session_php_fun() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to authenticate as any user on the site, including administrators, without a valid password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14078 | PAYGENT for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Callback Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14078</link><description>The PAYGENT for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This is due to missing authorization checks on the paygent_check_webhook function combined with the paygent_permission_callback function unconditionally returning true on line 199. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate payment callbacks and modify order statuses by sending forged payment notifications via the `/wp-json/paygent/v1/check/` endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8615 | CubeWP &amp;lt;= 1.1.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cubewp_shortcode_taxonomy Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8615</link><description>The CubeWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's cubewp_shortcode_taxonomy shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0725 | Integrate Dynamics 365 CRM &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Field Mapping Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0725</link><description>The Integrate Dynamics 365 CRM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12129 | CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12129</link><description>The CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.27 via the /cubewp-posts/v1/query-new and /cubewp-posts/v1/query REST API endpoints due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14478 | Demo Importer Plus &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Blind XML External Entity Injection via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14478</link><description>The Demo Importer Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to XML External Entity Injection (XXE) in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.9 via the SVG file upload functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to achieve code execution in vulnerable configurations. This only impacts sites on versions of PHP older than 8.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12984 | Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp;amp; AdSense &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12984</link><description>The Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0691 | CM E-Mail Blacklist &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;black_email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0691</link><description>The CM E-Mail Blacklist – Simple email filtering for safer registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'black_email' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0808 | Spin Wheel &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Unauthenticated Client-Side Prize Manipulation via &amp;#x27;prize_index&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0808</link><description>The Spin Wheel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to client-side prize manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This is due to the plugin trusting client-supplied prize selection data without server-side validation or randomization. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate which prize they win by modifying the 'prize_index' parameter sent to the server, allowing them to always select the most valuable prizes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0833 | Team Section Block &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Network Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0833</link><description>The Team Section Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied social network link URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12168 | Phrase TMS Integration for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.7.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12168</link><description>The Phrase TMS Integration for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_delete_log' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete log files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12825 | User Registration Using Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12825</link><description>The User Registration Using Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_cf7_form_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve form settings which includes Facebook app secrets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14029 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Event Approval via &amp;#x27;eventlist&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14029</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_admin_event_approval() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve arbitrary events via the 'eventlist' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13725 | Gutenberg Thim Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read via &amp;#x27;iconSVG&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13725</link><description>The Gutenberg Thim Blocks – Page Builder, Gutenberg Blocks for the Block Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file reads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient path validation in the server-side rendering of the thim-blocks/icon block. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server via the 'iconSVG' parameter, which can contain sensitive information such as wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14463 | Payment Button for PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.41 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Order Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14463</link><description>The Payment Button for PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized order creation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3.41. This is due to the plugin exposing a public AJAX endpoint (`wppaypalcheckout_ajax_process_order`) that processes checkout results without any authentication or server-side verification of the PayPal transaction. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary orders on the site with any chosen transaction ID, payment status, product name, amount, or customer information via direct POST requests to the AJAX endpoint, granted they can bypass basic parameter validation. If email sending is enabled, the plugin will also trigger purchase receipt emails to any email address supplied in the request, leading to order database corruption and unauthorized outgoing emails without any real PayPal transaction taking place.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0682 | Church Admin &amp;lt;= 5.0.28 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;audio_url&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0682</link><description>The Church Admin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.28 due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs in the 'audio_url' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0820 | RepairBuddy &amp;lt;= 4.1116 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Signature Upload to Orders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0820</link><description>The RepairBuddy – Repair Shop CRM &amp; Booking Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference due to missing capability checks on the wc_upload_and_save_signature_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1116. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary signatures to any order in the system, potentially modifying order metadata and triggering unauthorized status changes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 04:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12002 | Feeds for YouTube Pro &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12002</link><description>The Feeds for YouTube Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0 via the 'sby_check_wp_submit' AJAX action. This is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied data and the use of that data in a file operation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information, granted the 'Save Featured Images' setting is enabled and 'Disable WP Posts' is disabled. Note: This vulnerability only affects the Pro version of Feeds for YouTube.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12718 | Quick Contact Form &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Unauthenticated Open Mail Relay</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12718</link><description>The Quick Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Mail Relay in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.6. This is due to the 'qcf_validate_form' AJAX endpoint allowing a user controlled parameter to set the 'from' email address. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails to arbitrary recipients utilizing the server. The information is limited to the contact form submission details.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14075 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;email&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14075</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.7. This is due to the plugin exposing the 'hotel_booking_fetch_customer_info' AJAX action to unauthenticated users without proper capability checks, relying only on a nonce for protection. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive customer information including full names, addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses by providing a valid email address and a publicly accessible nonce.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14450 | Wallet System for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Wallet Balance Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14450</link><description>The Wallet System for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'change_wallet_fund_request_status_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to manipulate wallet withdrawal requests and arbitrarily increase their wallet balance or decrease other users' balances.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14632 | Filr – Secure document library &amp;lt;= 1.2.11 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14632</link><description>The Filr – Secure document library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via unrestricted file upload in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.11 due to insufficient file type restrictions in the FILR_Uploader class. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload malicious HTML files containing JavaScript that will execute whenever a user accesses the uploaded file, granted they have permission to create or edit posts with the 'filr' post type.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15403 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt;= 6.0.7.1 - Privilege Escalation via admin_order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15403</link><description>The RegistrationMagic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.7.1. This is due to the 'add_menu' function is accessible via the 'rm_user_exists' AJAX action and allows arbitrary updates to the 'admin_order' setting. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to injecting an empty slug into the order parameter, and manipulate the plugin's menu generation logic, and when the admin menu is subsequently built, the plugin adds 'manage_options' capability for the target role. Note: The vulnerability can only be exploited unauthenticated, but further privilege escalation requires at least a subscriber user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0518 | XSS in Secure Access Consoles prior to 14.20</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0518</link><description>CVE-2026-0518 is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in versions of 
Secure Access prior to 14.20. An attacker with administrative privileges
 can interfere with another administrator’s use of the console.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0519 | Information Disclosure in Secure Access Between 12.70 and 14.20</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0519</link><description>In Secure Access 12.70 and prior to 14.20, the logging 
subsystem may write an unredacted authentication token to logs under 
certain configurations. Any party with access to those logs could read 
the token and reuse it to access an integrated system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0517 | Denial of Service in Secure Access Servers Prior to 14.20.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0517</link><description>CVE-2026-0517 is a denial-of-service vulnerability in versions of Secure
 Access Server prior to 14.20. An attacker can send a specially crafted packet 
to a server and cause the server to crash</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22816 | Gradle fails to disable repositories which can expose builds to malicious artifacts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22816</link><description>Gradle is a build automation tool, and its native-platform tool provides Java bindings for native APIs. When resolving dependencies in versions before 9.3.0, some exceptions were not treated as fatal errors and would not cause a repository to be disabled. If a build encountered one of these exceptions, Gradle would continue to the next repository in the list and potentially resolve dependencies from a different repository. If a Gradle build used an unresolvable host name, Gradle would continue to work as long as all dependencies could be resolved from another repository. An unresolvable host name could be caused by allowing a repository's domain name registration to lapse or typo-ing the real domain name. This behavior could allow an attacker to register a service under the host name used by the build and serve malicious artifacts. The attack requires the repository to be listed before others in the build configuration. Gradle has introduced a change in behavior in Gradle 9.3.0 to stop searching other repositories when encountering these errors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22865 | Gradle&amp;#x27;s failure to disable repositories failing to answer can expose builds to malicious artifacts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22865</link><description>Gradle is a build automation tool, and its native-platform tool provides Java bindings for native APIs. When resolving dependencies in versions before 9.3.0, some exceptions were not treated as fatal errors and would not cause a repository to be disabled. If a build encountered one of these exceptions, Gradle would continue to the next repository in the list and potentially resolve dependencies from a different repository. An exception like NoHttpResponseException can indicate transient errors. If the errors persist after a maximum number of retries, Gradle would continue to the next repository. This behavior could allow an attacker to disrupt the service of a repository and leverage another repository to serve malicious artifacts. This attack requires the attacker to have control over a repository after the disrupted repository. Gradle has introduced a change in behavior in Gradle 9.3.0 to stop searching other repositories when encountering these errors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15528 | Open5GS GTPv2 Bearer Response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15528</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component GTPv2 Bearer Response Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 98f76e98df35cd6a35e868aa62715db7f8141ac1. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15529 | Open5GS s5c-handler.c sgwc_s5c_handle_create_session_response denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15529</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. Affected by this issue is the function sgwc_s5c_handle_create_session_response of the file src/sgwc/s5c-handler.c. Performing a manipulation results in denial of service. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named b19cf6a2dbf5d30811be4488bf059c865bd7d1d2. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23745 | node-tar Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Overwrite and Symlink Poisoning via Insufficient Path Sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23745</link><description>node-tar is a Tar for Node.js. The node-tar library (&lt;= 7.5.2) fails to sanitize the linkpath of Link (hardlink) and SymbolicLink entries when preservePaths is false (the default secure behavior). This allows malicious archives to bypass the extraction root restriction, leading to Arbitrary File Overwrite via hardlinks and Symlink Poisoning via absolute symlink targets. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20960 | Microsoft Power Apps Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20960</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21223 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56451 | Cross site scripting vulnerability in seeyon Zhiyuan A8+ Collaborative Management Software 7.0 via the topValue parameter to the seeyon/main...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56451</link><description>Cross site scripting vulnerability in seeyon Zhiyuan A8+ Collaborative Management Software 7.0 via the topValue parameter to the seeyon/main.do endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23643 | CakePHP PaginatorHelper::limitControl() vulnerable to reflected cross-site-scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23643</link><description>CakePHP is a rapid development framework for PHP. The PaginatorHelper::limitControl() method has a cross-site-scripting vulnerability via query string parameter manipulation. This issue has been fixed in 5.2.12 and 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23800 | WordPress Modular DS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23800</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Modular DS modular-connector allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Modular DS: from 2.5.2 before 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25297 | Poll, Survey &amp;amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage &amp;lt; 19.6.25 Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25297</link><description>Poll, Survey &amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage Wordpress plugin versions prior to 19.6.25 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via multiple parameters due to insufficient input validation and output escaping. An unauthenticated attacker can inject arbitrary script into content that executes when a victim views an affected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10064 | Omni Secure Files &amp;lt; 0.1.14 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10064</link><description>Omni Secure Files plugin versions prior to 0.1.14 contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the bundled plupload example endpoint. The /wp-content/plugins/omni-secure-files/plupload/examples/upload.php handler allows unauthenticated uploads without enforcing safe file type restrictions, enabling an attacker to place attacker-controlled files under the plugin's uploads directory. This can lead to remote code execution if a server-executable file type is uploaded and subsequently accessed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23735 | Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization (&amp;#x27;Race Condition&amp;#x27;) in graphql-modules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23735</link><description>GraphQL Modules is a toolset of libraries and guidelines dedicated to create reusable, maintainable, testable and extendable modules out of your GraphQL server. From 2.2.1 to before 2.4.1 and 3.1.1, when 2 or more parallel requests are made which trigger the same service, the context of the requests is mixed up in the service when the context is injected via @ExecutionContext(). ExecutionContext is often used to pass authentication tokens from incoming requests to services loading data from backend APIs. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.1 and 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23742 | Skipper arbitrary code execution through lua filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23742</link><description>Skipper is an HTTP router and reverse proxy for service composition. The default skipper configuration before 0.23.0 was -lua-sources=inline,file. The problem starts if untrusted users can create lua filters, because of -lua-sources=inline , for example through a Kubernetes Ingress resource. The configuration inline allows these user to create a script that is able to read the filesystem accessible to the skipper process and if the user has access to read the logs, they an read skipper secrets. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.23.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23744 | REC in MCPJam inspector due to HTTP Endpoint exposes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23744</link><description>MCPJam inspector is the local-first development platform for MCP servers. Versions 1.4.2 and earlier are vulnerable to remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, which allows an attacker to send a crafted HTTP request that triggers the installation of an MCP server, leading to RCE. Since MCPJam inspector by default listens on 0.0.0.0 instead of 127.0.0.1, an attacker can trigger the RCE remotely via a simple HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23731 | WeGIA Clickjacking Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23731</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, The web application is vulnerable to clickjacking attacks. The WeGIA application does not send any defensive HTTP headers related to framing protection. In particular, X-Frame-Options is missing andContent-Security-Policy with frame-ancestors directive is not configured. Because of this, an attacker can load any WeGIA page inside a malicious HTML document, overlay deceptive elements, hide real buttons, or force accidental interaction with sensitive workflows. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23728 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=DestinoControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23728</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=DestinoControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23729 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarDescricao, nomeClasse=ProdutoControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23729</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarDescricao and nomeClasse=ProdutoControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23730 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=ProdutoControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23730</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=ProdutoControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23724 | WeGIA Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) – atendido_idatendido Parameter on Occurrence Registration Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23724</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the html/atendido/cadastro_ocorrencia.php endpoint of the WeGIA application. The application does not sanitize user-controlled data before rendering it inside the “Atendido” selection dropdown. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23725 | WeGIA Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) – nome Parameter on Adopters Information Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23725</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the html/pet/adotantes/cadastro_adotante.php and html/pet/adotantes/informacao_adotantes.php endpoint of the WeGIA application. The application does not sanitize user-controlled input before rendering it inside the Adopters Information table, allowing persistent JavaScript injection. Any user who visits the page will have the payload executed automatically. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23726 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=TipoEntradaControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23726</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, An Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=TipoEntradaControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23727 | WeGIA has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in control.php Endpoint via nextPage Parameter (metodo=listarTodos, nomeClasse=TipoSaidaControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23727</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the /WeGIA/controle/control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically through the nextPage parameter when combined with metodo=listarTodos and nomeClasse=TipoSaidaControle. The application fails to validate or restrict the nextPage parameter, allowing attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external websites. This can be abused for phishing attacks, credential theft, malware distribution, and social engineering using the trusted WeGIA domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69581 | An issue was discovered in Chamillo LMS 1.11.2. The Social Network /personal_data endpoint exposes full sensitive user information even afte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69581</link><description>An issue was discovered in Chamillo LMS 1.11.2. The Social Network /personal_data endpoint exposes full sensitive user information even after logout because proper cache-control is missing. Using the browser back button restores all personal data, allowing unauthorized users on the same device to view confidential information. This leads to profiling, impersonation, targeted attacks, and significant privacy risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23722 | WeGIA has a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability allowing arbitrary code execution and UI redressing.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23722</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA system, specifically within the html/memorando/insere_despacho.php file. The application fails to properly sanitize or encode user-supplied input via the id_memorando GET parameter before reflecting it into the HTML source (likely inside a</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23723 | WeGIA has a Critical SQL Injection in Atendido_ocorrenciaControle via id_memorando parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23723</link><description>WeGIA is a web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to 3.6.2, an authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the Atendido_ocorrenciaControle endpoint via the id_memorando parameter. This flaw allows for full database exfiltration, exposure of sensitive PII, and potential arbitrary file reads in misconfigured environments. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23634 | Pepr Overly Permissive RBAC ClusterRole in Admin Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23634</link><description>Pepr is a type safe K8s middleware. Prior to 1.0.5 , Pepr defaults to a cluster-admin RBAC configuration and does not explicitly force or enforce least-privilege guidance for module authors. The default behavior exists to make the “getting started” experience smooth: new users can experiment with Pepr and create resources dynamically without needing to pre-configure RBAC. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23645 | SiYuan Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Unrestricted SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23645</link><description>SiYuan is self-hosted, open source personal knowledge management software. Prior to 3.5.4-dev2, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SiYuan Note. The application does not sanitize uploaded SVG files. If a user uploads and views a malicious SVG file (e.g., imported from an untrusted source), arbitrary JavaScript code is executed in the context of their authenticated session. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.4-dev2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47816 | Thecus N4800Eco Nas Server Control Panel - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47816</link><description>Thecus N4800Eco NAS Server Control Panel contains a command injection vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary system commands through user management endpoints. Attackers can inject commands via username and batch user creation parameters to execute shell commands with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47818 | DupTerminator 1.4.5639.37199 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47818</link><description>DupTerminator 1.4.5639.37199 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by inputting a long character string in the Excluded text box. Attackers can generate a payload of 8000 repeated characters to trigger the application to stop working on Windows 10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47820 | Ubee EVW327 - &amp;#x27;Enable Remote Access&amp;#x27; Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47820</link><description>Ubee EVW327 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to enable remote access without user interaction. Attackers can craft a malicious webpage that automatically submits a form to change router remote access settings to port 8080 without the user's consent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47821 | RarmaRadio 2.72.8 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47821</link><description>RarmaRadio 2.72.8 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing network configuration fields with large character buffers. Attackers can generate a 100,000 character buffer and paste it into multiple network settings fields to trigger application instability and potential crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47822 | DiskBoss Service 12.2.18 - &amp;#x27;diskbsa.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47822</link><description>DiskBoss Service 12.2.18 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its binary path configuration that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path by placing malicious executables in potential path locations to gain system-level access during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47823 | ePowerSvc 6.0.3008.0 - &amp;#x27;ePowerSvc.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47823</link><description>Acer ePowerSvc 6.0.3008.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47824 | iDailyDiary 4.30 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47824</link><description>iDailyDiary 4.30 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the preferences tab name field. Attackers can paste a 2,000,000 character buffer into the default diary tab name to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47825 | Acer Updater Service 1.2.3500.0 - &amp;#x27;UpdaterService.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47825</link><description>Acer Updater Service 1.2.3500.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files\Acer\Acer Updater\ to inject malicious executables that will run with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47826 | Acer Backup Manager Module 3.0.0.99 - &amp;#x27;IScheduleSvc.exe&amp;#x27;  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47826</link><description>Acer Backup Manager 3.0.0.99 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the NTI IScheduleSvc service that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\NTI\Acer Backup Manager\ to inject malicious executables that would run with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47827 | WebSSH for iOS 14.16.10 - &amp;#x27;mashREPL&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47827</link><description>WebSSH for iOS 14.16.10 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the mashREPL tool that allows attackers to crash the application by pasting malformed input. Attackers can trigger the vulnerability by copying a 300-character buffer of repeated 'A' characters into the mashREPL input field, causing the application to crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47828 | BOOTP Turbo 2.0.0.1253 - &amp;#x27;bootpt.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47828</link><description>BOOTP Turbo 2.0.0.1253 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path to execute arbitrary code with elevated LocalSystem privileges during system startup or reboot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47829 | DHCP Broadband 4.1.0.1503 - &amp;#x27;dhcpt.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47829</link><description>DHCP Broadband 4.1.0.1503 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its service configuration that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\DHCP Broadband 4\dhcpt.exe' to inject malicious code that will execute during service startup with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47831 | Sandboxie 5.49.7 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47831</link><description>Sandboxie 5.49.7 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overflowing the container folder input field. Attackers can paste a large buffer of repeated characters into the Sandbox container folder setting to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47832 | Sandboxie Plus 0.7.4 - &amp;#x27;SbieSvc&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47832</link><description>Sandboxie Plus 0.7.4 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the SbieSvc service that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47833 | WifiHotSpot 1.0.0.0 - &amp;#x27;WifiHotSpotService.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47833</link><description>WifiHotSpot 1.0.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its WifiHotSpotService.exe that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path during system startup or reboot to inject and run malicious executables with LocalSystem permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47834 | Schlix CMS 2.2.6-6 - &amp;#x27;title&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (Authenticated)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47834</link><description>Schlix CMS 2.2.6-6 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into category titles. Attackers can create a new contact category with a script payload that will execute when the page is viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47835 | Freeter 1.2.1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47835</link><description>Freeter 1.2.1 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to store malicious payloads in custom widget titles and files. Attackers can craft malicious files with embedded scripts that execute when victims interact with the application, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47836 | Markdown Explorer 0.1.1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47836</link><description>Markdown Explorer 0.1.1 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious code through file uploads and editor inputs. Attackers can upload markdown files with embedded JavaScript payloads to execute remote commands and potentially gain system access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47837 | Markdownify 1.2.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47837</link><description>Markdownify 1.2.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to store malicious payloads within markdown files. Attackers can upload crafted markdown files with embedded scripts that execute when the file is opened, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47838 | Markright 1.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47838</link><description>Markright 1.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to embed malicious payloads in markdown files. Attackers can upload specially crafted markdown files that execute arbitrary JavaScript when opened, potentially enabling remote code execution on the victim's system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47839 | Marky 0.0.1 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47839</link><description>Marky 0.0.1 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into markdown files. Attackers can upload crafted markdown files with embedded JavaScript payloads that execute when the file is opened, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47840 | Moeditor 0.2.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47840</link><description>Moeditor 0.2.0 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to store malicious payloads within markdown files. Attackers can upload specially crafted markdown files with embedded JavaScript that execute when opened, potentially enabling remote code execution on the victim's system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47841 | SnipCommand 0.1.0 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47841</link><description>SnipCommand 0.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious payloads into command snippets. Attackers can execute arbitrary code by embedding malicious JavaScript that triggers remote command execution through file or title inputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47842 | StudyMD 0.3.2 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47842</link><description>StudyMD 0.3.2 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into markdown files. Attackers can upload crafted markdown files with embedded JavaScript payloads that execute when the file is opened, potentially enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47844 | Xmind 2020 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47844</link><description>Xmind 2020 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious payloads into mind mapping files or custom headers. Attackers can craft malicious files with embedded JavaScript that execute system commands when opened, enabling remote code execution through mouse interactions or file opening.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47845 | Spy Emergency 25.0.650 -  Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47845</link><description>Spy Emergency 25.0.650 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configurations that allows local attackers to execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted file paths in SpyEmergencyHealth.exe and SpyEmergencySrv.exe to inject malicious code during system startup or service restart.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47847 | Disk Sorter Server 13.6.12 - &amp;#x27;Disk Sorter Server&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47847</link><description>Disk Sorter Server 13.6.12 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its binary path configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Disk Sorter Server\bin\disksrs.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23490 | pyasn1 has a DoS vulnerability in decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23490</link><description>pyasn1 is a generic ASN.1 library for Python. Prior to 0.6.2, a Denial-of-Service issue has been found that leads to memory exhaustion from malformed RELATIVE-OID with excessive continuation octets. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23535 | wlc Path traversal: Unsanitized API slugs in download command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23535</link><description>wlc is a Weblate command-line client using Weblate's REST API. Prior to 1.17.2, the multi-translation download could write to an arbitrary location when instructed by a crafted server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.17.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68924 | In Umbraco UmbracoForms through 8.13.16, an authenticated attacker can supply a malicious WSDL (aka Webservice) URL as a data source for rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68924</link><description>In Umbraco UmbracoForms through 8.13.16, an authenticated attacker can supply a malicious WSDL (aka Webservice) URL as a data source for remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48647 | In cpm_fwtp_msg_handler of cpm/google/lib/tracepoint/cpm_fwtp_ipc.c, there is a possible memory overwrite due to improper input validation. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48647</link><description>In cpm_fwtp_msg_handler of cpm/google/lib/tracepoint/cpm_fwtp_ipc.c, there is a possible memory overwrite due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62291 | In the eap-mschapv2 plugin (client-side) in strongSwan before 6.0.3, a malicious EAP-MSCHAPv2 server can send a crafted message of size 6 th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62291</link><description>In the eap-mschapv2 plugin (client-side) in strongSwan before 6.0.3, a malicious EAP-MSCHAPv2 server can send a crafted message of size 6 through 8, and cause an integer underflow that potentially results in a heap-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15032 | CVE-2025-15032: Increased Spoofing risk; custom new window missing about:blank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15032</link><description>Missing about:blank indicator in custom-sized new windows in Dia before 1.9.0 on macOS could allow an attacker to spoof a trusted domain in the window title and mislead users about the current site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61873 | Best Practical Request Tracker (RT) before 4.4.9, 5.0.9, and 6.0.2 allows CSV Injection via ticket values when TSV export is used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61873</link><description>Best Practical Request Tracker (RT) before 4.4.9, 5.0.9, and 6.0.2 allows CSV Injection via ticket values when TSV export is used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51602 | mmstu.c in VideoLAN VLC media player before 3.0.22 allows an out-of-bounds read and denial of service via a crafted 0x01 response from an MM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51602</link><description>mmstu.c in VideoLAN VLC media player before 3.0.22 allows an out-of-bounds read and denial of service via a crafted 0x01 response from an MMS server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43904 | In SchedMD Slurm before 24.11.5, 24.05.8, and 23.11.11, the accounting system can allow a Coordinator to promote a user to Administrator.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43904</link><description>In SchedMD Slurm before 24.11.5, 24.05.8, and 23.11.11, the accounting system can allow a Coordinator to promote a user to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31510 | In the portal in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.21.0, cross-site scripting (XSS) allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML (int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31510</link><description>In the portal in LemonLDAP::NG before 2.21.0, cross-site scripting (XSS) allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML (into the login page) via the tab parameter, for Choice authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24531 | In OpenSC pam_pkcs11 before 0.6.13, pam_sm_authenticate() wrongly returns PAM_IGNORE in many error situations (such as an error triggered by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24531</link><description>In OpenSC pam_pkcs11 before 0.6.13, pam_sm_authenticate() wrongly returns PAM_IGNORE in many error situations (such as an error triggered by a smartcard before login), allowing authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24528 | In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.22 (with incremental propagation), there is an integer overflow for a large update size to resize() in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24528</link><description>In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.22 (with incremental propagation), there is an integer overflow for a large update size to resize() in kdb_log.c. An authenticated attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write and kadmind daemon crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0629 | Authentication Bypass in Password Recovery Feature via Local Web App on Multiple VIGI Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0629</link><description>Authentication bypass in the password recovery feature of the local web interface across multiple VIGI camera models allows an attacker on the LAN to reset the admin password without verification by manipulating client-side state. Attackers can gain full administrative access to the device, compromising configuration and network security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44210 | This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44210</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved permissions checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44238 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to corrupt coproces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44238</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54556 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. A user may be able to view rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54556</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. A user may be able to view restricted content from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24089 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enume...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24089</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24090 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enume...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24090</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. An app may be able to enumerate a user's installed apps.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31186 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16.3. An app may be able to bypass Privacy pref...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31186</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in Xcode 16.3. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43508 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43508</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in macOS Tahoe 26.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23528 | Dask distributed Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Jupyter Proxy and Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23528</link><description>Dask distributed is a distributed task scheduler for Dask. Prior to 2026.1.0, when Jupyter Lab, jupyter-server-proxy, and Dask distributed are all run together, it is possible to craft a URL which will result in code being executed by Jupyter due to a cross-side-scripting (XSS) bug in the Dask dashboard. It is possible for attackers to craft a phishing URL that assumes Jupyter Lab and Dask may be running on localhost and using default ports. If a user clicks on the malicious link it will open an error page in the Dask Dashboard via the Jupyter Lab proxy which will cause code to be executed by the default Jupyter Python kernel. This vulnerability is fixed in 2026.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23529 | Arbitrary File Read in Google BigQuery Sink connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23529</link><description>Kafka Connect BigQuery Connector is an implementation of a sink connector from Apache Kafka to Google BigQuery. Prior to 2.11.0, there is an arbitrary file read in Google BigQuery Sink connector. Aiven's Google BigQuery Kafka Connect Sink connector requires Google Cloud credential configurations for authentication to BigQuery services. During connector configuration, users can supply credential JSON files that are processed by Google authentication libraries. The service fails to validate externally-sourced credential configurations before passing them to the authentication libraries. An attacker can exploit this by providing a malicious credential configuration containing crafted credential_source.file paths or credential_source.url endpoints, resulting in arbitrary file reads or SSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0949 | PEM versions prior to 9.8.1 are affected by a stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows users with access to the Manage Ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0949</link><description>PEM versions prior to 9.8.1 are affected by a stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows users with access to the Manage Charts menu to inject arbitrary JavaScript when creating a new chart, which is then executed by any user accessing the chart. By default only the superuser and users with pem_admin or pem_super_admin privileges are able to access the Manage Charts menu.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23523 | Dive allows One-click Remote Code Execution through Deep Links for MCP Install</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23523</link><description>Dive is an open-source MCP Host Desktop Application that enables integration with function-calling LLMs. Prior to 0.13.0, crafted deeplink can install an attacker-controlled MCP server configuration without sufficient user confirmation and can lead to arbitrary local command execution on the victim’s machine. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22782 | RustFS RPC signature verification logs shared secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22782</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. From &gt;= 1.0.0-alpha.1 to 1.0.0-alpha.79, invalid RPC signatures cause the server to log the shared HMAC secret (and expected signature), which exposes the secret to log readers and enables forged RPC calls. In crates/ecstore/src/rpc/http_auth.rs, the invalid signature branch logs sensitive data. This log line includes secret and expected_signature, both derived from the shared HMAC key. Any invalidly signed request triggers this path. The function is reachable from RPC and admin request handlers. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.0-alpha.80.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70746 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the timeZone parameter of the fromSetSysTime function. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70746</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the timeZone parameter of the fromSetSysTime function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29943 | Write what were condition within AMD CPUs may allow an admin-privileged attacker to modify the configuration of the CPU pipeline potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29943</link><description>Write what were condition within AMD CPUs may allow an admin-privileged attacker to modify the configuration of the CPU pipeline potentially resulting in the corruption of the stack pointer inside an SEV-SNP guest.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71020 | Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the security parameter of the sub_4C408 function. This vulnerability al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71020</link><description>Tenda AX-1806 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the security parameter of the sub_4C408 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21623 | Extension - stackideas.com - Persistent XSS in EasyDiscuss component 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21623</link><description>Lack of input filterung leads to a persistent XSS vulnerability in the forum post handling of the Easy Discuss component for Joomla.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21624 | Extension - stackideas.com - Persistent XSS in EasyDiscuss component 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21624</link><description>Lack of input filterung leads to a persistent XSS vulnerability in the user avatar text handling of the Easy Discuss component for Joomla.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21625 | Extension - stackideas.com - Lack of mime type validation in EasyDiscuss component 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21625</link><description>User provided uploads to the Easy Discuss component for Joomla aren't properly validated. Uploads are purely checked by file extensions, no mime type checks are happening.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68921 | SteelSeries Nahimic 3 1.10.7 allows Directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68921</link><description>SteelSeries Nahimic 3 1.10.7 allows Directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15104 | Nu Html Checker (validator.nu) - Restriction bypass vulnerability allowing local SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15104</link><description>Nu Html Checker (validator.nu) contains a restriction bypass that allows remote attackers to make the server perform arbitrary HTTP/HTTPS requests to internal resources, including localhost services. While the validator implements hostname-based protections to block direct access to localhost and 127.0.0.1, these controls can be bypassed using DNS rebinding techniques or domains that resolve to loopback addresses.This issue affects The Nu Html Checker (vnu): latest (commit 23f090a11bab8d0d4e698f1ffc197a4fe226a9cd).</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0695 | Stored XSS in Time Entry Audit Trail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0695</link><description>In ConnectWise PSA versions older than 2026.1, Time Entry notes stored in the Time Entry Audit Trail may be rendered without applying output encoding to certain content. Under specific conditions, this may allow stored script code to execute in the context of a user’s browser when the affected content is displayed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0696 | Session Cookies Missing HttpOnly Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0696</link><description>In ConnectWise PSA versions older than 2026.1, certain session cookies were not set with the HttpOnly attribute. In some scenarios, this could allow client-side scripts access to session cookie values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14510 | ABB Ability OPTIMAX Authentication Bypass in Single-Sign On</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14510</link><description>Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm vulnerability in ABB ABB Ability OPTIMAX.This issue affects ABB Ability OPTIMAX: 6.1, 6.2, from 6.3.0 before 6.3.1-251120, from 6.4.0 before 6.4.1-251120.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14894 | CVE-2025-14894</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14894</link><description>Livewire Filemanager, commonly used in Laravel applications, contains LivewireFilemanagerComponent.php, which does not perform file type and MIME validation, allowing for RCE through upload of a malicious php file that can then be executed via the /storage/ URL if a commonly performed setup process within Laravel applications has been completed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0612 | CVE-2026-0612</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0612</link><description>The Librarian contains a information leakage vulnerability through the `web_fetch` tool, which can be used to retrieve arbitrary external content provided by an attacker, which can be used to proxy requests through The Librarian infrastructure. The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all versions of TheLibrarian.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0613 | CVE-2026-0613</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0613</link><description>The Librarian contains an internal port scanning vulnerability, facilitated by the `web_fetch` tool, which can be used with SSRF-style behavior to perform GET requests to internal IP addresses and services, enabling scanning of the Hertzner cloud environment that TheLibrarian uses. The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0615 | CVE-2026-0615</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0615</link><description>The Librarian `supervisord` status page can be retrieved by the `web_fetch` tool, which can be used to retrieve running processes within TheLibrarian backend.  The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0616 | CVE-2026-0616</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0616</link><description>TheLibrarians web_fetch tool can be used to retrieve the Adminer interface content, which can then be used to log into the internal TheLibrarian backend system. The vendor has fixed the vulnerability in all affected versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14435 | Application-Level DoS via infinite re-render loop in user profile handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14435</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.8, 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.1, 11.0.x &lt;= 11.0.6 fail to prevent infinite re-renders on API errors which allows authenticated users to cause application-level DoS via triggering unbounded component re-render loops.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68675 | Apache Airflow: proxy credentials for various providers might leak in task logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68675</link><description>In Apache Airflow versions before 3.1.6, the proxies and proxy fields within a Connection may include proxy URLs containing embedded authentication information. These fields were not treated as sensitive by default and therefore were not automatically masked in log output. As a result, when such connections are rendered or printed to logs, proxy credentials embedded in these fields could be exposed.

Users are recommended to upgrade to 3.1.6 or later, which fixes this issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59870 | Improper management of a static JWT signing secret in the web application, where the secret lacks rotation , introducing a security risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59870</link><description>HCL MyXalytics v6.7 is affected by improper management of a static JWT signing secret in the web application, where the secret lacks rotation , introducing a security risk</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68438 | Apache Airflow: Secrets in rendered templates could contain parts of sensitive values when truncated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68438</link><description>In Apache Airflow versions before 3.1.6, when rendered template fields in a Dag exceed [core] max_templated_field_length, sensitive values could be exposed in cleartext in the Rendered Templates UI. This occurred because serialization of those fields used a secrets masker instance that did not include user-registered mask_secret() patterns, so secrets were not reliably masked before truncation and display.

Users are recommended to upgrade to 3.1.6 or later, which fixes this issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14844 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.16 - Missing Authentication to Insecure Direct Object Reference and Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14844</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authentication in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.16 via the 'rcp_stripe_create_setup_intent_for_saved_card' function due to missing capability check. Additionally, the plugin does not check a user-controlled key, which makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to leak Stripe SetupIntent client_secret values for any membership.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14822 | DoS from quadratic complexity in model.ParseHashtags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14822</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.8 fail to validate input size before processing hashtags which allows an authenticated attacker to exhaust CPU resources via a single HTTP request containing a post with thousands space-separated tokens</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12006 | Supermicro BMC firmware update validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12006</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC firmware validation logic at Supermicro MBD-X12STW-F . An attacker can update the system firmware with a specially crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12007 | Supermicro BMC firmware update validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12007</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC firmware validation logic at Supermicro MBD-X13SEM-F . An attacker can update the system firmware with a specially crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14757 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt;= 3.6.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Payment Status Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14757</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Payment Status Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.9 only when used in combination with Cost Calculator Builder PRO. This is due to the complete_payment AJAX action being registered via wp_ajax_nopriv, making it accessible to unauthenticated users, and the complete() function only verifying a nonce without checking user capabilities or order ownership. Since nonces are exposed to all visitors via window.ccb_nonces in the page source, any unauthenticated attacker can mark any order's payment status as "completed" without actual payment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60021 | Apache bRPC: Remote command injection vulnerability in heap builtin service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60021</link><description>Remote command injection vulnerability in heap profiler builtin service in Apache bRPC ((all versions &lt; 1.15.0)) on all platforms allows attacker to inject remote command.



Root Cause: The bRPC heap profiler built-in service (/pprof/heap) does not validate the user-provided extra_options parameter and executes it as a command-line argument. Attackers can execute remote commands using the extra_options parameter..

Affected scenarios: Use the built-in bRPC heap profiler service to perform jemalloc memory profiling.

How to Fix: we provide two methods, you can choose one of them:

1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.15.0.
2. Apply this patch ( https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/3101 ) manually.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0913 | User Submitted Posts &amp;lt;= 20260110 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;usp_access&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0913</link><description>The User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'usp_access' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 20260110 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1004 | Essential Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 6.5.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1004</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to and including 6.5.5 via the 'eael_product_quickview_popup' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve WooCommerce product information for products with draft, pending, or private status, which should normally be restricted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20759 | OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation, which may allow a logged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20759</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation, which may allow a logged-in user with the low("monitoring user") or higher privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20894 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If an attacking administ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20894</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If an attacking administrator configures the affected product with some malicious input, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of a victim administrator who accesses the setting screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22876 | Path Traversal vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If this vulnerability is explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22876</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability exists in multiple Network Cameras TRIFORA 3 series provided by TOA Corporation. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary files on the affected product may be retrieved by a logged-in user with the low("monitoring user") or higher privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14375 | RSS Aggregator – RSS Import, News Feeds, Feed to Post, and Autoblogging &amp;lt;= 5.0.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via className</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14375</link><description>The RSS Aggregator – RSS Import, News Feeds, Feed to Post, and Autoblogging plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘className’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1003 | GetGenie – AI Content Writer with Keyword Research &amp;amp; SEO Tracking Tools &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1003</link><description>The GetGenie plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to delete a specific post. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to delete any post on the WordPress site, including posts authored by other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14793 | DK PDF – WordPress PDF Generator &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14793</link><description>The DK PDF – WordPress PDF Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0 via the 'addContentToMpdf' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, author level and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14853 | LEAV Last Email Address Validator &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14853</link><description>The LEAV Last Email Address Validator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions &lt;= 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the display_settings_page function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0916 | Related Posts by Taxonomy &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;related_posts_by_tax&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0916</link><description>The Related Posts by Taxonomy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'related_posts_by_tax' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0939 | Rede Itaú for WooCommerce — Payment PIX, Credit Card and Debit &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Unauthenticated Order Status Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0939</link><description>The Rede Itaú for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to order status manipulation due to insufficient verification of data authenticity in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2. This is due to the plugin failing to verify the authenticity of payment callbacks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate WooCommerce order statuses, either marking unpaid orders as paid, or failed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0942 | Rede Itaú for WooCommerce — Payment PIX, Credit Card and Debit &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Rede Order Logs Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0942</link><description>The Rede Itaú for WooCommerce — Payment PIX, Credit Card and Debit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the clearOrderLogs() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete the Rede Order Logs metadata from all WooCommerce orders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0975 | DIAView - Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0975</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has Command Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23768 | lucy-xss-filter before commit 7c1de6d allows an attacker to induce server-side HEAD requests to arbitrary URLs when the ObjectSecurityListen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23768</link><description>lucy-xss-filter before commit 7c1de6d allows an attacker to induce server-side HEAD requests to arbitrary URLs when the ObjectSecurityListener or EmbedSecurityListener option is enabled and embed or object tags are used with a src attribute missing a file extension.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23769 | lucy-xss-filter before commit e5826c0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization caused by misconfigure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23769</link><description>lucy-xss-filter before commit e5826c0 allows an attacker to execute malicious JavaScript due to improper sanitization caused by misconfigured default superset rule files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0858 | Versions of the package net.sourceforge.plantuml:plantuml before 1.2026.0 are vulnerable to Stored XSS due to insufficient sanitization of i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0858</link><description>Versions of the package net.sourceforge.plantuml:plantuml before 1.2026.0 are vulnerable to Stored XSS due to insufficient sanitization of interactive attributes in GraphViz diagrams. As a result, a crafted PlantUML diagram can inject malicious JavaScript into generated SVG output, leading to arbitrary script execution in the context of applications that render the SVG.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12641 | Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Role Demotion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12641</link><description>The Awesome Support - WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.6. This is due to the 'wpas_do_mr_activate_user' function not verifying that a user has permission to modify other users' roles, combined with a nonce reuse vulnerability where public registration nonces are valid for privileged actions because all actions share the same nonce namespace. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to demote administrators to low-privilege roles via the 'wpas-do=mr_activate_user' action with a user-controlled 'user_id' parameter, granted they can access the publicly available registration/submit ticket page to extract a valid nonce.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12957 | All-in-One Video Gallery &amp;lt;= 4.5.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via VTT Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12957</link><description>The All-in-One Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.7. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting VTT files, allowing double extension files to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid VTT file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14384 | All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp;amp; Increase Traffic &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) AI Access Token and Credit Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14384</link><description>The All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp; Increase Traffic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the `/aioseo/v1/ai/credits` REST route in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to disclose the global AI access token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14982 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.14.11 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14982</link><description>The Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization leading to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 10.14.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view all booking records in the database, including personally identifiable information (PII) such as names, email addresses, phone numbers, physical addresses, payment status, booking costs, and booking hashes belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15370 | Shield Security &amp;lt;= 21.0.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Disable Google Authenticator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15370</link><description>The Shield: Blocks Bots, Protects Users, and Prevents Security Breaches plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 21.0.9 via the MfaGoogleAuthToggle class due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to disable Google Authenticator for any user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15526 | Fancy Product Designer | WooCommerce WordPress &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure via &amp;#x27;pdf&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15526</link><description>The Fancy Product Designer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8. This is due to improper error handling in the PDF upload functionality that exposes server filesystem paths and stack traces in error messages. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15527 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 10.2.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15527</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 10.2.2 via the api_get_post_summary function due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be retrieved. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from posts they may not be able to edit or read otherwise. This also affects password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1000 | MailerLite - WooCommerce integration &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Data Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1000</link><description>The MailerLite - WooCommerce integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification and deletion in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3. This is due to missing capability checks on the resetIntegration() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's integration settings, delete all plugin options, and drop the plugin's database tables (woo_mailerlite_carts and woo_mailerlite_jobs), resulting in complete loss of plugin data including customer abandoned cart information and sync job history.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1022 | Gotac｜Statistics Database System - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1022</link><description>Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1023 | Gotac｜Statistics Database System - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1023</link><description>Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to directly exploit a specific functionality to query database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1019 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1019</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read, modify, and delete database contents by using a specific functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1020 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1020</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has a Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to enumerate the system file directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1021 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1021</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attacker to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62581 | DIAView - Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62581</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has multiple vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62582 | DIAView - Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62582</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has multiple vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1018 | Gotac｜Police Statistics Database System - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1018</link><description>Police Statistics Database System developed by Gotac has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing Unauthenticated remote attacker to exploit Absolute Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61937 | AVEVA Process Optimization Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61937</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an unauthenticated 
miscreant to achieve remote code execution under OS system privileges of
 “taoimr” service, potentially resulting in complete compromise of the  model application server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61943 | AVEVA Process Optimization SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61943</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(Process Optimization Standard User) to tamper with queries in Captive 
Historian and achieve code execution under SQL Server administrative 
privileges, potentially resulting in complete compromise of the SQL 
Server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64691 | AVEVA Process Optimization Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64691</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(OS standard user) to tamper with TCL Macro scripts and escalate 
privileges to OS system, potentially resulting in complete compromise of
 the model application server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64729 | AVEVA Process Optimization Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64729</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(OS Standard User) to tamper with Process Optimization project files, 
embed code, and escalate their privileges to the identity of a victim 
user who subsequently interacts with the project files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64769 | AVEVA Process Optimization Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64769</link><description>The Process Optimization application suite leverages connection 
channels/protocols that by-default are not encrypted and could become 
subject to hijacking or data leakage in certain man-in-the-middle or 
passive inspection scenarios.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65117 | AVEVA Process Optimization Use of Potentially Dangerous Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65117</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(Process Optimization Designer User) to embed OLE objects into graphics,
 and escalate their privileges to the identity of a victim user who 
subsequently interacts with the graphical elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65118 | AVEVA Process Optimization Uncontrolled Search Path Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65118</link><description>The vulnerability, if exploited, could allow an authenticated miscreant 
(OS Standard User) to trick Process Optimization services into loading 
arbitrary code and escalate privileges to OS System, potentially 
resulting in complete compromise of the Model Application Server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>