<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:09:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2960 | TRENDnet TEW-637AP/TEW-638APB HTTP Request goahead sub_41DED0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2960</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in TRENDnet TEW-637AP and TEW-638APB 1.2.7/1.3.0.106. This affects the function sub_41DED0 of the file /bin/goahead of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2959 | TRENDnet TEW-410APB HTTP Request httpd sub_4019A0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-410APB 1.3.06b. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4019A0 of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2958 | TRENDnet TEW-818DRU HTTP Request httpd denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-818DRU 1.0.14.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2957 | TRENDnet TEW-411BRP+ HTTP Request httpd sub_401DB0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2957</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-411BRP+ 2.07. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function sub_401DB0 of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 19:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2956 | TRENDnet TI-G102i HTTP Request lighttpd plugins_call_handle_uri_raw null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2956</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TI-G102i 1.0.7.S0_ /1.0.8.S0_ and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function plugins_call_handle_uri_raw of the file /usr/sbin/lighttpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2955 | TOTOLINK A3000RU IBMS Configuration File ExportIbmsConfig.sh access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2955</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3000RU up to 5.9c.5185 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cgi-bin/ExportIbmsConfig.sh of the component IBMS Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2954 | mannaandpoem OpenManus File file_saver.py execute access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2954</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in mannaandpoem OpenManus up to 2025.3.13. This affects the function execute of the file app/tool/file_saver.py of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2953 | PyTorch torch.mkldnn_max_pool2d denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2953</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PyTorch 2.6.0+cu124. Affected by this issue is the function torch.mkldnn_max_pool2d. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2952 | Bluestar Micro Mall api.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2952</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Bluestar Micro Mall 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/api.php?mod=upload&amp;amp;type=1. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2951 | Bluestar Micro Mall data.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2951</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Bluestar Micro Mall 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/data.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1861 | Stream HTTP wrapper truncates redirect location to 1024 bytes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1861</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when parsing HTTP redirect in the response to an HTTP request, there is currently limit on the location value size caused by limited size of the location buffer to 1024. However as per RFC9110, the limit is recommended to be 8000. This may lead to incorrect URL truncation and redirecting to a wrong location.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 06:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1736 | Stream HTTP wrapper header check might omit basic auth header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1736</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when user-supplied headers are sent, the insufficient validation of the end-of-line characters may prevent certain headers from being sent or lead to certain headers be misinterpreted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1734 | Streams HTTP wrapper does not fail for headers with invalid name and no colon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1734</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when receiving headers from HTTP server, the headers missing a colon (:) are treated as valid headers even though they are not. This may confuse applications into accepting invalid headers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1219 | libxml streams use wrong content-type header when requesting a redirected resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1219</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when requesting a HTTP resource using the DOM or SimpleXML extensions, the wrong content-type header is used to determine the charset when the requested resource performs a redirect. This may cause the resulting document to be parsed incorrectly or bypass validations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55895 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55895</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 12:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11180 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11180</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Timer Widget ekit_countdown_timer_title parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13557 | Shortcodes by United Themes  &amp;lt;= 5.1.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13557</link><description>The Shortcodes by United Themes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2006 | Inline Image Upload for BBPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.19 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2006</link><description>The Inline Image Upload for BBPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the file uploading functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This may be exploitable by unauthenticated attackers when the "Allow guest users without accounts to create topics and replies" setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2249 | SoJ Soundslides &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2249</link><description>The SoJ SoundSlides plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the soj_soundslides_options_subpanel() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2266 | Checkout Mestres do WP for WooCommerce 8.6.5 - 8.7.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2266</link><description>The Checkout Mestres do WP for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the cwmpUpdateOptions() function in versions 8.6.5 to 8.7.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2803 | So-Called Air Quotes &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2803</link><description>The So-Called Air Quotes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2840 | DAP to Autoresponders Email Syncing &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2840</link><description>The DAP to Autoresponders Email Syncing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 through the publicly accessible phpinfo.php script. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1217 | Header parser of http stream wrapper does not handle folded headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1217</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when http request module parses HTTP response obtained from a server, folded headers are parsed incorrectly, which may lead to misinterpreting the response and using incorrect headers, MIME types, etc.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 05:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51477 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51477</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 

could allow an authenticated to obtain sensitive username information due to an observable response discrepancy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7577 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7577</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could disclose sensitive user credentials from log files during new installation of the product.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43186 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43186</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information that is stored locally under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 23:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2781 | WatchGuard Mobile VPN with SSL Local Privilege Escalation via Non-Standard Installation Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2781</link><description>The WatchGuard Mobile VPN with SSL Client on Windows does not properly configure directory permissions when installed in a non-default directory. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to escalate to SYSTEM privileges on a vulnerable system.



This issue affects Mobile VPN with SSL Client: from 11.0 through 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 22:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2782 | WatchGuard Terminal Services Agent Local Privilege Escalation via Non-Standard Installation Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2782</link><description>The WatchGuard Terminal Services Agent on Windows does not properly configure directory permissions when installed in a non-default directory. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to escalate to SYSTEM privileges on a vulnerable system.



This issue affects Terminal Services Agent: from 12.0 through 12.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 22:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58128 | In MISP before 2.4.193, menu_custom_right_link parameters can be set via the UI (i.e., without using the CLI) and thus attackers with admin ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58128</link><description>In MISP before 2.4.193, menu_custom_right_link parameters can be set via the UI (i.e., without using the CLI) and thus attackers with admin privileges can conduct XSS attacks via a global menu link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 22:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58129 | In MISP before 2.4.193, menu_custom_right_link_html parameters can be set via the UI (i.e., without using the CLI) and thus attackers with a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58129</link><description>In MISP before 2.4.193, menu_custom_right_link_html parameters can be set via the UI (i.e., without using the CLI) and thus attackers with admin privileges can conduct XSS attacks against every page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 22:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58130 | In app/Controller/Component/RestResponseComponent.php in MISP before 2.4.193, REST endpoints have a lack of sanitization for non-JSON respon...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58130</link><description>In app/Controller/Component/RestResponseComponent.php in MISP before 2.4.193, REST endpoints have a lack of sanitization for non-JSON responses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 22:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25579 | TOTOLINK A3002R V4.0.0-B20230531.1404 is vulnerable to Command Injection in /bin/boa via bandstr.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25579</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R V4.0.0-B20230531.1404 is vulnerable to Command Injection in /bin/boa via bandstr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28094 | shopxo v6.4.0 has a ssrf/xss vulnerability in multiple places.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28094</link><description>shopxo v6.4.0 has a ssrf/xss vulnerability in multiple places.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28096 | OneNav 1.1.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in custom headers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28096</link><description>OneNav 1.1.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in custom headers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28097 | OneNav 1.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in custom headers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28097</link><description>OneNav 1.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in custom headers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28090 | maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the Collection Custom Interface feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28090</link><description>maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the Collection Custom Interface feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28092 | ShopXO v6.4.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via image upload function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28092</link><description>ShopXO v6.4.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via image upload function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28093 | ShopXO v6.4.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Email Settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28093</link><description>ShopXO v6.4.0 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Email Settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28087 | Sourcecodester Online Exam System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via dash.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28087</link><description>Sourcecodester Online Exam System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via dash.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28089 | maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Scheduled Task function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28089</link><description>maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Scheduled Task function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28091 | maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability via Add Article.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28091</link><description>maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability via Add Article.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56975 | InvoicePlane (all versions tested as of December 2024) v.1.6.11 and before contains a remote code execution vulnerability in the upload_file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56975</link><description>InvoicePlane (all versions tested as of December 2024) v.1.6.11 and before contains a remote code execution vulnerability in the upload_file method of the Upload controller.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28256 | An issue in TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setWebWlanIdx of the file /li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28256</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the setWebWlanIdx of the file /lib/cste_modules/wireless.so.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 21:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24292 | A Prototype Pollution issue in Aliconnect /sdk v.0.0.6 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the aim function in the aim.js compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24292</link><description>A Prototype Pollution issue in Aliconnect /sdk v.0.0.6 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the aim function in the aim.js component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57083 | A prototype pollution in the component Module.mergeObjects (redoc/bundles/redoc.lib.js:2) of redoc &lt;= 2.2.0 allows attackers to cause a Deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57083</link><description>A prototype pollution in the component Module.mergeObjects (redoc/bundles/redoc.lib.js:2) of redoc &lt;= 2.2.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6875 | Infinispan: infinispan: rest compare api has buffer leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6875</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Infinispan component in Red Hat Data Grid. The REST compare API may have a buffer leak and an out of memory error can occur when sending continual requests with large POST data to the REST API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28254 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Leantime v3.2.1 and before allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28254</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Leantime v3.2.1 and before allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the first name field in processMentions().</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2927 | ESAFENET CDG getFileTypeList.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2927</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5.6.3.154.205. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /parameter/getFileTypeList.jsp. The manipulation of the argument typename leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38985 | janryWang products depath v1.0.6 and cool-path v1.1.2 were discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the set() method at setIn (lib/in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38985</link><description>janryWang products depath v1.0.6 and cool-path v1.1.2 were discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the set() method at setIn (lib/index.js:90). This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38988 | alizeait unflatto &lt;= 1.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the method exports.unflatto at /dist/index.js. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38988</link><description>alizeait unflatto &lt;= 1.0.2 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the method exports.unflatto at /dist/index.js. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22953 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Epicor HCM 2021 1.9, specifically in the filter parameter of the JsonFetcher.svc endpoint. An at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22953</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Epicor HCM 2021 1.9, specifically in the filter parameter of the JsonFetcher.svc endpoint. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL payloads into the filter parameter, enabling the unauthorized execution of arbitrary SQL commands on the backend database. If certain features (like xp_cmdshell) are enabled, this may lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2925 | HDF5 H5MM.c H5MM_realloc double free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2925</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function H5MM_realloc of the file src/H5MM.c. The manipulation of the argument mem leads to double free. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2926 | HDF5 H5Ocache.c H5O__cache_chk_serialize null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2926</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function H5O__cache_chk_serialize of the file src/H5Ocache.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2924 | HDF5 H5HLcache.c H5HL__fl_deserialize heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2924</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6. This affects the function H5HL__fl_deserialize of the file src/H5HLcache.c. The manipulation of the argument free_block leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2922 | Netis WF-2404 BusyBox Shell cleartext storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2922</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netis WF-2404 1.1.124EN. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component BusyBox Shell. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of sensitive information. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2923 | HDF5 H5Fint.c H5F_addr_encode_len heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2923</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6. Affected by this issue is the function H5F_addr_encode_len of the file src/H5Fint.c. The manipulation of the argument pp leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 19:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2920 | Netis WF-2404 passwd weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2920</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netis WF-2404 1.1.124EN. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /еtc/passwd. The manipulation leads to use of weak hash. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2921 | Netis WF-2404 passwd default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2921</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Netis WF-2404 1.1.124EN. Affected is an unknown function of the file /etc/passwd. The manipulation with the input Realtek leads to use of default password. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31162 | fig2dev float point exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31162</link><description>Floating point exception in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker to availability via local input manipulation via get_slope function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31163 | fig2dev segmentation fault</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31163</link><description>Segmentation fault in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker to availability via local input manipulation via put_patternarc function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31164 | fig2dev heap-buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31164</link><description>heap-buffer overflow in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker to availability via local input manipulation via  create_line_with_spline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2917 | ChestnutCMS read readFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2917</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ChestnutCMS up to 1.5.3. Affected is the function readFile of the file /dev-api/cms/file/read. The manipulation of the argument filePath leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2919 | Netis WF-2404 UART hardware allows activation of test or debug logic at runtime</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2919</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netis WF-2404 1.1.124EN. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component UART. The manipulation leads to hardware allows activation of test or debug logic at runtime. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2915 | HDF5 H5Faccum.c H5F__accum_free heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2915</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6. This vulnerability affects the function H5F__accum_free of the file src/H5Faccum.c. The manipulation of the argument overlap_size leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2916 | Aishida Call Center System amr2mp3 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2916</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Aishida Call Center System up to 20250314. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /doscall/weixin/open/amr2mp3. The manipulation of the argument File leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2913 | HDF5 H5FL.c H5FL__blk_gc_list use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2913</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function H5FL__blk_gc_list of the file src/H5FL.c. The manipulation of the argument H5FL_blk_head_t leads to use after free. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2914 | HDF5 H5FScache.c H5FS__sinfo_Srialize_Sct_cb heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2914</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6. This affects the function H5FS__sinfo_Srialize_Sct_cb of the file src/H5FScache.c. The manipulation of the argument sect leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2912 | HDF5 H5Omessage.c H5O_msg_flush heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2912</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HDF5 up to 1.14.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function H5O_msg_flush of the file src/H5Omessage.c. The manipulation of the argument oh leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2713 | Improper File Permission Handling in Google gVisor runsc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2713</link><description>Google gVisor's runsc component exhibited a local privilege escalation vulnerability due to incorrect handling of file access permissions, which allowed unprivileged users to access restricted files. This occurred because the process initially ran with root-like permissions until the first fork.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51624 | WordPress Já-Já Pagamentos for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51624</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jajapagamentos Já-Já Pagamentos for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Já-Já Pagamentos for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54291 | WordPress PluginPass plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.10 - Arbitrary File Download/Delete vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54291</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound PluginPass allows Manipulating Web Input to File System Calls. This issue affects PluginPass: from n/a through 0.9.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54362 | WordPress GetShop ecommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54362</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in NotFound GetShop ecommerce allows Path Traversal. This issue affects GetShop ecommerce: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22356 | WordPress Stencies plugin &amp;lt;= 0.58 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22356</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stencies Stencies allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Stencies: from n/a through 0.58.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22360 | WordPress WP Azure offload plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22360</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Azure offload allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Azure offload: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22501 | WordPress Improve My City plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22501</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Improve My City Improve My City allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Improve My City: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22523 | WordPress Schedule Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22523</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Schedule allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Schedule: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22526 | WordPress PHP/MySQL CPU performance statistics Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22526</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NotFound PHP/MySQL CPU performance statistics allows Object Injection. This issue affects PHP/MySQL CPU performance statistics: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22566 | WordPress ULTIMATE VIDEO GALLERY Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound ULTIMATE VIDEO GALLERY allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ULTIMATE VIDEO GALLERY: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22575 | WordPress SUPER RESPONSIVE SLIDER Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in extendyourweb SUPER RESPONSIVE SLIDER allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects SUPER RESPONSIVE SLIDER: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22767 | WordPress GlobalPayments WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22767</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in globalpayments GlobalPayments WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects GlobalPayments WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31010 | WordPress SimplyRETS Real Estate IDX plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - CSRF to Multiple Admin Actions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31010</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ReichertBrothers SimplyRETS Real Estate IDX allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects SimplyRETS Real Estate IDX: from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30211 | KEX init error results with excessive memory usage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30211</link><description>Erlang/OTP is a set of libraries for the Erlang programming language. Prior to versions OTP-27.3.1, 26.2.5.10, and 25.3.2.19, a maliciously formed KEX init message can result with high memory usage. Implementation does not verify RFC specified limits on algorithm names (64 characters) provided in KEX init message. Big KEX init packet may lead to inefficient processing of the error data. As a result, large amount of memory will be allocated for processing malicious data. Versions OTP-27.3.1, OTP-26.2.5.10, and OTP-25.3.2.19 fix the issue. Some workarounds are available. One may set option `parallel_login` to `false` and/or reduce the `max_sessions` option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30372 | Emlog Pro contains an SQL injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30372</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. Emlog Pro versions pro-2.5.7 and pro-2.5.8 contain an SQL injection vulnerability. `search_controller.php` does not use addslashes after urldecode, allowing the preceeding addslashes to be bypassed by URL double encoding. This could result in potential leakage of sensitive information from the user database. Version pro-2.5.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30371 | Metabase vulnerable to circumvention of local link access protection in GeoJson endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30371</link><description>Metabase is a business intelligence and embedded analytics tool. Versions prior to v0.52.16.4, v1.52.16.4, v0.53.8, and v1.53.8 are vulnerable to circumvention of local link access protection in GeoJson endpoint. Self hosted Metabase instances that are using the GeoJson feature could be potentially impacted if their Metabase is colocated with other unsecured resources. This is fixed in v0.52.16.4, v1.52.16.4, v0.53.8, and v1.53.8. Migrating to Metabase Cloud or redeploying Metabase in a dedicated subnet with strict outbound port controls is an available workaround.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39311 | Publify Vulnerable To Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Via Redirects Requiring User Interaction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39311</link><description>Publify is a self hosted Web publishing platform on Rails. Prior to version 10.0.1 of Publify, corresponding to versions prior to 10.0.2 of the `publify_core` rubygem, publisher on a `publify` application is able to perform a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack on an administrator using the redirect functionality. The exploitation of this XSS vulnerability requires the administrator to click a malicious link. An attack could attempt to hide their payload by using HTML, or other encodings, as to not make it obvious to an administrator that this is a malicious link. A publisher may attempt to use this vulnerability to escalate their privileges and become an administrator. Version 10.0.1 of Publify and version 10.0.2 of the `publify_core` rubygem fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29928 | authentik&amp;#x27;s deletion of sessions did not revoke sessions when using database session storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29928</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. Prior to versions 2024.12.4 and 2025.2.3, when authentik was configured to use the database for session storage (which is a non-default setting), deleting sessions via the Web Interface or the API would not revoke the session and the session holder would continue to have access to authentik. authentik 2025.2.3 and 2024.12.4 fix this issue. Switching to the cache-based session storage until the authentik instance can be upgraded is recommended. This will however also delete all existing sessions and users will have to re-authenticate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48615 | Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in libarchive 3.7.6 and earlier when running program bsdtar in function header_pax_extension at rchiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48615</link><description>Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in libarchive 3.7.6 and earlier when running program bsdtar in function header_pax_extension at rchive_read_support_format_tar.c:1844:8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2877 | Event-driven-ansible: exposure inventory passwords in plain text when starting a rulebook activation with verbosity set to debug in eda</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2877</link><description>A flaw was found in the Ansible Automation Platform's Event-Driven Ansible. In configurations where verbosity is set to "debug", inventory passwords are exposed in plain text when starting a rulebook activation. This issue exists for any "debug" action in a rulebook and also affects Event Streams.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2901 | Org.jboss.hal-hal-parent: stored cross-site scripting (xss) in jboss eap management console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2901</link><description>A flaw was found in the JBoss EAP Management Console, where a stored Cross-site scripting vulnerability occurs when an application improperly sanitizes user input before storing it in a data store. When this stored data is later included in web pages without adequate sanitization, malicious scripts can execute in the context of users who view these pages, leading to potential data theft, session hijacking, or other malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1781 | There is a XXE in W3CSS Validator versions before cssval-20250226 that allows an attacker to use specially-crafted XML objects to coerce ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1781</link><description>There is a XXE in W3CSS Validator versions before cssval-20250226 that allows an attacker to use specially-crafted XML objects to coerce server-side request forgery (SSRF).  This could be exploited to read arbitrary local files if an attacker has access to exception messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28220 | Tenda W6_S v1.0.0.4_510 has a Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the setcfm function, which allows remote attackers to cause web server crash ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28220</link><description>Tenda W6_S v1.0.0.4_510 has a Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the setcfm function, which allows remote attackers to cause web server crash via parameter funcpara1 passed to the binary through a POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28219 | Netgear DC112A V1.0.0.64 has an OS command injection vulnerability in the usb_adv.cgi, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28219</link><description>Netgear DC112A V1.0.0.64 has an OS command injection vulnerability in the usb_adv.cgi, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via parameter "deviceName" passed to the binary through a POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28221 | Tenda W6_S v1.0.0.4_510 has a Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the set_local_time function, which allows remote attackers to cause web serve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28221</link><description>Tenda W6_S v1.0.0.4_510 has a Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the set_local_time function, which allows remote attackers to cause web server crash via parameter time passed to the binary through a POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0986 | IBM PowerVM Hypervisor data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0986</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW1050.00 through FW1050.30 and FW1060.00 through FW1060.20 could allow a local user, under certain Linux processor combability mode configurations, to cause undetected data loss or errors when performing gzip compression using HW acceleration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2863 | Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2863</link><description>Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the web application of saTECH BCU firmware version 2.1.3, which could allow an unauthenticated local attacker to exploit active administrator sessions and perform malicious actions. The malicious actions that can be executed by the attacker depend on the logged-in user, and may include rebooting the device or modifying roles and permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2864 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2864</link><description>SaTECH BCU in its firmware version 2.1.3 allows an attacker to inject malicious code into the legitimate website owning the affected device, once the cookie is set. This attack only impacts the victim's browser (reflected XSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2865 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2865</link><description>SaTECH BCU, in its firmware version 2.1.3, could allow XSS attacks and other malicious resources to be stored on the web server. An attacker with some knowledge of the web application could send a malicious request to the victim users. Through this request, the victims would interpret the code (resources) stored on another malicious website owned by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2858 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2858</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the saTECH BCU firmware version 2.1.3. An attacker with access to the CLI of the device could make use of the nice command to bypass all restrictions and elevate privileges as a superuser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2859 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2859</link><description>An attacker with access to the network where the vulnerable device is located could capture traffic and obtain cookies from the user, allowing them to steal a user's active session and make changes to the device via the web, depending on the privileges obtained by the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2860 | Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2860</link><description>SaTECH BCU in its firmware version 2.1.3, allows an authenticated attacker to access information about the credentials that users have within the web (.xml file). In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must know the path, regardless of the user's privileges on the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2861 | Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2861</link><description>SaTECH BCU in its firmware version 2.1.3 uses the HTTP protocol. The use of the HTTP protocol for web browsing has the problem that information is exchanged in unencrypted text. Since sensitive data such as credentials are exchanged, an attacker could obtain them and log in legitimately.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2862 | Weak Encoding for Password vulnerability in saTECH BCU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2862</link><description>SaTECH BCU, in its firmware version 2.1.3, performs weak password encryption. This allows an attacker with access to the device's system or website to obtain the credentials, as the storage methods used are not strong enough in terms of encryption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11504 | SQL Injection in Streamsoft Prestiż</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11504</link><description>Input from multiple fields in Streamsoft Prestiż is not sanitized properly, leading to an SQL injection vulnerability, which might be exploited by an authenticated remote attacker. 
This issue was fixed in 18.1.376.37 version of the software.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7407 | Weak password encoding in Streamsoft Prestiż</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7407</link><description>Use of a custom password encoding algorithm in Streamsoft Prestiż software allows straightforward decoding of passwords using their encoded forms, which are stored in the application's database. One has to know the encoding algorithm, but it can be deduced by observing how password are transformed. 
This issue was fixed in 18.2.377 version of the software.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2909 | Lack of encryption vulnerability in DuoxMe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2909</link><description>The lack of encryption in the DuoxMe (formerly Blue) application binary in versions prior to 3.3.1 for iOS devices allows an attacker to gain unauthorised access to the application code and discover sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2910 | User enumeration vulnerability in MeetMe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2910</link><description>User enumeration in the password reset module of the MeetMe authentication service in versions prior to 2024-09 allows an attacker to determine whether an email address is registered through specific error messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2911 | Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in MeetMe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2911</link><description>Unauthorised access to the call forwarding service system in MeetMe products in versions prior to 2024-09 allows an attacker to identify multiple users and perform brute force attacks via extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2908 | Lack of encryption vulnerability in DuoxMe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2908</link><description>The lack of encryption in the DuoxMe (formerly Blue) application binary in versions prior to 3.3.1 for iOS devices allows an attacker to gain unauthorised access to the application code and discover sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31432 | WordPress Pop-Up Chop Chop &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31432</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Chop Chop Pop-Up Chop Chop allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Pop-Up Chop Chop: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31433 | WordPress Magic Embeds &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31433</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Miguel Sirvent Magic Embeds allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Magic Embeds: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31434 | WordPress FormLift for Infusionsoft Web Forms &amp;lt;= 7.5.19 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31434</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Adrian Tobey FormLift for Infusionsoft Web Forms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FormLift for Infusionsoft Web Forms: from n/a through 7.5.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31435 | WordPress Microblog Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31435</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Efficient Scripts Microblog Poster allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Microblog Poster: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31437 | WordPress WP-OGP &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in David Miller WP-OGP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP-OGP: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31438 | WordPress WP Supersized &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31438</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Benoit De Boeck WP Supersized allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Supersized: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31439 | WordPress Browser Caching with .htaccess 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31439</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in tobias_.MerZ Browser Caching with .htaccess allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Browser Caching with .htaccess: from 1.2.1 through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31440 | WordPress Terms of Use plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31440</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Strategy11 Team Terms of Use allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Terms of Use: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31443 | WordPress KK I Like It plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31443</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Krzysztof Furtak KK I Like It allows Stored XSS. This issue affects KK I Like It: from n/a through 1.7.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31444 | WordPress ShowTime Slideshow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31444</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in youtag ShowTime Slideshow allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShowTime Slideshow: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31447 | WordPress NertWorks All in One Social Share Tools &amp;lt;=1.26 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31447</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nertworks NertWorks All in One Social Share Tools allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects NertWorks All in One Social Share Tools: from n/a through 1.26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31448 | WordPress Simple Trackback Disabler &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31448</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in misteraon Simple Trackback Disabler allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple Trackback Disabler: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31449 | WordPress The Visitor Counter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31449</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in EricH The Visitor Counter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects The Visitor Counter: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31450 | WordPress Toggle Box &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31450</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in phantom.omaga Toggle Box allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Toggle Box: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31451 | WordPress wBounce &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31451</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kevinweber wBounce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects wBounce: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31452 | WordPress WP Ultimate Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31452</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mindshare Labs, Inc. WP Ultimate Search allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Ultimate Search: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31453 | WordPress YouTube SimpleGallery &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31453</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stian Andreassen YouTube SimpleGallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects YouTube SimpleGallery: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31456 | WordPress Ultimate Security Checker plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Security Rescan vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31456</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in bsndev Ultimate Security Checker allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Ultimate Security Checker: from n/a through 4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31457 | WordPress LWS SMS &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31457</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aurélien LWS LWS SMS allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects LWS SMS: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31458 | WordPress Video Embedder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31458</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in forsgren Video Embedder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Video Embedder: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31459 | WordPress Login Alert plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31459</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PasqualePuzio Login Alert allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Login Alert: from n/a through 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31460 | WordPress OmniLeads Scripts and Tags Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31460</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in danielmuldernl OmniLeads Scripts and Tags Manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects OmniLeads Scripts and Tags Manager: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31463 | WordPress TGG WP Optimizer &amp;lt;= 1.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31463</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Preetinder Singh TGG WP Optimizer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects TGG WP Optimizer: from n/a through 1.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31464 | WordPress Text Selection Color &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31464</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nazmur Rahman Text Selection Color allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Text Selection Color: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31465 | WordPress Better Section Navigation Widget &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31465</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in cornershop Better Section Navigation Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Better Section Navigation Widget: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31466 | WordPress Duplicate Page and Post &amp;lt;= 1.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31466</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Falcon Solutions Duplicate Page and Post allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Duplicate Page and Post: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31469 | WordPress Clear Sucuri Cache &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31469</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in webrangers Clear Sucuri Cache allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Clear Sucuri Cache: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31470 | WordPress Page Takeover &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31470</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FancyThemes Page Takeover allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Page Takeover: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31471 | WordPress Duplicate Page and Post &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31471</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Falcon Solutions Duplicate Page and Post allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Duplicate Page and Post: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31472 | WordPress Flatty &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31472</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michele Marri Flatty allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Flatty: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31473 | WordPress WP Database Optimizer &amp;lt;= 1.2.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31473</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in matthewprice1178 WP Database Optimizer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Database Optimizer: from n/a through 1.2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31474 | WordPress WP Database Optimizer &amp;lt;= 1.2.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31474</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in matthewprice1178 WP Database Optimizer allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Database Optimizer: from n/a through 1.2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 12:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2815 | Administrator Z &amp;lt;= 2025.03.24 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2815</link><description>The Administrator Z plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the adminz_import_backup() function in all versions up to, and including, 2025.03.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 11:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2870 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Clinic Queuing System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2870</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in version 1.0 of the Clinic Queuing System. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the page parameter in /patient_side.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2868 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Clinic Queuing System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2868</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in version 1.0 of the Clinic Queuing System. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the page parameter in /index.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2869 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Clinic Queuing System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2869</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in version 1.0 of the Clinic Queuing System. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the id parameter in /manage_user.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-24008 | An exposure of sensitive system information to an unauthorized control sphere vulnerability [CWE-497] in FortiDDoS version 5.4.0, version 5....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24008</link><description>An exposure of sensitive system information to an unauthorized control sphere vulnerability [CWE-497] in FortiDDoS version 5.4.0, version 5.3.2 and below, version 5.2.0, version 5.1.0, version 5.0.0, version 4.7.0, version 4.6.0, version 4.5.0, version 4.4.2 and below, FortiDDoS-CM version 5.3.0, version 5.2.0, version 5.1.0, version 5.0.0, version 4.7.0, FortiVoice version 6.0.6 and below, FortiRecorder version 6.0.3 and below and FortiMail version 6.4.1 and below, version 6.2.4 and below, version 6.0.9 and below may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to obtain potentially sensitive software-version information by reading a JavaScript file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10307 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10307</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions from 12.10 before 17.8.6, 17.9 before 17.9.3, and 17.10 before 17.10.1. A maliciously crafted file can cause uncontrolled CPU consumption when viewing the associated merge request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12619 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12619</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.0 before 17.8.6, 17.9 before 17.9.3, and 17.10 before 17.10.1, allowing internal users to gain unauthorized access to internal projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27001 | WordPress Shipmondo plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Authenticated Arbitrary WordPress Option Disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27001</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Shipmondo Shipmondo – A complete shipping solution for WooCommerce allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Shipmondo – A complete shipping solution for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31073 | WordPress Unlimited &amp;lt;= 1.45 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31073</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Compete Themes Unlimited allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Unlimited: from n/a through 1.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31075 | WordPress MicroPayments plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.29 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31075</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in videowhisper MicroPayments allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MicroPayments: from n/a through 2.9.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31076 | WordPress WP Compress for MainWP plugin &amp;lt;= 6.30.03 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31076</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in WP Compress WP Compress for MainWP allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Compress for MainWP: from n/a through 6.30.03.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31077 | WordPress Ultimate Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31077</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ultimate Blocks Ultimate Blocks allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Ultimate Blocks: from n/a through 3.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31079 | WordPress Usermaven plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31079</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in usermaven Usermaven allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Usermaven: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31083 | WordPress Leaky Paywall &amp;lt;= 4.21.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31083</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ZEEN101 Leaky Paywall allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Leaky Paywall: from n/a through 4.21.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31088 | WordPress Paid Member Subscriptions &amp;lt;= 2.14.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31088</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Paid Member Subscriptions allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Paid Member Subscriptions: from n/a through 2.14.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31090 | WordPress Dropdown Multisite selector &amp;lt; 0.9.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31090</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in alordiel Dropdown Multisite selector allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dropdown Multisite selector: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31093 | WordPress RPS Include Content &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31093</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in redpixelstudios RPS Include Content allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects RPS Include Content: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31094 | WordPress WP Posts Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31094</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in teastudio.pl WP Posts Carousel allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Posts Carousel: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31096 | WordPress PostX &amp;lt;= 4.1.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31096</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPXPO PostX allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects PostX: from n/a through 4.1.25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31099 | WordPress Slider by BestWebSoft &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31099</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in bestwebsoft Slider by BestWebSoft allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Slider by BestWebSoft: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31102 | WordPress Hostel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31102</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bob Hostel allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Hostel: from n/a through 1.1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-16149 | An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation in FortiClientEMS version 6.2.0 may allow a remote attacker to execute unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16149</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation in FortiClientEMS version 6.2.0 may allow a remote attacker to execute unauthorized code by injecting malicious payload in the user profile of a FortiClient instance being managed by the vulnerable system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1705 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1705</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation within the td_ajax_get_views AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27567 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the NickName registration screen of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27567</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the NickName registration screen of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is using the configuration page or functions accessible only from the LAN side of the product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27574 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the USB storage file-sharing function of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27574</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the USB storage file-sharing function of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is using the configuration page or functions accessible only from the LAN side of the product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27716 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file/folder listing process of the USB st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27716</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file/folder listing process of the USB storage file-sharing function of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, the product's files may be obtained and/or altered by a crafted HTTP request to specific functions of the product from a device connected to the LAN side.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27718 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file upload process of the USB storage fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27718</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file upload process of the USB storage file-sharing function of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, the product's files may be obtained and/or altered or arbitrary code may be executed by a crafted HTTP request to specific functions of the product from a device connected to the LAN side.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27726 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file download process of the USB storage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27726</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file download process of the USB storage file-sharing function of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, the product's files may be obtained and/or altered by a crafted HTTP request to specific functions of the product from a device connected to the LAN side.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27932 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file deletion process of the USB storage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27932</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in the file deletion process of the USB storage file-sharing function of HGW-BL1500HM Ver 002.002.003 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may delete a file on the device or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2074 | Advanced Google reCAPTCHA &amp;lt;= 1.29 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;sSearch&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2074</link><description>The Advanced Google reCAPTCHA plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the ‘sSearch’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.29 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries, particularly when the plugin’s settings page hasn’t been visited and its welcome message has not been dismissed. This issue can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 07:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2578 | Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia &amp;lt;= 1.2.19 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2578</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar &amp;#8211; Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.19 via the 'wpAmeliaApiCall' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 07:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2328 | Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2328</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'dnd_remove_uploaded_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary file paths (such as ../../../../wp-config.php) to uploaded files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when an Administrator deletes the message. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the Flamingo plugin to be installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 07:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2485 | Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 1.3.8.7 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via PHAR to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2485</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8.7 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'dnd_upload_cf7_upload'
 function. This makes it possible for attackers to inject a PHP Object through a PHAR file. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. This vulnerability may be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when a form is present on the site with the file upload action. The Flamingo plugin must be installed and activated in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 07:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1762 | Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner &amp;lt; 2.5.4 - Arbitrary Tickets Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1762</link><description>The Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner WordPress plugin before 2.5.4 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 06:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2027 | A double free vulnerability has been identified in the ASUS System Analysis service. This vulnerability can be triggered by sending speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2027</link><description>A double free vulnerability has been identified in the ASUS System Analysis service. This vulnerability can be triggered by sending specially crafted local RPC requests, leading to the service crash and potentially memory manipulation in some rare circumstances.
Refer to the 'Security Update for MyASUS' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2804 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;account_id&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;account_username&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2804</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress, used by the Newspaper theme, is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'account_id' and 'account_username' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31335 | The OpenSAML C++ library before 3.3.1 allows forging of signed SAML messages via parameter manipulation (when using SAML bindings that rely ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31335</link><description>The OpenSAML C++ library before 3.3.1 allows forging of signed SAML messages via parameter manipulation (when using SAML bindings that rely on non-XML signatures).</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2294 | Kubio AI Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2294</link><description>The Kubio AI Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.1 via thekubio_hybrid_theme_load_template function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2894 | Unitree Go1 Robot Dog Backdoor Control Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2894</link><description>The Go1 also known as "The World's First Intelligence Bionic Quadruped Robot Companion of Consumer Level," contains an undocumented backdoor that can enable the manufacturer, and anyone in possession of the correct API key, complete remote control over the affected robotic device using the CloudSail remote access service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24381 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability. An unauthenticated at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24381</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a targeted application user being redirected to arbitrary web URLs. The vulnerability could be leveraged by attackers to conduct phishing attacks that cause users to divulge sensitive information. Exploitation may allow for session theft.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13939 | String::Compare::ConstantTime for Perl through 0.321 is vulnerable to timing attacks that allow an attacker to guess the length of a secret string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13939</link><description>String::Compare::ConstantTime for Perl through 0.321 is vulnerable to timing attacks that allow an attacker to guess the length of a secret string.

As stated in the documentation: "If the lengths of the strings are different, because equals returns false right away the size of the secret string may be leaked (but not its contents)."

This is similar to CVE-2020-36829</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49601 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49601</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23383 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23383</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24377 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24377</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24378 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24378</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24379 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24379</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24380 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24380</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24385 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24385</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24386 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24386</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49563 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49563</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges and elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49564 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49564</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges and elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49565 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49565</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution and Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22398 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22398</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary command execution as root. Exploitation may lead to a system take over by an attacker. This vulnerability is considered critical as it can be leveraged to completely compromise the operating system. Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24382 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24382</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24383 | Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24383</link><description>Dell Unity, version(s) 5.4 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability to delete arbitrary files. This vulnerability is considered critical as it can be leveraged to delete critical system files as root. Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 02:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1860 | Data::Entropy for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1860</link><description>Data::Entropy for Perl 0.007 and earlier use the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>