<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:58:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-38322 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a do_binauth NULL pointer dereference that be triggered with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38322</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a do_binauth NULL pointer dereference that be triggered with a crafted GET HTTP request with a missing User-Agent HTTP header. Triggering this issue results in crashing OpenNDS (a Denial-of-Service condition). The issue occurs when the client is about to be authenticated, and can be triggered only when the BinAuth option is set.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38324 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It allows users to skip the splash page sequence when it is using t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38324</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It allows users to skip the splash page sequence when it is using the default FAS key and when OpenNDS is configured as FAS (default).</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38315 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a try_to_authenticate NULL pointer dereference that can be t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38315</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a try_to_authenticate NULL pointer dereference that can be triggered with a crafted GET HTTP with a missing client token query string parameter. Triggering this issue results in crashing OpenNDS (a Denial-of-Service condition).</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38316 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. When the custom unescape callback is enabled, attackers can execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38316</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. When the custom unescape callback is enabled, attackers can execute arbitrary OS commands by inserting them into the URL portion of HTTP GET requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38320 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a show_preauthpage NULL pointer dereference that can be trig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38320</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a show_preauthpage NULL pointer dereference that can be triggered with a crafted GET HTTP with a missing User-Agent header. Triggering this issue results in crashing OpenNDS (a Denial-of-Service condition).</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38314 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a NULL pointer dereference in preauthenticated() that can be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38314</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before version 10.1.2. It has a NULL pointer dereference in preauthenticated() that can be triggered with a crafted GET HTTP request with a missing redirect query string parameter. Triggering this issue results in crashing OpenNDS (a Denial-of-Service condition).</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38313 | An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before 10.1.2. it has a do_binauth NULL pointer dereference that can be triggered with a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38313</link><description>An issue was discovered in OpenNDS Captive Portal before 10.1.2. it has a do_binauth NULL pointer dereference that can be triggered with a crafted GET HTTP request with a missing client redirect query string parameter. Triggering this issue results in crashing openNDS (a Denial-of-Service condition). The issue occurs when the client is about to be authenticated, and can be triggered only when the BinAuth option is set.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39545 | CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X Single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39545</link><description>CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier allows a attacker to log in to the product may execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39546 | CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X Single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39546</link><description>CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier allows a attacker to log in to the product may execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39547 | CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X Single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39547</link><description>CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier allows a attacker to log in to the product may execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39548 | CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X Single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39548</link><description>CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier allows a attacker to log in to the product may execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39544 | CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X Single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39544</link><description>CLUSTERPRO X Ver5.1 and earlier and EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.1 and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X SingleServerSafe 5.0 and earlier allows a attacker to log in to the product may execute an arbitrary command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41101 | An issue was discovered in the captive portal in OpenNDS before version 10.1.3. get_query in http_microhttpd.c does not validate the length ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41101</link><description>An issue was discovered in the captive portal in OpenNDS before version 10.1.3. get_query in http_microhttpd.c does not validate the length of the query string of GET requests. This leads to a stack-based buffer overflow in versions 9.x and earlier, and to a heap-based buffer overflow in versions 10.x and later. Attackers may exploit the issue to crash OpenNDS (Denial-of-Service condition) or to inject and execute arbitrary bytecode (Remote Code Execution).</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41102 | An issue was discovered in the captive portal in OpenNDS before version 10.1.3. It has multiple memory leaks due to not freeing up allocated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41102</link><description>An issue was discovered in the captive portal in OpenNDS before version 10.1.3. It has multiple memory leaks due to not freeing up allocated memory. This may lead to a Denial-of-Service condition due to the consumption of all available memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48655 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Controller/Component/IndexFilterComponent.php does not properly filter out query paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48655</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Controller/Component/IndexFilterComponent.php does not properly filter out query parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48656 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Model/AppModel.php mishandles order clauses.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48656</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Model/AppModel.php mishandles order clauses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48657 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Model/AppModel.php mishandles filters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48657</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Model/AppModel.php mishandles filters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48658 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Model/AppModel.php lacks a checkParam function for alphanumerics, underscore, dash, peri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48658</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Model/AppModel.php lacks a checkParam function for alphanumerics, underscore, dash, period, and space.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48659 | An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Controller/AppController.php mishandles parameter parsing.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48659</link><description>An issue was discovered in MISP before 2.4.176. app/Controller/AppController.php mishandles parameter parsing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38130 | Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to delete data in the sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38130</link><description>Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to delete data in the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 04:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42428 | Directory traversal vulnerability in CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to dele...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42428</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to delete directories and files in the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 04:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47283 | Directory traversal vulnerability in CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to obta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47283</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to obtain files in the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 04:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47675 | CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47675</link><description>CubeCart prior to 6.5.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 04:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48648 | Concrete CMS before 8.5.13 and 9.x before 9.2.2 allows unauthorized access because directories can be created with insecure permissions. Fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48648</link><description>Concrete CMS before 8.5.13 and 9.x before 9.2.2 allows unauthorized access because directories can be created with insecure permissions. File creation functions (such as the Mkdir() function) gives universal access (0777) to created folders by default. Excessive permissions can be granted when creating a directory with permissions greater than 0755 or when the permissions argument is not specified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48649 | Concrete CMS before 8.5.13 and 9.x before 9.2.2 allows stored XSS on the Admin page via an uploaded file name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48649</link><description>Concrete CMS before 8.5.13 and 9.x before 9.2.2 allows stored XSS on the Admin page via an uploaded file name.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45382 | In the module "SoNice Retour" (sonice_retour) up to version 2.1.0 from Common-Services for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45382</link><description>In the module "SoNice Retour" (sonice_retour) up to version 2.1.0 from Common-Services for PrestaShop, a guest can download personal information without restriction by performing a path traversal attack. Due to a lack of permissions control and a lack of control in the path name construction, a guest can perform a path traversal to view all files on the information system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 02:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45387 | In the module "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel, XML) Export PRO" (exportproducts) in versions up to 5.0.0 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45387</link><description>In the module "Product Catalog (CSV, Excel, XML) Export PRO" (exportproducts) in versions up to 5.0.0 from MyPrestaModules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection via `exportProduct::_addDataToDb().`</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 02:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48031 | OpenSupports v4.11.0 is vulnerable to Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type. In the comment function, an attacker can bypass secur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48031</link><description>OpenSupports v4.11.0 is vulnerable to Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type. In the comment function, an attacker can bypass security restrictions and upload a .bat file by manipulating the file's magic bytes to masquerade as an allowed type. This can enable the attacker to execute arbitrary code or establish a reverse shell, leading to unauthorized file writes or control over the victim's station via a crafted file upload operation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 02:17:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48078 | SQL Injection vulnerability in add.php in Simple CRUD Functionality v1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the 'title' para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48078</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in add.php in Simple CRUD Functionality v1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the 'title' parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48231 | Use-After-Free in win_close() in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48231</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. When closing a window, vim may try to access already freed window structure. Exploitation beyond crashing the application has not been shown to be viable. This issue has been addressed in commit `25aabc2b` which has been included in release version 9.0.2106. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47025 | An issue in Free5gc v.3.3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the free5gc-compose component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47025</link><description>An issue in Free5gc v.3.3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the free5gc-compose component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48232 | Floating point Exception in adjust_plines_for_skipcol() in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48232</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. A floating point exception may occur when calculating the line offset for overlong lines and smooth scrolling is enabled and the cpo-settings include the 'n' flag. This may happen when a window border is present and when the wrapped line continues on the next physical line directly in the window border because the 'cpo' setting includes the 'n' flag. Only users with non-default settings are affected and the exception should only result in a crash. This issue has been addressed in commit `cb0b99f0` which has been included in release version 9.0.2107. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48233 | overflow with count for :s command in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48233</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. If the count after the :s command is larger than what fits into a (signed) long variable, abort with e_value_too_large. Impact is low, user interaction is required and a crash may not even happen in all situations. This issue has been addressed in commit `ac6378773` which has been included in release version 9.0.2108. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48234 | overflow in nv_z_get_count in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48234</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. When getting the count for a normal mode z command, it may overflow for large counts given. Impact is low, user interaction is required and a crash may not even happen in all situations. This issue has been addressed in commit `58f9befca1` which has been included in release version 9.0.2109. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48235 | overflow in ex address parsing in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48235</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. When parsing relative ex addresses one may unintentionally cause an
overflow. Ironically this happens in the existing overflow check, because the line number becomes negative and LONG_MAX - lnum will cause the overflow. Impact is low, user interaction is required and a crash may not even happen in all situations. This issue has been addressed in commit `060623e` which has been included in release version 9.0.2110. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48236 | overflow in get_number in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48236</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. When using the z= command, the user may overflow the count with values larger
than MAX_INT. Impact is low, user interaction is required and a crash may not even happen in all situations. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `73b2d379` which has been included in release version 9.0.2111. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47686 | WordPress Arigato Autoresponder and Newsletter Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47686</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Arigato Autoresponder and Newsletter plugin &lt;= 2.7.2.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48237 | overflow in shift_line in vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48237</link><description>Vim is an open source command line text editor. In affected versions when shifting lines in operator pending mode and using a very large value, it may be possible to overflow the size of integer. Impact is low, user interaction is required and a crash may not even happen in all situations. This issue has been addressed in commit `6bf131888` which has been included in version 9.0.2112. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47687 | WordPress Woo Custom and Sequential Order Number Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47687</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in VJInfotech Woo Custom and Sequential Order Number plugin &lt;= 2.6.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47112 | Authenticated users can view job names and groups they do not have authorization to view in Rundeck</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47112</link><description>Rundeck is an open source automation service with a web console, command line tools and a WebAPI. In affected versions access to two URLs used in both Rundeck Open Source and Process Automation products could allow authenticated users to access the URL path, which provides a list of job names and groups for any project, without the necessary authorization checks. The output of these endpoints only exposes the name of job groups and the jobs contained within the specified project. The output is read-only and the access does not allow changes to the information. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.17.3. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may block access to the two URLs used in either Rundeck Open Source or Process Automation products at a load balancer level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47688 | WordPress Youtube SpeedLoad Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47688</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Alexufo Youtube SpeedLoad plugin &lt;= 0.6.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48222 | Authenticated users can view or delete jobs they do not have authorization for in Rundeck</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48222</link><description>Rundeck is an open source automation service with a web console, command line tools and a WebAPI. In affected versions access to two URLs used in both Rundeck Open Source and Process Automation products could allow authenticated users to access the URL path, which would allow access to view or delete jobs, without the necessary authorization checks. This issue has been addressed in version 4.17.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47642 | Stream description leaks to ex-subscribers in Zulip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47642</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. It was discovered by the Zulip development team that active users who had previously been subscribed to a stream incorrectly continued being able to use the Zulip API to access metadata for that stream. As a result, users who had been removed from a stream, but still had an account in the organization, could still view metadata for that stream (including the stream name, description, settings, and an email address used to send emails into the stream via the incoming email integration). This potentially allowed users to see changes to a stream’s metadata after they had lost access to the stream. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 7.5 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 21:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40314 | Cross-site scripting in bootstrap.jsp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40314</link><description>Cross-site scripting in bootstrap.jsp in multiple versions of OpenNMS Meridian and Horizon allows an attacker access to confidential session information. The solution is to upgrade to Horizon 32.0.5 or newer and Meridian 2023.1.9 or newer










Meridian
and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for
installation within an organization's private networks and should not be
directly accessible from the Internet. 

OpenNMS thanks 

Moshe Apelbaum

 for reporting this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 21:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6014 | MLflow Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6014</link><description>An attacker is able to arbitrarily create an account in MLflow bypassing any authentication requirment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6020 | Ray Static File Local File Include</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6020</link><description>LFI in Ray's /static/ directory allows attackers to read any file on the server without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46213 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) on “Show Syntax Highlighted” View in Search Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46213</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.0.7 and 9.1.2, ineffective escaping in the “Show syntax Highlighted” feature can result in the execution of unauthorized code in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 20:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46214 | Remote code execution (RCE) in Splunk Enterprise through Insecure XML Parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46214</link><description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.0.7 and 9.1.2, Splunk Enterprise does not safely sanitize extensible stylesheet language transformations (XSLT) that users supply. This means that an attacker can upload malicious XSLT which can result in remote code execution on the Splunk Enterprise instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 20:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32796 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Enquiry Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32796</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MingoCommerce WooCommerce Product Enquiry plugin &lt;= 2.3.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 20:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32957 | WordPress Team Members Showcase Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32957</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Dazzlersoft Team Members Showcase plugin &lt;= 1.3.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 20:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34375 | WordPress Seo By 10Web Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34375</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in 10Web SEO by 10Web plugin &lt;= 1.2.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36008 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36008</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36026 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36026</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39926 | WordPress Under Construction / Maintenance Mode from Acurax Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39926</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Acurax Under Construction / Maintenance Mode from Acurax plugin &lt;= 2.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28621 | WordPress Raise Mag Theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 and Wishful Blog theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28621</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wishfulthemes Raise Mag, Wishfulthemes Wishful Blog themes allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Raise Mag: from n/a through 1.0.7; Wishful Blog: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47239 | WordPress Easy PayPal Shopping Cart Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47239</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Scott Paterson Easy PayPal Shopping Cart plugin &lt;= 1.1.10 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48134 | nagayama_copabowl Line 13.6.1 is vulnerable to Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48134</link><description>nagayama_copabowl Line 13.6.1 is vulnerable to Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47240 | WordPress CBX Map for Google Map &amp;amp; OpenStreetMap Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47240</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Codeboxr CBX Map for Google Map &amp; OpenStreetMap plugin &lt;= 1.1.11 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47242 | WordPress ANAC XML Bandi di Gara Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47242</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Marco Milesi ANAC XML Bandi di Gara plugin &lt;= 7.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47245 | WordPress ANAC XML Viewer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47245</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Marco Milesi ANAC XML Viewer plugin &lt;= 1.7 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47508 | WordPress Master Slider Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47508</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Averta Master Slider Pro plugin &lt;= 3.6.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47509 | WordPress Edit WooCommerce Templates Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47509</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ioannup Edit WooCommerce Templates plugin &lt;= 1.1.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47511 | WordPress Pinyin Slugs Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47511</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SO WP Pinyin Slugs plugin &lt;= 2.3.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47512 | WordPress Product Enquiry for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47512</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gravity Master Product Enquiry for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 3.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47514 | WordPress Star CloudPRNT for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47514</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in lawrenceowen, gcubero, acunnningham, fmahmood Star CloudPRNT for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 2.0.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48052 | Missing SSL certificate validation in HTTPie v3.2.2 allows attackers to eavesdrop on communications between the host and server via a man-in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48052</link><description>Missing SSL certificate validation in HTTPie v3.2.2 allows attackers to eavesdrop on communications between the host and server via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48053 | Archery v1.10.0 uses a non-random or static IV for Cipher Block Chaining (CBC) mode in AES encryption. This vulnerability can lead to the di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48053</link><description>Archery v1.10.0 uses a non-random or static IV for Cipher Block Chaining (CBC) mode in AES encryption. This vulnerability can lead to the disclosure of information and communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48054 | Missing SSL certificate validation in localstack v2.3.2 allows attackers to eavesdrop on communications between the host and server via a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48054</link><description>Missing SSL certificate validation in localstack v2.3.2 allows attackers to eavesdrop on communications between the host and server via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48055 | SuperAGI v0.0.13 was discovered to use a hardcoded key for encryption operations. This vulnerability can lead to the disclosure of informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48055</link><description>SuperAGI v0.0.13 was discovered to use a hardcoded key for encryption operations. This vulnerability can lead to the disclosure of information and communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48056 | PyPinkSign v0.5.1 uses a non-random or static IV for Cipher Block Chaining (CBC) mode in AES encryption. This vulnerability can lead to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48056</link><description>PyPinkSign v0.5.1 uses a non-random or static IV for Cipher Block Chaining (CBC) mode in AES encryption. This vulnerability can lead to the disclosure of information and communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6176 | Kernel: local dos vulnerability in scatterwalk_copychunks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6176</link><description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the Linux kernel API for the cryptographic algorithm scatterwalk functionality. This issue occurs when a user constructs a malicious packet with specific socket configuration, which could allow a local user to crash the system or escalate their privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47055 | ZDI-CAN-21765: Adobe Premiere Pro M4A File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47055</link><description>Adobe Premiere Pro version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47056 | ZDI-CAN-21763: Adobe Premiere Pro MP4 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47056</link><description>Adobe Premiere Pro version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47057 | ZDI-CAN-21764: Adobe Premiere Pro MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47057</link><description>Adobe Premiere Pro version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47058 | ZDI-CAN-21766: Adobe Premiere Pro MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47058</link><description>Adobe Premiere Pro version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47059 | ZDI-CAN-21767: Adobe Premiere Pro MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47059</link><description>Adobe Premiere Pro version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47060 | ZDI-CAN-21792: Adobe Premiere Pro MP4 File Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47060</link><description>Adobe Premiere Pro version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6013 | H2O Local File Include</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6013</link><description>H2O is vulnerable to stored XSS vulnerability which can lead to a Local File Include attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6017 | H2O S3 Bucket Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6017</link><description>H2O included a reference to an S3 bucket that no longer existed allowing an attacker to take over the S3 bucket URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6019 | Ray Command Injection in cpu_profile Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6019</link><description>A command injection exists in Ray's cpu_profile URL parameter allowing attackers to execute os commands on the system running the ray dashboard remotely without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6021 | Ray Log File Local File Include</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6021</link><description>LFI in Ray's log API endpoint allows attackers to read any file on the server without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6022 | Prefect Cross Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6022</link><description>An attacker is able to steal secrets and potentially gain remote code execution via CSRF using the Prefect API.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6038 | H2O Local File Include</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6038</link><description>An attacker is able to read any file on the server hosting the H2O dashboard without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6015 | MLflow Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6015</link><description>MLflow allowed arbitrary files to be PUT onto the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6016 | H2O Remote Code Execution via POJO Model Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6016</link><description>An attacker is able to gain remote code execution on a server hosting the H2O dashboard through it's POJO model import feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6018 | MLflow Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6018</link><description>An attacker can overwrite any file on the server hosting MLflow without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6023 | ModelDB Local File Include</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6023</link><description>An attacker can read any file on the filesystem on the server hosting ModelDB through an LFI in the artifact_path URL parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26368 | Adobe InCopy Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability v1.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26368</link><description>Adobe InCopy versions 18.5 (and earlier) and 17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47046 | ZDI-CAN-21684: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47046</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47047 | ZDI-CAN-21685: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47047</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47048 | ZDI-CAN-21688: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47048</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47049 | ZDI-CAN-21690: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47049</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47050 | ZDI-CAN-21686: Adobe Audition M4A File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47050</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47051 | ZDI-CAN-21683: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47051</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47052 | ZDI-CAN-21687: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47052</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47053 | ZDI-CAN-21689: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47053</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47054 | ZDI-CAN-21782: Adobe Audition MP4 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47054</link><description>Adobe Audition version 24.0 (and earlier) and 23.6.1 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47040 | ZDI-CAN-21698: Adobe Media Encoder MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47040</link><description>Adobe Media Encoder version 24.0.2 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47041 | ZDI-CAN-21697: Adobe Media Encoder MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47041</link><description>Adobe Media Encoder version 24.0.2 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47042 | ZDI-CAN-21696: Adobe Media Encoder MP4 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47042</link><description>Adobe Media Encoder version 24.0.2 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47043 | ZDI-CAN-21699: Adobe Media Encoder MP4 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47043</link><description>Adobe Media Encoder version 24.0.2 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47044 | ZDI-CAN-21789: Adobe Media Encoder MP4 File Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47044</link><description>Adobe Media Encoder version 24.0.2 (and earlier) and 23.6 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6121 | Kernel: nvme: info leak due to out-of-bounds read in nvmet_ctrl_find_get</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6121</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in the NVMe-oF/TCP subsystem in the Linux kernel. This flaw allows a remote attacker to send a crafted TCP packet, triggering a heap-based buffer overflow that results in kmalloc data to be printed (and potentially leaked) to the kernel ring buffer (dmesg).</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44327 | ZDI-CAN-21793: Adobe Bridge MP4 File Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44327</link><description>Adobe Bridge versions 13.0.4 (and earlier) and 14.0.0 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44328 | ZDI-CAN-21797: Adobe Bridge MP4 File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44328</link><description>Adobe Bridge versions 13.0.4 (and earlier) and 14.0.0 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44329 | ZDI-CAN-21798: Adobe Bridge MP4 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44329</link><description>Adobe Bridge versions 13.0.4 (and earlier) and 14.0.0 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44330 | Adobe Photoshop 2023 CC 24.7 Memory Corruption Vulnerability III.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44330</link><description>Adobe Photoshop versions 24.7.1 (and earlier) and 25.0 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44331 | Adobe Photoshop 2023 CC 24.7 Memory Corruption Vulnerability IV.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44331</link><description>Adobe Photoshop versions 24.7.1 (and earlier) and 25.0 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44332 | Adobe Photoshop 2023 CC 24.7 Memory Corruption Vulnerability II.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44332</link><description>Adobe Photoshop versions 24.7.1 (and earlier) and 25.0 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44333 | Adobe Photoshop 2023 CC 24.7 Memory Corruption Vulnerability V.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44333</link><description>Adobe Photoshop versions 24.7.1 (and earlier) and 25.0 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44334 | Adobe Photoshop 2023 CC 24.7 Memory Corruption Vulnerability VI.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44334</link><description>Adobe Photoshop versions 24.7.1 (and earlier) and 25.0 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44335 | Adobe Photoshop 2023 CC 24.7 Memory Corruption Vulnerability I.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44335</link><description>Adobe Photoshop versions 24.7.1 (and earlier) and 25.0 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4771 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in CKSource CKEditor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4771</link><description>A Cross-Site scripting vulnerability has been found in CKSource CKEditor affecting versions 4.15.1 and earlier. An attacker could send malicious javascript code through the /ckeditor/samples/old/ajax.html file and retrieve an authorized user's information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6174 | Out-of-bounds Read in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6174</link><description>SSH dissector crash in Wireshark 4.0.0 to 4.0.10 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44341 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability I</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44341</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44342 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability II.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44342</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44343 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability III.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44343</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44344 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability V.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44344</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44345 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability VII.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44345</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by a Improper Input Validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44346 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability VIII.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44346</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44347 | Adobe InDesign CC 2023 Memory Corruption Vulnerability IX.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44347</link><description>Adobe InDesign versions ID18.5 (and earlier) and ID17.4.2 (and earlier) are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44336 | TALOS-2023-1794 - Adobe Acrobat Reader Thermometer use-after-free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44336</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44337 | ZDI-CAN-21509: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44337</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44338 | ZDI-CAN-21493: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44338</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44339 | ZDI-CAN-21422: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC AcroForm value Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44339</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44340 | ZDI-CAN-21424: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44340</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44348 | ZDI-CAN-21925: (bypass of VULN-24891) Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44348</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44356 | ZDI-CAN-21956: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44356</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44357 | ZDI-CAN-21930: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44357</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44358 | ZDI-CAN-21971: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44358</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44359 | ZDI-CAN-21936: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44359</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44360 | ZDI-CAN-21882: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44360</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44361 | ZDI-CAN-22041: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44361</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44365 | ZDI-CAN-21931: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44365</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44366 | ZDI-CAN-21928: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44366</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44367 | ZDI-CAN-21929: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44367</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44371 | ZDI-CAN-21998: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44371</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44372 | TALOS-2023-1842 - Adobe Acrobat Reader U3D page event use-after-free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44372</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 23.006.20360 (and earlier) and 20.005.30524 (and earlier) are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6119 | An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Trellix GetSusp prior to version 5.0.0.27 allows a local, low privilege attacker to gain a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6119</link><description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Trellix GetSusp prior to version 5.0.0.27 allows a local, low privilege attacker to gain access to files that usually require a higher privilege level.  This is caused by GetSusp not correctly protecting a directory that it creates during execution, allowing an attacker to take over file handles used by GetSusp. As this runs with high privileges, the attacker gains elevated permissions. The file handles are opened as read-only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44292 | Dell Repository Manager, 3.4.3 and prior, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability in its installation module. A local low-privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44292</link><description>Dell Repository Manager, 3.4.3 and prior, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability in its installation module. A local low-privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to gaining escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44282 | Dell Repository Manager, 3.4.3 and prior, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability in its installation module. A local low-privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44282</link><description>Dell Repository Manager, 3.4.3 and prior, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability in its installation module. A local low-privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to gaining escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39259 | Dell OS Recovery Tool, versions 2.2.4013, 2.3.7012.0, and 2.3.7515.0 contain an Improper Access Control Vulnerability. A local authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39259</link><description>Dell OS Recovery Tool, versions 2.2.4013, 2.3.7012.0, and 2.3.7515.0 contain an Improper Access Control Vulnerability. A local authenticated non-administrator user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the elevation of privilege on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39246 | Dell Encryption, Dell Endpoint Security Suite Enterprise, and Dell Security Management Server version prior to 11.8.1 contain an Insecure Op...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39246</link><description>Dell Encryption, Dell Endpoint Security Suite Enterprise, and Dell Security Management Server version prior to 11.8.1 contain an Insecure Operation on Windows Junction Vulnerability during installation. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to create an arbitrary folder inside a restricted directory, leading to Privilege Escalation</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26031 | Privilege escalation in Apache Hadoop Yarn container-executor binary on Linux systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26031</link><description>Relative library resolution in linux container-executor binary in Apache Hadoop 3.3.1-3.3.4 on Linux allows local user to gain root privileges. If the YARN cluster is accepting work from remote (authenticated) users, this MAY permit remote users to gain root privileges.

Hadoop 3.3.0 updated the " YARN Secure Containers https://hadoop.apache.org/docs/stable/hadoop-yarn/hadoop-yarn-site/SecureContainer.html " to add a feature for executing user-submitted applications in isolated linux containers.

The native binary HADOOP_HOME/bin/container-executor is used to launch these containers; it must be owned by root and have the suid bit set in order for the YARN processes to run the containers as the specific users submitting the jobs.

The patch " YARN-10495 https://issues.apache.org/jira/browse/YARN-10495 . make the rpath of container-executor configurable" modified the library loading path for loading .so files from "$ORIGIN/" to ""$ORIGIN/:../lib/native/". This is the a path through which libcrypto.so is located. Thus it is is possible for a user with reduced privileges to install a malicious libcrypto library into a path to which they have write access, invoke the container-executor command, and have their modified library executed as root.
If the YARN cluster is accepting work from remote (authenticated) users, and these users' submitted job are executed in the physical host, rather than a container, then the CVE permits remote users to gain root privileges.

The fix for the vulnerability is to revert the change, which is done in  YARN-11441 https://issues.apache.org/jira/browse/YARN-11441 , "Revert YARN-10495". This patch is in hadoop-3.3.5.

To determine whether a version of container-executor is vulnerable, use the readelf command. If the RUNPATH or RPATH value contains the relative path "./lib/native/" then it  is at risk

$ readelf -d container-executor|grep 'RUNPATH\|RPATH' 
0x000000000000001d (RUNPATH)            Library runpath: [$ORIGIN/:../lib/native/]

If it does not, then it is safe:

$ readelf -d container-executor|grep 'RUNPATH\|RPATH' 
0x000000000000001d (RUNPATH)            Library runpath: [$ORIGIN/]

For an at-risk version of container-executor to enable privilege escalation, the owner must be root and the suid bit must be set

$ ls -laF /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor
---Sr-s---. 1 root hadoop 802968 May 9 20:21 /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor

A safe installation lacks the suid bit; ideally is also not owned by root.

$ ls -laF /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor
-rwxr-xr-x. 1 yarn hadoop 802968 May 9 20:21 /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor

This configuration does not support Yarn Secure Containers, but all other hadoop services, including YARN job execution outside secure containers continue to work.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32469 | Dell Precision Tower BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A locally authenticated malicious user with admin privileges ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32469</link><description>Dell Precision Tower BIOS contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A locally authenticated malicious user with admin privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to perform arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44296 | Dell ELab-Navigator, version 3.1.9 contains a hard-coded credential vulnerability. A local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44296</link><description>Dell ELab-Navigator, version 3.1.9 contains a hard-coded credential vulnerability. A local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access to sensitive data. Successful exploitation may result in the compromise of confidential user information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 07:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47213 | First Corporation's DVRs use a hard-coded password, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to rewrite or obtain the configuration...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47213</link><description>First Corporation's DVRs use a hard-coded password, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to rewrite or obtain the configuration information of the affected device. Note that updates are provided only for Late model of CFR-4EABC, CFR-4EAB, CFR-8EAB, CFR-16EAB, MD-404AB, and MD-808AB. As for the other products, apply the workaround.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47674 | Missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in First Corporation's DVRs allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to rewrite o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47674</link><description>Missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in First Corporation's DVRs allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to rewrite or obtain the configuration information of the affected device. Note that updates are provided only for Late model of CFR-4EABC, CFR-4EAB, CFR-8EAB, CFR-16EAB, MD-404AB, and MD-808AB. As for the other products, apply the workaround.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43752 | OS command injection vulnerability in WRC-X3000GS2-W v1.05 and earlier, WRC-X3000GS2-B v1.05 and earlier, and WRC-X3000GS2A-B v1.05 and earl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43752</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability in WRC-X3000GS2-W v1.05 and earlier, WRC-X3000GS2-B v1.05 and earlier, and WRC-X3000GS2A-B v1.05 and earlier allows a network-adjacent authenticated user to execute an arbitrary OS command by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43757 | Inadequate encryption strength vulnerability in multiple routers provided by ELECOM CO.,LTD. and LOGITEC CORPORATION allows a network-adjace...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43757</link><description>Inadequate encryption strength vulnerability in multiple routers provided by ELECOM CO.,LTD. and LOGITEC CORPORATION allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to guess the encryption key used for wireless LAN communication and intercept the communication. As for the affected products/versions, see the information provided by the vendor under [References] section.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47335 | Insecure permissions in the setNFZEnable function of Autel Robotics EVO Nano drone v1.6.5 allows attackers to breach the geo-fence and fly i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47335</link><description>Insecure permissions in the setNFZEnable function of Autel Robotics EVO Nano drone v1.6.5 allows attackers to breach the geo-fence and fly into no-fly zones.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47003 | An issue in RedisGraph v.2.12.10 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a crafted string in DataBloc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47003</link><description>An issue in RedisGraph v.2.12.10 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a crafted string in DataBlock_ItemIsDeleted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43275 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 in 110 backend management interface via /catalog_add.php, allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43275</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 in 110 backend management interface via /catalog_add.php, allows attackers to create crafted web pages due to a lack of verification of the token value of the submitted form.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 04:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35437 | SQL injection vulnerability in LMXCMS v.1.4 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code via the TagsAction.class.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35437</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in LMXCMS v.1.4 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code via the TagsAction.class.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 04:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47471 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in strukturag libde265 v1.10.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the slice_segment_hea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47471</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in strukturag libde265 v1.10.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the slice_segment_header function in the slice.cc component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 03:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47470 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg before github commit 4565747056a11356210ed8edcecb920105e40b60 allows a remote attacker to achieve an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47470</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg before github commit 4565747056a11356210ed8edcecb920105e40b60 allows a remote attacker to achieve an out-of-array write, execute arbitrary code, and cause a denial of service (DoS) via the ref_pic_list_struct function in libavcodec/evc_ps.c</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47263 | Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service (DoS) in the antivirus engine when scanning a fuzzed PE32 file. This affects WithSecur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47263</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service (DoS) in the antivirus engine when scanning a fuzzed PE32 file. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant (formerly F-Secure Atlant) 15 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47264 | Certain WithSecure products have a buffer over-read whereby processing certain fuzz file types may cause a denial of service (DoS). This aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47264</link><description>Certain WithSecure products have a buffer over-read whereby processing certain fuzz file types may cause a denial of service (DoS). This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant (formerly F-Secure Atlant) 15 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48204 | An issue in PublicCMS v.4.0.202302.e allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the appToken and Parameters parameter of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48204</link><description>An issue in PublicCMS v.4.0.202302.e allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the appToken and Parameters parameter of the api/method/getHtml component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48199 | An issue in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the QR code funciton in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48199</link><description>An issue in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the QR code funciton in the manageapikeys component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48198 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48198</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the product description component in the api/stock/products endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48197 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48197</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the QR code function in the manageapikeys component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4689 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4689</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the eae_save_elements function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable/disable elementor addon elements via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4690 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4690</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the eae_save_config function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change configuration settings for the plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4723 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7 v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4723</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7 via the ajax_eae_post_data function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including post/page ids and titles including  those of with pending/draft/future/private status.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5381 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and inc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5381</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48200 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48200</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the equipment description component within /equipment/ component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47347 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP messages whose Sequence Number...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47347</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP messages whose Sequence Number is mutated to overflow bytes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47444 | An issue discovered in OpenCart 4.0.0.0 to 4.0.2.3 allows authenticated backend users having common/security write privilege can write arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47444</link><description>An issue discovered in OpenCart 4.0.0.0 to 4.0.2.3 allows authenticated backend users having common/security write privilege can write arbitrary untrusted data inside config.php and admin/config.php, resulting in remote code execution on the underlying server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47345 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP message with malformed PFCP He...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47345</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP message with malformed PFCP Heartbeat message whose Recovery Time Stamp IE length is mutated to zero.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41442 | An issue in Kloudq Technologies Limited Tor Equip 1.0, Tor Loco Mini 1.0 through 3.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41442</link><description>An issue in Kloudq Technologies Limited Tor Equip 1.0, Tor Loco Mini 1.0 through 3.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the MQTT component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48365 | Qlik Sense Enterprise for Windows before August 2023 Patch 2 allows unauthenticated remote code execution, aka QB-21683. Due to improper val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48365</link><description>Qlik Sense Enterprise for Windows before August 2023 Patch 2 allows unauthenticated remote code execution, aka QB-21683. Due to improper validation of HTTP headers, a remote attacker is able to elevate their privilege by tunneling HTTP requests, allowing them to execute HTTP requests on the backend server that hosts the repository application. The fixed versions are August 2023 Patch 2, May 2023 Patch 6, February 2023 Patch 10, November 2022 Patch 12, August 2022 Patch 14, May 2022 Patch 16, February 2022 Patch 15, and November 2021 Patch 17. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-41265.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48224 | Cryptographically Weak Generation of One-Time Codes for Identity Verification in ethyca-fides</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48224</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform for managing the fulfillment of data privacy requests in a runtime environment, and the enforcement of privacy regulations in code. The Fides Privacy Center allows data subject users to submit privacy and consent requests to data controller users of the Fides web application. Privacy requests allow data subjects to submit a request to access all person data held by the data controller, or delete/erase it.  Consent request allows data subject users to modify their privacy preferences for how the data controller uses their personal data e.g. data sales and sharing consent opt-in/opt-out. If `subject_identity_verification_required` in the `[execution]` section of `fides.toml` or the env var `FIDES__EXECUTION__SUBJECT_IDENTITY_VERIFICATION_REQUIRED` is set to `True` on the fides webserver backend, data subjects are sent a one-time code to their email address or phone number, depending on messaging configuration, and the one-time code must be entered in the Privacy Center UI by the data subject before the privacy or consent request is submitted. It was identified that the one-time code values for these requests were generated by the python `random` module, a cryptographically weak pseduo-random number generator (PNRG). If an attacker generates several hundred consecutive one-time codes, this vulnerability allows the attacker to predict all future one-time code values during the lifetime of the backend python process. There is no security impact on data access requests as the personal data download package is not shared in the Privacy Center itself. However, this vulnerability allows an attacker to (i) submit a verified data erasure request, resulting in deletion of data for the targeted user and (ii) submit a verified consent request, modifying a user's privacy preferences. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.24.0`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6105 | ManageEngine Information Disclosure in Multiple Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6105</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in multiple ManageEngine products that can result in encryption keys being exposed. A low-privileged OS user with access to the host where an affected ManageEngine product is installed can view and use the exposed key to decrypt product database passwords. This allows the user to access the ManageEngine product database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22818 | Multiple DLL Search Order hijacking Vulnerabilities in SanDisk Security Installer for Windows </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22818</link><description>Multiple DLL Search Order Hijack vulnerabilities were addressed in the SanDisk Security Installer for
Windows that could allow attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by executing the installer
in the same folder as the malicious DLL. This can lead to the execution of arbitrary
code with the privileges of the vulnerable application or obtain a certain level of persistence
on the compromised host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41699 | Payara Platform: URL Redirection to untrusted site using FORM authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41699</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server, Micro and Embedded (Servlet Implementation modules) allows Redirect Access to Libraries.This issue affects Payara Server, Micro and Embedded: from 5.0.0 before 5.57.0, from 4.1.2.191 before 4.1.2.191.46, from 6.0.0 before 6.8.0, from 6.2023.1 before 6.2023.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30954 | Gotham Video Broken Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30954</link><description>The Gotham video-application-server service contained a race condition which would cause it to not apply certain acls new videos if the source system had not yet initialized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47636 | Full Path Disclosure via re-export document in pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47636</link><description>The Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. Full Path Disclosure (FPD) vulnerabilities enable the attacker to see the path to the webroot/file. e.g.: /home/omg/htdocs/file/. Certain vulnerabilities, such as using the load_file() (within a SQL Injection) query to view the page source, require the attacker to have the full path to the file they wish to view. In the case of pimcore, the fopen() function here doesn't have an error handle when the file doesn't exist on the server so the server response raises the full path "fopen(/var/www/html/var/tmp/export-{ uniqe id}.csv)". This issue has been patched in commit `10d178ef771` which has been included in release version 1.2.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47637 | SQL Injection in Admin Grid Filter API in Pimcore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47637</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. In affected versions the `/admin/object/grid-proxy` endpoint calls `getFilterCondition()` on fields of classes to be filtered for, passing input from the request, and later executes the returned SQL.  One implementation of `getFilterCondition()` is in `Multiselect`, which does not normalize/escape/validate the passed value. Any backend user with very basic permissions can execute arbitrary SQL statements and thus alter any data or escalate their privileges to at least admin level. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 11.1.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48011 | GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the flush_ref_samples function at /gpac/src/isome...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48011</link><description>GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the flush_ref_samples function at /gpac/src/isomedia/movie_fragments.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48013 | GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a double free via the gf_filterpacket_del function at /gpac/src/filter_core...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48013</link><description>GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a double free via the gf_filterpacket_del function at /gpac/src/filter_core/filter.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48014 | GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the hevc_parse_vps_extension function at /media_tools/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48014</link><description>GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the hevc_parse_vps_extension function at /media_tools/av_parsers.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48219 | Special characters in unescaped text nodes can trigger mXSS in TinyMCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48219</link><description>TinyMCE is an open source rich text editor. A mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS) vulnerability was discovered in TinyMCE’s core undo/redo functionality and other APIs and plugins. Text nodes within specific parents are not escaped upon serialization according to the HTML standard. If such text nodes contain a special character reserved as an internal marker, they can be combined with other HTML patterns to form malicious snippets. These snippets pass the initial sanitisation layer when the content is parsed into the editor body, but can trigger XSS when the special internal marker is removed from the content and re-parsed. his vulnerability has been patched in TinyMCE versions 6.7.3 and 5.10.9. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5997 | Use after free in Garbage Collection in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corrupti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5997</link><description>Use after free in Garbage Collection in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6112 | Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6112</link><description>Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34982 | AVEVA Operations Control Logger External Control of File Name or Path </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34982</link><description>This external control vulnerability, if exploited, could allow a local OS-authenticated user with standard privileges to delete files with System privilege on the machine where these products are installed, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33873 | AVEVA Operations Control Logger Execution with Unnecessary Privileges </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33873</link><description>This privilege escalation vulnerability, if exploited, cloud allow a local OS-authenticated user with standard privileges to escalate to System privilege on the machine where these products are installed, resulting in complete compromise of the target machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48087 | xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/clearLog and /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailCat.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48087</link><description>xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/clearLog and /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailCat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48088 | xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailPage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48088</link><description>xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailPage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48089 | xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via /xxl-job-admin/jobcode/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48089</link><description>xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via /xxl-job-admin/jobcode/save.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5676 | Eclipse OpenJ9 possible infinite busy hang</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5676</link><description>In Eclipse OpenJ9 before version 0.41.0, the JVM can be forced into an infinite busy hang on a spinlock or a segmentation fault if a shutdown signal (SIGTERM, SIGINT or SIGHUP) is received before the JVM has finished initializing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5720 | Quarkus: build env information disclosure via gradle plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5720</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus, where it does not properly sanitize artifacts created using the Gradle plugin, allowing certain build system information to remain. This flaw allows an attacker to access potentially sensitive information from the build system within the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4602 | The Namaste! LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'course_id'  parameter in versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4602</link><description>The Namaste! LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'course_id'  parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.6.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5245 | Using MLeap for loading a saved model (zip archive) can lead to path traversal/arbitrary file creation and possibly remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5245</link><description>FileUtil.extract() enumerates all zip file entries and extracts each file without validating whether file paths in the archive are outside the intended directory.

When creating an instance of TensorflowModel using the saved_model format and an exported tensorflow model, the apply() function invokes the vulnerable implementation of FileUtil.extract().

Arbitrary file creation can directly lead to code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23549 | DoS via long hostnames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23549</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Checkmk &lt;2.2.0p15, &lt;2.1.0p37, &lt;=2.0.0p39 allows priviledged attackers to cause partial denial of service of the UI via too long hostnames.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34062 | In Reactor Netty HTTP Server, versions 1.1.x prior to 1.1.13 and versions 1.0.x prior to 1.0.39, a malicious user can send a request using a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34062</link><description>In Reactor Netty HTTP Server, versions 1.1.x prior to 1.1.13 and versions 1.0.x prior to 1.0.39, a malicious user can send a request using a specially crafted URL that can lead to a directory traversal attack.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable if Reactor Netty HTTP Server is configured to serve static resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 09:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46672 | Logstash Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46672</link><description>An issue was identified by Elastic whereby sensitive information is recorded in Logstash logs under specific circumstances.

The prerequisites for the manifestation of this issue are:

  *  Logstash  is configured to log in JSON format https://www.elastic.co/guide/en/logstash/current/running-logstash-command-line.html , which is not the default logging format.


  *  Sensitive data is stored in the Logstash keystore and referenced as a variable in Logstash configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4889 | The Shareaholic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shareaholic' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4889</link><description>The Shareaholic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shareaholic' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.7.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6133 | The Forminator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient blacklisting on the 'forminator_allowed_mime...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6133</link><description>The Forminator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient blacklisting on the 'forminator_allowed_mime_types' function in versions up to, and including, 1.27.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, but due to the htaccess configuration, remote code cannot be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47584 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47584</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted VPR file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47585 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47585</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted VPR file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47586 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47586</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted VPR file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41597 | EyouCms v1.6.2 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin/twitter.php?active_t.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41597</link><description>EyouCms v1.6.2 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin/twitter.php?active_t.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47446 | Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the profile.php page via fullname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47446</link><description>Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the profile.php page via fullname parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47580 | Multiple improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer issues exist in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47580</link><description>Multiple improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer issues exist in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1, V8, or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47581 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47581</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1, V8, or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47582 | Access of uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47582</link><description>Access of uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1, V8, or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47583 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in TELLUS Simulator V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1 or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47583</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in TELLUS Simulator V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1 or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47445 | Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the username parameter in preschool/admin/ page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47445</link><description>Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the username parameter in preschool/admin/ page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40923 | MyPrestaModules ordersexport before v5.0 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at send.php via the key and save_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40923</link><description>MyPrestaModules ordersexport before v5.0 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at send.php via the key and save_setting parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6032 | A CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal')
vulnerability exists that could cause a file system...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6032</link><description>A CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal')
vulnerability exists that could cause a file system enumeration and file download when an
attacker navigates to the Network Management Card via HTTPS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5987 | A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (Cross-site Scripting)
vulnerability that could cause a vulnerability l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5987</link><description>A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (Cross-site Scripting)
vulnerability that could cause a vulnerability leading to a cross site scripting condition where
attackers can have a victim’s browser run arbitrary JavaScript when they visit a page containing
the injected payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5986 | A CWE-601 URL Redirection to Untrusted Site vulnerability exists that could cause an openredirect vulnerability leading to a cross site scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5986</link><description>A CWE-601 URL Redirection to Untrusted Site vulnerability exists that could cause an openredirect vulnerability leading to a cross site scripting attack. By providing a URL-encoded input
attackers can cause the software’s web application to redirect to the chosen domain after a
successful login is performed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5984 | A CWE-494 Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could allow
modified firmware to be uploaded when an authorized...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5984</link><description>A CWE-494 Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could allow
modified firmware to be uploaded when an authorized admin user begins a firmware update
procedure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5985 | A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability
exists that could cause compromise of a user’s browser wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5985</link><description>A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability
exists that could cause compromise of a user’s browser when an attacker with admin privileges
has modified system values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47678 | An improper access control vulnerability exists in RT-AC87U all versions. An attacker may read or write files that are not intended to be ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47678</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in RT-AC87U all versions. An attacker may read or write files that are not intended to be accessed by connecting to a target device via tftp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47308 | In the module "Newsletter Popup PRO with Voucher/Coupon code" (newsletterpop) before version 2.6.1 from Active Design for PrestaShop, a gues...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47308</link><description>In the module "Newsletter Popup PRO with Voucher/Coupon code" (newsletterpop) before version 2.6.1 from Active Design for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions. The method `NewsletterpopsendVerificationModuleFrontController::checkEmailSubscription()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47309 | Nukium nkmgls before version 3.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via NkmGlsCheckoutModuleFrontController::displayAjaxSavePhone...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47309</link><description>Nukium nkmgls before version 3.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via NkmGlsCheckoutModuleFrontController::displayAjaxSavePhoneMobile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43979 | ETS Soft ybc_blog before v4.4.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component Ybc_blogBlogModuleFrontController:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43979</link><description>ETS Soft ybc_blog before v4.4.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component Ybc_blogBlogModuleFrontController::getPosts().</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>