<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 08:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-38826 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Follet Learning Solutions Destiny through 20.0_1U. via the handlewpesearchform.do. sear...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38826</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Follet Learning Solutions Destiny through 20.0_1U. via the handlewpesearchform.do. searchString.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 08:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49226 | An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. Command injection in the traceroute feature of the administration console allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49226</link><description>An issue was discovered in Peplink Balance Two before 8.4.0. Command injection in the traceroute feature of the administration console allows users with admin privileges to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34267 | An issue was discovered in RWS WorldServer before 11.7.3. Adding a token parameter with the value of 02 bypasses all authentication requirem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34267</link><description>An issue was discovered in RWS WorldServer before 11.7.3. Adding a token parameter with the value of 02 bypasses all authentication requirements. Arbitrary Java code can be uploaded and executed via a .jar archive to the ws-api/v2/customizations/api endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34268 | An issue was discovered in RWS WorldServer before 11.7.3. /clientLogin deserializes Java objects without authentication, leading to command ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34268</link><description>An issue was discovered in RWS WorldServer before 11.7.3. /clientLogin deserializes Java objects without authentication, leading to command execution on the host.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36485 | The workflow-engine of ILIAS before 7.23 and 8 before 8.3 allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary system commands on the applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36485</link><description>The workflow-engine of ILIAS before 7.23 and 8 before 8.3 allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary system commands on the application server as the application user via a malicious BPMN2 workflow definition file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36486 | The workflow-engine of ILIAS before 7.23 and 8 before 8.3 allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary system commands on the applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36486</link><description>The workflow-engine of ILIAS before 7.23 and 8 before 8.3 allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary system commands on the application server as the application user by uploading a workflow definition file with a malicious filename.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49954 | The CRM Integration in 3CX before 18.0.9.23 and 20 before 20.0.0.1494 allows SQL Injection via a first name, search string, or email address...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49954</link><description>The CRM Integration in 3CX before 18.0.9.23 and 20 before 20.0.0.1494 allows SQL Injection via a first name, search string, or email address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31224 | There is broken access control during authentication in Jamf Pro Server before 10.46.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31224</link><description>There is broken access control during authentication in Jamf Pro Server before 10.46.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48652 | Concrete CMS 9 before 9.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /ccm/system/dialogs/logs/delete_all/submit. An attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48652</link><description>Concrete CMS 9 before 9.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /ccm/system/dialogs/logs/delete_all/submit. An attacker can force an admin user to delete server report logs on a web application to which they are currently authenticated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:22:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28872 | Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 13.10 allows attackers to execute DLL files with SYSTEM privileges by creating a sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28872</link><description>Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 13.10 allows attackers to execute DLL files with SYSTEM privileges by creating a symbolic link from a %LOCALAPPDATA%\Temp\NcpSupport* location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31297 | An issue was discovered in SESAMI planfocus CPTO (Cash Point &amp; Transport Optimizer) 6.3.8.6 718. There is XSS via the Name field when modify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31297</link><description>An issue was discovered in SESAMI planfocus CPTO (Cash Point &amp; Transport Optimizer) 6.3.8.6 718. There is XSS via the Name field when modifying a client.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47091 | An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) SNS 4.3.13 through 4.3.22 before 4.3.23, SNS 4.6.0 through 4.6.9 before 4.6.10...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47091</link><description>An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) SNS 4.3.13 through 4.3.22 before 4.3.23, SNS 4.6.0 through 4.6.9 before 4.6.10, and SNS 4.7.0 through 4.7.1 before 4.7.2. An attacker can overflow the cookie threshold, making an IPsec connection impossible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 07:03:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37185 | C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the function zfp_prec_decompress at zfp/blosc2-zfp.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37185</link><description>C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the function zfp_prec_decompress at zfp/blosc2-zfp.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37186 | C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference in ndlz/ndlz8x8.c via a NULL pointer to memset.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37186</link><description>C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference in ndlz/ndlz8x8.c via a NULL pointer to memset.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37187 | C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the zfp/blosc2-zfp.c zfp_acc_decompress. function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37187</link><description>C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the zfp/blosc2-zfp.c zfp_acc_decompress. function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37188 | C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the function zfp_rate_decompress at zfp/blosc2-zfp.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37188</link><description>C-blosc2 before 2.9.3 was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the function zfp_rate_decompress at zfp/blosc2-zfp.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47247 | In SysAid On-Premise before 23.3.34, there is an edge case in which an end user is able to delete a Knowledge Base article, aka bug 15102.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47247</link><description>In SysAid On-Premise before 23.3.34, there is an edge case in which an end user is able to delete a Knowledge Base article, aka bug 15102.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31289 | Pexip Infinity before 31.2 has Improper Input Validation for signalling, allowing remote attackers to trigger an abort.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31289</link><description>Pexip Infinity before 31.2 has Improper Input Validation for signalling, allowing remote attackers to trigger an abort.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31455 | Pexip Infinity before 31.2 has Improper Input Validation for RTCP, allowing remote attackers to trigger an abort.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31455</link><description>Pexip Infinity before 31.2 has Improper Input Validation for RTCP, allowing remote attackers to trigger an abort.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37225 | Pexip Infinity before 32 allows Webapp1 XSS via preconfigured links.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37225</link><description>Pexip Infinity before 32 allows Webapp1 XSS via preconfigured links.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40236 | In Pexip VMR self-service portal before 3, the same SSH host key is used across different customers' installations, which allows authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40236</link><description>In Pexip VMR self-service portal before 3, the same SSH host key is used across different customers' installations, which allows authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43675 | An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. Reflected XSS in the Network Element Manager exists via /oms1350/pages/otn/cpbLogDisplay via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43675</link><description>An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. Reflected XSS in the Network Element Manager exists via /oms1350/pages/otn/cpbLogDisplay via the filename parameter, under /oms1350/pages/otn/connection/E2ERoutingDisplayWithOverLay via the id parameter, and under /oms1350/pages/otn/mainOtn via all parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49328 | On a Wolters Kluwer B.POINT 23.70.00 server running Linux on premises, during the authentication phase, a validated system user can achieve ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49328</link><description>On a Wolters Kluwer B.POINT 23.70.00 server running Linux on premises, during the authentication phase, a validated system user can achieve remote code execution via Argument Injection in the server-to-server module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41762 | An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. Multiple Reflected XSS vulnerabilities exist in the Network Element Manager via any parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41762</link><description>An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. Multiple Reflected XSS vulnerabilities exist in the Network Element Manager via any parameter to log.pl, the bench or pid parameter to top.pl, or the id parameter to easy1350.pl.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:04:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39822 | In NOKIA NFM-T R19.9, a SQL Injection vulnerability occurs in /cgi-bin/R19.9/easy1350.pl of the VM Manager WebUI via the id or host HTTP GET...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39822</link><description>In NOKIA NFM-T R19.9, a SQL Injection vulnerability occurs in /cgi-bin/R19.9/easy1350.pl of the VM Manager WebUI via the id or host HTTP GET parameter. An authenticated attacker is required for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41760 | An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. Relative Path Traversal can occur under /oms1350/data/cpb/log of the Network Element Manager v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41760</link><description>An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. Relative Path Traversal can occur under /oms1350/data/cpb/log of the Network Element Manager via the filename parameter, allowing a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41761 | An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. An Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability exists under /cgi-bin/R19.9/viewlog.pl of the VM Mana...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41761</link><description>An issue was discovered in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9. An Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability exists under /cgi-bin/R19.9/viewlog.pl of the VM Manager WebUI via the logfile parameter, allowing a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39818 | In NOKIA NFM-T R19.9, an OS Command Injection vulnerability occurs in /cgi-bin/R19.9/log.pl of the VM Manager WebUI via the cmd HTTP GET par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39818</link><description>In NOKIA NFM-T R19.9, an OS Command Injection vulnerability occurs in /cgi-bin/R19.9/log.pl of the VM Manager WebUI via the cmd HTTP GET parameter. This allows authenticated users to execute commands, with root privileges, on the operating system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39820 | In Network Element Manager in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9, an Unprotected Storage of Credentials vulnerability occurs under /root/RestUploadManager.xm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39820</link><description>In Network Element Manager in NOKIA NFM-T R19.9, an Unprotected Storage of Credentials vulnerability occurs under /root/RestUploadManager.xml.DRC and /DEPOT/KECustom_199/OTNE_DRC/RestUploadManager.xml. A remote user, authenticated to the operating system, with access privileges to the directory /root or /DEPOT, is able to read cleartext credentials to access the web portal NFM-T and control all the PPS Network elements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51772 | One Identity Password Manager before 5.13.1 allows Kiosk Escape. This product enables users to reset their Active Directory passwords on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51772</link><description>One Identity Password Manager before 5.13.1 allows Kiosk Escape. This product enables users to reset their Active Directory passwords on the login screen of a Windows client. It launches a Chromium based browser in Kiosk mode to provide the reset functionality. The escape sequence is: wait for a session timeout, click on the Help icon, observe that there is a browser window for the One Identity website, navigate to any website that offers file upload, navigate to cmd.exe from the file explorer window, and launch cmd.exe as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48654 | One Identity Password Manager before 5.13.1 allows Kiosk Escape. This product enables users to reset their Active Directory passwords on the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48654</link><description>One Identity Password Manager before 5.13.1 allows Kiosk Escape. This product enables users to reset their Active Directory passwords on the login screen of a Windows client. It launches a Chromium based browser in Kiosk mode to provide the reset functionality. The escape sequence is: go to the Google ReCAPTCHA section, click on the Privacy link, observe that there is a new browser window, navigate to any website that offers file upload, navigate to cmd.exe from the file explorer window, and launch cmd.exe as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30451 | In TYPO3 11.5.24, the filelist component allows attackers (who have access to the administrator panel) to read arbitrary files via directory...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30451</link><description>In TYPO3 11.5.24, the filelist component allows attackers (who have access to the administrator panel) to read arbitrary files via directory traversal in the baseuri field, as demonstrated by POST /typo3/record/edit with ../../../ in data[sys_file_storage]*[data][sDEF][lDEF][basePath][vDEF].</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51771 | In MicroHttpServer (aka Micro HTTP Server) through a8ab029, _ParseHeader in lib/server.c allows a one-byte recv buffer overflow via a long U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51771</link><description>In MicroHttpServer (aka Micro HTTP Server) through a8ab029, _ParseHeader in lib/server.c allows a one-byte recv buffer overflow via a long URI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7100 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System bwdates-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7100</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fdate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248952.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 03:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7099 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System bwdates-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7099</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file bwdates-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248951.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 02:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38927 | IBM Aspera Console cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38927</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  210322.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 02:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49880 | IBM Financial Transaction Manager for SWIFT Services data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49880</link><description>In the Message Entry and Repair (MER) facility of IBM Financial Transaction Manager for SWIFT Services 3.2.4 the sending address and the message type of FIN messages are assumed to be immutable. However, an attacker might modify these elements of a business transaction.  IBM X-Force ID:  273183.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 02:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43064 | IBM i code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43064</link><description>Facsimile Support for IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library call.  A malicious actor could cause arbitrary code to run with the privilege of the user invoking the facsimile support.  IBM X-Force ID:  267689.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 02:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7098 | icret EasyImages hide.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7098</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in icret EasyImages 2.8.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file app/hide.php. The manipulation of the argument key leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248950 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 02:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7097 | code-projects Water Billing System addbill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7097</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Water Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /addbill.php. The manipulation of the argument owners_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248949 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 02:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7096 | code-projects Faculty Management System crud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7096</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Faculty Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/php/crud.php. The manipulation of the argument fieldname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248948.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 01:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7095 | Totolink A7100RU HTTP POST Request main buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7095</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink A7100RU 7.4cu.2313_B20191024. Affected by this issue is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument flag leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248942 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 01:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7094 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway nsasg6.0.tgz information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7094</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /protocol/nsasg6.0.tgz. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248941 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 01:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7093 | KylinSoft kylin-system-updater com.kylin.systemupgrade Service UpgradeStrategiesDbus.py os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7093</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in KylinSoft kylin-system-updater up to 2.0.5.16-0k2.33. Affected is an unknown function of the file /usr/share/kylin-system-updater/SystemUpdater/UpgradeStrategiesDbus.py of the component com.kylin.systemupgrade Service. The manipulation of the argument SetDownloadspeedMax leads to os command injection. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248940. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7092 | Uniway UW-302VP Admin Web Interface wlan_basic_set.cgi cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7092</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Uniway UW-302VP 2.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boaform/wlan_basic_set.cgi of the component Admin Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument wlanssid/password leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248939. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7102 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7102</link><description>Use of a Third Party library produced a vulnerability in Barracuda Networks Inc. Barracuda ESG Appliance which allowed Parameter Injection.This issue affected Barracuda ESG Appliance, from 5.1.3.001 through 9.2.1.001, until Barracuda removed the vulnerable logic.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7101 | Arbitrary Code Execution (ACE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7101</link><description>Spreadsheet::ParseExcel version 0.65 is a Perl module used for parsing Excel files. Spreadsheet::ParseExcel is vulnerable to an arbitrary code execution (ACE) vulnerability due to passing unvalidated input from a file into a string-type “eval”. Specifically, the issue stems from the evaluation of Number format strings (not to be confused with printf-style format strings) within the Excel parsing logic.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7091 | Dreamer CMS uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7091</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /upload/uploadFile. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248938 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51714 | An issue was discovered in the HTTP2 implementation in Qt before 5.15.17, 6.x before 6.2.11, 6.3.x through 6.5.x before 6.5.4, and 6.6.x bef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51714</link><description>An issue was discovered in the HTTP2 implementation in Qt before 5.15.17, 6.x before 6.2.11, 6.3.x through 6.5.x before 6.5.4, and 6.6.x before 6.6.2. network/access/http2/hpacktable.cpp has an incorrect HPack integer overflow check.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51767 | OpenSSH through 9.6, when common types of DRAM are used, might allow row hammer attacks (for authentication bypass) because the integer valu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51767</link><description>OpenSSH through 9.6, when common types of DRAM are used, might allow row hammer attacks (for authentication bypass) because the integer value of authenticated in mm_answer_authpassword does not resist flips of a single bit. NOTE: this is applicable to a certain threat model of attacker-victim co-location in which the attacker has user privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 06:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51765 | sendmail through at least 8.14.7 allows SMTP smuggling in certain configurations. Remote attackers can use a published exploitation techniqu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51765</link><description>sendmail through at least 8.14.7 allows SMTP smuggling in certain configurations. Remote attackers can use a published exploitation technique to inject e-mail messages that appear to originate from the sendmail server, allowing bypass of an SPF protection mechanism. This occurs because sendmail supports &lt;LF&gt;.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;LF&gt; but some other popular e-mail servers do not.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 05:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51766 | Exim through 4.97 allows SMTP smuggling in certain configurations. Remote attackers can use a published exploitation technique to inject e-m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51766</link><description>Exim through 4.97 allows SMTP smuggling in certain configurations. Remote attackers can use a published exploitation technique to inject e-mail messages that appear to originate from the Exim server, allowing bypass of an SPF protection mechanism. This occurs because Exim supports &lt;LF&gt;.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;LF&gt; but some other popular e-mail servers do not.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 05:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51764 | Postfix through 3.8.4 allows SMTP smuggling unless configured with smtpd_data_restrictions=reject_unauth_pipelining (or certain other option...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51764</link><description>Postfix through 3.8.4 allows SMTP smuggling unless configured with smtpd_data_restrictions=reject_unauth_pipelining (or certain other options that exist in recent versions). Remote attackers can use a published exploitation technique to inject e-mail messages that appear to originate from the Postfix server, allowing bypass of an SPF protection mechanism. This occurs because Postfix supports &lt;LF&gt;.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;LF&gt; but some other popular e-mail servers do not. To prevent attack variants (by always disallowing &lt;LF&gt; without &lt;CR&gt;), a different solution is required: the smtpd_forbid_bare_newline=yes option with a Postfix minimum version of 3.5.23, 3.6.13, 3.7.9, 3.8.4, or 3.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 05:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51763 | csv_builder.rb in ActiveAdmin (aka Active Admin) before 3.2.0 allows CSV injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51763</link><description>csv_builder.rb in ActiveAdmin (aka Active Admin) before 3.2.0 allows CSV injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7090 | Sudo: improper handling of ipa_hostname leads to privilege mismanagement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7090</link><description>A flaw was found in sudo in the handling of ipa_hostname, where ipa_hostname from /etc/sssd/sssd.conf was not propagated in sudo. Therefore, it leads to privilege mismanagement vulnerability in applications, where client hosts retain privileges even after retracting them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49594 | An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the challenge functionality of instipod DuoUniversalKeycloakAuthenticator 1.0.7 plugin. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49594</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the challenge functionality of instipod DuoUniversalKeycloakAuthenticator 1.0.7 plugin. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An user login to Keycloak using  DuoUniversalKeycloakAuthenticator plugin triggers this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15036 | Deis Workflow Manager race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15036</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Deis Workflow Manager up to 2.3.2. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to race condition. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. Upgrading to version 2.3.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 31fe3bccbdde134a185752e53380330d16053f7f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248847. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 20:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125108 | w3c online-spellchecker-py spellchecker cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in w3c online-spellchecker-py up to 20140130. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file spellchecker. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The identifier of the patch is d6c21fd8187c5db2a50425ff80694149e75d722e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-248849 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 16:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7008 | Systemd-resolved: unsigned name response in signed zone is not refused when dnssec=yes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7008</link><description>A vulnerability was found in systemd-resolved. This issue may allow systemd-resolved to accept records of DNSSEC-signed domains even when they have no signature, allowing man-in-the-middles (or the upstream DNS resolver) to manipulate records.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 13:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36769 | The Widget Settings Importer/Exporter Plugin  for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wp_ajax_import_widget_datap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36769</link><description>The Widget Settings Importer/Exporter Plugin  for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wp_ajax_import_widget_dataparameter AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6744 | The Divi theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'et_pb_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6744</link><description>The Divi theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'et_pb_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied custom field data. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5962 | ioLogik E1200 Series: Weak Cryptographic Algorithm Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5962</link><description>A weak cryptographic algorithm vulnerability has been identified in ioLogik E1200 Series firmware versions v3.3 and prior. This vulnerability can help an attacker compromise the confidentiality of sensitive data. This vulnerability may lead an attacker to get unexpected authorization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5961 | ioLogik E1200 Series: Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5961</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability has been identified in ioLogik E1200 Series firmware versions v3.3 and prior. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to trick a client into making an unintentional request to the web server, which will be treated as an authentic request. This vulnerability may lead an attacker to perform operations on behalf of the victimized user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6971 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in versions 1.0.8 to 1.3.9 via the 'content-dir' HTTP heade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6971</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in versions 1.0.8 to 1.3.9 via the 'content-dir' HTTP header. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include remote files on the server, resulting in code execution. NOTE: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that the target server's php.ini is configured with 'allow_url_include' set to 'on'. This feature is deprecated as of PHP 7.4 and is disabled by default, but can still be explicitly enabled in later versions of PHP.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6972 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 via the 'content-backu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6972</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 via the 'content-backups' and 'content-name', 'content-manifest', or 'content-bmitmp' and 'content-identy' HTTP headers. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, including the wp-config.php file, which can make site takeover and remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7002 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to OS Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9  via the 'url' p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7002</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to OS Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9  via the 'url' parameter. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to execute arbitrary commands on the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>