<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-53738 | WordPress Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster plugin &amp;lt;=1.3.9.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53738</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Gabe Livan Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster: from n/a through 1.3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12002 | Tenda FH451/FH1201/FH1202/FH1206 GetIPTV websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12002</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda FH451, FH1201, FH1202 and FH1206 up to 20241129. Affected by this vulnerability is the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 13:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12001 | code-projects Wazifa System Setting updatesettings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /controllers/updatesettings.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12000 | code-projects Blood Bank System Setting updatesettings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/updatesettings.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11998 | code-projects Farmacia visualizer-forneccedor.chp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /visualizer-forneccedor.chp. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 09:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11997 | code-projects Farmacia vendas.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /vendas.php. The manipulation of the argument notaFiscal leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 08:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11996 | code-projects Farmacia editar-fornecedor.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11996</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /editar-fornecedor.php. The manipulation of the argument cidade leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 07:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11252 | Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share &amp;lt;= 3.3.69 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via heateor_mastodon_share Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11252</link><description>The Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the heateor_mastodon_share parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.69 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 05:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43702 | GPU DDK - MLIST/PM render state buffers writable allowing arbitrary writes to kernel memory pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43702</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to allow unprivileged access to arbitrary physical memory page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 03:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43703 | GPU DDK - Duplicate calls to RGXCreateFreeList on the same reservation leads to GPU UAF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43703</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to achieve unauthorised reads and writes of physical memory from the GPU HW.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 03:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53623 | Incorrect access control in the component l_0_0.xml of TP-Link ARCHER-C7 v5 allows attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53623</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component l_0_0.xml of TP-Link ARCHER-C7 v5 allows attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 22:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54159 | stalld through 1.19.7 allows local users to cause a denial of service (file overwrite) via a /tmp/rtthrottle symlink attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54159</link><description>stalld through 1.19.7 allows local users to cause a denial of service (file overwrite) via a /tmp/rtthrottle symlink attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 22:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11995 | code-projects Farmacia pagamento.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11995</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pagamento.php. The manipulation of the argument total leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 21:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35366 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 is Integer Overflow. The vulnerability exists in the parse_options function of sbgdec.c within the libavformat module. When pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35366</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 is Integer Overflow. The vulnerability exists in the parse_options function of sbgdec.c within the libavformat module. When parsing certain options, the software does not adequately validate the input. This allows for negative duration values to be accepted without proper bounds checking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35368 | FFmpeg n7.0 is affected by a Double Free via the rkmpp_retrieve_frame function within libavcodec/rkmppdec.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35368</link><description>FFmpeg n7.0 is affected by a Double Free via the rkmpp_retrieve_frame function within libavcodec/rkmppdec.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 20:10:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35367 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 has an Out-of-bounds Read via libavcodec/ppc/vp8dsp_altivec.c, static const vec_s8 h_subpel_filters_outer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35367</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 has an Out-of-bounds Read via libavcodec/ppc/vp8dsp_altivec.c, static const vec_s8 h_subpel_filters_outer</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35371 | Ant-Media-Serverv2.8.2 is affected by Improper Output Neutralization for Logs. The vulnerability stems from insufficient input sanitization ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35371</link><description>Ant-Media-Serverv2.8.2 is affected by Improper Output Neutralization for Logs. The vulnerability stems from insufficient input sanitization in the logging mechanism. Without proper filtering or validation, user-controllable data, such as identifiers or other sensitive information, can be included in log entries without restrictions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36610 | A deserialization vulnerability exists in the Stub class of the VarDumper module in Symfony v7.0.3. The vulnerability stems from deficiencie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36610</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability exists in the Stub class of the VarDumper module in Symfony v7.0.3. The vulnerability stems from deficiencies in the original implementation when handling properties with null or uninitialized values. An attacker could construct specific serialized data and use this vulnerability to execute unauthorized code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36612 | Zulip from 8.0 to 8.3 contains a memory leak vulnerability in the handling of popovers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36612</link><description>Zulip from 8.0 to 8.3 contains a memory leak vulnerability in the handling of popovers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53504 | A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Siyuan 3.1.11 via the notebook parameter in /searchHistory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53504</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Siyuan 3.1.11 via the notebook parameter in /searchHistory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53505 | A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Siyuan 3.1.11 via the id parameter at /getAssetContent.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53505</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Siyuan 3.1.11 via the id parameter at /getAssetContent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53506 | A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Siyuan 3.1.11 via the ids array parameter in /batchGetBlockAttrs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53506</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in Siyuan 3.1.11 via the ids array parameter in /batchGetBlockAttrs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53507 | A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Siyuan 3.1.11 in /getHistoryItems.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53507</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Siyuan 3.1.11 in /getHistoryItems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53979 | Ansible collection &amp;quot;ibm.ibm_zhmc&amp;quot; has passwords in clear text in log file and in output of some modules when specified as input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53979</link><description>ibm.ibm_zhmc is an Ansible collection for the IBM Z HMC. The Ansible collection "ibm.ibm_zhmc" writes password-like properties in clear text into its log file and into the output returned by some of its Ansible module in the following cases: 1. The 'boot_ftp_password' and 'ssc_master_pw' properties are passed as input to the zhmc_partition Ansible module. 2. The 'ssc_master_pw' and 'zaware_master_pw' properties are passed as input to the zhmc_lpar Ansible module. 3. The 'password' property is passed as input to the zhmc_user Ansible module (just in log file, not in module output). 4. The 'bind_password' property is passed as input to the zhmc_ldap_server_definition Ansible module. These properties appear in the module output only when they were specified in the module input and when creating or updating the corresponding resources. They do not appear in the output when retrieving facts for the corresponding resources. These properties appear in the log file only when the "log_file" module input parameter is used. By default, no log file is created. This issue has been fixed in ibm.ibm_zhmc version 1.9.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53980 | Spoofed length byte traps CC2538 in endless loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53980</link><description>RIOT is an open-source microcontroller operating system, designed to match the requirements of Internet of Things (IoT) devices and other embedded devices. A malicious actor can send a IEEE 802.15.4 packet with spoofed length byte and optionally spoofed FCS, which eventually results into an endless loop on a CC2538 as receiver. Before PR #20998, the receiver would check for the location of the CRC bit using the packet length byte by considering all 8 bits, instead of discarding bit 7, which is what the radio does. This then results into reading outside of the RX FIFO.  Although it prints an error when attempting to read outside of the RX FIFO, it will continue doing this. This may lead to a discrepancy in the CRC check according to the firmware and the radio. If the CPU judges the CRC as correct and the radio is set to `AUTO_ACK`, when the packet requests and acknowledgment the CPU will go into the state `CC2538_STATE_TX_ACK`. However, if the radio judged the CRC as incorrect, it will not send an acknowledgment, and thus the `TXACKDONE` event will not fire. It will then never return to the state `CC2538_STATE_READY` since the baseband processing is still disabled. Then the CPU will be in an endless loop. Since setting to idle is not forced, it won't do it if the radio's state is not `CC2538_STATE_READY`. A fix has not yet been made.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53983 | Server-side request forgery in Backstage Scaffolder plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53983</link><description>The Backstage Scaffolder plugin Houses types and utilities for building scaffolder-related modules. A vulnerability is identified in Backstage Scaffolder template functionality where Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) can be exploited to perform Git config injection. The vulnerability allows an attacker to capture privileged git tokens used by the Backstage Scaffolder plugin. With these tokens, unauthorized access to sensitive resources in git can be achieved. The impact is considered medium severity as the Backstage Threat Model recommends restricting access to adding and editing templates in the Backstage Catalog plugin. The issue has been resolved in versions `v0.4.12`, `v0.5.1` and `v0.6.1` of the `@backstage/plugin-scaffolder-node` package. Users are encouraged to upgrade to this version to mitigate the vulnerability. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may ensure that templates do not change git config.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36611 | In Symfony v7.07, a security vulnerability was identified in the FormLoginAuthenticator component, where it failed to adequately handle case...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36611</link><description>In Symfony v7.07, a security vulnerability was identified in the FormLoginAuthenticator component, where it failed to adequately handle cases where the username or password field of a login request is empty. This flaw could lead to various security risks, including improper authentication logic handling or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53861 | Issuer field partial matches allowed in pyjwt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53861</link><description>pyjwt is a JSON Web Token implementation in Python. An incorrect string comparison is run for `iss` checking, resulting in `"acb"` being accepted for `"_abc_"`. This is a bug introduced in version 2.10.0: checking the "iss" claim changed from `isinstance(issuer, list)` to `isinstance(issuer, Sequence)`. Since str is a Sequnce, but not a list, `in` is also used for string comparison. This results in `if "abc" not in "__abcd__":` being checked instead of `if "abc" != "__abc__":`. Signature checks are still present so real world impact is likely limited to denial of service scenarios. This issue has been patched in version 2.10.1. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53864 | Cross-site Scripting in a field that is used in the Content name pattern in ibexa/admin-ui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53864</link><description>Ibexa Admin UI Bundle is all the necessary parts to run the Ibexa DXP Back Office interface. The Content name pattern is used to build Content names from one or more fields. An XSS vulnerability has been found in this mechanism. Content edit permission is required to exploit it. After the fix, any existing injected XSS will not run. This issue has been patched in version 4.6.14. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53865 | Python package &amp;quot;zhmcclient&amp;quot; has passwords in clear text in its HMC and API logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53865</link><description>zhmcclient is a pure Python client library for the IBM Z HMC Web Services API. In affected versions the Python package "zhmcclient" writes password-like properties in clear text into its HMC and API logs in the following cases: 1. The 'boot-ftp-password' and 'ssc-master-pw' properties when creating or updating a partition in DPM mode, in the zhmcclient API and HMC logs. 2. The 'ssc-master-pw' and 'zaware-master-pw' properties when updating an LPAR in classic mode, in the zhmcclient API and HMC logs. 3. The 'ssc-master-pw' and 'zaware-master-pw' properties when creating or updating an image activation profile in classic mode, in the zhmcclient API and HMC logs. 4. The 'password' property when creating or updating an HMC user, in the zhmcclient API log. 5. The 'bind-password' property when creating or updating an LDAP server definition, in the zhmcclient API and HMC logs. This issue affects only users of the zhmcclient package that have enabled the Python loggers named "zhmcclient.api" (for the API log) or "zhmcclient.hmc" (for the HMC log) and that use the functions listed above. This issue has been fixed in zhmcclient version 1.18.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36615 | FFmpeg n7.0 has a race condition vulnerability in the VP9 decoder. This could lead to a data race if video encoding parameters were being ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36615</link><description>FFmpeg n7.0 has a race condition vulnerability in the VP9 decoder. This could lead to a data race if video encoding parameters were being exported, as the side data would be attached in the decoder thread while being read in the output thread.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36616 | An integer overflow in the component /libavformat/westwood_vqa.c of FFmpeg n6.1.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service in the appli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36616</link><description>An integer overflow in the component /libavformat/westwood_vqa.c of FFmpeg n6.1.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service in the application via a crafted VQA file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52809 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability with prototype pollution in vue-i18n</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52809</link><description>vue-i18n  is an internationalization plugin for Vue.js. In affected versions vue-i18n can be passed locale messages to `createI18n` or `useI18n`. When locale message ASTs are generated in development mode there is a possibility of Cross-site Scripting attack. This issue has been addressed in versions 9.14.2, and 10.0.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52810 | Prototype Pollution in @intlify/shared &amp;gt;=9.7.0 &amp;lt;= 10.0.4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52810</link><description>@intlify/shared is a shared library for the intlify project. The latest version of @intlify/shared (10.0.4) is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution through the entry function(s) lib.deepCopy. An attacker can supply a payload with Object.prototype setter to introduce or modify properties within the global prototype chain, causing denial of service (DoS) as the minimum consequence. Moreover, the consequences of this vulnerability can escalate to other injection-based attacks, depending on how the library integrates within the application. For instance, if the polluted property propagates to sensitive Node.js APIs (e.g., exec, eval), it could enable an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the application's context. This issue has been addressed in versions 9.14.2, and 10.0.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53848 | check-jsonschema default caching for remote schemas allows for cache confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53848</link><description>check-jsonschema is a CLI and set of pre-commit hooks for jsonschema validation. The default cache strategy uses the basename of a remote schema as the name of the file in the cache, e.g. `https://example.org/schema.json` will be stored as `schema.json`. This naming allows for conflicts. If an attacker can get a user to run `check-jsonschema` against a malicious schema URL, e.g., `https://example.evil.org/schema.json`, they can insert their own schema into the cache and it will be picked up and used instead of the appropriate schema. Such a cache confusion attack could be used to allow data to pass validation which should have been rejected. This issue has been patched in version 0.30.0. All users are advised to upgrade. A few workarounds exist: 1. Users can use `--no-cache` to disable caching. 2. Users can use `--cache-filename` to select filenames for use in the cache, or to ensure that other usages do not overwrite the cached schema. (Note: this flag is being deprecated as part of the remediation effort.) 3. Users can explicitly download the schema before use as a local file, as in `curl -LOs https://example.org/schema.json; check-jsonschema --schemafile ./schema.json`</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52003 | X-Forwarded-Prefix Header still allows for Open Redirect in traefik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52003</link><description>Traefik (pronounced traffic) is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. There is a vulnerability in Traefik that allows the client to provide the X-Forwarded-Prefix header from an untrusted source. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.11.14 and 3.2.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52800 | Potential XXE (XML External Entity Injection) vulnerability in veraPDF CLI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52800</link><description>veraPDF is an open source PDF/A validation library. Executing policy checks using custom schematron files via the CLI invokes an XSL transformation that may theoretically lead to a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability. This doesn't affect the standard validation and policy checks functionality, veraPDF's common use cases. Most veraPDF users don't insert any custom XSLT code into policy profiles, which are based on Schematron syntax rather than direct XSL transforms. For users who do, only load custom policy files from sources you trust. This issue has not yet been patched. Users are advised to be cautious of XSLT code until a patch is available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52801 | Brute force takeover of OpenID Connect session cookies in sftpgo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52801</link><description>sftpgo is a full-featured and highly configurable event-driven file transfer solution. Server protocols: SFTP, HTTP/S, FTP/S, WebDAV. The OpenID Connect implementation allows authenticated users to brute force session cookies and thereby gain access to other users' data, since the cookies are generated predictably using the xid library and are therefore unique but not cryptographically secure. This issue was fixed in version v2.6.4, where cookies are opaque and cryptographically secure strings. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36617 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 has an integer overflow vulnerability in the FFmpeg CAF decoder.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36617</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 has an integer overflow vulnerability in the FFmpeg CAF decoder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36618 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the AVI demuxer of the libavformat library which allows for an integer overflow, potentially resulting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36618</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the AVI demuxer of the libavformat library which allows for an integer overflow, potentially resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36620 | moby v25.0.0 - v26.0.2 is vulnerable to NULL Pointer Dereference via daemon/images/image_history.go.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36620</link><description>moby v25.0.0 - v26.0.2 is vulnerable to NULL Pointer Dereference via daemon/images/image_history.go.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36622 | In RaspAP raspap-webgui 3.0.9 and earlier, a command injection vulnerability exists in the clearlog.php script. The vulnerability is due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36622</link><description>In RaspAP raspap-webgui 3.0.9 and earlier, a command injection vulnerability exists in the clearlog.php script. The vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user input passed via the logfile parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49360 | Path traversal in Sandboxie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49360</link><description>Sandboxie is a sandbox-based isolation software for 32-bit and 64-bit Windows NT-based operating systems. An authenticated user (**UserA**) with no privileges is authorized to read all files created in sandbox belonging to other users in the sandbox folders `C:\Sandbox\UserB\xxx`. An authenticated attacker who can use `explorer.exe` or `cmd.exe` outside any sandbox can read other users' files in `C:\Sandbox\xxx`. By default in Windows 7+, the `C:\Users\UserA` folder is not readable by **UserB**.
All files edited or created during the sandbox processing are affected by the vulnerability. All files in C:\Users are safe. If `UserB` runs a cmd in a sandbox, he will be able to access `C:\Sandox\UserA`. In addition, if **UserB** create a folder `C:\Sandbox\UserA` with malicious ACLs, when **UserA** will user the sandbox, Sandboxie doesn't reset ACLs ! This issue has not yet been fixed. Users are advised to limit access to their systems using Sandboxie.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 18:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36621 | moby v25.0.5 is affected by a Race Condition in builder/builder-next/adapters/snapshot/layer.go. The vulnerability could be used to trigger ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36621</link><description>moby v25.0.5 is affected by a Race Condition in builder/builder-next/adapters/snapshot/layer.go. The vulnerability could be used to trigger concurrent builds that call the EnsureLayer function resulting in resource leaks/exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36623 | moby v25.0.3 has a Race Condition vulnerability in the streamformatter package which can be used to trigger multiple concurrent write operat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36623</link><description>moby v25.0.3 has a Race Condition vulnerability in the streamformatter package which can be used to trigger multiple concurrent write operations resulting in data corruption or application crashes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36624 | Zulip 8.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the construct_copy_div function in copy_and_paste.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36624</link><description>Zulip 8.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the construct_copy_div function in copy_and_paste.js.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36619 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the WAVARC decoder of the libavcodec library which allows for an integer overflow when handling certain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36619</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the WAVARC decoder of the libavcodec library which allows for an integer overflow when handling certain block types, leading to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36625 | Zulip 8.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the replace_emoji_with_text function in ui_util.ts.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36625</link><description>Zulip 8.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the replace_emoji_with_text function in ui_util.ts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36626 | In prestashop 8.1.4, a NULL pointer dereference was identified in the math_round function within Tools.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36626</link><description>In prestashop 8.1.4, a NULL pointer dereference was identified in the math_round function within Tools.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49803 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49803</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49804 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49804</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 

could allow a locally authenticated non-administrative user to escalate their privileges due to unnecessary permissions used to perform certain tasks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49805 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance hard coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49805</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 

contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49806 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance hard coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49806</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 

contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35369 | In FFmpeg version n6.1.1, specifically within the avcodec/speexdec.c module, a potential security vulnerability exists due to insufficient v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35369</link><description>In FFmpeg version n6.1.1, specifically within the avcodec/speexdec.c module, a potential security vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation of certain parameters when parsing Speex codec extradata. This vulnerability could lead to integer overflow conditions, potentially resulting in undefined behavior or crashes during the decoding process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47193 | WithSecure Elements Agent for Mac before 24.3, MDR before 24.3, and Elements Client Security for Mac before 16.10 allow a remote Denial of S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47193</link><description>WithSecure Elements Agent for Mac before 24.3, MDR before 24.3, and Elements Client Security for Mac before 16.10 allow a remote Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52778 | DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52778</link><description>DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /function/audit/newstatistics/mon_stat_hist.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52779 | DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52779</link><description>DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /function/audit/newstatistics/mon_stat_top10.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52780 | DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52780</link><description>DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /function/system/basic/mgmt_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52781 | DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52781</link><description>DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /function/system/tool/traceroute.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52782 | DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52782</link><description>DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /function/audit/newstatistics/mon_stat_hist_new.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52777 | DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L, &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52777</link><description>DCME-320 &lt;=7.4.12.90, DCME-520 &lt;=9.25.5.11, DCME-320-L, &lt;=9.3.5.26, and DCME-720 &lt;=9.1.5.11 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via /function/system/basic/license_update.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48406 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SunBK201 umicat through v.0.3.2 and fixed in v.0.3.3 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48406</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SunBK201 umicat through v.0.3.2 and fixed in v.0.3.3 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the power(uct_int_t x, uct_int_t n) in src/uct_upstream.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 15:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36671 | nodemcu before v3.0.0-release_20240225 was discovered to contain an integer overflow via the getnum function at /modules/struct.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36671</link><description>nodemcu before v3.0.0-release_20240225 was discovered to contain an integer overflow via the getnum function at /modules/struct.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 14:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11990 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) en SurgeMail de NetWin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11990</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SurgeMail v78c2 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via an elaborate payload injected into vulnerable parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 13:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11992 | Path traversal vulnerability in Quick.CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11992</link><description>Absolute path traversal vulnerability in Quick.CMS, version 6.7, the exploitation of which could allow remote users to bypass the intended restrictions and download any file if it has the appropriate permissions outside of documentroot configured on the server via the aDirFiles%5B0%5D parameter in the admin.php page. This vulnerability allows an attacker to delete files stored on the server due to a lack of proper verification of user-supplied input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 13:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47094 | Logging of sitesecret to automations log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47094</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p22, &lt;2.2.0p37, &lt;2.1.0p50 (EOL) causes remote site secrets to be written to web log files accessible to local site users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 09:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50357 | FutureNet NXR series routers provided by Century Systems Co., Ltd. have REST-APIs, which are configured as disabled in the initial (factory ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50357</link><description>FutureNet NXR series routers provided by Century Systems Co., Ltd. have REST-APIs, which are configured as disabled in the initial (factory default) configuration. But, REST-APIs are unexpectedly enabled when the affected product is powered up, provided either http-server (GUI) or Web authentication is enabled. The factory default configuration makes http-server (GUI) enabled, which means REST-APIs are also enabled. The username and the password for REST-APIs are configured in the factory default configuration. As a result, an attacker may obtain and/or alter the affected product's settings via REST-APIs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 09:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11013 | Command Injection vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver9.2 to Ver10.10.21, for Ver10.8 up to Ver10.8.27, for Ver10.9 up to V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11013</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver9.2 to Ver10.10.21, for Ver10.8 up to Ver10.8.27, for Ver10.9 up to Ver10.9.14 and UNIVERGE IX-R/IX-V Ver1.2.15 and earlier allows a attacker to inject an arbitrary CLI commands to be executed on the device via the management interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 08:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11014 | Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver9.2 to Ver10.10.21, for Ver10.8 up to Ver10.8.27 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11014</link><description>Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NEC Corporation UNIVERGE IX from Ver9.2 to Ver10.10.21, for Ver10.8 up to Ver10.8.27 and for Ver10.9 up to Ver10.9.14 allows a attacker to hijack the authentication of screens on the device via the management interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 08:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9044 | XML External Entity (XXE) Vulnerability in EasyTax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9044</link><description>A XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability has been identified in Easy Tax Client Software 2023 1.2 and earlier across multiple platforms, including Windows, Linux, and macOS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11481 | A vulnerability in ESM 11.6.10 allows unauthenticated access to the internal Snowservice API. This leads to improper handling of path traver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11481</link><description>A vulnerability in ESM 11.6.10 allows unauthenticated access to the internal Snowservice API. This leads to improper handling of path traversal, insecure forwarding to an AJP backend without adequate validation, and lack of authentication for accessing internal API endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11482 | A vulnerability in ESM 11.6.10 allows unauthenticated access to the internal Snowservice API and enables remote code execution through comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11482</link><description>A vulnerability in ESM 11.6.10 allows unauthenticated access to the internal Snowservice API and enables remote code execution through command injection, executed as the root user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11982 | Billion Electric router - Plaintext Storage of a Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11982</link><description>Certain models of routers from Billion Electric has a Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability. Remote attackers with administrator privileges can access the user settings page to retrieve plaintext passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11983 | Billion Electric router - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11983</link><description>Certain models of routers from Billion Electric has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary system commands into a specific SSH function and execute them on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11981 | Billion Electric router - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11981</link><description>Certain models of routers from Billion Electric has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability, allowing unautheticated attackers to retrive contents of arbitrary web pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11980 | Billion Electric in-vehicle router - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11980</link><description>Certain modes of in-vehicle routers from Billion Electric have a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to directly access the specific functionality to obtain partial device information, modify the WiFi SSID, and restart the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10704 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.8.31 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10704</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.31 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10980 | Element Pack Elementor Addons &amp;lt; 5.10.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10980</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid, Carousel and Remote Arrows) WordPress plugin before 5.10.3 does not validate and escape some of its Cookie Consent block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53701 | Multiple FCNT Android devices provide the original security features such as "privacy mode" where arbitrary applications can be set not to b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53701</link><description>Multiple FCNT Android devices provide the original security features such as "privacy mode" where arbitrary applications can be set not to be displayed, etc.
Under certain conditions, and when an attacker can directly operate the device which its screen is unlocked by a user, the provided security features' setting pages may be exposed and/or the settings may be altered, without authentication. For example, specific applications in the device configured to be hidden may be displayed and/or activated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39162 | pyspider through 0.3.10 allows /update XSS. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39162</link><description>pyspider through 0.3.10 allows /update XSS. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48651 | In ProFTPD through 1.3.8b before cec01cc, supplemental group inheritance grants unintended access to GID 0 because of the lack of supplement...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48651</link><description>In ProFTPD through 1.3.8b before cec01cc, supplemental group inheritance grants unintended access to GID 0 because of the lack of supplemental groups from mod_sql.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45495 | MSA FieldServer Gateway 5.0.0 through 6.5.2 allows cross-origin WebSocket hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45495</link><description>MSA FieldServer Gateway 5.0.0 through 6.5.2 allows cross-origin WebSocket hijacking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35451 | LinkStack 2.7.9 through 4.7.7 allows resources\views\components\favicon.blade.php link SSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35451</link><description>LinkStack 2.7.9 through 4.7.7 allows resources\views\components\favicon.blade.php link SSRF.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54124 | In Click Studios Passwordstate before build 9920, there is a potential permission escalation on the edit folder screen.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54124</link><description>In Click Studios Passwordstate before build 9920, there is a potential permission escalation on the edit folder screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54123 | Backdrop CMS before 1.28.4 and 1.29.x before 1.29.2 allows XSS via an SVG document, if the SVG tag is allowed for a text format.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54123</link><description>Backdrop CMS before 1.28.4 and 1.29.x before 1.29.2 allows XSS via an SVG document, if the SVG tag is allowed for a text format.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11978 | Interinfo DreamMaker - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11978</link><description>DreamMaker from Interinfo has a Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 02:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11979 | Interinfo DreamMaker - Unrestricted File Upload through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11979</link><description>DreamMaker from Interinfo has a Path Traversal vulnerability and does not restrict the types of uploaded files. This allows unauthenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files to any directory, leading to arbitrary code execution by uploading webshells.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 02:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8300 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in GENESIS64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8300</link><description>Dead Code vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 Version 10.97.2, 10.97.2 CFR1, 10.97.2 CRF2 and 10.97.3 and Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 Version 10.97.2, 10.97.2 CFR1, 10.97.2 CRF2 and 10.97.3 allows a local authenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by tampering with a specially crafted DLL. This could lead to disclose, tamper with, destroy, or delete information in the affected products, or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9852 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in GENESIS64 and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9852</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local authenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by storing a specially crafted DLL in a specific folder. This could lead to disclose, tamper with, destroy, or delete information in the affected products, or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8299 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in GENESIS64 and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8299</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local authenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by storing a specially crafted DLL in a specific folder. This could lead to disclose, tamper with, destroy, or delete information in the affected products, or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11970 | code-projects Concert Ticket Ordering System tour(cor).php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Concert Ticket Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tour(cor).php. The manipulation of the argument mai leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11971 | Guizhou Xiaoma Technology jpress Avatar upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11971</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Guizhou Xiaoma Technology jpress 5.1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /commons/attachment/upload of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument files leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11967 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system reset-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/reset-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11968 | code-projects Farmacia pagamento.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file pagamento.php. The manipulation of the argument notaFiscal leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11966 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11964 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/index.php. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11965 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system reset-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/reset-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52338 | Apache Arrow R package: Arbitrary code execution when loading a malicious data file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52338</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data in IPC and Parquet readers in the Apache Arrow R package versions 4.0.0 through 16.1.0 allows arbitrary code execution. An application is vulnerable if it 
reads Arrow IPC, Feather or Parquet data from untrusted sources (for 
example, user-supplied input files). This vulnerability only affects the arrow R package, not other Apache Arrow 
implementations or bindings unless those bindings are specifically used via the R package (for example, an R application that embeds a Python interpreter and uses PyArrow to read files from untrusted sources is still vulnerable if the arrow R package is an affected version). It is recommended that users of the arrow R package upgrade to 17.0.0 or later. Similarly, it
 is recommended that downstream libraries upgrade their dependency 
requirements to arrow 17.0.0 or later. If using an affected
version of the package, untrusted data can read into a Table and its internal to_data_frame() method can be used as a workaround (e.g., read_parquet(..., as_data_frame = FALSE)$to_data_frame()).


This issue affects the Apache Arrow R package: from 4.0.0 through 16.1.0.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 17.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 16:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11969 | Incorrect default permissions in Cradlepoint NetCloud Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11969</link><description>The NetCloud Exchange client for Windows, version 1.110.50, contains an insecure file and folder permissions vulnerability. A normal (non-admin) user could exploit the weakness in file and folder permissions to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code and maintain persistence on the compromised machine. It has been identified that full control permissions exist on the ‘Everyone’ group (i.e. any user who has local access to the operating system regardless of their privileges).</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11962 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11962</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11963 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site room.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/room.php. The manipulation of the argument troom leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52922 | can: bcm: Fix UAF in bcm_proc_show()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52922</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: bcm: Fix UAF in bcm_proc_show()

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in bcm_proc_show+0x969/0xa80
Read of size 8 at addr ffff888155846230 by task cat/7862

CPU: 1 PID: 7862 Comm: cat Not tainted 6.5.0-rc1-00153-gc8746099c197 #230
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0xd5/0x150
 print_report+0xc1/0x5e0
 kasan_report+0xba/0xf0
 bcm_proc_show+0x969/0xa80
 seq_read_iter+0x4f6/0x1260
 seq_read+0x165/0x210
 proc_reg_read+0x227/0x300
 vfs_read+0x1d5/0x8d0
 ksys_read+0x11e/0x240
 do_syscall_64+0x35/0xb0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

Allocated by task 7846:
 kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
 kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x9e/0xa0
 bcm_sendmsg+0x264b/0x44e0
 sock_sendmsg+0xda/0x180
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x735/0x920
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x11d/0x1b0
 __sys_sendmsg+0xfa/0x1d0
 do_syscall_64+0x35/0xb0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

Freed by task 7846:
 kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
 kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
 kasan_save_free_info+0x27/0x40
 ____kasan_slab_free+0x161/0x1c0
 slab_free_freelist_hook+0x119/0x220
 __kmem_cache_free+0xb4/0x2e0
 rcu_core+0x809/0x1bd0

bcm_op is freed before procfs entry be removed in bcm_release(),
this lead to bcm_proc_show() may read the freed bcm_op.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:17:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11961 | Guangzhou Huayi Intelligent Technology Jeewms WmOmNoticeHController.java preHandle information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11961</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Guangzhou Huayi Intelligent Technology Jeewms 3.7. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function preHandle of the file src/main/java/com/zzjee/wm/controller/WmOmNoticeHController.java. The manipulation of the argument request leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11959 | D-Link DIR-605L formResetStatistic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formResetStatistic of the file /goform/formResetStatistic. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11960 | D-Link DIR-605L formSetPortTr buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetPortTr of the file /goform/formSetPortTr. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7747 | Wallet for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Incorrect Conversion between Numeric Types</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7747</link><description>The Wallet for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to incorrect conversion between numeric types in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This is due to a numerical logic flaw when transferring funds to another user. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create funds during a transfer and distribute these funds to any number of other users or their own account, rendering products free. Attackers could also request to withdraw funds if the Wallet Withdrawal extension is used and the request is approved by an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 13:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53731 | WordPress Fintelligence Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53731</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fintelligence Fintelligence Calculator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fintelligence Calculator: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11402 | WordPress Block Editor Bootstrap Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11402</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP-speedup Block Editor Bootstrap Blocks allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Block Editor Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 6.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53732 | WordPress Footer Flyout Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53732</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP WOX Footer Flyout Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Footer Flyout Widget: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53733 | WordPress Fence URL plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53733</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rohit Harsh Fence URL allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fence URL: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53734 | WordPress Idealien Category Enhancements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53734</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Idealien Studios Idealien Category Enhancements allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Idealien Category Enhancements: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53736 | WordPress Custom Shortcode Sidebars plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53736</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jason Grim Custom Shortcode Sidebars allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Shortcode Sidebars: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53737 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53737</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Mailster allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52474 | WordPress Express Payments plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52474</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LLC «TriIncom» Express Payments Module allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Express Payments Module: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11620 | WordPress Rank Math SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.231 - Arbitrary .htaccess Overwrite to Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11620</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Rank Math SEO allows Code Injection.This issue affects Rank Math SEO: from n/a through 1.0.231.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52475 | WordPress Wawp plugin &amp;lt; 3.0.18 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52475</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Automation Web Platform Wawp allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Wawp: from n/a before 3.0.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52481 | WordPress Jobify theme &amp;lt;= 4.2.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52481</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Astoundify Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme: from n/a through 4.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52490 | WordPress Pathomation plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52490</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Pathomation allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Pathomation: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52495 | WordPress Distance Based Shipping Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.21 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52495</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eniture Technology Distance Based Shipping Calculator allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Distance Based Shipping Calculator: from n/a through 2.0.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52496 | WordPress Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52496</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AbsolutePlugins Absolute Addons For Elementor allows Local Code Inclusion.This issue affects Absolute Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52497 | WordPress Shopready plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52497</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in quomodosoft Shopready allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Shopready: from n/a through 3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52498 | WordPress SP Blog Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52498</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Softpulse Infotech SP Blog Designer allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects SP Blog Designer: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52499 | WordPress Pricing table addon for elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52499</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Kardi Pricing table addon for elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pricing table addon for elementor: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52501 | WordPress Office Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52501</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in webbytemplate Office Locator.This issue affects Office Locator: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8308 | Siempelkamp: SQL injection due to improper handling of HTTP request input data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8308</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can insert a SQL injection in the web application due to improper handling of HTTP request input data which allows to exfiltrate all data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10670 | Primary Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10670</link><description>The Primary Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 via the [prim_elementor_template] shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10780 | Restaurant &amp;amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10780</link><description>The Restaurant &amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9 via the 'narestaurant_elementor_template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10798 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1003 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10798</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1003 via the 'wpr-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created via Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11082 | Tumult Hype Animations &amp;lt;= 1.9.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via hypeanimations_panel Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11082</link><description>The Tumult Hype Animations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the hypeanimations_panel() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11103 | Contest Gallery &amp;lt;= 24.0.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Reset to Privilege Escalation/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11103</link><description>The Contest Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 24.0.7. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11599 | Domain Restriction Bypass on Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11599</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.0.x &lt;= 10.0.1, 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.3, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.11 fail to properly validate email addresses which allows an unauthenticated user to bypass email domain restrictions via carefully crafted input on email registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22037 | Database password leaked by systemd uyuni-server-attestation service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22037</link><description>The uyuni-server-attestation systemd service needs a database_password environment variable. This file has 640 permission, and cannot be shown users, but the environment is still exposed by systemd to non-privileged users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8672 | Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp;amp; Block Control Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8672</link><description>The Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp; Block Control Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.7 via the display logic functionality that extends several page builders. This is due to the plugin allowing users to supply input that will be passed through eval() without any filtering or capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server. Special note: We suggested the vendor implement an allowlist of functions and limit the ability to execute commands to just administrators, however, they did not take our advice. We are considering this patched, however, we believe it could still be further hardened and there may be residual risk with how the issue is currently patched.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22038 | DoS attacks, information leaks etc. with crafted Git repositories in obs-scm-bridge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22038</link><description>Various problems in obs-scm-bridge allows attackers that create specially crafted git repositories to leak information of cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49502 | Reflected XSS in Setup Wizard, HTTP Proxy credentials pane in spacewalk-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49502</link><description>A Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in the Setup Wizard, HTTP Proxy credentials pane in spacewalk-web allows attackers to attack users by providing specially crafted URLs to click.
This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.2.7.8.1: before 5.0.15-150600.3.10.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: before 4.3.42-150400.3.52.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49503 | Reflected XSS in Setup Wizard, Organization Credentials in  spacewalk-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49503</link><description>A Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SUSE manager allows attackers to execute Javascript code in the organization credentials sub page.
This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.2.7.8.1: before 5.0.15-150600.3.10.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: before 4.3.42-150400.3.52.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52283 | Missing sanitation of inputs allowed arbitrary users to conduct a stored XSS attack that triggers for users that view a certain project</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52283</link><description>Missing sanitation of inputs allowed arbitrary users to conduct a stored XSS attack that triggers for users that view a certain project</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11203 | EmbedPress – Embed PDF, 3D Flipbook, Social Feeds, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, YouTube Videos, Audios, Google Maps in Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;provider_name&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11203</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, 3D Flipbook, Social Feeds, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, YouTube Videos, Audios, Google Maps in Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘provider_name parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11333 | HLS Player &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11333</link><description>The HLS Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hls_player' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11366 | SEO Landing Page Generator &amp;lt;= 1.66.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11366</link><description>The SEO Landing Page Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.66.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11431 | Ragic Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11431</link><description>The Ragic Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ragic' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11458 | FAQ Builder AYS &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11458</link><description>The FAQ Builder AYS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ays_faq_tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11684 | Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11684</link><description>The Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11685 | Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;add_query_arg&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11685</link><description>The `Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie` plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of `add_query_arg` without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action, such as clicking on a specially crafted link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11761 | LegalWeb Cloud &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11761</link><description>The LegalWeb Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'legalweb-popup' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11786 | Login with Vipps and MobilePay &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11786</link><description>The Login with Vipps and MobilePay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'continue-with-vipps' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11788 | StreamWeasels YouTube Integration &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11788</link><description>The StreamWeasels YouTube Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sw-youtube-embed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8066 | File Manager Pro – Filester &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8066</link><description>The File Manager Pro – Filester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing validation in the 'fsConnector' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, and granted permissions by an Administrator, to upload a new .htaccess file allowing them to subsequently upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9669 | File Manager Pro – Filester &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local JavaScript File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9669</link><description>The File Manager Pro – Filester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local JavaScript File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via the 'fm_locale' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36466 | Unauthenticated Zabbix frontend takeover when SSO is being used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36466</link><description>A bug in the code allows an attacker to sign a forged zbx_session cookie, which then allows them to sign in with admin permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 07:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11925 | WP JobSearch &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11925</link><description>The JobSearch WP Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity when verifying an email address through the user_account_activation function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including site administrators if the users email is known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 07:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10473 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.5.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10473</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Logo Settings when outputing them in pages where the Logo Slider shortcode is embed, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10493 | Element Pack Elementor Addons &amp;lt; 5.10.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10493</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) WordPress plugin before 5.10.3 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10510 | adBuddy+ (AdBlocker Detection) by NetfunkDesign &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10510</link><description>The adBuddy+ (AdBlocker Detection) by NetfunkDesign WordPress plugin through 1.1.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10896 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.5.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10896</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Logo and Slider settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11918 | Image Alt Text &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Image Alt Text Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11918</link><description>The Image Alt Text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data| due to a missing capability check on the iat_add_alt_txt_action and iat_update_alt_txt_action AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the alt text on arbitrary images.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46939 | Game Extension Engine Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46939</link><description>The game extension engine of versions 1.2.7.0 and earlier exposes some components, and attackers can construct parameters to perform path traversal attacks, which can overwrite local specific files</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38309 | There are multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in V-SFT (v6.2.2.0 and earlier), TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier), and TELLUS L...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38309</link><description>There are multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in V-SFT (v6.2.2.0 and earlier), TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier), and TELLUS Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier).
If a user opens a specially crafted file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38389 | There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and TELLUS Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens a sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38389</link><description>There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and TELLUS Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens a specially crafted file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38658 | There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in V-Server (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and V-Server Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38658</link><description>There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in V-Server (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and V-Server Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens a specially crafted file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53008 | Inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling') issue exists in HAProxy. If this vulnerability is exploited...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53008</link><description>Inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling') issue exists in HAProxy. If this vulnerability is exploited,  a remote attacker may access a path that is restricted by ACL (Access Control List) set on the product. As a result, the attacker may obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9377 | In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9377</link><description>In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>