<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-21466 | PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in CertificatePolicy in framework prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21466</link><description>PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in CertificatePolicy in framework prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access contentProvider without proper permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21467 | Error in 3GPP specification implementation in Exynos baseband prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows incorrect handling of unencrypted messa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21467</link><description>Error in 3GPP specification implementation in Exynos baseband prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows incorrect handling of unencrypted message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21468 | Improper access control vulnerability in Telephony prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to access files with escalated permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21468</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Telephony prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to access files with escalated permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21469 | Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21469</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information using com.samsung.android.wifi.GEOFENCE action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21470 | Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21470</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SLocation prior to SMR Apr-2022 Release 1 allows local attackers to get device location information using com.samsung.android.wifi.NETWORK_LOCATION action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21471 | Improper access control vulnerability in SemClipboard prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to read arbitrary files with system p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21471</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SemClipboard prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to read arbitrary files with system permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21472 | Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21472</link><description>Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code in bootloader.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21473 | Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21473</link><description>Improper input validation with Exynos Fastboot USB Interface prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code in bootloader.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21475 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21475</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21476 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21476</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in libaudiosaplus_sec.so library prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21477 | Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21477</link><description>Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21478 | Improper input validation vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21478</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in TIGERF trustlet prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21479 | Improper authorization in Smart suggestions prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 in Android 13 and 4.1.01.0 in Android 12 allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21479</link><description>Improper authorization in Smart suggestions prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 in Android 13 and 4.1.01.0 in Android 12 allows remote attackers to register a schedule.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21480 | Improper input validation vulnerability in CertByte prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21480</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in CertByte prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to launch privileged activities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21481 | Improper URL input validation vulnerability in Samsung Account application prior to version 14.1.0.0 allows remote attackers to get sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21481</link><description>Improper URL input validation vulnerability in Samsung Account application prior to version 14.1.0.0 allows remote attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21482 | Missing authorization vulnerability in Camera prior to versions 11.1.02.18 in Android 11, 12.1.03.8 in Android 12 and 13.1.01.4 in Android 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21482</link><description>Missing authorization vulnerability in Camera prior to versions 11.1.02.18 in Android 11, 12.1.03.8 in Android 12 and 13.1.01.4 in Android 13  allows physical attackers to install package through Galaxy store before completion of Setup wizard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21483 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.53.6 allows local attacker to access protected data using exporte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21483</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.53.6 allows local attacker to access protected data using exported service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9785 | Misconfigured certificate validation with self-signed certificates for Print Deploy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9785</link><description>PaperCut Print Deploy is an optional component that integrates with PaperCut NG/MF which simplifies printer deployment and management. When the component is deployed to an environment, the customer has an option to configure the system to use a self-signed certificate. If the customer does not fully configure the system to leverage the trust database on the clients, it opens up the communication between clients and the server to man-in-the-middle attacks. 

It was discovered that certain parts of the documentation related to the configuration of SSL in Print Deploy were lacking, which could potentially contribute to a misconfiguration of the Print Deploy client installation. PaperCut strongly recommends to use valid certificates to secure installations and to follow the updated documentation to ensure the correct SSL configuration. Those who use private CAs and/or self-signed certificates should make sure to copy their Certification Authority certificate, or their self signed certificate if using only one, to the trust store of their operating system and to the Java key store</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58176 | Dive&amp;#x27;s improper processing of custom urls can lead to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58176</link><description>Dive is an open-source MCP Host Desktop Application that enables integration with function-calling LLMs. In versions 0.9.0 through 0.9.3, there is a one-click Remote Code Execution vulnerability triggered through a custom url value, `transport` in the JSON object. An attacker can exploit the vulnerability in the following two scenarios: a victim visits a malicious website controlled by the attacker and the website redirect to the URL automatically, or a victim clicks on such a crafted link embedded on a legitimate website (e.g., in user-generated content). In both cases, the browser invokes Dive's custom URL handler (dive:), which launches the Dive app and processes the crafted URL, leading to arbitrary code execution on the victim’s machine. This vulnerability is caused by improper processing of custom url. This is fixed in version 0.9.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58351 | Outline&amp;#x27;s Local File Storage Feature can Cause CSP Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58351</link><description>Outline is a service that allows for collaborative documentation. In versions 0.72.0 through 0.83.0, Outline introduced a feature which facilitates local file system storage capabilities as an optional file storage strategy. This feature allowed a CSP bypass as well as a ContentType bypass that might facilitate further attacks. In the case of self-hosting and using Outline FILE_STORAGE=local on the same domain as the Outline application, a malicious payload can be uploaded as a file attachment and bypass those CSP restrictions, allowing script execution within the context of another user. This is fixed in version 0.84.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7039 | Glib: buffer under-read on glib through glib/gfileutils.c via get_tmp_file()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7039</link><description>A flaw was found in glib. An integer overflow during temporary file creation leads to an out-of-bounds memory access, allowing an attacker to potentially perform path traversal or access private temporary file content by creating symbolic links. This vulnerability allows a local attacker to manipulate file paths and access unauthorized data. The core issue stems from insufficient validation of file path lengths during temporary file operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58163 | FreeScout&amp;#x27;s deserialization of untrusted data can lead to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58163</link><description>FreeScout is a free help desk and shared inbox built with PHP's Laravel framework. In versions 1.8.185 and below, the application performs deserialization of data that can allow authenticated attackers with knowledge of the application's APP_KEY to achieve remote code execution. The vulnerability can be exploited via endpoint: `/help/{mailbox_id}/auth/{customer_id}/{hash}/{timestamp}` where the `customer_id` and `timestamp` parameters are processed through the decrypt function in `app/Helper.php` without proper validation. The vulnerable code performs decryption using Laravel's built-in encryption functions, which subsequently deserializes the decrypted payload without sanitization. This is fixed in version 1.8.186.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9847 | ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9847</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file register.php. This manipulation of the argument uimage causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9848 | ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System userlist.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9848</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ScriptAndTools Real Estate Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/userlist.php. Such manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57806 | Local Deep Research&amp;#x27;s API keys are stored in plain text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57806</link><description>Local Deep Research is an AI-powered research assistant for deep, iterative research. Versions 0.2.0 through 0.6.7 stored confidential information, including API keys, in a local SQLite database without encryption. This behavior was not clearly documented outside of the database architecture page. Users were not given the ability to configure the database location, allowing anyone with access to the container or host filesystem to retrieve sensitive data in plaintext by accessing the .db file. This is fixed in version 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9843 | Das Parking Management System 停车场管理系统 FindAll information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9843</link><description>A flaw has been found in Das Parking Management System 停车场管理系统 6.2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Operator/FindAll. This manipulation causes information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9845 | code-projects Fruit Shop Management System products.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9845</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fruit Shop Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file products.php. Such manipulation of the argument product_code/gen_name/product_name/supplier leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9842 | Das Parking Management System 停车场管理系统 Search information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9842</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Das Parking Management System 停车场管理系统 6.2.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Operator/Search. The manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54588 | Envoy: Race condition in Dynamic Forward Proxy leads to use-after-free and segmentation faults</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54588</link><description>Envoy is an open source L7 proxy and communication bus designed for large modern service oriented architectures. Versions 1.34.0 through 1.34.4 and 1.35.0 contain a use-after-free (UAF) vulnerability in the DNS cache, causing abnormal process termination. The vulnerability is in Envoy's Dynamic Forward Proxy implementation, occurring when a completion callback for a DNS resolution triggers new DNS resolutions or removes existing pending resolutions. This condition may occur when the following conditions are met: dynamic Forwarding Filter is enabled, the `envoy.reloadable_features.dfp_cluster_resolves_hosts` runtime flag is enabled, and the Host header is modified between the Dynamic Forwarding Filter and Router filters. This issue is resolved in versions 1.34.5 and 1.35.1. To work around this issue, set the envoy.reloadable_features.dfp_cluster_resolves_hosts runtime flag to false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9841 | code-projects Mobile Shop Management System AddNewProduct.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9841</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Mobile Shop Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file AddNewProduct.php. The manipulation of the argument ProductImage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9260 | Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp;amp; Conversational Form Builder 5.1.16 - 6.1.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection To Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9260</link><description>The Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Conversational Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions 5.1.16 to 6.1.1 via deserialization of untrusted input in the parseUserProperties function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to read arbitrary files. If allow_url_include is enabled on the server, remote code execution is possible.
While the vendor patched this issue in version 6.1.0, the patch caused a fatal error in the vulnerable code, due to a missing class import, so we consider 6.1.2 to be the most complete and best patched version</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9840 | itsourcecode Sports Management System gametype.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9840</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Admin/gametype.php. Executing manipulation of the argument code can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9838 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9838</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/subject/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9839 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9839</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/course/index.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40653 | In multiple functions of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to retain a permission forever in the background due to a lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40653</link><description>In multiple functions of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to retain a permission forever in the background due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49720 | In multiple functions of Permissions.java, there is a possible way to override the state of the user's location permissions due to a logic e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49720</link><description>In multiple functions of Permissions.java, there is a possible way to override the state of the user's location permissions due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49722 | In showAvatarPicker of EditUserPhotoController.java, there is a possible cross user image leak due to a confused deputy. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49722</link><description>In showAvatarPicker of EditUserPhotoController.java, there is a possible cross user image leak due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49728 | In generateFileInfo of BluetoothOppSendFileInfo.java, there is a possible cross user media disclosure due to a confused deputy. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49728</link><description>In generateFileInfo of BluetoothOppSendFileInfo.java, there is a possible cross user media disclosure due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49730 | In FuseDaemon.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49730</link><description>In FuseDaemon.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22416 | In onCreate of ChooserActivity.java , there is a possible way to view other users' images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22416</link><description>In onCreate of ChooserActivity.java , there is a possible way to view other users' images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22417 | In finishTransition of Transition.java, there is a possible way to bypass touch filtering restrictions due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22417</link><description>In finishTransition of Transition.java, there is a possible way to bypass touch filtering restrictions due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22418 | In multiple locations, there is a possible confused deputy due to Intent Redirect. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22418</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible confused deputy due to Intent Redirect. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22419 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead the user into enabling malicious phone calls forwarding due to a tapjacking/overla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22419</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead the user into enabling malicious phone calls forwarding due to a tapjacking/overlay attack. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22421 | In contentDescForNotification of NotificationContentDescription.kt, there is a possible notification content leak through the lockscreen due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22421</link><description>In contentDescForNotification of NotificationContentDescription.kt, there is a possible notification content leak through the lockscreen due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22422 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead a user into approving an authentication prompt for one app when its result will be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22422</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to mislead a user into approving an authentication prompt for one app when its result will be used in another due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22423 | In ParseTag of dng_ifd.cpp, there is a possible way to crash the image renderer due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22423</link><description>In ParseTag of dng_ifd.cpp, there is a possible way to crash the image renderer due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22427 | In onCreate of NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity.java, there is a possible way to grant notification access above the lock screen due t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22427</link><description>In onCreate of NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity.java, there is a possible way to grant notification access above the lock screen due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22428 | In hasInteractAcrossUsersFullPermission of AppInfoBase.java, there is a possible way to grant permissions to an app on the secondary user fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22428</link><description>In hasInteractAcrossUsersFullPermission of AppInfoBase.java, there is a possible way to grant permissions to an app on the secondary user from the primary user due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22429 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22429</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to execute arbitrary code due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22430 | In isInSignificantPlace of multiple files, there is a possible way to access sensitive information due to a missing permission check. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22430</link><description>In isInSignificantPlace of multiple files, there is a possible way to access sensitive information due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22431 | In multiple locations, there is a possible method for a malicious app to prevent dialing emergency services under limited circumstances due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22431</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible method for a malicious app to prevent dialing emergency services under limited circumstances due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local denial of service until the phone reboots with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22433 | In canForward of IntentForwarderActivity.java, there is a possible bypass of the cross profile intent filter most commonly used in Work Prof...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22433</link><description>In canForward of IntentForwarderActivity.java, there is a possible bypass of the cross profile intent filter most commonly used in Work Profile scenarios due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22434 | In handleKeyGestureEvent of PhoneWindowManager.java, there is a possible lock screen bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22434</link><description>In handleKeyGestureEvent of PhoneWindowManager.java, there is a possible lock screen bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22435 | In avdt_msg_ind of avdt_msg.cc, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to paired device escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22435</link><description>In avdt_msg_ind of avdt_msg.cc, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22437 | In setMediaButtonReceiver of multiple files, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities from background due to a logic error in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22437</link><description>In setMediaButtonReceiver of multiple files, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities from background due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22438 | In afterKeyEventLockedInterruptable of InputDispatcher.cpp, there is a possible use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22438</link><description>In afterKeyEventLockedInterruptable of InputDispatcher.cpp, there is a possible use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22439 | In onLastAccessedStackLoaded of ActionHandler.java , there is a possible way to bypass storage restrictions across apps due to a missing per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22439</link><description>In onLastAccessedStackLoaded of ActionHandler.java , there is a possible way to bypass storage restrictions across apps due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22442 | In multiple functions of DevicePolicyManagerService.java, there is a possible way to install unauthorized applications into a newly created ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22442</link><description>In multiple functions of DevicePolicyManagerService.java, there is a possible way to install unauthorized applications into a newly created work profile due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26416 | In initializeSwizzler of SkBmpStandardCodec.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26416</link><description>In initializeSwizzler of SkBmpStandardCodec.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9836 | macrozheng mall paySuccess authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This vulnerability affects the function paySuccess of the file /order/paySuccess. The manipulation of the argument orderId results in authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9837 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9837</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/modules/student/index.php. This manipulation of the argument studentId causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9835 | macrozheng mall cancelUserOrder cancelOrder authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9835</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This affects the function cancelOrder of the file /order/cancelUserOrder. The manipulation of the argument orderId leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9833 | SourceCodester Online Farm Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9833</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Login/login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument uname results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9834 | PHPGurukul Small CRM registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9834</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registration.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9831 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System edit-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9831</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-services.php. This manipulation of the argument sername causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9832 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System register-router.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9832</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /routers/register-router.php. Such manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9323 | Foxit PDF Reader JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9323</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-27101.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9324 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9324</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26802.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9325 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9325</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26785.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9326 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9326</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26784.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9327 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9327</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26774.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9328 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9328</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26773.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9329 | Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9329</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26772.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9330 | Foxit PDF Reader Update Service Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9330</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Update Service Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Foxit Reader Update Service. The product loads a library from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8298 | Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CQueryInformationHandleCustomized11nOids Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8298</link><description>Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CQueryInformationHandleCustomized11nOids Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Realtek RTL8811AU drivers. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CQueryInformationHandleCustomized11nOids function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-25864.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8299 | Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver MgntActSet_TEREDO_SET_RS_PACKET Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8299</link><description>Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver MgntActSet_TEREDO_SET_RS_PACKET Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the MgntActSet_TEREDO_SET_RS_PACKET function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25857.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8300 | Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8300</link><description>Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-26552.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8301 | Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8301</link><description>Realtek RTL8811AU rtwlanu.sys N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek RTL8811AU drivers. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-24786.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8302 | Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8302</link><description>Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi Driver rtwlanu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Realtek rtl81xx SDK Wi-Fi driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the N6CSet_DOT11_CIPHER_DEFAULT_KEY function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-26553.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9273 | CData API Server MySQL Misconfiguration Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9273</link><description>CData API Server MySQL Misconfiguration Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of CData API Server. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the usage of MySQL connections. When connecting to a MySQL server, the product enables an option that gives the MySQL server permission to request local files from the MySQL client. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-23950.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9274 | Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9274</link><description>Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IMS files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21657.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9275 | Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9275</link><description>Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer IMS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Oxford Instruments Imaris Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IMS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21655.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9276 | Cockroach Labs cockroach-k8s-request-cert Empty Root Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9276</link><description>Cockroach Labs cockroach-k8s-request-cert Empty Root Password Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow remote attackers to bypass authentication on systems that use the affected version of the Cockroach Labs cockroach-k8s-request-cert container image.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the system shadow file. The issue results from a blank password setting for the root user. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-22195.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9830 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System add-customer-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9830</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add-customer-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sids[] results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6685 | ATEN eco DC Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6685</link><description>ATEN eco DC Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of ATEN eco DC. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the web-based interface. The issue results from the lack of validating the assigned user role when handling requests. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-26647.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7974 | rocket.chat Incorrect Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7974</link><description>rocket.chat Incorrect Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of rocket.chat. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the web service, which listens on TCP port 3000 by default. The issue results from incorrect authorization. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the application. Was ZDI-CAN-26517.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7975 | Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7975</link><description>Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Anritsu ShockLine. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CHX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-26913.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7976 | Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7976</link><description>Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Anritsu ShockLine. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CHX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-26882.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8613 | Vacron Camera ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8613</link><description>Vacron Camera ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Vacron Camera devices. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the webs.cgi endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25892.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8614 | NoMachine Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8614</link><description>NoMachine Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NoMachine.  An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of OpenSSL. The product loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-26766.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36162 | IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36162</link><description>IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 8.1 before 8.1.2.2 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information about configuration on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9829 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9829</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43726 | Dell Alienware Command Center 5.x (AWCC), versions prior to 5.10.2.0, contains an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Followi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43726</link><description>Dell Alienware Command Center 5.x (AWCC), versions prior to 5.10.2.0, contains an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following')" vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57775 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57775</link><description>There is a heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability due to improper bounds checking when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57777 | Out Of Bounds Write in displ2.dll when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57777</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking in displ2.dll when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9188 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9188</link><description>There is a deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57774 | Out Of Bounds Write of invalid data when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57774</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in invalid data when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57776 | Out Of Bounds Write to invalid address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57776</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in an invalid address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57778 | Out Of Bounds Write to invalid source address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57778</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in an invalid source address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9189 | Out Of Bounds Write when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9189</link><description>There is an out of bounds write vulnerability due to improper bounds checking resulting in a large destination address when parsing a DSB file with Digilent DASYLab.  This vulnerability may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted DSB file.  The vulnerability affects all versions of DASYLab.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32100 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32100</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. A programming mistake for buffer copy leads to out-of-bounds writes via malformed ROHC packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32098 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 6.3 through 8.3 on Windows. An attacker can achieve Elevation of Privileges to SYSTEM by exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32098</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Magician 6.3 through 8.3 on Windows. An attacker can achieve Elevation of Privileges to SYSTEM by exploiting insecure file delete operations during the update process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50565 | Doubo ERP 1.0 has an SQL injection vulnerability due to a lack of filtering of user input, which can be remotely initiated by an attacker.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50565</link><description>Doubo ERP 1.0 has an SQL injection vulnerability due to a lack of filtering of user input, which can be remotely initiated by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51966 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the PDF preview functionality of uTools thru 7.1.1. When a user previews a specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51966</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the PDF preview functionality of uTools thru 7.1.1. When a user previews a specially crafted PDF file, embedded JavaScript code executes within the application's privileged context, potentially allowing attackers to steal sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55824 | ModStartCMS v9.5.0 has an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which allows attackers to write malicious files and execute malicious commands...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55824</link><description>ModStartCMS v9.5.0 has an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which allows attackers to write malicious files and execute malicious commands to obtain sensitive data on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55476 | FireShare FileShare 1.2.25 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the sort parameter of the endpoint: GET /api/videos/pu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55476</link><description>FireShare FileShare 1.2.25 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the sort parameter of the endpoint: GET /api/videos/public?sort= This parameter is unsafely evaluated in a SQL ORDER BY clause without proper sanitization, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary SQL subqueries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55474 | Many Notes 0.10.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which allows malicious Markdown files to execute JavaScript when viewed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55474</link><description>Many Notes 0.10.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS), which allows malicious Markdown files to execute JavaScript when viewed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9828 | Tenda CP6 uhttp sub_2B7D04 risky encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9828</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CP6 11.10.00.243. The affected element is the function sub_2B7D04 of the component uhttp. Executing manipulation can lead to risky cryptographic algorithm. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55472 | SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Tirreno v0.9.5, specifically in the /admin/loadUsers API endpoint. The vulnerability arises due to uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55472</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Tirreno v0.9.5, specifically in the /admin/loadUsers API endpoint. The vulnerability arises due to unsafe handling of user-supplied input in the columns[0][data] parameter, which is directly used in SQL queries without proper validation or parameterization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55373 | Incorrect access control in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to escalate privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55373</link><description>Incorrect access control in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to escalate privileges and execute commands with Administrator rights.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55473 | Asian Arts Talents Foundation (AATF) Website v5.1.x and Docker version 2024.12.8.1 are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55473</link><description>Asian Arts Talents Foundation (AATF) Website v5.1.x and Docker version 2024.12.8.1 are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability exists in the /ip.php endpoint, which processes and displays the X-Forwarded-For HTTP header without proper sanitization or output encoding. This allows an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code that will execute in visitor browsers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9696 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in SunPower PVS6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9696</link><description>The SunPower PVS6's BluetoothLE interface is vulnerable due to its use of hardcoded encryption parameters and publicly accessible protocol details. An attacker within Bluetooth range could exploit this vulnerability to gain full access to the device's servicing interface. This access allows the attacker to perform actions such as firmware replacement, disabling power production, modifying grid settings, creating SSH tunnels, altering firewall settings, and manipulating connected devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55372 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55372</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Beakon Application before v5.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57611 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the dump() method allows an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57611</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the dump() method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service. The vulnerability exists because the method fails to check the return value of avfilter_graph_dump() for NULL, leading to a crash if the underlying memory allocation fails.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57612 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the name() method allows an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57612</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Null pointer dereference vulnerability in the name() method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service. The vulnerability exists because the method fails to check for a NULL return value from the av_get_sample_fmt_name() C function, which can be triggered by providing an unrecognized sample format.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57613 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the input() constructor funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57613</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the input() constructor function allows an attacker to cause a denial of service. The vulnerability is triggered when the avio_alloc_context() call fails and returns NULL, which is then stored and later dereferenced by the Io struct's Drop implementation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57614 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Integer overflow and invalid input vulnerability in the cached method all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57614</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) Integer overflow and invalid input vulnerability in the cached method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service or potentially execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability occurs when dimension parameters are zero or exceed i32::MAX, leading to an unchecked cast that violates the underlying C function's preconditions and triggers undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57615 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) An integer overflow vulnerability in the Vector::new constructor function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57615</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) An integer overflow vulnerability in the Vector::new constructor function allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via a null pointer dereference. The vulnerability stems from an unchecked cast of a usize parameter to c_int, which can result in a negative value being passed to the underlying C function sws_allocVec().</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57616 | An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A use-after-free vulnerability in the write_interleaved method allows an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57616</link><description>An issue was discovered in rust-ffmpeg 0.3.0 (after comit 5ac0527) A use-after-free vulnerability in the write_interleaved method allows an attacker to cause a denial of service or memory corruption. The method violates Rust's aliasing rules by modifying a data structure through a mutable pointer while only holding an immutable reference, which can lead to undefined behavior when the data is accessed later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51423 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Infor Global HR GHR v.11.23.03.00.21 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51423</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Infor Global HR GHR v.11.23.03.00.21 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the class parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54599 | The Bevy Event service through 2025-07-22, as used for eBay Seller Events and other activities, allows account takeover, if SSO is used, whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54599</link><description>The Bevy Event service through 2025-07-22, as used for eBay Seller Events and other activities, allows account takeover, if SSO is used, when a victim changes the email address that they have configured. To exploit this, an attacker would create their own account and perform an SSO login. The root cause of the issue is SSO misconfiguration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48705 | Wavlink AC1200 with firmware versions M32A3_V1410_230602 and M32A3_V1410_240222 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48705</link><description>Wavlink AC1200 with firmware versions M32A3_V1410_230602 and M32A3_V1410_240222 are vulnerable to a post-authentication command injection while resetting the password. This vulnerability is specifically found within the "set_sys_adm" function of the "adm.cgi" binary, and is due to improper santization of the user provided "newpass" field</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50755 | Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_cmd function via the command parameter. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50755</link><description>Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_cmd function via the command parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50757 | Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_adm function via the username parameter. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50757</link><description>Wavlink WN535K3 20191010 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the set_sys_adm function via the username parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2413 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s ProKuafor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2413</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft ProKuafor allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects ProKuafor: from s1.02.08 before v1.02.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9784 | Undertow: undertow madeyoureset http/2 ddos vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9784</link><description>A flaw was found in Undertow where malformed client requests can trigger server-side stream resets without triggering abuse counters. This issue, referred to as the "MadeYouReset" attack, allows malicious clients to induce excessive server workload by repeatedly causing server-side stream aborts. While not a protocol bug, this highlights a common implementation weakness that can be exploited to cause a denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12974 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s ProKuaför</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12974</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akinsoft ProKuaför allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects ProKuaför: from s1.02.07 before v1.02.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0670 | IDOR in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s ProKuafor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0670</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Akinsoft ProKuafor allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects ProKuafor: from s1.02.07 before v1.02.08.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46047 | A User enumeration vulnerability in the /CredentialsServlet/ForgotPassword endpoint in Silverpeas 6.4.1 and 6.4.2 allows remote attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46047</link><description>A User enumeration vulnerability in the /CredentialsServlet/ForgotPassword endpoint in Silverpeas 6.4.1 and 6.4.2 allows remote attackers to determine valid usernames via the Login parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58259 | Rancher affected by unauthenticated Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58259</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Rancher Manager in which it 
did not enforce request body size limits on certain public 
(unauthenticated) and authenticated API endpoints. This allows a 
malicious user to exploit this by sending excessively large payloads, 
which are fully loaded into memory during processing, leading to Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2414 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2414</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.03 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56254 | PHPGurukul Employee Leave Management System 2.1 contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in leave-details.php. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56254</link><description>PHPGurukul Employee Leave Management System 2.1 contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in leave-details.php. An authenticated user can change the leaveid parameter in the URL to access leave application details of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52284 | Rancher Fleet Helm Values are stored inside BundleDeployment in plain text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52284</link><description>Unauthorized disclosure of sensitive data: Any user with `GET` or `LIST` permissions on `BundleDeployment` resources could retrieve Helm values containing credentials or other secrets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0640 | IDOR in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0640</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.02 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57140 | rsbi-pom 4.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the /bi/service/model/DatasetService path.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57140</link><description>rsbi-pom 4.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the /bi/service/model/DatasetService path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12973 | Host Header Injection in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12973</link><description>Origin Validation Error vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows HTTP Response Splitting, CAPEC - 87 - Forceful Browsing.This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.01 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12972 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s OctoCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12972</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akinsoft OctoCloud allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects OctoCloud: from s1.09.01 before v1.11.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46810 | A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of openSUSE Tumbleweed traefik2 allows the traefik user to escalate ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46810</link><description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of openSUSE Tumbleweed traefik2 allows the traefik user to escalate to root. This issue affects Tumbleweed: from ? before 2.11.29.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52551 | Proprietary protocol allows for unauthenticated file operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52551</link><description>E2 Facility Management Systems use a proprietary protocol that allows for unauthenticated file operations on any file in the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52543 | Login to the application services using only the password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52543</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) application services (MGW and RCI) uses client side hashing for authentication. An attacker can authenticate by obtaining only the password hash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52544 | Arbitrary read file from the filesystem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52544</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) has a floor plan feature that allows for an unauthenticated attacker to upload floor plan files. By uploading a specially crafted floor plan file, an attacker can access any file from the E3 file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52545 | Privilege escalation in the application services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52545</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) RCI service contains an API call to read users info, which returns all usernames and password hashes for the application services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52546 | Stored XSS by uploading a specially crafted floor plan file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52546</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) has a floor plan feature that allows for an unauthenticated attacker to upload floor plan files. By uploading a specially crafted floor plan file, an attacker can inject a stored XSS to the floorplan web page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52547 | DoS to the application services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52547</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) MGW contains an API call that lacks input validation. An attacker can use this command to continuously crash the application services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52548 | Enabling SSH and Shellinabox on the vulnerable machine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52548</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) contains a hidden API call in the application services that enables SSH and Shellinabox, which exist but are disabled by default. An attacker with admin access to the application services can utilize this API to enable remote access to the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52549 | Predictable root linux password generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52549</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) generates the root linux password on each boot. An attacker can generate the root linux password for a vulnerable device based on known or easy to fetch parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52550 | Firmware upgrade packages are unsigned</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52550</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor Control (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) firmware upgrade packages are unsigned. An attacker can forge malicious firmware upgrade packages. An attacker with admin access to the application services can install a malicious firmware upgrade.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6519 | Consistent predictable generation of the password for the default admin user &amp;quot;ONEDAY&amp;quot; to the application services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6519</link><description>E3 Site Supervisor (firmware version &lt; 2.31F01) has a default admin user "ONEDAY" with a daily generated password. An attacker can predictably generate the password for ONEDAY. The oneday user cannot be deleted or modified by any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5662 | Deserialization Vulnerability in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5662</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability exists in the H2O-3 REST API (POST /99/ImportSQLTable) that affects all versions up to 3.46.0.7. This vulnerability allows remote code execution (RCE) due to improper validation of JDBC connection parameters when using a Key-Value format. The vulnerability is present in the MySQL JDBC Driver version 8.0.19 and JDK version 8u112. The issue is resolved in version 3.46.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9573 | Command Injection in extension “Backup Plus” (ns_backup)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9573</link><description>The ns_backup extension through 13.0.2 for TYPO3 allows command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41030 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Deporsite by T-INNOVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41030</link><description>Lack of authorisation in Deporsite by T-INNOVA. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain information from other users via GET ‘/ajax/TInnova_v2/Integrantes_Recurso_v2_1/llamadaAjax/buscarPersona’ using the ‘dni’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41031 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Deporsite by T-INNOVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41031</link><description>Lack of authorisation in Deporsite by T-INNOVA. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to change other users' profile pictures via a POST request using the parameters ‘IdPersona’ and “Foto” in ‘/ajax/TInnova_c/FotoUsuario/llamadaAjax/uploadImage’.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41690 | Endress+Hauser: Proline 10 Maintenance credentials may be exposed under certain conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41690</link><description>A low-privileged attacker in bluetooth range may be able to access the password of a higher-privilege user (Maintenance) by viewing the device’s event log. This vulnerability could allow the Operator to authenticate as the Maintenance user, thereby gaining unauthorized access to sensitive configuration settings and the ability to modify device parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44017 | "Gunosy" App contains a vulnerability where sensitive information may be included in the application's outbound communication. If a user acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44017</link><description>"Gunosy" App contains a vulnerability where sensitive information may be included in the application's outbound communication. If a user accesses a crafted URL, an attacker may obtain the JWT (JSON Web Token).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9815 | alaneuler batteryKid NSXPCListener PrivilegeHelper.swift missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9815</link><description>A weakness has been identified in alaneuler batteryKid up to 2.1 on macOS. The affected element is an unknown function of the file PrivilegeHelper/PrivilegeHelper.swift of the component NSXPCListener. This manipulation causes missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9813 | Tenda CH22 SetSambaConf formSetSambaConf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9813</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This issue affects the function formSetSambaConf of the file /goform/SetSambaConf. The manipulation of the argument samba_userNameSda leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9814 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9814</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnumber results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9811 | Campcodes Farm Management System reviewInput.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Farm Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /reviewInput.php. Performing manipulation of the argument rating results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9812 | Tenda CH22 exeCommand formexeCommand buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9812</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/exeCommand. Executing manipulation of the argument cmdinput can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8662 | OpenAM (OpenAM Consortium Edition) contains a vulnerability that may cause it to malfunction as a SAML IdP due to a tampered request.This is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8662</link><description>OpenAM (OpenAM Consortium Edition) contains a vulnerability that may cause it to malfunction as a SAML IdP due to a tampered request.This issue affects OpenAM: from 14.0.0 through 14.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58161 | MobSF Path Traversal in GET /download/&amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; using absolute filenames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58161</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. In version 4.4.0, the GET /download/ route uses string path verification via os.path.commonprefix, which allows an authenticated user to download files outside the DWD_DIR download directory from "neighboring" directories whose absolute paths begin with the same prefix as DWD_DIR (e.g., .../downloads_bak, .../downloads.old). This is a Directory Traversal (escape) leading to a data leak. This issue has been patched in version 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58162 | MobSF Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write (AR-Slip) via Absolute Path in .a Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58162</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. In version 4.4.0, an authenticated user who uploaded a specially prepared one.a, can write arbitrary files to any directory writable by the user of the MobSF process. This issue has been patched in version 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58178 | Command Injection via sonarqube-scan-action GitHub Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58178</link><description>SonarQube Server and Cloud is a static analysis solution for continuous code quality and security inspection. In versions 4 to 5.3.0, a command injection vulnerability was discovered in the SonarQube Scan GitHub Action that allows untrusted input arguments to be processed without proper sanitization. Arguments sent to the action are treated as shell expressions, allowing potential execution of arbitrary commands. A fix has been released in SonarQube Scan GitHub Action 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57808 | ESP-IDF web_server basic auth bypass using empty or incomplete Authorization header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57808</link><description>ESPHome is a system to control microcontrollers remotely through Home Automation systems. In version 2025.8.0 in the ESP-IDF platform, ESPHome's web_server authentication check can pass incorrectly when the client-supplied base64-encoded Authorization value is empty or is a substring of the correct value. This allows access to web_server functionality (including OTA, if enabled) without knowing any information about the correct username or password. This issue has been patched in version 2025.8.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9805 | SimStudioAI sim route.ts server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9805</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SimStudioAI sim up to 51b1e97fa22c48d144aef75f8ca31a74ad2cfed2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file apps/sim/app/api/proxy/image/route.ts. The manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The patch is identified as 3424a338b763115f0269b209e777608e4cd31785. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9806 | Tenda F1202 Administrative shadow hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9806</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.9/1.2.0.14/1.2.0.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /etc_ro/shadow of the component Administrative Interface. This manipulation with the input Fireitup causes hard-coded credentials. The attack can only be executed locally. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9802 | RemoteClinic profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9802</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in RemoteClinic 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /staff/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9801 | SimStudioAI sim path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9801</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SimStudioAI sim up to ed9b9ad83f1a7c61f4392787fb51837d34eeb0af. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation of the argument filePath leads to path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The identifier of the patch is 45372aece5e05e04b417442417416a52e90ba174. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9800 | SimStudioAI sim HTML File route.ts import unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9800</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SimStudioAI sim up to ed9b9ad83f1a7c61f4392787fb51837d34eeb0af. Affected by this issue is the function Import of the file apps/sim/app/api/files/upload/route.ts of the component HTML File Parser. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases. This patch is called 45372aece5e05e04b417442417416a52e90ba174. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9797 | mrvautin expressCart Edit Product edit injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9797</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in mrvautin expressCart up to b31302f4e99c3293bd742c6d076a721e168118b0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/product/edit/ of the component Edit Product Page. This manipulation causes injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9799 | Langfuse Webhook promptRouter.ts promptChangeEventSourcing server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9799</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Langfuse up to 3.88.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function promptChangeEventSourcing of the file web/src/features/prompts/server/routers/promptRouter.ts of the component Webhook Handler. Performing manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9796 | thinkgem JeeSite EncodeUtils.java decodeUrl2 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9796</link><description>A vulnerability was found in thinkgem JeeSite up to 5.12.1. This affects the function decodeUrl2 of the file common/src/main/java/com/jeesite/common/codec/EncodeUtils.java. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 5.13.0 mitigates this issue. The patch is identified as 63773c97a56bdb3649510e83b66c16db4754965b. Upgrading the affected component is recommended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28988 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk Java Deserialization Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28988</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a Java Deserialization Remote Code Execution vulnerability that, if exploited, would allow an attacker to run commands on the host machine. This vulnerability was found by the ZDI team after researching a previous vulnerability and providing this report. The ZDI team was able to discover an unauthenticated attack during their research. 





We recommend all Web Help Desk customers apply the patch, which is now available. 





We thank Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) for its ongoing partnership in coordinating with SolarWinds on responsible disclosure of this and other potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9795 | xujeff tianti 天梯 UploadController.java ajaxUploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9795</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in xujeff tianti 天梯 up to 2.3. The impacted element is the function ajaxUploadFile of the file src/main/java/com/jeff/tianti/controller/UploadController.java. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9794 | Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System pos_transac.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9794</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pages/pos_transac.php?action=add. Executing manipulation of the argument cash/firstname can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9793 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System Setting admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9793</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /setting/admin.php of the component Setting Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument ddlBranch results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9792 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System e_all_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9792</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /e_dashboard/e_all_info.php. Such manipulation of the argument mid leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9791 | Tenda AC20 fromAdvSetMacMtuWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9791</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC20 16.03.08.05. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/fromAdvSetMacMtuWan. This manipulation of the argument wanMTU causes stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9810 | TOCTOU race in Linenoise enables arbitrary file overwrite and permission changes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9810</link><description>TOCTOU  in linenoiseHistorySave in linenoise allows local attackers to overwrite arbitrary files and change permissions via a symlink race between fopen("w") on the history path and subsequent chmod() on the same path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9790 | SourceCodester Hotel Reservation System updateabout.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9790</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/updateabout.php. The manipulation of the argument address results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9809 | Out-of-bounds write in cdfs_open_cue_track in libretro libretro-common latest on all platforms allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9809</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in cdfs_open_cue_track in libretro libretro-common latest on all platforms allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .cue file with a file path exceeding PATH_MAX_LENGTH that is copied using memcpy into a fixed-size buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3586 | In Liferay Portal 7.4.3.27 through 7.4.3.42, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20, 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3586</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.4.3.27 through 7.4.3.42, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20, 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 update 27 through update 42 (Liferay PaaS, and Liferay Self-Hosted), the Objects module does not restrict the use of Groovy scripts in Object actions for Admin Users. This allows remote authenticated admin users with the Instance Administrator role to execute arbitrary Groovy scripts (i.e., remote code execution) through Object actions. 

In contrast, in Liferay DXP (Liferay SaaS), the use of Groovy in Object actions is not allowed due to the high security risks it poses. 

Starting from Liferay DXP 2024.Q2 and later, a new feature has been introduced in Instance Settings that allows administrators to configure whether Groovy scripts are allowed in their instances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9789 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System edituser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9789</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edituser.php. The manipulation of the argument userid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9788 | SourceCodester/Campcodes School Log Management System admin_class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9788</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester/Campcodes School Log Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_class.php. Executing manipulation of the argument id_no can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9375 | xmltodict 0.14.2 - XML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9375</link><description>XML Injection vulnerability in xmltodict allows Input Data Manipulation.This issue affects xmltodict: 0.14.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55007 | Knowage vulnerable to server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55007</link><description>Knowage is an open source analytics and business intelligence suite. Prior to version 8.1.37, Knowage is vulnerable to server-side request forgery. The vulnerability allows attackers to send requests to arbitrary hosts/paths. Since the attacker is not able to read the response, the impact of this vulnerability is limited. However, an attacker could be able to leverage this vulnerability to scan the internal network. This issue has been patched in version 8.1.37.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57799 | StreamVault can perform remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57799</link><description>StreamVault is a multi-platform video parsing and downloading tool. Prior to version 250822, after logging into the StreamVault-system, an attacker can modify certain system parameters, construct malicious commands, execute command injection attacks against the system, and ultimately gain server privileges. Users of all versions of the StreamVault system to date who have not modified their background passwords or use weak passwords are at risk of having their systems taken over via remote command execution. This issue has been patched in version 250822.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9786 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System teacher_signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /teacher_signup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument firstname results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9783 | TOTOLINK A702R formParentControl sub_418030 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9783</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in TOTOLINK A702R 4.0.0-B20211108.1423. This issue affects the function sub_418030 of the file /boafrm/formParentControl. Executing manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0656 | IBM Concert Software cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0656</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33082 | IBM Concert Software cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33082</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33083 | IBM Concert Software cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33083</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33084 | IBM Concert Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33084</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33099 | IBM Concert Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33099</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 could allow a remote attacker to perform unauthorized actions using man in the middle techniques due to improper certificate validation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33102 | IBM Concert Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33102</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 1.1.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9782 | TOTOLINK A702R formOneKeyAccessButton sub_4466F8 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9782</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R 4.0.0-B20211108.1423. This vulnerability affects the function sub_4466F8 of the file /boafrm/formOneKeyAccessButton. Performing manipulation of the argument submit-url results in buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9781 | TOTOLINK A702R formFilter sub_4162DC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9781</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A702R 4.0.0-B20211108.1423. This affects the function sub_4162DC of the file /boafrm/formFilter. Such manipulation of the argument ip6addr leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9780 | TOTOLINK A702R formIpQoS sub_419BE0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9780</link><description>A flaw has been found in TOTOLINK A702R 4.0.0-B20211108.1423. Affected by this issue is the function sub_419BE0 of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS. This manipulation of the argument mac causes buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12925 | Host Header Injection in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12925</link><description>Improper Validation of Certificate with Host Mismatch vulnerability in Akınsoft QR Menü allows HTTP Response Splitting.This issue affects QR Menü: from s1.05.05 before v1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0610 | CSRF in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0610</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Akınsoft QR Menü allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects QR Menü: from s1.05.06 before v1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2412 | OTP Bypass in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2412</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Akinsoft QR Menu allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects QR Menu: from s1.05.07 before v1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12914 | XSS in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12914</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Akınsoft QR Menü allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects QR Menü: from s1.05.05 before v1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12924 | Open Redirect in Akinsoft&amp;#x27;s QR Menu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12924</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Akınsoft QR Menü allows Forceful Browsing, Phishing.This issue affects QR Menü: from s1.05.05 before v1.05.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9779 | TOTOLINK A702R formFilter sub_4162DC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9779</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in TOTOLINK A702R 4.0.0-B20211108.1423. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_4162DC of the file /boafrm/formFilter. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9778 | Tenda W12 Administrative shadow hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9778</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda W12 up to 3.0.0.6(3948). Affected is an unknown function of the file /etc_ro/shadow of the component Administrative Interface. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36133 | IBM App Connect Enterprise information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36133</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container CD: 9.2.0 through 11.6.0, 12.1.0 through 12.14.0, and 12.0 LTS: 12.0.0 through 12.0.14stores potentially sensitive information in log files during installation that could be read by a local user on the container.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9775 | RemoteClinic edit-my-profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9775</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RemoteClinic up to 2.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /staff/edit-my-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument image results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9774 | RemoteClinic edit-patient.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9774</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in RemoteClinic up to 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /patients/edit-patient.php. The manipulation of the argument Email leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9773 | RemoteClinic edit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9773</link><description>A flaw has been found in RemoteClinic up to 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /staff/edit.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Last Name can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 10:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9772 | RemoteClinic edit.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9772</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in RemoteClinic up to 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /staff/edit.php. Performing manipulation of the argument image results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9771 | SourceCodester Eye Clinic Management System search_index_Diagnosis.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9771</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Eye Clinic Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /main/search_index_Diagnosis.php. Such manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9770 | Campcodes Hospital Management System Admin Dashboard Login admin sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9770</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/ of the component Admin Dashboard Login. This manipulation of the argument Password causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 08:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9769 | D-Link DI-7400G+ mng_platform.asp sub_478D28 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9769</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DI-7400G+ 19.12.25A1. Affected is the function sub_478D28 of the file /mng_platform.asp. The manipulation of the argument addr with the input `echo 12345 &gt; poc.txt` results in command injection. An attack on the physical device is feasible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38691 | In BootROM, there is a possible missing validation for Certificate Type 0. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38691</link><description>In BootROM, there is a possible missing validation for Certificate Type 0. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38692 | In BootROM, there is a missing size check for RSA keys in Certificate Type 0 validation. This could lead to memory buffer overflow without r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38692</link><description>In BootROM, there is a missing size check for RSA keys in Certificate Type 0 validation. This could lead to memory buffer overflow without requiring additional execution privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38693 | In FDL1, there is a possible missing payload size check. This could lead to memory buffer overflow without requiring additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38693</link><description>In FDL1, there is a possible missing payload size check. This could lead to memory buffer overflow without requiring additional execution privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38694 | In BootRom, there is a possible unchecked write address. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38694</link><description>In BootRom, there is a possible unchecked write address. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38695 | In BootRom, there's a possible unchecked command index. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38695</link><description>In BootRom, there's a possible unchecked command index. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38696 | In BootRom, there's a possible missing payload size check. This could lead to memory buffer overflow without requiring additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38696</link><description>In BootRom, there's a possible missing payload size check. This could lead to memory buffer overflow without requiring additional execution privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9768 | itsourcecode Sports Management System mode.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9768</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Admin/mode.php. The manipulation of the argument code leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58318 | DIAView - Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58318</link><description>Delta Electronics DIAView has an authentication bypass vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9767 | itsourcecode Sports Management System sporttype.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9767</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /Admin/sporttype.php. Executing manipulation of the argument code can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9766 | itsourcecode Sports Management System facilitator.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9766</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Admin/facilitator.php. Performing manipulation of the argument code results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 06:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9765 | itsourcecode Sports Management System tournament_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9765</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /Admin/tournament_details.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 06:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9764 | itsourcecode Sports Management System resultdetails.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9764</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Admin/resultdetails.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54857 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in SkyBridge BASIC MB-A130 Ver.1.5.8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54857</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in SkyBridge BASIC MB-A130 Ver.1.5.8 and earlier. If exploited, a remote unauthenticated attacker may execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20703 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20703</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01599794; Issue ID: MSV-3708.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20704 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20704</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01516959; Issue ID: MSV-3502.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20705 | In monitor_hang, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20705</link><description>In monitor_hang, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09989078; Issue ID: MSV-3964.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20706 | In mbrain, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20706</link><description>In mbrain, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09924624; Issue ID: MSV-3826.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20707 | In geniezone, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20707</link><description>In geniezone, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09924201; Issue ID: MSV-3820.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20708 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20708</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01123853; Issue ID: MSV-4131.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6507 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6507</link><description>A vulnerability in the h2oai/h2o-3 repository allows attackers to exploit deserialization of untrusted data, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution and reading of system files. This issue affects the latest master branch version 3.47.0.99999. The vulnerability arises from the ability to bypass regular expression filters intended to prevent malicious parameter injection in JDBC connections. Attackers can manipulate spaces between parameters to evade detection, allowing for unauthorized file access and code execution. The vulnerability is addressed in version 3.46.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9763 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System student_signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9763</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /student_signup.php. The manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9761 | Campcodes Online Feeds Product Inventory System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9761</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Online Feeds Product Inventory System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /feeds/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9760 | Portabilis i-Educar Matricula API aluno improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9760</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /module/Api/aluno of the component Matricula API. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7405 | Information Disclosure, Information Tampering, and Denial of Service (DoS) Vulnerability in MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7405</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read or write the device values of the product and stop the operation of the programs, since MODBUS/TCP in the products does not have authentication features.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7731 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7731</link><description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain credential information by intercepting SLMP communication messages, and read or write the device values of the product and stop the operations of programs by using the obtained credential information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9759 | Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System ajax.php signup sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9759</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function Signup of the file /ajax.php. Performing manipulation of the argument lastname results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9570 | Sunnet｜eHRD CTMS - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9570</link><description>The eHRD CTMS developed by Sunnet has an Arbitrary File Reading vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9758 | deepakmisal24 Chemical Inventory Management System inventory_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9758</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in deepakmisal24 Chemical Inventory Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /inventory_form.php. Such manipulation of the argument chem_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9567 | Sunnet｜eHRD CTMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9567</link><description>The eHRD developed by Sunnet has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9568 | Sunnet｜eHRD CTMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9568</link><description>The eHRD developed by Sunnet has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9569 | Sunnet｜eHRD CTMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9569</link><description>The eHRD developed by Sunnet has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9757 | Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System ajax.php login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9757</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is the function Login of the file /ajax.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9755 | Khanakag-17 Library Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9755</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Khanakag-17 Library Management System up to 60ed174506094dcd166e34904a54288e5d10ff24. This affects an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9756 | PHPGurukul User Management System change-emailid.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9756</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul User Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/change-emailid.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9754 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System Edit Profile edit-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9754</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /edit-profile.php of the component Edit Profile Page. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9753 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System Patient Search patient-search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9753</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/patient-search.php of the component Patient Search Module. Performing manipulation of the argument Search by Name Mobile No results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9752 | D-Link DIR-852 SOAP Service soap.cgi soapcgi_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9752</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-852 1.00CN B09. Impacted is the function soapcgi_main of the file soap.cgi of the component SOAP Service. Such manipulation of the argument service leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>