<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:18:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-20703 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20703</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01599794; Issue ID: MSV-3708.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20704 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20704</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01516959; Issue ID: MSV-3502.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20705 | In monitor_hang, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20705</link><description>In monitor_hang, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09989078; Issue ID: MSV-3964.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20706 | In mbrain, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20706</link><description>In mbrain, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09924624; Issue ID: MSV-3826.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20707 | In geniezone, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20707</link><description>In geniezone, there is a possible memory corruption due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09924201; Issue ID: MSV-3820.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20708 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20708</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01123853; Issue ID: MSV-4131.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6507 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6507</link><description>A vulnerability in the h2oai/h2o-3 repository allows attackers to exploit deserialization of untrusted data, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution and reading of system files. This issue affects the latest master branch version 3.47.0.99999. The vulnerability arises from the ability to bypass regular expression filters intended to prevent malicious parameter injection in JDBC connections. Attackers can manipulate spaces between parameters to evade detection, allowing for unauthorized file access and code execution. The vulnerability is addressed in version 3.46.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9763 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System student_signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9763</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /student_signup.php. The manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9761 | Campcodes Online Feeds Product Inventory System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9761</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Online Feeds Product Inventory System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /feeds/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9760 | Portabilis i-Educar Matricula API aluno improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9760</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /module/Api/aluno of the component Matricula API. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7405 | Information Disclosure, Information Tampering, and Denial of Service (DoS) Vulnerability in MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7405</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read or write the device values of the product and stop the operation of the programs, since MODBUS/TCP in the products does not have authentication features.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7731 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7731</link><description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain credential information by intercepting SLMP communication messages, and read or write the device values of the product and stop the operations of programs by using the obtained credential information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9759 | Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System ajax.php signup sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9759</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function Signup of the file /ajax.php. Performing manipulation of the argument lastname results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9570 | Sunnet慂란HRD CTMS - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9570</link><description>The eHRD CTMS developed by Sunnet has an Arbitrary File Reading vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9758 | deepakmisal24 Chemical Inventory Management System inventory_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9758</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in deepakmisal24 Chemical Inventory Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /inventory_form.php. Such manipulation of the argument chem_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9567 | Sunnet慂란HRD CTMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9567</link><description>The eHRD developed by Sunnet has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9568 | Sunnet慂란HRD CTMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9568</link><description>The eHRD developed by Sunnet has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9569 | Sunnet慂란HRD CTMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9569</link><description>The eHRD developed by Sunnet has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9757 | Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System ajax.php login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9757</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes/SourceCodester Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is the function Login of the file /ajax.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9755 | Khanakag-17 Library Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9755</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Khanakag-17 Library Management System up to 60ed174506094dcd166e34904a54288e5d10ff24. This affects an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9756 | PHPGurukul User Management System change-emailid.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9756</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul User Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/change-emailid.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9754 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System Edit Profile edit-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9754</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /edit-profile.php of the component Edit Profile Page. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9753 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System Patient Search patient-search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9753</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/patient-search.php of the component Patient Search Module. Performing manipulation of the argument Search by Name Mobile No results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9752 | D-Link DIR-852 SOAP Service soap.cgi soapcgi_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9752</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-852 1.00CN B09. Impacted is the function soapcgi_main of the file soap.cgi of the component SOAP Service. Such manipulation of the argument service leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9751 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9751</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9750 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9750</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9749 | HKritesh009 Grocery List Management Web App update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9749</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in HKritesh009 Grocery List Management Web App up to f491b681eb70d465f445c9a721415c965190f83b. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/update.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9748 | Tenda CH22 httpd IPSECsave fromIpsecitem stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9748</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. Affected by this issue is the function fromIpsecitem of the file /goform/IPSECsave of the component httpd. Executing manipulation of the argument ipsecno can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9747 | Koillection csrf_protection_controller.js cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9747</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Koillection up to 1.6.18. Affected is an unknown function of the file assets/controllers/csrf_protection_controller.js. Such manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.7.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 9ab8562d3f1e953da93fed63f9ee802c7ea26a9a. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. The vendor explains: "I ended up switching to a newer CSRF handling using stateless token."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 21:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9746 | Campcodes Hospital Management System Edit Doctor Specialization edit-doctor-specialization.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9746</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-doctor-specialization.php of the component Edit Doctor Specialization Page. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 21:22:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9745 | D-Link DI-500WF jhttpd version_upgrade.asp os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9745</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DI-500WF 14.04.10A1T. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /version_upgrade.asp of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument path leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9744 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9744</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=login. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 20:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9743 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System login_attendance2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9743</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file login_attendance2.php. Performing manipulation of the argument employee_id/date results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9742 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9742</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. Such manipulation of the argument user/pass leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9741 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System login_query12.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9741</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login_query12.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9740 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System log_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9740</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /log_query.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9739 | Campcodes Online Water Billing System process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9739</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Water Billing System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /process.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9738 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_tipo_ensino_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9738</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /intranet/educar_tipo_ensino_cad.php. Executing manipulation of the argument nm_tipo can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9737 | O2OA Personal Profile importmodel cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9737</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected is an unknown function of the file /x_query_assemble_designer/jaxrs/importmodel of the component Personal Profile Page. Performing manipulation of the argument description/applicationName/queryName results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 16:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9736 | O2OA Personal Profile statement cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9736</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This impacts an unknown function of the file /x_query_assemble_designer/jaxrs/statement of the component Personal Profile Page. Such manipulation of the argument description/queryName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 16:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9735 | O2OA Personal Profile table cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9735</link><description>A weakness has been identified in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This affects an unknown function of the file /x_query_assemble_designer/jaxrs/table of the component Personal Profile Page. This manipulation of the argument description/applicationName/queryName causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9734 | O2OA Personal Profile stat cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9734</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in O2OA up to 10.0-410. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /x_query_assemble_designer/jaxrs/stat of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument name/alias/description/applicationName results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9733 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System login_timeee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9733</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /login_timeee.php. Performing manipulation of the argument emp_id results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9732 | DCMTK dcm2img diybrpxt.h memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9732</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in DCMTK up to 3.6.9. This affects an unknown function in the library dcmimage/include/dcmtk/dcmimage/diybrpxt.h of the component dcm2img. Such manipulation leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The name of the patch is 7ad81d69b. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9731 | Tenda AC9 Administrative shadow hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9731</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda AC9 15.03.05.19. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /etc_ro/shadow of the component Administrative Interface. This manipulation causes hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9730 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System updateProfile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ajax/updateProfile.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9729 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration student-registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9729</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/student-registration.php. Performing manipulation of the argument studentname results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9728 | givanz Vvveb login.tpl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9728</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in givanz Vvveb 1.0.7.2. This affects an unknown part of the file app/template/user/login.tpl. Such manipulation of the argument Email/Password leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The name of the patch is bbd4c42c66ab818142240348173a669d1d2537fe. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 12:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9727 | D-Link DIR-816L soap.cgi soapcgi_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9727</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-816L 206b01. Affected by this issue is the function soapcgi_main of the file /soap.cgi. This manipulation of the argument service causes os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 11:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9726 | Campcodes Farm Management System review.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9726</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /review.php. The manipulation of the argument pid results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 11:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9725 | Cudy LT500E Web shadow hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9725</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Cudy LT500E up to 2.3.12. Affected is an unknown function of the file /squashfs-root/etc/shadow of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The attack must be carried out locally. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 2.3.13 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor explains: "[T]he firmware does store a default password of 'admin'. This password has been deprecated since LT500E firmware version 2.3.13 and is no longer used. The LT500E does not have an administrator password set by default; a new password (at least 8 characters ) must be manually created upon first login the web management page."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 10:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9724 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_nivel_ensino_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9724</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This impacts an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_nivel_ensino_cad.php. Executing manipulation of the argument nm_nivel/descricao can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 09:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9723 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_tipo_regime_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9723</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_tipo_regime_cad.php. Performing manipulation of the argument nm_tipo results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 09:17:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9722 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_tipo_ocorrencia_disciplinar_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9722</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_tipo_ocorrencia_disciplinar_cad.php. Such manipulation of the argument nm_tipo/descricao leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 08:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9721 | Portabilis i-Educar edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9721</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /module/FormulaMedia/edit. This manipulation of the argument nome/formulaMedia causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 07:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9720 | Portabilis i-Educar Cadastrar tabela de arredondamento edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9720</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /module/TabelaArredondamento/edit of the component Cadastrar tabela de arredondamento Page. The manipulation of the argument Nome results in cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9719 | O2OA Personal Profile script cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9719</link><description>A weakness has been identified in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /x_processplatform_assemble_designer/jaxrs/script of the component Personal Profile Page. Executing manipulation of the argument name/alias/description/applicationName can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 06:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9718 | O2OA Personal Profile process cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9718</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This affects an unknown part of the file /x_processplatform_assemble_designer/jaxrs/process of the component Personal Profile Page. Performing manipulation of the argument name/alias results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 05:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9717 | O2OA Personal Profile unit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9717</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /x_organization_assemble_control/jaxrs/unit/ of the component Personal Profile Page. Such manipulation of the argument name/shortName/distinguishedName/pinyin/pinyinInitial/levelName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 05:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9716 | O2OA Personal Profile form cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9716</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /x_processplatform_assemble_designer/jaxrs/form of the component Personal Profile Page. This manipulation of the argument name/alias/description causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 04:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5083 | Amministrazione Trasparente &amp;lt;= 9.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via print_r Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5083</link><description>The Amministrazione Trasparente plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 04:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32589 | WordPress Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32589</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 03:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32832 | WordPress Login with Phone Number plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.93 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32832</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hamid Alinia Login with phone number.This issue affects Login with phone number: from n/a through 1.6.93.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 03:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31100 | WordPress School Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.93.1 (02-07-2025) - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31100</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Mojoomla School Management allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 1.93.1 (02-07-2025).</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 03:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47696 | WordPress Blog Designer PRO plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Unauthenticated Non-Arbitrary Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47696</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Solwin Blog Designer PRO.This issue affects Blog Designer PRO: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 03:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9715 | O2OA Personal Profile script cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9715</link><description>A vulnerability was found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected is an unknown function of the file /x_cms_assemble_control/jaxrs/script of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument name/alias/description results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9706 | SourceCodester Water Billing System edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9706</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SourceCodester Water Billing System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 22:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9705 | SourceCodester Water Billing System paybill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9705</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Water Billing System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /paybill.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 21:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9704 | SourceCodester Water Billing System viewbill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9704</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Water Billing System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /viewbill.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 20:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9702 | SourceCodester Simple Cafe Billing System sales_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9702</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Simple Cafe Billing System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /sales_report.php. The manipulation of the argument month leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 19:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9701 | SourceCodester Simple Cafe Billing System receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9701</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Simple Cafe Billing System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /receipt.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 18:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9700 | SourceCodester Online Book Store publisher_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9700</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Online Book Store 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /publisher_list.php. This manipulation of the argument pubid causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9699 | SourceCodester Online Polling System Code checklogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9699</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Polling System Code 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/checklogin.php. The manipulation of the argument myusername results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9695 | GalleryVault Gallery Vault App com.thinkyeah.galleryvault AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9695</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in GalleryVault Gallery Vault App up to 4.5.2 on Android. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.thinkyeah.galleryvault. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 15:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9694 | Campcodes Advanced Online Voting System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9694</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Advanced Online Voting System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 15:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9692 | Campcodes Online Shopping System product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9692</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /product.php. Performing manipulation of the argument p results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10062 | XAMPP WebDAV PHP Upload Authentication Bypass RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10062</link><description>A vulnerability in XAMPP, developed by Apache Friends, version 1.7.3's default WebDAV configuration allows remote authenticated attackers to upload and execute arbitrary PHP code. The WebDAV service, accessible via /webdav/, accepts HTTP PUT requests using default credentials. This permits attackers to upload a malicious PHP payload and trigger its execution via a subsequent GET request, resulting in remote code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9691 | Campcodes Online Shopping System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9691</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Shopping System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /login.php. Such manipulation of the argument Password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2005-10004 | Cacti graph_view.php RCE via graph_start Parameter Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2005-10004</link><description>Cacti versions prior to 0.8.6-d contain a remote command execution vulnerability in the graph_view.php script. An authenticated user can inject arbitrary shell commands via the graph_start GET parameter, which is improperly handled during graph rendering. This flaw allows attackers to execute commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the web server process, potentially compromising system integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2009-20008 | Green Dam &amp;lt; 3.174 URL Processing Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2009-20008</link><description>Green Dam Youth Escort version 3.17 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow when processing overly long URLs. The flaw resides in the URL filtering component, which fails to properly validate input length before copying user-supplied data into a fixed-size buffer. A remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to visit a specially crafted webpage containing a long URL, resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2009-20010 | Dogfood CRM spell.php RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2009-20010</link><description>Dogfood CRM version 2.0.10 contains a remote command execution vulnerability in the spell.php script used by its mail subsystem. The vulnerability arises from unsanitized user input passed via a POST request to the data parameter, which is processed by the underlying shell without adequate escaping. This allows attackers to inject arbitrary shell commands and execute them on the server. The flaw is exploitable without authentication and was discovered by researcher LSO.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2009-20011 | ContentKeeper Web Appliance &amp;lt; 125.10 RCE via mimencode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2009-20011</link><description>ContentKeeper Web Appliance (now maintained by Impero Software)맜ersions prior to 125.10 are vulnerable to remote command execution due to insecure handling of file uploads via the mimencode CGI utility. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to upload and execute arbitrary scripts as the Apache user. Additionally, the exploit can optionally escalate privileges by abusing insecure PATH usage in the benetool binary, resulting in root-level access if successful.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10016 | BS.Player 2.57 Buffer Overflow via M3U Playlist Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10016</link><description>BS.Player version 2.57 (build 1051) contains a vulnerability in its playlist import functionality. When processing .m3u files, the application fails to properly validate the length of playlist entries, resulting in a buffer overflow condition. This flaw occurs during parsing of long URLs embedded in the playlist, allowing overwrite of Structured Exception Handler (SEH) records. The vulnerability is triggered upon opening a crafted playlist file and affects the Unicode parsing logic in the Windows client.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10017 | WM Downloader 3.1.2.2 Buffer Overflow via Malformed M3U File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10017</link><description>WM Downloader version 3.1.2.2 is vulnerable to a buffer overflow when processing a specially crafted .m3u playlist file. The application fails to properly validate input length, allowing an attacker to overwrite structured exception handler (SEH) records and execute arbitrary code. Exploitation occurs locally when a user opens the malicious file, and the payload executes with the privileges of the current user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10032 | Sunway Forcecontrol SNMP NetDBServer.exe Opcode 0x57</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10032</link><description>Sunway ForceControl version 6.1 SP3 and earlier contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SNMP NetDBServer service, which listens on TCP port 2001. The flaw is triggered when the service receives a specially crafted packet using opcode 0x57 with an overly long payload. Due to improper bounds checking during packet parsing, attacker-controlled data overwrites the Structured Exception Handler (SEH), allowing arbitrary code execution in the context of the service. This vulnerability can be exploited remotely without authentication and may lead to full system compromise on affected Windows hosts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2008-20001 | activePDF WebGrabber ActiveX Control Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2008-20001</link><description>activePDF WebGrabber version 3.8.2.0 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the GetStatus() method of the APWebGrb.ocx ActiveX control. By passing an overly long string to this method, a remote attacker can execute arbitrary code in the context of the vulnerable process. Although the control is not marked safe for scripting, exploitation is possible via crafted HTML content in Internet Explorer under permissive security settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2009-20009 | Belkin Bulldog Plus Web Service Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2009-20009</link><description>Belkin Bulldog Plus version 4.0.2 build 1219 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in its web service authentication handler. When a specially crafted HTTP request is sent with an oversized Authorization header, the application fails to properly validate the input length before copying it into a fixed-size buffer, resulting in memory corruption and potential remote code execution. Exploitation requires network access and does not require prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9690 | SourceCodester Advanced School Management System vendordetails sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9690</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Advanced School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /index.php/stock/vendordetails. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9689 | SourceCodester Advanced School Management System item_select sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9689</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Advanced School Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /index.php/stock/item_select. The manipulation of the argument q results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0165 | IBM watsonx Orchestrate Cartridge for IBM Cloud Pak for Data SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0165</link><description>IBM watsonx Orchestrate Cartridge for IBM Cloud Pak for Data 4.8.4, 4.8.5, and 5.0.0 through 5.2.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify, or delete information in the back-end database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9688 | Mupen64Plus is_viewer.c write_is_viewer integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9688</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Mupen64Plus up to 2.6.0. The affected element is the function write_is_viewer of the file src/device/cart/is_viewer.c. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9687 | Portabilis i-Educar processamentoApi improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9687</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /module/HistoricoEscolar/processamentoApi. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 12:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9686 | Portabilis i-Educar Listagem de 치reas de conhecimento edit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9686</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /module/AreaConhecimento/edit of the component Listagem de 치reas de conhecimento Page. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9685 | Portabilis i-Educar Listagem de 치reas de conhecimento view sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9685</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /module/AreaConhecimento/view of the component Listagem de 치reas de conhecimento Page. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9684 | Portabilis i-Educar Formula de C치lculo de M칠dia edit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9684</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /module/FormulaMedia/edit of the component Formula de C치lculo de M칠dia Page. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9683 | O2OA Personal Profile form cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9683</link><description>A vulnerability was found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /x_cms_assemble_control/jaxrs/form of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9682 | O2OA Personal Profile appdict cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9682</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /x_cms_assemble_control/jaxrs/design/appdict of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38677 | f2fs: fix to avoid out-of-boundary access in dnode page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38677</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: fix to avoid out-of-boundary access in dnode page

As Jiaming Zhang reported:

 
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x1c1/0x2a0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0x17e/0x800 mm/kasan/report.c:480
 kasan_report+0x147/0x180 mm/kasan/report.c:593
 data_blkaddr fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:3053 [inline]
 f2fs_data_blkaddr fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:3058 [inline]
 f2fs_get_dnode_of_data+0x1a09/0x1c40 fs/f2fs/node.c:855
 f2fs_reserve_block+0x53/0x310 fs/f2fs/data.c:1195
 prepare_write_begin fs/f2fs/data.c:3395 [inline]
 f2fs_write_begin+0xf39/0x2190 fs/f2fs/data.c:3594
 generic_perform_write+0x2c7/0x910 mm/filemap.c:4112
 f2fs_buffered_write_iter fs/f2fs/file.c:4988 [inline]
 f2fs_file_write_iter+0x1ec8/0x2410 fs/f2fs/file.c:5216
 new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
 vfs_write+0x546/0xa90 fs/read_write.c:686
 ksys_write+0x149/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xf3/0x3d0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

The root cause is in the corrupted image, there is a dnode has the same
node id w/ its inode, so during f2fs_get_dnode_of_data(), it tries to
access block address in dnode at offset 934, however it parses the dnode
as inode node, so that get_dnode_addr() returns 360, then it tries to
access page address from 360 + 934 * 4 = 4096 w/ 4 bytes.

To fix this issue, let's add sanity check for node id of all direct nodes
during f2fs_get_dnode_of_data().</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9681 | O2OA Personal Profile agent cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9681</link><description>A flaw has been found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected is an unknown function of the file /x_program_center/jaxrs/agent of the component Personal Profile Page. Executing manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9680 | O2OA Personal Profile page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9680</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This impacts an unknown function of the file /x_portal_assemble_designer/jaxrs/page of the component Personal Profile Page. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 07:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9679 | itsourcecode Student Information System course_edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9679</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Student Information System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /course_edit1.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9499 | Ocean Extra &amp;lt;= 2.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via oceanwp_library Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9499</link><description>The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's oceanwp_library shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9500 | TablePress &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcode_debug Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9500</link><description>The TablePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 땁hortcode_debug parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54946 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54946</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54944 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54944</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to write malicious code in a specific file, which may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54945 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54945</link><description>An external control of file name or path vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a malicious file by controlling the destination file path.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54942 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54942</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to access deployment functionality without prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54943 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54943</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to perform unauthorized application deployment due to the absence of proper access control checks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4956 | WordPress Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4956</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in AA-Team Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 02:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9618 | Related Posts Lite &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9618</link><description>The Related Posts Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.12. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 02:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>