<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:37:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-20084 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20084</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08944210; Issue ID: MSV-1561.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20085 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20085</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08944204; Issue ID: MSV-1560.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20086 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20086</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932916; Issue ID: MSV-1551.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20087 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20087</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932916; Issue ID: MSV-1550.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20088 | In keyinstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20088</link><description>In keyinstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08932099; Issue ID: MSV-1543.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20089 | In wlan, there is a possible denial of service due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20089</link><description>In wlan, there is a possible denial of service due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08861558; Issue ID: MSV-1526.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45527 | REDCap 14.7.0 allows HTML injection via the project title of a New Project action. This can lead to resultant logout CSRF via index.php?logo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45527</link><description>REDCap 14.7.0 allows HTML injection via the project title of a New Project action. This can lead to resultant logout CSRF via index.php?logout=1, and can also be used to insert a link to an external phishing website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45528 | CodeAstro MembershipM-PHP (aka Membership Management System in PHP) 1.0 allows add_members.php fullname stored XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45528</link><description>CodeAstro MembershipM-PHP (aka Membership Management System in PHP) 1.0 allows add_members.php fullname stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8365 | Vault Leaks AppRole Client Tokens And Accessor in Audit Log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8365</link><description>Vault Community Edition and Vault Enterprise experienced a regression where functionality that HMAC’d sensitive headers in the configured audit device, specifically client tokens and token accessors, was removed. This resulted in the plaintext values of client tokens and token accessors being stored in the audit log. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-8365, was fixed in Vault Community Edition and Vault Enterprise 1.17.5 and Vault Enterprise 1.16.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 02:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45269 | WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Carousel image selection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45269</link><description>WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Carousel image selection feature. While logged in to the WordPress site with Carousel Slider plugin enabled, accessing a crafted page may cause a user to alter the contents of the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45270 | WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Hero image selection feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45270</link><description>WordPress plugin "Carousel Slider" provided by Sayful Islam contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability on Hero image selection feature. While logged in to the WordPress site with Carousel Slider plugin enabled, accessing a crafted page may cause a user to alter the contents of the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45522 | Linen before cd37c3e does not verify that the domain is linen.dev or www.linen.dev when resetting a password. This occurs in create in apps/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45522</link><description>Linen before cd37c3e does not verify that the domain is linen.dev or www.linen.dev when resetting a password. This occurs in create in apps/web/pages/api/forgot-password/index.ts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 23:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8370 | Grocy SVG File Upload recipepictures cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8370</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Grocy up to 4.2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/files/recipepictures/ of the component SVG File Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument force_serve_as with the input picture' leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. NOTE: The project maintainer explains that "this is 'nonsense' and practically irrelevant according to the project's security policy" which expects additional authentication for the software.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 22:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45509 | In MISP through 2.4.196, app/Controller/BookmarksController.php does not properly restrict access to bookmarks data in the case where the us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45509</link><description>In MISP through 2.4.196, app/Controller/BookmarksController.php does not properly restrict access to bookmarks data in the case where the user is not an org admin.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45508 | HTMLDOC before 1.9.19 has an out-of-bounds write in parse_paragraph in ps-pdf.cxx because of an attempt to strip leading whitespace from a w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45508</link><description>HTMLDOC before 1.9.19 has an out-of-bounds write in parse_paragraph in ps-pdf.cxx because of an attempt to strip leading whitespace from a whitespace-only node.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5053 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.1.18 -  Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Mailchimp Integration Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5053</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Malichimp API key update due to an insufficient capability check on the verifyRequest function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.18. This makes it possible for Form Managers with a Subscriber-level access and above to modify the Mailchimp API key used for integration. At the same time, missing Mailchimp API key validation allows the redirect of the integration requests to the attacker-controlled server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8368 | code-projects Hospital Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8367 | HM Courts &amp;amp; Tribunals Service Probate Back Office Markdown NotificationService.java injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HM Courts &amp; Tribunals Service Probate Back Office up to c1afe0cdb2b2766d9e24872c4e827f8b82a6cd31. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/uk/gov/hmcts/probate/service/NotificationService.java of the component Markdown Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as d90230d7cf575e5b0852d56660104c8bd2503c34. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 04:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8366 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System Update My Profile Page index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?id=userProfileEdit of the component Update My Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument fname/lname/email with the input  leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 18:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44946 | kcm: Serialise kcm_sendmsg() for the same socket.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44946</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

kcm: Serialise kcm_sendmsg() for the same socket.

syzkaller reported UAF in kcm_release(). [0]

The scenario is

  1. Thread A builds a skb with MSG_MORE and sets kcm-&gt;seq_skb.

  2. Thread A resumes building skb from kcm-&gt;seq_skb but is blocked
     by sk_stream_wait_memory()

  3. Thread B calls sendmsg() concurrently, finishes building kcm-&gt;seq_skb
     and puts the skb to the write queue

  4. Thread A faces an error and finally frees skb that is already in the
     write queue

  5. kcm_release() does double-free the skb in the write queue

When a thread is building a MSG_MORE skb, another thread must not touch it.

Let's add a per-sk mutex and serialise kcm_sendmsg().

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_unlink include/linux/skbuff.h:2366 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_dequeue include/linux/skbuff.h:2385 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_queue_purge_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:3175 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_queue_purge include/linux/skbuff.h:3181 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in kcm_release+0x170/0x4c8 net/kcm/kcmsock.c:1691
Read of size 8 at addr ffff0000ced0fc80 by task syz-executor329/6167

CPU: 1 PID: 6167 Comm: syz-executor329 Tainted: G    B              6.8.0-rc5-syzkaller-g9abbc24128bc #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/25/2024
Call trace:
 dump_backtrace+0x1b8/0x1e4 arch/arm64/kernel/stacktrace.c:291
 show_stack+0x2c/0x3c arch/arm64/kernel/stacktrace.c:298
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:88 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0xd0/0x124 lib/dump_stack.c:106
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:377 [inline]
 print_report+0x178/0x518 mm/kasan/report.c:488
 kasan_report+0xd8/0x138 mm/kasan/report.c:601
 __asan_report_load8_noabort+0x20/0x2c mm/kasan/report_generic.c:381
 __skb_unlink include/linux/skbuff.h:2366 [inline]
 __skb_dequeue include/linux/skbuff.h:2385 [inline]
 __skb_queue_purge_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:3175 [inline]
 __skb_queue_purge include/linux/skbuff.h:3181 [inline]
 kcm_release+0x170/0x4c8 net/kcm/kcmsock.c:1691
 __sock_release net/socket.c:659 [inline]
 sock_close+0xa4/0x1e8 net/socket.c:1421
 __fput+0x30c/0x738 fs/file_table.c:376
 ____fput+0x20/0x30 fs/file_table.c:404
 task_work_run+0x230/0x2e0 kernel/task_work.c:180
 exit_task_work include/linux/task_work.h:38 [inline]
 do_exit+0x618/0x1f64 kernel/exit.c:871
 do_group_exit+0x194/0x22c kernel/exit.c:1020
 get_signal+0x1500/0x15ec kernel/signal.c:2893
 do_signal+0x23c/0x3b44 arch/arm64/kernel/signal.c:1249
 do_notify_resume+0x74/0x1f4 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:148
 exit_to_user_mode_prepare arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:169 [inline]
 exit_to_user_mode arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:178 [inline]
 el0_svc+0xac/0x168 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:713
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x84/0xfc arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:730
 el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:598

Allocated by task 6166:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x40/0x78 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 kasan_save_alloc_info+0x70/0x84 mm/kasan/generic.c:626
 unpoison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:314 [inline]
 __kasan_slab_alloc+0x74/0x8c mm/kasan/common.c:340
 kasan_slab_alloc include/linux/kasan.h:201 [inline]
 slab_post_alloc_hook mm/slub.c:3813 [inline]
 slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3860 [inline]
 kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x204/0x4c0 mm/slub.c:3903
 __alloc_skb+0x19c/0x3d8 net/core/skbuff.c:641
 alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:1296 [inline]
 kcm_sendmsg+0x1d3c/0x2124 net/kcm/kcmsock.c:783
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:745 [inline]
 sock_sendmsg+0x220/0x2c0 net/socket.c:768
 splice_to_socket+0x7cc/0xd58 fs/splice.c:889
 do_splice_from fs/splice.c:941 [inline]
 direct_splice_actor+0xec/0x1d8 fs/splice.c:1164
 splice_direct_to_actor+0x438/0xa0c fs/splice.c:1108
 do_splice_direct_actor 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4539 | Web Application Firewall &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4539</link><description>The Web Application Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address or country from logging in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 09:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4100 | WP Cerber Security &amp;lt;= 9.4 - IP Protection Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4100</link><description>The WP Cerber Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Protection bypass in versions up to, and including 9.4 due to the plugin improperly checking for a visitor's IP address. This makes it possible for an attacker whose IP address has been blocked to bypass this control by setting the X-Forwarded-For: HTTP header to an IP Address that hasn't been blocked.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4536 | IP Vault – WP Firewall &amp;lt;= 1.1 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4536</link><description>The IP Vault – WP Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address or country from logging in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7717 | WP Events Manager &amp;lt;= 2.1.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7717</link><description>The WP Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.11 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8108 | Share This Image &amp;lt;= 2.01 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via alignment Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8108</link><description>The Share This Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'alignment' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.01 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0109 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause a crash by passing in a malformed ELF file. A suc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0109</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause a crash by passing in a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may cause an out of bounds read in the unprivileged process memory which could lead to a limited denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0110 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause an out-of-bound write by passing in a malformed E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0110</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause an out-of-bound write by passing in a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0111 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command 'cuobjdump' where a user may cause a crash or produce incorrect output by passing a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0111</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command 'cuobjdump' where a user may cause a crash or produce incorrect output by passing a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a limited denial of service or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39579 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contains an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A local high privileged att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39579</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contains an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain root-level access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8276 | WPZOOM Portfolio Lite – Filterable Portfolio Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8276</link><description>The WPZOOM Portfolio Lite – Filterable Portfolio Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’ attribute within the 'wp:wpzoom-blocks' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39578 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.1 contains a UNIX symbolic link (symlink) following vulnerability. A local high privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39578</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.1 contains a UNIX symbolic link (symlink) following vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service, information tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44945 | netfilter: nfnetlink: Initialise extack before use in ACKs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44945</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nfnetlink: Initialise extack before use in ACKs

Add missing extack initialisation when ACKing BATCH_BEGIN and BATCH_END.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 06:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3886 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via envato_code[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3886</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘envato_code[]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the on_ajax_check_envato_code function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5212 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via envato_code[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5212</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘envato_code[]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the on_ajax_register_forum_user function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7435 | Attire &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7435</link><description>The Attire theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 02:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39747 | IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39747</link><description>IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services 6.0, 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3 uses default credentials for potentially critical functionality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 02:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>