<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-22900 | Totolink N600R v4.3.0cu.7647_B20210106 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the macCloneMac parameter in the setWanConfig function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22900</link><description>Totolink N600R v4.3.0cu.7647_B20210106 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the macCloneMac parameter in the setWanConfig function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24358 | gorilla/csrf CSRF vulnerability due to broken Referer validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24358</link><description>gorilla/csrf provides Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) prevention middleware for Go web applications &amp; services. Prior to 1.7.2, gorilla/csrf does not validate the Origin header against an allowlist. Its executes its validation of the Referer header for cross-origin requests only when it believes the request is being served over TLS. It determines this by inspecting the r.URL.Scheme value. However, this value is never populated for "server" requests per the Go spec, and so this check does not run in practice. This vulnerability allows an attacker who has gained XSS on a subdomain or top level domain to perform authenticated form submissions against gorilla/csrf protected targets that share the same top level domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28399 | An issue in Erick xmall v.1.1 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the updateAddress method of the Address Control...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28399</link><description>An issue in Erick xmall v.1.1 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the updateAddress method of the Address Controller class.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29213 | A zip slip vulnerability in the component \service\migrate\MigrateForm.java of JEEWMS v3.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29213</link><description>A zip slip vulnerability in the component \service\migrate\MigrateForm.java of JEEWMS v3.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted Zip file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5616 | In Ubuntu, gnome-control-center did not properly reflect SSH remote login status when the system was configured to use systemd socket activa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5616</link><description>In Ubuntu, gnome-control-center did not properly reflect SSH remote login status when the system was configured to use systemd socket activation for openssh-server. This could unknowingly leave the local machine exposed to remote SSH access contrary to expectation of the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 18:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42193 | HCL BigFix Web Reports is susceptible to a Man-In-The-Middle (MITM) attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42193</link><description>HCL BigFix Web Reports' service communicates over HTTPS but exhibits a weakness in its handling of SSL certificate validation. This scenario presents a possibility of man-in-the-middle (MITM) attacks and data exposure as, if exploited, this vulnerability could potentially lead to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 18:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42189 | HCL BigFix Web Reports might be subject to a Denial of Service (DoS) attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42189</link><description>HCL BigFix Web Reports might be subject to a Denial of Service (DoS) attack, due to a potentially weak validation of an API parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 18:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42200 | HCL BigFix Web Reports is potentially susceptible to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42200</link><description>HCL BigFix Web Reports might be subject to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack, due to a potentially weak validation of user input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 18:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28100 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in dingfanzuCMS v.1.0 allows a attacker to execute arbitrary code via not filtering the content correctly at t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28100</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in dingfanzuCMS v.1.0 allows a attacker to execute arbitrary code via not filtering the content correctly at the "operateOrder.php" id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29705 | code-gen &lt;=2.0.6 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The project does not have permission control allowing anyone to access such proj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29705</link><description>code-gen &lt;=2.0.6 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The project does not have permission control allowing anyone to access such projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27289 | A replay attack vulnerability was discovered in a Zigbee smart home kit manufactured by Ksix (Zigbee Gateway Module = v1.0.3, Door Sensor = ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27289</link><description>A replay attack vulnerability was discovered in a Zigbee smart home kit manufactured by Ksix (Zigbee Gateway Module = v1.0.3, Door Sensor = v1.0.7, Motion Sensor = v1.0.12), where the Zigbee anti-replay mechanism - based on the frame counter field - is improperly implemented. As a result, an attacker within wireless range can resend captured packets with a higher sequence number, which the devices incorrectly accept as legitimate messages. This allows spoofed commands to be injected without authentication, triggering false alerts and misleading the user through notifications in the mobile application used to monitor the network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50960 | A command injection vulnerability in the Nmap diagnostic tool in the admin web console of Extron SMP 111 &lt;=3.01, SMP 351 &lt;=2.16, and SMP 352...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50960</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the Nmap diagnostic tool in the admin web console of Extron SMP 111 &lt;=3.01, SMP 351 &lt;=2.16, and SMP 352 &lt;= 2.16 allows a remote authenticated attacker with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33026 | In PeaZip through 10.4.0, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33026</link><description>In PeaZip through 10.4.0, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of PeaZip. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of archived files. When extracting files from a crafted archive that bears the Mark-of-the-Web, PeaZip does not propagate the Mark-of-the-Web to the extracted files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33027 | In Bandisoft Bandizip through 7.37, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the Mark-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33027</link><description>In Bandisoft Bandizip through 7.37, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of Bandizip. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of archived files. When extracting files from a crafted archive that bears the Mark-of-the-Web, Bandizip does not propagate the Mark-of-the-Web to the extracted files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33028 | In WinZip through 29.0, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-8811. This vulnerability a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33028</link><description>In WinZip through 29.0, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-8811. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of WinZip. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of archived files. When extracting files from a crafted archive that bears the Mark-of-the-Web, WinZip does not propagate the Mark-of-the-Web to the extracted files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3617 | Local Privilege Escalation in ThinManager®</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3617</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation ThinManager. When the software starts up, files are deleted in the temporary folder causing the Access Control Entry of the directory to inherit permissions from the parent directory. If exploited, a threat actor could inherit elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3618 | Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3618</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation ThinManager. The software fails to adequately verify the outcome of memory allocation while processing Type 18 messages. If exploited, a threat actor could cause a denial-of-service on the target software.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32776 | OpenRazer Vulnerable to Out of Bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32776</link><description>OpenRazer is an open source driver and user-space daemon to control Razer device lighting and other features on GNU/Linux. By writing specially crafted data to the `matrix_custom_frame` file, an attacker can cause the custom kernel driver to read more bytes than provided by user space. This data will be written into the RGB arguments which will be sent to the USB device. This issue has been patched in v3.10.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32779 | labsai/eddi Vulnerable to Path Traversal (Zip Slip) in ZIP Import Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32779</link><description>E.D.D.I (Enhanced Dialog Driven Interface) is a middleware to connect and manage LLM API bots. In versions before 5.5.0, an attacker with access to the `/backup/import` API endpoint can write arbitrary files to locations outside the intended extraction directory due to a Zip Slip vulnerability. Although the application runs as a non-root user (`185`), limiting direct impact on system-level files, this vulnerability can still be exploited to overwrite application files (e.g., JAR libraries) owned by the application user. This overwrite can potentially lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) within the application's context. This issue has been patched in version 5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32780 | BleachBit for Windows Has DLL Untrusted Path Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32780</link><description>BleachBit cleans files to free disk space and to maintain privacy. BleachBit for Windows up to version 4.6.2 is vulnerable to a DLL Hijacking vulnerability. By placing a malicious DLL with the name uuid.dll in the folder C:\Users\\AppData\Local\Microsoft\WindowsApps\, an attacker can execute arbitrary code every time BleachBit is run. This issue has been patched in version 4.9.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29817 | Microsoft Power Automate Desktop Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29817</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-18243 | SQL injection vulnerability found in Enricozab CMS v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via /hdo/hdo-view-case.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-18243</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability found in Enricozab CMS v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via /hdo/hdo-view-case.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36842 | An issue in Oncord+ Android Infotainment Systems OS Android 12, Model Hardware TS17,Hardware part Number F57L_V3.2_20220301, and Build Numbe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36842</link><description>An issue in Oncord+ Android Infotainment Systems OS Android 12, Model Hardware TS17,Hardware part Number F57L_V3.2_20220301, and Build Number PlatformVER:K24-2023/05/09-v0.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ADB port component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11084 | Potential Username Enumeration in Helix ALM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11084</link><description>Helix ALM prior to 2025.1 returns distinct error responses during authentication, allowing an attacker to determine whether a username exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28198 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Hitout car sale 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the orderBy parameter of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28198</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Hitout car sale 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the orderBy parameter of the StoreController.java component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32911 | Libsoup: double free on  soup_message_headers_get_content_disposition() through  &amp;quot;soup-message-headers.c&amp;quot; via &amp;quot;params&amp;quot; ghashtable value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32911</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, which is vulnerable to a use-after-free memory issue not on the heap in the soup_message_headers_get_content_disposition() function. This flaw allows a malicious HTTP client to cause memory corruption in the libsoup server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13177 | Symlink Following in Netskope Client Postinstall Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13177</link><description>Netskope Client on Mac OS is impacted by a vulnerability in which the postinstall script does not properly validate the path of the file “nsinstallation”. A standard user could potentially create a symlink of the file “nsinstallation” to escalate the privileges of a different file on the system. 
This issue affects Netskope Client: before 123.0, before 117.1.11.2310, before 120.1.10.2306.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24948 | In JotUrl 2.0, passwords are sent via HTTP GET-type requests, potentially exposing credentials to eavesdropping or insecure records.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24948</link><description>In JotUrl 2.0, passwords are sent via HTTP GET-type requests, potentially exposing credentials to eavesdropping or insecure records.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24949 | In JotUrl 2.0, is possible to bypass security requirements during the password change process.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24949</link><description>In JotUrl 2.0, is possible to bypass security requirements during the password change process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28142 | Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3_1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the folder...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28142</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3_1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the foldername in /boafrm/formDiskCreateShare.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28143 | Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3_1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the groupn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28143</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3_1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the groupname at the /boafrm/formDiskCreateGroup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28144 | Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a stack overflow vlunerability via peerPin param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28144</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a stack overflow vlunerability via peerPin parameter in the formWsc function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2830 | By crafting a malformed file name for an attachment in a multipart message, an attacker can trick Thunderbird into including a directory lis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2830</link><description>By crafting a malformed file name for an attachment in a multipart message, an attacker can trick Thunderbird into including a directory listing of /tmp when the message is forwarded or edited as a new message. This vulnerability could allow attackers to disclose sensitive information from the victim's system. This vulnerability is not limited to Linux; similar behavior has been observed on Windows as well. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 137.0.2 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3522 | Thunderbird processes the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header to handle attachments which can be hosted externally. When an email is op...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3522</link><description>Thunderbird processes the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header to handle attachments which can be hosted externally. When an email is opened, Thunderbird accesses the specified URL to  determine file size, and navigates to it when the user clicks the attachment. Because the URL is not validated or sanitized, it can reference internal resources like chrome:// or SMB share file:// links, potentially leading to hashed Windows credential leakage and opening the door to more serious security issues. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 137.0.2 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3523 | When an email contains multiple attachments with external links via the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header, only the last link is show...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3523</link><description>When an email contains multiple attachments with external links via the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header, only the last link is shown when hovering over any attachment. Although the correct link is used on click, the misleading hover text could trick users into downloading content from untrusted sources. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 137.0.2 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32949 | PeerTube User Import Authenticated Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32949</link><description>This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to cause the server to consume very large amounts of disk space when extracting a Zip Bomb. 

If user import is enabled (which is the default setting), any registered user can upload an archive for importing. The code uses the yauzl library for reading the archive. The yauzl library does not contain any mechanism to detect or prevent extraction of a  Zip Bomb https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zip_bomb . Therefore, when using the User Import functionality with a Zip Bomb, PeerTube will try extracting the archive which will cause a disk space resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28145 | Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via partition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28145</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via partition in /boafrm/formDiskFormat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32948 | PeerTube ActivityPub Playlist Creation Blind SSRF and DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32948</link><description>The vulnerability allows any attacker to cause the PeerTube server to stop functioning, or in special cases send requests to arbitrary URLs (Blind SSRF). Attackers can send ActivityPub activities to PeerTube's "inbox" endpoint. By abusing the "Create Activity" functionality, it is possible to create crafted playlists which will cause either denial of service or an attacker-controlled blind SSRF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27980 | cashbook v4.0.3 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in /api/entry/flow/invoice/show?invoice=.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27980</link><description>cashbook v4.0.3 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in /api/entry/flow/invoice/show?invoice=.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32947 | PeerTube ActivityPub Crawl Infinite Loop DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32947</link><description>This vulnerability allows any attacker to cause the PeerTube server to stop responding to requests due to an infinite loop in the "inbox" endpoint when receiving crafted ActivityPub activities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29281 | In PerfreeBlog version 4.0.11, regular users can exploit the arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the attach component to upload arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29281</link><description>In PerfreeBlog version 4.0.11, regular users can exploit the arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the attach component to upload arbitrary files and execute code within them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28137 | The TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 were found to contain a pre-auth remote command execution vulnerability in the setNoticeCfg funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28137</link><description>The TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 were found to contain a pre-auth remote command execution vulnerability in the setNoticeCfg function through the NoticeUrl parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29280 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 in the website name field of the backend system settings interface a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29280</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in PerfreeBlog v4.0.11 in the website name field of the backend system settings interface allows an attacker to insert and execute arbitrary malicious code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28136 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the downloadFile.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28136</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the downloadFile.cgi.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32944 | PeerTube User Import Authenticated Persistent Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32944</link><description>The vulnerability allows any authenticated user to cause the PeerTube server to stop functioning in a persistent manner.  If user import is enabled (which is the default setting), any registered user can upload an archive for importing. The code uses the yauzl library for reading the archive. If the yauzl library encounters a filename that is considered illegal, it raises an exception that is uncaught by PeerTube, leading to a crash which repeats infinitely on startup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:04:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32945 | PeerTube Arbitrary Playlist Creation via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32945</link><description>The vulnerability allows an existing user to add playlists to a different user’s channel using the PeerTube REST API. The vulnerable code sets the owner of the new playlist to be the user who performed the request, and then sets the associated channel to the channel ID supplied by the request, without checking if it belongs to the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:04:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32946 | PeerTube Arbitrary Playlist Creation via ActivityPub Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32946</link><description>This vulnerability allows any attacker to add playlists to a different user’s channel using the ActivityPub protocol. The vulnerable code sets the owner of the new playlist to be the user who performed the request, and then sets the associated channel to the channel ID supplied by the request, without checking if it belongs to the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3608 | A race condition existed in nsHttpTransaction that could have been exploited to cause memory corruption, potentially leading to an exploitab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3608</link><description>A race condition existed in nsHttpTransaction that could have been exploited to cause memory corruption, potentially leading to an exploitable condition. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 137.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32102 | CrushFTP 9.x and 10.x through 10.8.4 and 11.x through 11.3.1 allows SSRF via the host and port parameters in a command=telnetSocket request ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32102</link><description>CrushFTP 9.x and 10.x through 10.8.4 and 11.x through 11.3.1 allows SSRF via the host and port parameters in a command=telnetSocket request to the /WebInterface/function/ URI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32103 | CrushFTP 9.x and 10.x through 10.8.4 and 11.x through 11.3.1 allows directory traversal via the /WebInterface/function/ URI to read files ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32103</link><description>CrushFTP 9.x and 10.x through 10.8.4 and 11.x through 11.3.1 allows directory traversal via the /WebInterface/function/ URI to read files accessible by SMB at UNC share pathnames, bypassing SecurityManager restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26741 | WordPress Email Notifications for Updates &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26741</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AWEOS GmbH Email Notifications for Updates allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Email Notifications for Updates: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26743 | WordPress Advance WP Query Search Filter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26743</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in TC.K Advance WP Query Search Filter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Advance WP Query Search Filter: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26744 | WordPress JetBlog plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26744</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetBlog allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects JetBlog: from n/a through 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26745 | WordPress RS Elements Elementor Addon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26745</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RSTheme RS Elements Elementor Addon allows Stored XSS. This issue affects RS Elements Elementor Addon: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26889 | WordPress hockeydata LOS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26889</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound hockeydata LOS allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects hockeydata LOS: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26894 | WordPress Coming Soon, Maintenance Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26894</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound Coming Soon, Maintenance Mode allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Coming Soon, Maintenance Mode: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26942 | WordPress JetTricks &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26942</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound JetTricks allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects JetTricks: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26944 | WordPress JetPopup &amp;lt;= 2.0.11 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26944</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound JetPopup allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects JetPopup: from n/a through 2.0.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26954 | WordPress ZooEffect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26954</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 1pluginjquery ZooEffect allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ZooEffect: from n/a through 1.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26955 | WordPress Industrial Lite theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26955</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VW Themes Industrial Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Industrial Lite: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26958 | WordPress JetBlog &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26958</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound JetBlog allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects JetBlog: from n/a through 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26959 | WordPress Administrator Z &amp;lt;= 2025.03.24 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26959</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Quý Lê 91 Administrator Z allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Administrator Z: from n/a through 2025.03.24.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26982 | WordPress DSGVO Youtube plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26982</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Eric-Oliver Mächler DSGVO Youtube allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects DSGVO Youtube: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26990 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1006 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26990</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.7.1006.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30962 | WordPress FS Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30962</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound FS Poster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FS Poster: from n/a through 6.5.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30964 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.5.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30964</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in EPC Photography. This issue affects Photography: from n/a through 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30965 | WordPress WPJobBoard plugin &amp;lt; 5.11.1 - Multiple Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerabilities vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30965</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NotFound WPJobBoard allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WPJobBoard: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30985 | WordPress GNUCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30985</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NotFound GNUCommerce allows Object Injection. This issue affects GNUCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31011 | WordPress SimplyRETS Real Estate IDX plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31011</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ReichertBrothers SimplyRETS Real Estate IDX allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects SimplyRETS Real Estate IDX: from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26992 | WordPress Landing Page Cat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26992</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fatcatapps Landing Page Cat allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Landing Page Cat: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32929 | WordPress Barcode Generator for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32929</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dmitry V. (CEO of "UKR Solution") Barcode Generator for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Barcode Generator for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32943 | PeerTube HLS Video Files Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32943</link><description>The vulnerability allows any authenticated user to leak the contents of arbitrary “.m3u8” files from the PeerTube server due to a path traversal in the HLS endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1688 | System configuration password reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1688</link><description>Milestone Systems has discovered a
security vulnerability in Milestone XProtect installer that resets system
configuration password after the upgrading from older versions using specific
installers.



The system configuration
password is an additional, optional protection that is enabled on the
Management Server.


To mitigate the issue, we highly recommend updating system configuration password via GUI with a standard procedure.



Any system upgraded with
2024 R1 or 2024 R2 release installer is vulnerable to this issue.



Systems upgraded from 2023
R3 or older with version 2025 R1 and newer are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2083 | Logo Carousel Gutenberg Block &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sliderId Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2083</link><description>The Logo Carousel Gutenberg Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘sliderId’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3575 | Insecure Direct Object Reference en Deporsite de T-INNOVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3575</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability in Deporsite from T-INNOVA allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive information from others users via "idUsuario" parameter in "/helper/Familia/establecerUsuarioSeleccion" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3574 | Insecure Direct Object Reference on Deporsite by T-INNOVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3574</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability in Deporsite from T-INNOVA allows an attacker to retrieve sensitive information from others users via "idUsuario" parameter in "/helper/Familia/obtenerFamiliaUsuario" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3579 | Code Injection Vulnerability in AiDex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3579</link><description>In versions prior to Aidex 1.7, an authenticated malicious user, taking advantage of an open registry, could execute unauthorised commands within the system. This includes executing operating system (Unix) commands, interacting with internal services such as PHP or MySQL, and even invoking native functions of the framework used, such as Laravel or Symfony. This execution is achieved by Prompt Injection attacks through the /api//message endpoint, manipulating the content of the ‘content’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45712 | SolarWinds Serv-U Client-Side Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45712</link><description>SolarWinds Serv-U is vulnerable to a client-side cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The vulnerability can only be performed by an authenticated account, on the local machine, from the local browser session. Therefore the risk is very low.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3578 | Adversarial Input Handling Vulnerability in AiDex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3578</link><description>A malicious, authenticated user in Aidex, versions prior to 1.7, could list credentials of other users, create or modify existing users in the application, list credentials of users in production or development environments. In addition, it would be possible to cause bugs that would result in the exfiltration of sensitive information, such as details about the software or internal system paths. These actions could be carried out through the misuse of LLM Prompt (chatbot) technology, via the /api//message endpoint, by manipulating the contents of the ‘content’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13207 | Widget for Social Page Feeds &amp;lt; 6.4.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13207</link><description>The Widget for Social Page Feeds WordPress plugin before 6.4.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13610 | Simple Social Media Share Buttons &amp;lt; 6.0.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13610</link><description>The Simple Social Media Share Buttons  WordPress plugin before 6.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3576 | Krb5: kerberos rc4-hmac-md5 checksum vulnerability enabling message spoofing via md5 collisions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3576</link><description>A vulnerability in the MIT Kerberos implementation allows GSSAPI-protected messages using RC4-HMAC-MD5 to be spoofed due to weaknesses in the MD5 checksum design. If RC4 is preferred over stronger encryption types, an attacker could exploit MD5 collisions to forge message integrity codes. This may lead to unauthorized message tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3622 | Xorbits Inference model.py load deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3622</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Xorbits Inference up to 1.4.1. This issue affects the function load of the file xinference/thirdparty/cosyvoice/cli/model.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2225 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;rael_title_tag&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2225</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘rael_title_tag' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32993 | Vision Helpdesk through 5.7.0 allows Time-Based Blind SQL injection via the Forgot Password (aka index.php?/home/forgot-password) vis_userna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32993</link><description>Vision Helpdesk through 5.7.0 allows Time-Based Blind SQL injection via the Forgot Password (aka index.php?/home/forgot-password) vis_username parameter. Authentication is not needed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3573 | Versions of the package jquery-validation before 1.20.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in the showLabel() function, which may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3573</link><description>Versions of the package jquery-validation before 1.20.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in the showLabel() function, which may take input from a user-controlled placeholder value. This value will populate a message via $.validator.messages in a user localizable dictionary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 05:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29983 | Dell Trusted Device, versions prior to 7.0.3.0, contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability. A l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29983</link><description>Dell Trusted Device, versions prior to 7.0.3.0, contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29984 | Dell Trusted Device, versions prior to 7.0.3.0, contain an Incorrect Default Permissions  vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29984</link><description>Dell Trusted Device, versions prior to 7.0.3.0, contain an Incorrect Default Permissions  vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3612 | Demtec Graphytics HTTP GET Parameter visualization cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3612</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Demtec Graphytics 5.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /visualization of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3613 | Demtec Graphytics visualization cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3613</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Demtec Graphytics 5.0.7 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /visualization. The manipulation of the argument description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32996 | In http-proxy-middleware before 2.0.8 and 3.x before 3.0.4, writeBody can be called twice because "else if" is not used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32996</link><description>In http-proxy-middleware before 2.0.8 and 3.x before 3.0.4, writeBody can be called twice because "else if" is not used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32997 | In http-proxy-middleware before 2.0.9 and 3.x before 3.0.5, fixRequestBody proceeds even if bodyParser has failed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32997</link><description>In http-proxy-middleware before 2.0.9 and 3.x before 3.0.5, fixRequestBody proceeds even if bodyParser has failed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3470 | TS Poll – Survey, Versus Poll, Image Poll, Video Poll &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;s&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3470</link><description>The TS Poll – Survey, Versus Poll, Image Poll, Video Poll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the s parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32987 | Arctera eDiscovery Platform before 10.3.2, when Enterprise Vault Collection Module is used, places a cleartext password on a command line in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32987</link><description>Arctera eDiscovery Platform before 10.3.2, when Enterprise Vault Collection Module is used, places a cleartext password on a command line in EVSearcher.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24797 | Meshtastic incorrectly hands malformed packets leads to controlled buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24797</link><description>Meshtastic is an open source mesh networking solution. A fault in the handling of mesh packets containing invalid protobuf data can result in an attacker-controlled buffer overflow, allowing an attacker to hijack execution flow, potentially resulting in remote code execution. This attack does not require authentication or user interaction, as long as the target device rebroadcasts packets on the default channel. This vulnerability fixed in 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32428 | Jupyter Remote Desktop Proxy makes TigerVNC accessible via the network and not just via a UNIX socket as intended</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32428</link><description>Jupyter Remote Desktop Proxy allows you to run a Linux Desktop on a JupyterHub. jupyter-remote-desktop-proxy was meant to rely on UNIX sockets readable only by the current user since version 3.0.0, but when used with TigerVNC, the VNC server started by jupyter-remote-desktop-proxy were still accessible via the network. This vulnerability does not affect users having TurboVNC as the vncserver executable. This issue is fixed in 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31491 | AutoGPT allows leakage of cross-domain cookies and protected headers in requests redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31491</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents that automate complex workflows. Prior to 0.6.1, AutoGPT allows of leakage of cross-domain cookies and protected headers in requests redirect. AutoGPT uses a wrapper around the requests python library, located in autogpt_platform/backend/backend/util/request.py. In this wrapper, redirects are specifically NOT followed for the first request. If the wrapper is used with allow_redirects set to True (which is the default), any redirect is not followed by the initial request, but rather re-requested by the wrapper using the new location. However, there is a fundamental flaw in manually re-requesting the new location: it does not account for security-sensitive headers which should not be sent cross-origin, such as the Authorization and Proxy-Authorization header, and cookies. For example in autogpt_platform/backend/backend/blocks/github/_api.py, an Authorization header is set when retrieving data from the GitHub API. However, if GitHub suffers from an open redirect vulnerability (such as the made-up example of https://api.github.com/repos/{owner}/{repo}/issues/comments/{comment_id}/../../../../../redirect/?url=https://joshua.hu/), and the script can be coerced into visiting it with the Authorization header, the GitHub credentials in the Authorization header will be leaked. This allows leaking auth headers and private cookies. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31494 | AutoGPT allows cross-user sharing of node execution results through WebSockets API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31494</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents that automate complex workflows. The AutoGPT Platform's WebSocket API transmitted node execution updates to subscribers based on the graph_id+graph_version. Additionally, there was no check prohibiting users from subscribing with another user's graph_id+graph_version. As a result, node execution updates from one user's graph execution could be received by another user within the same instance. This vulnerability does not occur between different instances or between users and non-users of the platform. Single-user instances are not affected. In private instances with a user white-list, the impact is limited by the fact that all potential unintended recipients of these node execution updates must have been admitted by the administrator. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31490 | AutoGPT allows SSRF due to DNS Rebinding in requests wrapper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31490</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents that automate complex workflows. Prior to 0.6.1, AutoGPT allows SSRF due to DNS Rebinding in requests wrapper. AutoGPT is built with a wrapper around Python's requests library, hardening the application against SSRF. The code for this wrapper can be found in autogpt_platform/backend/backend/util/request.py. The requested hostname of a URL which is being requested is validated, ensuring that it does not resolve to any local ipv4 or ipv6 addresses. However, this check is not sufficient, as a DNS server may initially respond with a non-blocked address, with a TTL of 0. This means that the initial resolution would appear as a non-blocked address. In this case, validate_url() will return the url as successful. After validate_url() has successfully returned the url, the url is then passed to the real request() function. When the real request() function is called with the validated url, request() will once again resolve the address of the hostname, because the record will not have been cached (due to TTL 0). This resolution may be in the "invalid range". This type of attack is called a "DNS Rebinding Attack". This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3593 | ZHENFENG13/code-projects My-Blog-layui authorImg upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3593</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZHENFENG13/code-projects My-Blog-layui 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function Upload of the file /admin/upload/authorImg/. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 22:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3591 | ZHENFENG13/code-projects My-Blog-layui edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3591</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZHENFENG13/code-projects My-Blog-layui 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/v1/blog/edit. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3592 | ZHENFENG13/code-projects My-Blog-layui edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3592</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZHENFENG13/code-projects My-Blog-layui 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/v1/link/edit. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3590 | Adianti Framework deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3590</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Adianti Framework up to 8.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 8.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 21:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3589 | SourceCodester Music Class Enrollment System manage_class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3589</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Music Class Enrollment System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_class.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 21:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43840 | IBM Aspera Console XPath injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43840</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4

is vulnerable to an XPath injection vulnerability, which could allow an authenticated attacker to exfiltrate sensitive application data and/or determine the structure of the XML document.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43850 | IBM Aspera Console cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43850</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4

is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43851 | IBM Aspera Console information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43851</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4

uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27272 | IBM Aspera Console weak password requirements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27272</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4 allows passwords to be reused when a new user logs into the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43852 | IBM Aspera Console information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43852</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4 could disclose sensitive information in HTTP headers that could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3588 | joelittlejohn jsonschema2pojo JSON File SchemaRule.java apply stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3588</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in joelittlejohn jsonschema2pojo 1.2.2. This issue affects the function apply of the file org/jsonschema2pojo/rules/SchemaRule.java of the component JSON File Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43847 | IBM Aspera Console information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43847</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to set the HTTPOnly flag. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information from the cookie.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3587 | ZeroWdd/code-projects studentmanager getTeacherList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3587</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ZeroWdd/code-projects studentmanager 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /getTeacherList. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1782 | Unsanitized input in language form field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1782</link><description>In HylaFAX Enterprise Web Interface and AvantFAX, the language form element is not properly sanitized 
before being used and can be misused to include an arbitrary file in the
 PHP code allowing an attacker to do anything as the web server user. 
This flaw requires the attacker to be authenticated with a valid user account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3585 | westboy CicadasCMS JSP Parser upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3585</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /upload/ of the component JSP Parser. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29720 | Dify v1.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component controllers.console.remote_files.RemoteFileUpload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29720</link><description>Dify v1.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component controllers.console.remote_files.RemoteFileUploadApi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3277 | An integer overflow can be triggered in SQLite’s `concat_ws()` function. The resulting, truncated integer is then used to allocate a buffer....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3277</link><description>An integer overflow can be triggered in SQLite’s `concat_ws()` function. The resulting, truncated integer is then used to allocate a buffer. When SQLite then writes the resulting string to the buffer, it uses the original, untruncated size and thus a wild Heap Buffer overflow of size ~4GB can be triggered. This can result in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2572 | WhatsUp Gold NmConfigurationManager.exe database manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2572</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.3, a 

database manipulation 

vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to modify the contents of WhatsUp.dbo.WrlsMacAddressGroup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32931 | DevDojo Voyager 1.4.0 through 1.8.0, when Laravel 8 or later is used, allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32931</link><description>DevDojo Voyager 1.4.0 through 1.8.0, when Laravel 8 or later is used, allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands via a specific php artisan command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22371 | SQL-injection in admin_login_handler allows unauthenticated user to log in as an administrator in SicommNet BASEC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22371</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SicommNet BASEC (SaaS Service) login page allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to Bypass Authentication and execute arbitrary SQL commands. This issue at least affects BASEC for the date of 14 Dec 2021 onwards. It is very likely that this vulnerability has been present in the solution before that.

As of the date of this CVE record, there has been no patch</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22372 | Insecure password storage in SicommNet BASEC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22372</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in SicommNet BASEC on SaaS allows Password Recovery.
Passwords are either stored in plain text using reversible encryption, allowing an attacker with sufficient privileges to extract plain text passwords easily.

This issue affects BASEC: from 14 Dec 2021.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22373 | XSS, HTML and Style injection on login page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22373</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SicommNet BASEC on SaaS allows Reflected XSS, XSS Through HTTP Query Strings, Rendering of Arbitrary HTML and alternation of CSS Styles
This issue affects BASEC: from 14 Dec 2021.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3571 | Fannuo Enterprise Content Management System 凡诺企业网站管理系统 cms_chip.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3571</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fannuo Enterprise Content Management System 凡诺企业网站管理系统 1.1/4.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/cms_chip.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49825 | IBM Robotic Process Automation session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49825</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation and Robotic Process Automation for Cloud Pak 21.0.0 through 21.0.7.20 and 23.0.0 through 23.0.20 does not invalidate session after a logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2424 | Leaked Metadata of Deleted Files via Bookmark Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2424</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.9 fail to check if a file has been deleted when creating a bookmark which allows an attacker who knows the IDs of deleted files to obtain metadata of the files via bookmark creation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2475 | Unauthorized Bot Login Using Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2475</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.1, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.9 fail to invalidate the cache when a user account is converted to a bot which allows an attacker to login to the bot exactly one time via normal credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32912 | Libsoup: null pointer dereference in client when server  omits the &amp;quot;nonce&amp;quot; parameter in an unauthorized response with digest  authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32912</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, where SoupAuthDigest is vulnerable to a NULL pointer dereference. The HTTP server may cause the libsoup client to crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32914 | Libsoup: oob read on libsoup through function  &amp;quot;soup_multipart_new_from_message&amp;quot; in soup-multipart.c leads to crash or  exit of process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32914</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, where the soup_multipart_new_from_message() function is vulnerable to an out-of-bounds read. This flaw allows a malicious HTTP client to induce the libsoup server to read out of bounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32909 | Libsoup: null pointer dereference on libsoup through  function &amp;quot;sniff_mp4&amp;quot; in soup-content-sniffer.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32909</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. SoupContentSniffer may be vulnerable to a NULL pointer dereference in the sniff_mp4 function. The HTTP server may cause the libsoup client to crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32910 | Libsoup: null pointer deference on libsoup via  /auth/soup-auth-digest.c through &amp;quot;soup_auth_digest_authenticate&amp;quot; on  client when server omits the &amp;quot;realm&amp;quot; parameter in an unauthorized  response with digest authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32910</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, where soup_auth_digest_authenticate() is vulnerable to a NULL pointer dereference. This issue may cause the libsoup client to crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32930 | ** RESERVED ** 94list 5831c82 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in delete_bd_user().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32930</link><description>** RESERVED ** 94list 5831c82 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in delete_bd_user().</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3570 | JamesZBL/code-projects db-hospital-drug ContentController.java save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JamesZBL/code-projects db-hospital-drug 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function Save of the file ContentController.java. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2160 | Pega Platform versions 8.4.3 to Infinity 24.2.1 are affected by an XSS issue with Mashup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2160</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.4.3 to Infinity 24.2.1 are affected by an XSS issue with Mashup</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2161 | Pega Platform versions 7.2.1 to Infinity 24.2.1 are affected by an XSS issue with Mashup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2161</link><description>Pega Platform versions 7.2.1 to Infinity 24.2.1 are affected by an XSS issue with Mashup</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32906 | Libsoup: out of bounds reads in soup_headers_parse_request()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32906</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, where the soup_headers_parse_request() function may be vulnerable to an out-of-bound read. This flaw allows a malicious user to use a specially crafted HTTP request to crash the HTTP server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32907 | Libsoup: denial of service in server when client requests a large amount of  overlapping ranges with range header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32907</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. The implementation of HTTP range requests is vulnerable to a resource consumption attack. This flaw allows a malicious client to request the same range many times in a single HTTP request, causing the server to use large amounts of memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32908 | Libsoup: denial of service on libsoup through http/2 server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32908</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. The HTTP/2 server in libsoup may not fully validate the values of pseudo-headers :scheme, :authority, and :path, which may allow a user to cause a denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3569 | JamesZBL/code-projects db-hospital-drug ShiroConfig.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3569</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JamesZBL/code-projects db-hospital-drug 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ShiroConfig.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:10:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32913 | Libsoup: null pointer dereference in  soup_message_headers_get_content_disposition when &amp;quot;filename&amp;quot; parameter  is present, but has no value in content-disposition header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32913</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup, where the soup_message_headers_get_content_disposition() function is vulnerable to a NULL pointer dereference. This flaw allows a malicious HTTP peer to crash a libsoup client or server that uses this function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3568 | Webkul Krayin CRM SVG File edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3568</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Webkul Krayin CRM up to 2.1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/settings/users/edit/ of the component SVG File Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor prepares a fix for the next major release and explains that he does not think therefore that this should qualify for a CVE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3567 | veal98 小牛肉 Echo 开源社区系统 Ticket LoginTicketInterceptor.java preHandle improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3567</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in veal98 小牛肉 Echo 开源社区系统 4.2. Affected is the function preHandle of the file src/main/java/com/greate/community/controller/interceptor/LoginTicketInterceptor.java of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3566 | veal98 小牛肉 Echo 开源社区系统 uploadMdPic unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3566</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in veal98 小牛肉 Echo 开源社区系统 4.2. This issue affects the function uploadMdPic of the file /discuss/uploadMdPic. The manipulation of the argument editormd-image-file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10087 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10087</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might craft a link containing a malicious script, which then gets directly embedded in references to other resources, what causes the script to run in user's context multiple times. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10088 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10088</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into filling a login form with a malicious script, what causes the script to run in user's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10089 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10089</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Stored XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into filling a form designed for changing user's data with a malicious script, what causes the script to run in user's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10090 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10090</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into filling a form designed for adding users with a malicious script, what causes the script to run in user's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13597 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13597</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into filling a form sent to login panel at /softcom/ with a malicious script, what causes the script to run in user's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13598 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13598</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is  vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. Using a functionality of creating new form fields one creates new parameters vulnerable to XSS attacks. A user tricked into filling such a form with a malicious script will run the code in their's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49705 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49705</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to client-side Denial of Servise (DoS) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into using an URL with a d parameter set to an unhandled value. All the subsequent requests will not be accepted as the server returns an error message. Since this parameter is sent as part of a session cookie, the issue persists until the session expires or the user deletes cookies manually. 
Similar effect might be achieved when a user tries to change platform language to an unimplemented one.
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49706 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49706</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Open Redirect attacks by including base64 encoded URLs in the target parameter sent in a POST request to one of the endpoints.
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49707 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49707</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Reflected XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into filling a form designed for resetting user's password with a malicious script, what causes the script to run in user's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49708 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49708</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, is vulnerable to Stored XSS (Cross-site Scripting) attacks. An attacker might trick a user into filling a form designed for setting delivery address with a malicious script, what causes the script to run in user's context. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49709 | XSS in iKSORIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49709</link><description>Internet Starter, one of SoftCOM iKSORIS system modules, allows for setting an arbitrary session cookie value. An attacker with an access to user's browser might set such a cookie, wait until the user logs in and then use the same cookie to take over the account. 
Moreover, the system does not destroy the old sessions when creating new ones, what expands the time frame in which an attack might be performed. 
This vulnerability has been patched in version 79.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3565 | huanfenz/code-projects StudentManager Announcement Management Section uploadArticle.do unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3565</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in huanfenz/code-projects StudentManager 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /upload/uploadArticle.do of the component Announcement Management Section. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3564 | huanfenz/code-projects StudentManager Teacher String improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3564</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in huanfenz/code-projects StudentManager up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Teacher String Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27009 | WordPress My auctions allegro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27009</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wphocus My auctions allegro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects My auctions allegro: from n/a through 3.6.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3563 | WuzhiCMS Setting index.php set code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3563</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WuzhiCMS 4.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function Set of the file /index.php?m=attachment&amp;amp;f=index&amp;_su=wuzhicms&amp;amp;v=set&amp;amp;submit=1 of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument Setting leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3562 | Yonyou YonBIP userfile FileInputStream path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yonyou YonBIP MA2.7. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function FileInputStream of the file /mobsm/common/userfile. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3561 | ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3561</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall 1.0.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3560 | ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall product cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3560</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall 1.0.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /product. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 09:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3559 | ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall 20 ForeProductListController sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3559</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall 1.0.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function ForeProductListController of the file /mall/product/0/20. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 09:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3558 | ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall uploadUserHeadImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3558</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ghostxbh uzy-ssm-mall 1.0.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /mall/user/uploadUserHeadImage. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24859 | Apache Roller: Insufficient Session Expiration on Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24859</link><description>A session management vulnerability exists in Apache Roller before version 6.1.5 where active user sessions are not properly invalidated after password changes. When a user's password is changed, either by the user themselves or by an administrator, existing sessions remain active and usable. This allows continued access to the application through old sessions even after password changes, potentially enabling unauthorized access if credentials were compromised.

This issue affects Apache Roller versions up to and including 6.1.4.

The vulnerability is fixed in Apache Roller 6.1.5 by implementing centralized session management that properly invalidates all active sessions when passwords are changed or users are disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 08:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3557 | ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3557</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP 3.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 08:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31344 | The giflib open-source component has a buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31344</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in openEuler giflib on Linux. This vulnerability is associated with program files gif2rgb.C.

This issue affects giflib: through 5.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 07:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3556 | ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP login.php excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3556</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP 3.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 07:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32093 | Syatem admin profile modification by delegated granular administration role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32093</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.1, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.9 fail to restrict certain operations on system admins to only other system admins, which allows delegated granular administration users with the "Edit Other Users" permission to perform unauthorized modifications to system administrators via improper permission validation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 07:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3555 | ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP login.php excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3555</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP 3.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 07:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30516 | Unauthorized Notification Exposure in Mobile App Under Specific Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30516</link><description>Mattermost Mobile Apps versions &lt;=2.25.0  fail to terminate sessions during logout under certain conditions (e.g. poor connectivity), allowing unauthorized users on shared devices to access sensitive notification content via continued mobile notifications</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 07:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3554 | phpshe api.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3554</link><description>A vulnerability was found in phpshe 1.8. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file api.php?mod=cron&amp;amp;act=buyer. The manipulation of the argument act leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 06:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9230 | PowerPress Podcasting &amp;lt; 11.9.18 - Author+ XSS via Podcast URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9230</link><description>The PowerPress Podcasting plugin by Blubrry WordPress plugin before 11.9.18 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings when adding a podcast, which could allow author and above users to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 06:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2563 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt; 4.1.2- Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2563</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership  WordPress plugin before 4.1.2 does not prevent users to set their account role when the Membership Addon is enabled, leading to a privilege escalation issue and allowing unauthenticated users to gain admin privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 06:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3553 | phpshe admin.php pe_delete sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3553</link><description>A vulnerability was found in phpshe 1.8. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function pe_delete of the file /admin.php?mod=brand&amp;amp;act=del. The manipulation of the argument brand_id[] leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 06:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3552 | Lingxing ERP UploadAjax.ashx unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3552</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Lingxing ERP 2. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /Api/TinyMce/UploadAjax.ashx. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 05:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3551 | Lingxing ERP FileUpload.ashx DoUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3551</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Lingxing ERP 2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function DoUpload of the file /Api/FileUpload.ashx?method=DoUpload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3550 | wowjoy 浙江湖州华卓信息科技有限公司 Internet Doctor Workstation System detail improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3550</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wowjoy 浙江湖州华卓信息科技有限公司 Internet Doctor Workstation System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /v1/pushConfig/detail/. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 03:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3549 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp File MD3Loader.cpp ValidateSurfaceHeaderOffsets heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3549</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. Affected is the function Assimp::MD3Importer::ValidateSurfaceHeaderOffsets of the file code/AssetLib/MD3/MD3Loader.cpp of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 03:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3548 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp File types.h Set heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3548</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp up to 5.4.3. This issue affects the function aiString::Set in the library include/assimp/types.h of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 02:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3547 | frdel Agent-Zero get_work_dir_files path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3547</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in frdel Agent-Zero 0.8.1.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /get_work_dir_files. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 02:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3572 | INTUMIT SmartRobot - Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3572</link><description>SmartRobot from INTUMIT has a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to probe internal network and even access arbitrary local files on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 02:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3545 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request setLanguage FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3545</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon of the file /api/wizard/setLanguage of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack needs to be approached within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 02:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3546 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getLanguage FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3546</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon of the file /api/wizard/getLanguage of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 02:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3543 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request setsyncpppoecfg FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3543</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/setsyncpppoecfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3544 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getCapabilityWeb FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3544</link><description>A vulnerability was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon of the file /api/wizard/getCapabilityWeb of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3542 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request getsyncpppoecfg FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3542</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014. This affects the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/getsyncpppoecfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3541 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request getSpecs FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3541</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014. Affected by this issue is the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/getSpecs of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3540 | H3C Magic NX15/Magic NX30 Pro/Magic NX400/Magic R3010 HTTP POST Request getCapability FCGI_WizardProtoProcess command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3540</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400 and Magic R3010 up to V100R014. Affected by this vulnerability is the function FCGI_WizardProtoProcess of the file /api/wizard/getCapability of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 22:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3445 | A Path Traversal "Zip Slip" vulnerability has been identified in mholt/archiver in Go. This vulnerability allows using a crafted ZIP file co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3445</link><description>A Path Traversal "Zip Slip" vulnerability has been identified in mholt/archiver in Go. This vulnerability allows using a crafted ZIP file containing path traversal symlinks to create or overwrite files with the user's privileges or application utilizing the library.

When using the archiver.Unarchive functionality with ZIP files, like this: archiver.Unarchive(zipFile, outputDir),  A crafted ZIP file can be extracted in such a way that it writes files to the affected system with the same privileges as the application executing this vulnerable functionality. Consequently, sensitive files may be overwritten, potentially leading to privilege escalation, code execution, and other severe outcomes in some cases.

It's worth noting that a similar vulnerability was found in TAR files (CVE-2024-0406). Although a fix was implemented, it hasn't been officially released, and the affected project has since been deprecated. The successor to mholt/archiver is a new project called mholt/archives, and its initial release (v0.1.0) removes the Unarchive() functionality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 22:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3539 | H3C Magic BE18000 HTTP POST Request getBasicInfo FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3539</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in H3C Magic NX15, Magic NX30 Pro, Magic NX400, Magic R3010 and Magic BE18000 up to V100R014. Affected is the function FCGI_CheckStringIfContainsSemicolon of the file /api/wizard/getBasicInfo of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 22:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3538 | D-Link DI-8100 jhttpd auth.asp auth_asp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3538</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function auth_asp of the file /auth.asp of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument callback leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 18:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56406 | Perl 5.34, 5.36, 5.38 and 5.40 are vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow when transliterating non-ASCII bytes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56406</link><description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Perl. 

When there are non-ASCII bytes in the left-hand-side of the `tr` operator, `S_do_trans_invmap` can overflow the destination pointer `d`.

   $ perl -e '$_ = "\x{FF}" x 1000000; tr/\xFF/\x{100}/;' 
   Segmentation fault (core dumped)

It is believed that this vulnerability can enable Denial of Service and possibly Code Execution attacks on platforms that lack sufficient defenses.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3423 | IBM Aspera Faspex 5 cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3423</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.11 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3537 | Tutorials-Website Employee Management System update-user.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3537</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tutorials-Website Employee Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update-user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3536 | Tutorials-Website Employee Management System delete-user.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3536</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tutorials-Website Employee Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete-user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 11:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3535 | shuanx BurpAPIFinder BurpApiFinder.db denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3535</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in shuanx BurpAPIFinder up to 2.0.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file BurpApiFinder.db. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 11:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3534 | PowerCreator CMS OpenPublicCourse.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3534</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PowerCreator CMS 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /OpenPublicCourse.aspx. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3533 | YouDianCMS index.html.Attackers cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3533</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in YouDianCMS 9.5.21. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /App/Tpl/Admin/Default/Channel/index.html.Attackers. The manipulation of the argument Parent leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 10:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3532 | YouDianCMS index.html.Attackers cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3532</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in YouDianCMS 9.5.21. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /App/Tpl/Member/Default/Order/index.html.Attackers. The manipulation of the argument OrderNumber leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 06:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3531 | YouDianCMS index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3531</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in YouDianCMS 9.5.21. This affects an unknown part of the file /App/Tpl/Admin/Default/Log/index.html. The manipulation of the argument UserName/LogType leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 05:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>