<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:16:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-2145 | cym1102 nginxWebUI Web Management check cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2145</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 4.3.7. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /adminPage/conf/check of the component Web Management Interface. Such manipulation of the argument nginxDir leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2143 | D-Link DIR-823X DDNS Service set_ddns os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2143</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/set_ddns of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation of the argument ddnsType/ddnsDomainName/ddnsUserName/ddnsPwd leads to os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2142 | D-Link DIR-823X set_qos sub_420688 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2142</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420688 of the file /goform/set_qos. Executing a manipulation can lead to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2141 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM URL PermissionServiceImpl.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2141</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM up to 11.3.3. This affects an unknown part of the file gateway/src/main/java/com/kakarote/gateway/service/impl/PermissionServiceImpl.java of the component URL Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2140 | Tenda TX9 setMacFilterCfg sub_4223E0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2140</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4223E0 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg. Such manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2139 | Tenda TX9 fast_setting_wifi_set sub_432580 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2139</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_432580 of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2138 | Tenda TX9 SetStaticRouteCfg sub_42D03C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected is the function sub_42D03C of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2137 | Tenda TX3 SetIpMacBind buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda TX3 up to 16.03.13.11_multi. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2136 | projectworlds Online Food Ordering System view-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2136</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectworlds Online Food Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /view-ticket.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2134 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-doctors.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /hms/admin/manage-doctors.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2135 | UTT HiPER 810 formPdbUpConfig sub_43F020 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_43F020 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument policyNames results in command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2132 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2132</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument txtcat results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2133 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2133</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. This manipulation of the argument txtimage causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2130 | BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret search_username index.ts command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2130</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret up to 1.0.12. This affects an unknown part of the file src/index.ts of the component search_username. Executing a manipulation of the argument Username can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.13 is able to mitigate this issue. This patch is called b1ae073c4b3e789ab8de36dc6ca8111ae9399e7a. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2131 | XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server input_text os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2131</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server 0.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function input_text. The manipulation of the argument text leads to os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15027 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15027</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15100 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via jay_panel_ajax_update_profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15100</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_panel_ajax_update_profile' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2129 | D-Link DIR-823X set_ac_status os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/set_ac_status. Performing a manipulation of the argument ac_ipaddr/ac_ipstatus/ap_randtime results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2205 | WeKan Meteor Publication cards.js CardPubSubBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2205</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This affects an unknown part of the file server/publications/cards.js of the component Meteor Publication Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to mitigate this issue. The name of the patch is 0f5a9c38778ca550cbab6c5093470e1e90cb837f. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2206 | WeKan Administrative Repair fixDuplicateLists.js FixDuplicateBleed access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2206</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WeKan up to 8.20. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file server/methods/fixDuplicateLists.js of the component Administrative Repair Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to resolve this issue. The patch is named 4ce181d17249778094f73d21515f7f863f554743. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2207 | WeKan Activity Publication activities.js LinkedBoardActivitiesBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2207</link><description>A weakness has been identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file server/publications/activities.js of the component Activity Publication Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is capable of addressing this issue. This patch is called 91a936e07d2976d4246dfe834281c3aaa87f9503. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2208 | WeKan Rules rules.js RulesBleed authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2208</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in WeKan up to 8.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file server/publications/rules.js of the component Rules Handler. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is recommended to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is a787bcddf33ca28afb13ff5ea9a4cb92dceac005. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2209 | WeKan Custom Translation translationBody.js setCreateTranslation improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2209</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in WeKan up to 8.18. The affected element is the function setCreateTranslation of the file client/components/settings/translationBody.js of the component Custom Translation Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 8.19 is sufficient to fix this issue. The patch is identified as f244a43771f6ebf40218b83b9f46dba6b940d7de. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2120 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration Parameter set_server_settings os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2120</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/set_server_settings of the component Configuration Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument terminal_addr/server_ip/server_port leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2122 | Xiaopi Panel WAF Firewall demo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2122</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Xiaopi Panel up to 20260126. This impacts an unknown function of the file /demo.php of the component WAF Firewall. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2118 | UTT HiPER 810 rehttpd formReleaseConnect sub_4407D4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2118</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_4407D4 of the file /goform/formReleaseConnect of the component rehttpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument Isp_Name can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2117 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_activity.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument activity_id results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:02:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2116 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_expenses.php. Such manipulation of the argument expenses_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 23:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2115 | itsourcecode Society Management System delete_expenses.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2115</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete_expenses.php. This manipulation of the argument expenses_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25859 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.20 Migration Functionality Insufficient Permission Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25859</link><description>Wekan versions prior to 8.20 allow non-administrative users to access migration functionality due to insufficient permission checks, potentially resulting in unauthorized migration operations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2114 | itsourcecode Society Management System edit_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2114</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Society Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25560 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 LDAP Authentication Filter Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25560</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an LDAP filter injection vulnerability in LDAP authentication. User-supplied username input is incorporated into LDAP search filters and DN-related values without adequate escaping, allowing an attacker to manipulate LDAP queries during authentication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25561 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Attachment Upload Object Relationship Validation Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25561</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization weakness in the attachment upload API. The API does not fully validate that provided identifiers (such as boardId, cardId, swimlaneId, and listId) are consistent and refer to a coherent card/board relationship, enabling attempts to upload attachments with mismatched object relationships.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25562 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Attachments Publication Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25562</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an information disclosure vulnerability in the attachments publication. Attachment metadata can be returned without properly scoping results to boards and cards accessible to the requesting user, potentially exposing attachment metadata to unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25563 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Checklist Creation Cross-Board IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25563</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in checklist creation and related checklist routes. The implementation does not verify that the supplied cardId belongs to the supplied boardId, allowing cross-board ID tampering by manipulating identifiers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25564 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Checklist Deletion IDOR via Missing Relationship Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25564</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in checklist creation and related checklist routes. The implementation does not verify that the supplied cardId belongs to the supplied boardId, allowing cross-board ID tampering by manipulating identifiers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25565 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Read-only Board Roles Can Update Cards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25565</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization vulnerability where certain card update API paths validate only board read access rather than requiring write permission. This can allow users with read-only roles to perform card updates that should require write access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25566 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Cross-board Card Move Without Destination Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25566</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization vulnerability in card move logic. A user can specify a destination board/list/swimlane without adequate authorization checks for the destination and without validating that destination objects belong to the destination board, potentially enabling unauthorized cross-board moves.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25567 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 Card Comment Author Spoofing via User-controlled authorId</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25567</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in the card comment creation API. The endpoint accepts an authorId from the request body, allowing an authenticated user to spoof the recorded comment author by supplying another user's identifier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25568 | WeKan &amp;lt; 8.19 allowPrivateOnly Setting Enforcement Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25568</link><description>WeKan versions prior to 8.19 contain an authorization logic vulnerability where the instance configuration setting allowPrivateOnly is not sufficiently enforced at board creation time. When allowPrivateOnly is enabled, users can still create public boards due to incomplete server-side enforcement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25857 | Tenda G300-F Command Injection via formSetWanDiag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25857</link><description>Tenda G300-F router firmware versio 16.01.14.2 and prior contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the WAN diagnostic functionality (formSetWanDiag). The implementation constructs a shell command that invokes curl and incorporates attacker-controlled input into the command line without adequate neutralization. As a result, a remote attacker with access to the affected management interface can inject additional shell syntax and execute arbitrary commands on the device with the privileges of the management process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25858 | macrozheng mall &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 Unauthenticated Password Reset via OTP Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25858</link><description>macrozheng mall version 1.0.3 and prior contains an authentication vulnerability in the mall-portal password reset workflow that allows an unauthenticated attacker to reset arbitrary user account passwords using only a victimâ€™s telephone number. The password reset flow exposes the one-time password (OTP) directly in the API response and validates password reset requests solely by comparing the provided OTP to a value stored by telephone number, without verifying user identity or ownership of the telephone number. This enables remote account takeover of any user with a known or guessable telephone number.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15564 | Mapnik value.cpp operator divide by zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15564</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Mapnik up to 4.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function mapnik::detail::mod&lt;...&gt;::operator of the file src/value.cpp. The manipulation leads to divide by zero. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2113 | yuan1994 tpadmin WebUploader preview.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2113</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yuan1994 tpadmin up to 1.3.12. This affects an unknown part in the library /public/static/admin/lib/webuploader/0.1.5/server/preview.php of the component WebUploader. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2111 | JeecgBoot Retrieval-Augmented Generation edit path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2111</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /airag/knowledge/doc/edit of the component Retrieval-Augmented Generation Module. Executing a manipulation of the argument filePath can lead to path traversal. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2110 | Tasin1025 SwiftBuy login.php excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2110</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tasin1025 SwiftBuy up to 0f5011372e8d1d7edfd642d57d721c9fadc54ec7. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. Performing a manipulation results in improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2109 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Delete Category undo improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2109</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in jsbroks COCO Annotator up to 0.11.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/undo/ of the component Delete Category Handler. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2108 | jsbroks COCO Annotator Endpoint long_task denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2108</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jsbroks COCO Annotator up to 0.11.1. This impacts an unknown function of the file /api/info/long_task of the component Endpoint. This manipulation causes denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2107 | yeqifu warehouse Log Info LoginfoController.java batchDeleteLoginfo improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function loadAllLoginfo/deleteLoginfo/batchDeleteLoginfo of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\LoginfoController.java of the component Log Info Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2106 | yeqifu warehouse Notice Management NoticeController.java batchDeleteNotice improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. The impacted element is the function addNotice/updateNotice/deleteNotice/batchDeleteNotice of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\NoticeController.java of the component Notice Management. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2105 | yeqifu warehouse Department Management DeptController.java deleteDept improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2105</link><description>A flaw has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. The affected element is the function addDept/updateDept/deleteDept of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\DeptController.java of the component Department Management. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2090 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2090</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/message/search.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument term can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2089 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2089</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/subject/controller.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2088 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System accepted-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2088</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/accepted-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument delid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2087 | SourceCodester Online Class Record System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2087</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Online Class Record System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. This manipulation of the argument user_email causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2086 | UTT HiPER 810G Management formFireWall strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2086</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formFireWall of the component Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument GroupName results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2085 | D-Link DWR-M921 USSD Configuration Endpoint formUSSDSetup sub_419F20 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2085</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. Affected is the function sub_419F20 of the file /boafrm/formUSSDSetup of the component USSD Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ussdValue leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2084 | D-Link DIR-823X set_language os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2084</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/set_language. Executing a manipulation of the argument langSelection can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 11:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2083 | code-projects Social Networking Site delete_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2083</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Social Networking Site 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /delete_post.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2082 | D-Link DIR-823X set_mac_clone os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2082</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_mac_clone. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2081 | D-Link DIR-823X set_password os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2081</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_password. This manipulation of the argument http_passwd causes os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2080 | UTT HiPER 810 formUser setSysAdm command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2080</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. This issue affects the function setSysAdm of the file /goform/formUser. The manipulation of the argument passwd1 leads to command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15476 | The Bucketlister &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Bucket List Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15476</link><description>The The Bucketlister plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the bucketlister_do_admin_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add delete or modify arbitrary bucket list items.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15477 | The Bucketlister &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via `category` and `id` Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15477</link><description>The Bucketlister plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode `category` and `id` attributes in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameters and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0555 | Premmerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;premmerce_wizard_actions&amp;#x27; AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0555</link><description>The Premmerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'premmerce_wizard_actions' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.20. This is due to missing capability checks and insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the `state` parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page (the Premmerce Wizard admin page).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1082 | TITLE ANIMATOR &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1082</link><description>The TITLE ANIMATOR plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings page form handler in `inc/settings-page.php`. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1570 | Simple Bible Verse via Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1570</link><description>The Simple Bible Verse via Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `verse` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1573 | OMIGO &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1573</link><description>The OMIGO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `omigo_donate_button` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1608 | Video Onclick &amp;lt;= 0.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1608</link><description>The Video Onclick plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `youtube` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1611 | Wikiloops Track Player &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1611</link><description>The Wikiloops Track Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `wikiloops` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1613 | Wonka Slide &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1613</link><description>The Wonka Slide plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `list_class` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1634 | Subitem AL Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1634</link><description>The Subitem AL Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1643 | MP-Ukagaka &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1643</link><description>The MP-Ukagaka plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1675 | Advanced Country Blocker &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Unauthenticated Authorization Bypass via Insecure Default Secret Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1675</link><description>The Advanced Country Blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authorization Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to the use of a predictable default value for the secret bypass key created during installation without requiring users to change it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the geolocation blocking mechanism by appending the key to any URL on sites where the administrator has not changed the default value.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2079 | yeqifu warehouse Menu Management MenuController.java deleteMenu improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2079</link><description>A flaw has been found in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This vulnerability affects the function addMenu/updateMenu/deleteMenu of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\MenuController.java of the component Menu Management. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2078 | yeqifu warehouse Permission Management PermissionController.java deletePermission improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2078</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. This affects the function addPermission/updatePermission/deletePermission of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\PermissionController.java of the component Permission Management. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 08:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2077 | yeqifu warehouse Role Management RoleController.java deleteRole improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2077</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected by this issue is the function addRole/updateRole/deleteRole of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\RoleController.java of the component Role Management Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2076 | yeqifu warehouse User Management Endpoint UserController.java deleteUser improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2076</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function addUser/updateUser/deleteUser of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\UserController.java of the component User Management Endpoint. This manipulation causes improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 07:06:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15491 | Post Slides &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Contributor+ Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15491</link><description>The Post Slides WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not validate some shortcode attributes before using them to generate paths passed to include function/s, allowing any authenticated users such as with contributor or higher roles to perform LFI attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12159 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.4.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12159</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_raw_content shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12803 | Bold Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_tabs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12803</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin 'bt_bb_tabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13463 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting in Post Grid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13463</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Grid component in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15267 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_accordion_item Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15267</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_accordion_item shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2075 | yeqifu warehouse Role-Permission Binding RoleController.java saveRolePermission access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2075</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yeqifu warehouse up to aaf29962ba407d22d991781de28796ee7b4670e4. Affected is the function saveRolePermission of the file dataset\repos\warehouse\src\main\java\com\yeqifu\sys\controller\RoleController.java of the component Role-Permission Binding Handler. The manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2074 | O2OA HTTP POST Request check xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2074</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in O2OA up to 9.0.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /x_program_center/jaxrs/mpweixin/check of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31990 | HCL DevOps Velocity is susceptible to a Denial of Service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31990</link><description>Rate limiting for certain API calls is not being enforced, making HCL Velocity vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) attacks.  An attacker could flood the system with a large number of requests, overwhelming its resources and causing it to become unresponsive to legitimate users.  This vulnerability is fixed in 5.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2073 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2073</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/user/index.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2071 | UTT è¿›å– 520W formP2PLimitConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2071</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT è¿›å– 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formP2PLimitConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument except results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37079 | Wing FTP Server &amp;lt; 6.2.7 - Cross-site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37079</link><description>Wing FTP Server versions prior to 6.2.7 contain a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the web administration interface that allows attackers to delete admin users. Attackers can craft a malicious HTML page with a hidden form to submit a request that deletes the administrative user account without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37095 | Cyberoam Authentication Client 2.1.2.7 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37095</link><description>Cyberoam Authentication Client 2.1.2.7 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting Structured Exception Handler (SEH) memory. Attackers can craft a malicious input in the 'Cyberoam Server Address' field to trigger a bind TCP shell on port 1337 with system-level access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37106 | Business Live Chat Software 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (Add Admin)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37106</link><description>Business Live Chat Software 1.0 contains a cross-site request forgery vulnerability that allows attackers to change user account roles without authentication. Attackers can craft a malicious HTML form to modify user privileges by submitting a POST request to the user creation endpoint with administrative access parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37107 | Core FTP LE 2.2 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37107</link><description>Core FTP LE 2.2 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overwriting the account field with a large buffer. Attackers can create a text file with 20,000 repeated characters and paste it into the account field to cause the application to become unresponsive and require reinstallation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37109 | aSc TimeTables 2020.11.4 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37109</link><description>aSc TimeTables 2020.11.4 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overwriting the Subject title field with a large buffer. Attackers can generate a 1000-character buffer and paste it into the Subject title to trigger an application crash and potential instability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37122 | SpotFTP-FTP Password Recover 2.4.8 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37122</link><description>SpotFTP-FTP Password Recover 2.4.8 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by generating a large buffer overflow. Attackers can create a text file with 1000 'Z' characters and input it as a registration code to trigger the application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37135 | AMSS++ 4.7 - Backdoor Admin Account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37135</link><description>AMSS++ 4.7 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows attackers to access administrative accounts using hardcoded credentials. Attackers can log in with the default admin username and password '1234' to gain unauthorized administrative access to the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37141 | AMSS++ v 4.31 - &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37141</link><description>AMSS++ version 4.31 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the mail module's maildetail.php script through the 'id' parameter. Attackers can manipulate the 'id' parameter in /modules/mail/main/maildetail.php to inject malicious SQL queries and potentially access or modify database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37146 | Aptina AR0130 960P 1.3MP Camera - Remote Configuration Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37146</link><description>ACE Security WiP-90113 HD Camera contains a configuration disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive configuration files. Attackers can access the camera's configuration backup by sending a GET request to the /config_backup.bin endpoint, exposing credentials and system settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37147 | ATutor 2.2.4 - &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37147</link><description>ATutor 2.2.4 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the admin user deletion page that allows authenticated attackers to manipulate database queries through the 'id' parameter. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by injecting malicious SQL code into the 'id' parameter of the admin_delete.php script to potentially extract or modify database information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37154 | eLection 2.0 - &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37154</link><description>eLection 2.0 contains an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the candidate management endpoint that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the 'id' parameter. Attackers can leverage SQLMap to exploit the vulnerability, potentially gaining remote code execution by uploading backdoor files to the web application directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37155 | Core FTP Lite 1.3 - Denial of Service (PoC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37155</link><description>Core FTP Lite 1.3 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the username input field that allows attackers to crash the application by supplying oversized input. Attackers can generate a 7000-byte payload of repeated 'A' characters to trigger an application crash without requiring additional interaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37157 | DBPower C300 HD Camera - Remote Configuration Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37157</link><description>DBPower C300 HD Camera contains a configuration disclosure vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive credentials through an unprotected configuration backup endpoint. Attackers can download the configuration file and extract hardcoded username and password by accessing the /tmpfs/config_backup.bin resource.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37159 | Cuckoo Clock 5.0 - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37159</link><description>Parallaxis Cuckoo Clock 5.0 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting memory registers in the alarm scheduling feature. Attackers can craft a malicious payload exceeding 260 bytes to overwrite EIP and EBP, enabling shellcode execution with potential remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37160 | SprintWork 2.3.1 - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37160</link><description>SprintWork 2.3.1 contains multiple local privilege escalation vulnerabilities through insecure file, service, and folder permissions on Windows systems. Local unprivileged users can exploit missing executable files and weak service configurations to create a new administrative user and gain complete system access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37161 | Wedding Slideshow Studio 1.36 - &amp;#x27;Name&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37161</link><description>Wedding Slideshow Studio 1.36 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting the registration name field with malicious payload. Attackers can craft a specially designed payload to trigger remote code execution, demonstrating the ability to run system commands like launching the calculator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37162 | Wedding Slideshow Studio 1.36 - &amp;#x27;Key&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37162</link><description>Wedding Slideshow Studio 1.36 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the registration key input that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting memory. Attackers can craft a malicious payload of 1608 bytes to trigger a stack-based buffer overflow and execute commands through the registration key field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37163 | QuickDate 1.3.2 - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37163</link><description>QuickDate 1.3.2 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows remote attackers to manipulate database queries through the '_located' parameter in the find_matches endpoint. Attackers can inject UNION-based SQL statements to extract database information including user credentials, database name, and system version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37164 | AbsoluteTelnet 11.12 - &amp;quot;license entry&amp;quot; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37164</link><description>AbsoluteTelnet 11.12 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows local attackers to crash the application by supplying an oversized license name. Attackers can generate a 2500-character payload and paste it into the license entry field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37165 | AbsoluteTelnet 11.12 - &amp;quot;license name&amp;quot; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37165</link><description>AbsoluteTelnet 11.12 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows local attackers to crash the application by supplying an oversized license name. Attackers can generate a 2500-character payload and paste it into the license name field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37166 | AbsoluteTelnet 11.12 - &amp;#x27;SSH2/username&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37166</link><description>AbsoluteTelnet 11.12 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the SSH2 username input field that allows local attackers to crash the application. Attackers can overwrite the username field with a 1000-byte buffer, causing the application to become unresponsive and terminate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37170 | TapinRadio 2.12.3 - &amp;#x27;address&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37170</link><description>TapinRadio 2.12.3 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the application proxy address configuration that allows local attackers to crash the application. Attackers can overwrite the address field with 3000 bytes of arbitrary data to trigger an application crash and prevent normal program functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37171 | TapinRadio 2.12.3 - &amp;#x27;username&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37171</link><description>TapinRadio 2.12.3 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the application proxy username configuration that allows local attackers to crash the application. Attackers can overwrite the username field with 10,000 bytes of arbitrary data to trigger an application crash and prevent normal program functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25793 | Nebula Has Possible Blocklist Bypass via ECDSA Signature Malleability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25793</link><description>Nebula is a scalable overlay networking tool. In versions from 1.7.0 to 1.10.2, when using P256 certificates (which is not the default configuration), it is possible to evade a blocklist entry created against the fingerprint of a certificate by using ECDSA Signature Malleability to use a copy of the certificate with a different fingerprint. This issue has been patched in version 1.10.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25803 | 3DP-MANAGER Uses Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25803</link><description>3DP-MANAGER is an inbound generator for 3x-ui. In version 2.0.1 and prior, the application automatically creates an administrative account with known default credentials (admin/admin) upon the first initialization. Attackers with network access to the application's login interface can gain full administrative control, managing VPN tunnels and system settings. This issue will be patched in version 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25804 | Antrea has invalid enforcement order for network policy rules caused by integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25804</link><description>Antrea is a Kubernetes networking solution intended to be Kubernetes native. Prior to versions 2.3.2 and 2.4.3, Antrea's network policy priority assignment system has a uint16 arithmetic overflow bug that causes incorrect OpenFlow priority calculations when handling a large numbers of policies with various priority values. This results in potentially incorrect traffic enforcement. This issue has been patched in versions 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25644 | DataHub&amp;#x27;s LDAP Ingestion Source vulnerable to MITM attack through TLS downgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25644</link><description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. Prior to version 1.3.1.8, the LDAP ingestion source is vulnerable to MITM attack through TLS downgrade. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25749 | Heap Overflow in Vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25749</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. Prior to version 9.1.2132, a heap buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Vim's tag file resolution logic when processing the 'helpfile' option. The vulnerability is located in the get_tagfname() function in src/tag.c. When processing help file tags, Vim copies the user-controlled 'helpfile' option value into a fixed-size heap buffer of MAXPATHL + 1 bytes (typically 4097 bytes) using an unsafe STRCPY() operation without any bounds checking. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.2132.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25754 | AdonisJS multipart body parsing has Prototype Pollution issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25754</link><description>AdonisJS is a TypeScript-first web framework. Prior to versions 10.1.3 and 11.0.0-next.9, a prototype pollution vulnerability in AdonisJS multipart form-data parsing may allow a remote attacker to manipulate object prototypes at runtime. This issue has been patched in versions 10.1.3 and 11.0.0-next.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25762 | AdonisJS vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) via Unrestricted Memory Buffering in PartHandler during File Type Detection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25762</link><description>AdonisJS is a TypeScript-first web framework. Prior to versions 10.1.3 and 11.0.0-next.9, a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the multipart file handling logic of @adonisjs/bodyparser. When processing file uploads, the multipart parser may accumulate an unbounded amount of data in memory while attempting to detect file types, potentially leading to excessive memory consumption and process termination. This issue has been patched in versions 10.1.3 and 11.0.0-next.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25757 | Unauthenticated Spree Commerce users can view completed guest orders by Order ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25757</link><description>Spree is an open source e-commerce solution built with Ruby on Rails. Prior to versions 5.0.8, 5.1.10, 5.2.7, and 5.3.2, unauthenticated users can view completed guest orders by Order ID. This issue may lead to disclosure of PII of guest users (including names, addresses and phone numbers). This issue has been patched in versions 5.0.8, 5.1.10, 5.2.7, and 5.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2070 | UTT è¿›å– 520W formPolicyRouteConf strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2070</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT è¿›å– 520W 1.7.7-180627. The affected element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPolicyRouteConf. Such manipulation of the argument GroupName leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25763 | Command Injection on OpenProject repositories leads to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25763</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to versions 16.6.7 and 17.0.3, an arbitrary file write vulnerability exists in OpenProjectâ€™s repository changes endpoint (/projects/:project_id/repository/changes) when rendering the â€œlatest changesâ€ view via git log. By supplying a specially crafted rev value (for example, rev=--output=/tmp/poc.txt), an attacker can inject git log command-line options. When OpenProject executes the SCM command, Git interprets the attacker-controlled rev as an option and writes the output to an attacker-chosen path. As a result, any user with the :browse_repository permission on the project can create or overwrite arbitrary files that the OpenProject process user is permitted to write. The written contents consist of git log output, but by crafting custom commits the attacker can still upload valid shell scripts, ultimately leading to RCE. The RCE lets the attacker create a reverse shell to the target host and view confidential files outside of OpenProject, such as /etc/passwd. This issue has been patched in versions 16.6.7 and 17.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25764 | OpenProject vulnerable to Stored HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25764</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to versions 16.6.7 and 17.0.3, an HTML injection vulnerability occurs in the time tracking function of OpenProject. The application does not escape HTML tags, an attacker with administrator privileges can create a work package with the name containing the HTML tags and add it to the Work package section when creating time tracking. This issue has been patched in versions 16.6.7 and 17.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2069 | ggml-org llama.cpp GBNF Grammar llama-grammar.cpp llama_grammar_advance_stack stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2069</link><description>A flaw has been found in ggml-org llama.cpp up to 55abc39. Impacted is the function llama_grammar_advance_stack of the file llama.cpp/src/llama-grammar.cpp of the component GBNF Grammar Handler. This manipulation causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. Patch name: 18993. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1731 | Remote code execution vulnerability in BeyondTrust Remote Support (RS) and Privileged Remote Access (PRA)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1731</link><description>BeyondTrust Remote Support (RS) and certain older versions of Privileged Remote Access (PRA) contain a critical pre-authentication remote code execution vulnerability. By sending specially crafted requests, an unauthenticated remote attacker may be able to execute operating system commands in the context of the site user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1727 | Information Disclosure via Bucket Squatting in Google Cloud Agentspace.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1727</link><description>The Agentspace service was affected by a vulnerability that exposed sensitive information due to the use of predictable Google Cloud Storage bucket names. These names were utilized for error logs and temporary staging during data imports from GCS and Cloud SQL. This predictability allowed an attacker to engage in "bucket squatting" by establishing these buckets before a victim's initial use.

All versions after December 12th, 2025 have been updated to protect from this vulnerability. No user action is required for this.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25760 | Website Path Traversal / Arbitrary File Read (Authenticated) in Sliver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25760</link><description>Sliver is a command and control framework that uses a custom Wireguard netstack. Prior to 1.6.11, a path traversal in the website content subsystem lets an authenticated operator read arbitrary files on the Sliver server host. This is an authenticated path traversal / arbitrary file read issue, and it can expose credentials, configs, and keys. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2068 | UTT è¿›å– 520W formSyslogConf strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2068</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT è¿›å– 520W 1.7.7-180627. This issue affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formSyslogConf. The manipulation of the argument ServerIp results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68621 | Trilium Notes has a Timing Attack Vulnerability in /api/login/sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68621</link><description>Trilium Notes is an open-source, cross-platform hierarchical note taking application with focus on building large personal knowledge bases.  Prior to 0.101.0, a critical timing attack vulnerability in Trilium's sync authentication endpoint allows unauthenticated remote attackers to recover HMAC authentication hashes byte-by-byte through statistical timing analysis. This enables complete authentication bypass without password knowledge, granting full read/write access to victim's knowledge base. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.101.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25123 | Homarr affected by Unauthenticated SSRF / Port-Scan Primitive via widget.app.ping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25123</link><description>Homarr is an open-source dashboard. Prior to 1.52.0, a public (unauthenticated) tRPC endpoint widget.app.ping accepts an arbitrary url and performs a server-side request to that URL. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to trigger outbound HTTP requests from the Homarr server, enabling SSRF behavior and a reliable port-scanning primitive (open vs closed ports can be inferred from statusCode vs fetch failed and timing). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.52.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25533 | Enclave has a sandbox escape via infinite recursion and error objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25533</link><description>Enclave is a secure JavaScript sandbox designed for safe AI agent code execution. Prior to 2.10.1, the existing layers of security in enclave-vm are insufficient: The AST sanitization can be bypassed with dynamic property accesses, the hardening of the error objects does not cover the peculiar behavior or the vm module and the function constructor access prevention can be side-stepped by leveraging host object references. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.10.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25758 | Spree allows unauthenticated users can access all guest addresses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25758</link><description>Spree is an open source e-commerce solution built with Ruby on Rails. A critical IDOR vulnerability exists in Spree Commerce's guest checkout flow that allows any guest user to bind arbitrary guest addresses to their order by manipulating address ID parameters. This enables unauthorized access to other guests' personally identifiable information (PII) including names, addresses and phone numbers. The vulnerability bypasses existing ownership validation checks and affects all guest checkout transactions. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.10.3, 5.0.8, 5.1.10, 5.2.7, and 5.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25516 | NiceGUI&amp;#x27;s XSS vulnerability in ui.markdown() allows arbitrary JavaScript execution through unsanitized HTML content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25516</link><description>NiceGUI is a Python-based UI framework. The ui.markdown() component uses the markdown2 library to convert markdown content to HTML, which is then rendered via innerHTML. By default, markdown2 allows raw HTML to pass through unchanged. This means that if an application renders user-controlled content through ui.markdown(), an attacker can inject malicious HTML containing JavaScript event handlers. Unlike other NiceGUI components that render HTML (ui.html(), ui.chat_message(), ui.interactive_image()), the ui.markdown() component does not provide or require a sanitize parameter, leaving applications vulnerable to XSS attacks. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25544 | Payload has an SQL Injection in JSON/RichText Queries on PostgreSQL/SQLite Adapters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25544</link><description>Payload is a free and open source headless content management system. Prior to 3.73.0, when querying JSON or richText fields, user input was directly embedded into SQL without escaping, enabling blind SQL injection attacks. An unauthenticated attacker could extract sensitive data (emails, password reset tokens) and achieve full account takeover without password cracking. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.73.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25574 | Payload Affected by Cross-Collection IDOR in payload-preferences Access Control (Multi-Auth Environments)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25574</link><description>Payload is a free and open source headless content management system. Prior to 3.74.0, a cross-collection Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in the payload-preferences internal collection. In multi-auth collection environments using Postgres or SQLite with default serial/auto-increment IDs, authenticated users from one auth collection can read and delete preferences belonging to users in different auth collections when their numeric IDs collide. This vulnerability has been patched in v3.74.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25732 | NiceGUI&amp;#x27;s Path Traversal via Unsanitized FileUpload.name Enables Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25732</link><description>NiceGUI is a Python-based UI framework. Prior to 3.7.0, NiceGUI's FileUpload.name property exposes client-supplied filename metadata without sanitization, enabling path traversal when developers use the pattern UPLOAD_DIR / file.name. Malicious filenames containing ../ sequences allow attackers to write files outside intended directories, with potential for remote code execution through application file overwrites in vulnerable deployment patterns. This design creates a prevalent security footgun affecting applications following common community patterns. Note: Exploitation requires application code incorporating file.name into filesystem paths without sanitization. Applications using fixed paths, generated filenames, or explicit sanitization are not affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25580 | Pydantic AI Affected by Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in URL Download Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25580</link><description>Pydantic AI is a Python agent framework for building applications and workflows with Generative AI. From 0.0.26 to before 1.56.0, aServer-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in Pydantic AI's URL download functionality. When applications accept message history from untrusted sources, attackers can include malicious URLs that cause the server to make HTTP requests to internal network resources, potentially accessing internal services or cloud credentials. This vulnerability only affects applications that accept message history from external users. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.56.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25581 | SCEditor affected by DOM XSS via emoticon URL/HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25581</link><description>SCEditor is a lightweight WYSIWYG BBCode and XHTML editor. Prior to 3.2.1, if an attacker has the ability control configuration options passed to sceditor.create(), like emoticons, charset, etc. then it's possible for them to trigger an XSS attack due to lack of sanitisation of configuration options. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25593 | OpenClaw Affected by Unauthenticated Local RCE via WebSocket config.apply</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25593</link><description>OpenClaw is a personal AI assistant. Prior to 2026.1.20, an unauthenticated local client could use the Gateway WebSocket API to write config via config.apply and set unsafe cliPath values that were later used for command discovery, enabling command injection as the gateway user. This vulnerability is fixed in 2026.1.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2067 | UTT è¿›å– 520W formTimeGroupConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2067</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT è¿›å– 520W 1.7.7-180627. This vulnerability affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formTimeGroupConfig. The manipulation of the argument year1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25592 | Semantic Kernel has an Arbitrary File Write via AI Agent Function Calling in .NET SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25592</link><description>Semantic Kernel is an SDK used to build, orchestrate, and deploy AI agents and multi-agent systems. Prior to 1.70.0, an Arbitrary File Write vulnerability has been identified in Microsoft's Semantic Kernelâ€¯.NET SDK, specifically within theâ€¯SessionsPythonPlugin. The problem has been fixed in Microsoft.SemanticKernel.Core version 1.70.0. As a mitigation, users can create a Function Invocation Filter which checks the arguments being passed to any calls to DownloadFileAsyncâ€¯ or UploadFileAsync and ensures the provided localFilePath is allow listed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25597 | PrestaShop has a time based enumeration in FO login form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25597</link><description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Prior to 8.2.4 and 9.0.3, there is a time-based user enumeration vulnerability in the user authentication functionality of PrestaShop. This vulnerability allows an attacker to determine whether a customer account exists in the system by measuring response times. This vulnerability is fixed in 8.2.4 and 9.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25628 | Qdrant affected by arbitrary file write via `/logger` endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25628</link><description>Qdrant is a vector similarity search engine and vector database. From 1.9.3 to before 1.16.0, it is possible to append to arbitrary files via /logger endpoint using an attacker-controlled on_disk.log_file path. Minimal privileges are required (read-only access). This vulnerability is fixed in 1.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25631 | Domain allowlist bypass enables credential exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25631</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to 1.121.0, there is a vulnerability in the HTTP Request node's credential domain validation allowed an authenticated attacker to send requests with credentials to unintended domains, potentially leading to credential exfiltration. This only might affect user who have credentials that use wildcard domain patterns (e.g., *.example.com) in the "Allowed domains" setting. This issue is fixed in version 1.121.0 and later.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25632 | EPyT-Flow has unsafe JSON deserialization (__type__)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25632</link><description>EPyT-Flow is a Python package designed for the easy generation of hydraulic and water quality scenario data of water distribution networks. Prior to 0.16.1, EPyT-Flowâ€™s REST API parses attacker-controlled JSON request bodies using a custom deserializer (my_load_from_json) that supports a type field. When type is present, the deserializer dynamically imports an attacker-specified module/class and instantiates it with attacker-supplied arguments. This allows invoking dangerous classes such as subprocess.Popen, which can lead to OS command execution during JSON parsing. This also affects the loading of JSON files. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.16.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25634 | iccDEV memcpy-param-overlap in CIccTagMultiProcessElement::Apply()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25634</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools that allow for the interaction, manipulation, and application of ICC color management profiles. Prior to 2.3.1.4, SrcPixel and DestPixel stack buffers overlap in CIccTagMultiProcessElement::Apply() int IccTagMPE.cpp. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25729 | DeepAudit Affected by User Enumeration via Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25729</link><description>DeepAudit is a multi-agent system for code vulnerability discovery. In 3.0.4 and earlier, there is an improper access control vulnerability in the /api/v1/users/ endpoint allows any authenticated user to enumerate all users in the system and retrieve sensitive information including email addresses, phone numbers, full names, and role information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2066 | UTT è¿›å– 520W formIpGroupConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2066</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT è¿›å– 520W 1.7.7-180627. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formIpGroupConfig. Executing a manipulation of the argument groupName can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25635 | calibre has a Path Traversal Leading to Arbitrary File Write and Potential Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25635</link><description>calibre is an e-book manager. Prior to 9.2.0, Calibre's CHM reader contains a path traversal vulnerability that allows arbitrary file writes anywhere the user has write permissions. On Windows (haven't tested on other OS's), this can lead to Remote Code Execution by writing a payload to the Startup folder, which executes on next login. This vulnerability is fixed in 9.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25636 | calibre has a Path Traversal Leading to Arbitrary File Corruption and Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25636</link><description>calibre is an e-book manager. In 9.1.0 and earlier, a path traversal vulnerability in Calibre's EPUB conversion allows a malicious EPUB file to corrupt arbitrary existing files writable by the Calibre process. During conversion, Calibre resolves CipherReference URI from META-INF/encryption.xml to an absolute filesystem path and opens it in read-write mode, even when it points outside the conversion extraction directory. This vulnerability is fixed in 9.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25731 | Calibre Affected by Arbitrary Code Execution via Server-Side Template Injection in Calibre HTML Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25731</link><description>calibre is an e-book manager. Prior to 9.2.0, a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in Calibre's Templite templating engine allows arbitrary code execution when a user converts an ebook using a malicious custom template file via the --template-html or --template-html-index command-line options. This vulnerability is fixed in 9.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25640 | Pydantic AI affected by Stored XSS via Path Traversal in Web UI CDN URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25640</link><description>Pydantic AI is a Python agent framework for building applications and workflows with Generative AI. From 1.34.0 to before 1.51.0,  a path traversal vulnerability in the Pydantic AI web UI allows an attacker to serve arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the application by crafting a malicious URL. In affected versions, the CDN URL is constructed using a version query parameter from the request URL. This parameter is not validated, allowing path traversal sequences that cause the server to fetch and serve attacker-controlled HTML/JavaScript from an arbitrary source on the same CDN, instead of the legitimate chat UI package. If a victim clicks the link or visits it via an iframe, attacker-controlled code executes in their browser, enabling theft of chat history and other client-side data. This vulnerability only affects applications that use Agent.to_web to serve a chat interface and clai web to serve a chat interface from the CLI. These are typically run locally (on localhost), but may also be deployed on a remote server. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.51.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2065 | Flycatcher Toys smART Pixelator Bluetooth Low Energy missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2065</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Flycatcher Toys smART Pixelator 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Bluetooth Low Energy Interface. Performing a manipulation results in missing authentication. The attack can only be performed from the local network. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25520 | SandboxJS has a Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25520</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Prior to 0.8.29, The return values of functions aren't wrapped. Object.values/Object.entries can be used to get an Array containing the host's Function constructor, by using Array.prototype.at you can obtain the hosts Function constructor, which can be used to execute arbitrary code outside of the sandbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25586 | SandboxJS has a Sandbox Escape via Prototype Whitelist Bypass and Host Prototype Pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25586</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Prior to 0.8.29, a sandbox escape is possible by shadowing hasOwnProperty on a sandbox object, which disables prototype whitelist enforcement in the property-access path. This permits direct access to __proto__ and other blocked prototype properties, enabling host Object.prototype pollution and persistent cross-sandbox impact. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25587 | SandboxJS has a Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25587</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Prior to 0.8.29, as Map is in SAFE_PROTOYPES, it's prototype can be obtained via Map.prototype. By overwriting Map.prototype.has the sandbox can be escaped. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25641 | SandboxJS has a sandbox escape via TOCTOU bug on keys in property accesses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25641</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Prior to 0.8.29, there is a sandbox escape vulnerability due to a mismatch between the key on which the validation is performed and the key used for accessing properties. Even though the key used in property accesses is annotated as string, this is never enforced. So, attackers can pass malicious objects that coerce to different string values when used, e.g., one for the time the key is sanitized using hasOwnProperty(key) and a different one for when the key is used for the actual property access. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.29.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2064 | Portabilis i-Educar User Data meusdadod.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2064</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /intranet/meusdadod.php of the component User Data Page. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15320 | Tanium addressed a denial of service vulnerability in Tanium Client.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15320</link><description>Tanium addressed a denial of service vulnerability in Tanium Client.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1709 | Keylime: keylime: authentication bypass allows unauthorized administrative operations due to missing client-side tls authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1709</link><description>A flaw was found in Keylime. The Keylime registrar, since version 7.12.0, does not enforce client-side Transport Layer Security (TLS) authentication. This authentication bypass vulnerability allows unauthenticated clients with network access to perform administrative operations, including listing agents, retrieving public Trusted Platform Module (TPM) data, and deleting agents, by connecting without presenting a client certificate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22254 | Winter Affected by Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Asset Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22254</link><description>Winter is a free, open-source content management system (CMS) based on the Laravel PHP framework. Versions of Winter CMS before 1.2.10 allow users with access to the CMS Asset Manager were able to upload SVGs without automatic sanitization. To actively exploit this security issue, an attacker would need access to the Backend with a user account with the following permission: cms.manage_assets. The Winter CMS maintainers strongly recommend that the cms.manage_assets permission only be reserved to trusted administrators and developers in general. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25642 | HedgeDoc security headers for uploaded files were not working</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25642</link><description>HedgeDoc is an open source, real-time, collaborative, markdown notes application. Prior to 1.10.6, files served below the /uploads/ endpoint did not use a more strict security-policy. This resulted in a too open Content-Security-Policy and furthermore opened the possibility to host malicious interactive web content (such as fake login forms) using SVG files. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25643 | Frigate Affected by Authenticated Remote Command Execution (RCE) and Container Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25643</link><description>Frigate is a network video recorder (NVR) with realtime local object detection for IP cameras. Prior to 0.16.4, a critical Remote Command Execution (RCE) vulnerability has been identified in the Frigate integration with go2rtc. The application does not sanitize user input in the video stream configuration (config.yaml), allowing direct injection of system commands via the exec: directive. The go2rtc service executes these commands without restrictions. This vulnerability is only exploitable by an administrator or users who have exposed their Frigate install to the open internet with no authentication which allows anyone full administrative control. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.16.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25727 | time affected by a stack exhaustion denial of service attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25727</link><description>time provides date and time handling in Rust. From 0.3.6 to before 0.3.47, when user-provided input is provided to any type that parses with the RFC 2822 format, a denial of service attack via stack exhaustion is possible. The attack relies on formally deprecated and rarely-used features that are part of the RFC 2822 format used in a malicious manner. Ordinary, non-malicious input will never encounter this scenario. A limit to the depth of recursion was added in v0.3.47. From this version, an error will be returned rather than exhausting the stack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25647 | Lute has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Markdown hyperlink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25647</link><description>Lute is a structured Markdown engine supporting Go and JavaScript. Lute 1.7.6 and earlier (as used in SiYuan before) has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Markdown rendering engine. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript into a Markdown text/note. When another user clicks the rendered content, the script executes in the context of their session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25650 | MCP Salesforce Connector has arbitrary attribute access which leads to disclosure of Salesforce auth token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25650</link><description>MCP Salesforce Connector is a Model Context Protocol (MCP) server implementation for Salesforce integration. Prior to 0.1.10, arbitrary attribute access leads to disclosure of Salesforce auth token. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25651 | client-certificate-auth has an Open Redirect via Host Header Injection in HTTP-to-HTTPS redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25651</link><description>client-certificate-auth is middleware for Node.js implementing client SSL certificate authentication/authorization. Versions 0.2.1 and 0.3.0 of client-certificate-auth contain an open redirect vulnerability. The middleware unconditionally redirects HTTP requests to HTTPS using the unvalidated Host header, allowing an attacker to redirect users to arbitrary domains. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25751 | FUXA Unauthenticated Exposure of Plaintext Database Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25751</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. An information disclosure vulnerability in FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to retrieve sensitive administrative database credentials. Exploitation allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain the full system configuration, including administrative credentials for the InfluxDB database. Possession of these credentials may allow an attacker to authenticate directly to the database service, enabling them to read, modify, or delete all historical process data, or perform a Denial of Service by corrupting the database. This affects FUXA through version 1.2.9. This issue has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25752 | FUXA Unauthenticated Remote Arbitrary Device Tag Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25752</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. An authorization bypass vulnerability in FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to modify device tags via WebSockets. Exploitation allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass role-based access controls and overwrite arbitrary device tags or disable communication drivers, exposing connected ICS/SCADA environments to follow-on actions. This may allow an attacker to manipulate physical processes and disconnected devices from the HMI. This affects FUXA through version 1.2.9. This issue has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25753 | PlaciPy has a Hard-Coded Default Password for All Student Accounts (Account Takeover)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25753</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the application uses a hard-coded, static default password for all newly created student accounts. This results in mass account takeover, allowing any attacker to log in as any student once the password is known.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2063 | D-Link DIR-823X Web Management set_ac_server os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2063</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/set_ac_server of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ac_server results in os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23989 | REVA Public Link Exploit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23989</link><description>REVA is an interoperability platform. Prior to 2.42.3 and 2.40.3, a bug in the GRPC authorization middleware of the "Reva" component of OpenCloud allows a malicious user to bypass the scope verification of a public link. By exploiting this via the the "archiver" service this can be leveraged to create an archive (zip or tar-file) containing all resources that this creator of the public link has access to. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.42.3 and 2.40.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2062 | Open5GS PGW S5U Address sgwc_sxa_handle_session_modification_response null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2062</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Open5GS up to 2.7.6. This affects the function sgwc_s5c_handle_modify_bearer_response/sgwc_sxa_handle_session_modification_response of the component PGW S5U Address Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is f1bbd7b57f831e2a070780a7d8d5d4c73babdb59. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69212 | OpenSTAManager has an OS Command Injection in P7M File Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69212</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. In 2.9.8 and earlier, a critical OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in the P7M (signed XML) file decoding functionality. An authenticated attacker can upload a ZIP file containing a .p7m file with a malicious filename to execute arbitrary system commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69214 | OpenSTAManager has a SQL Injection in ajax_select.php (componenti endpoint)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69214</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. In 2.9.8 and earlier, an SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the ajax_select.php endpoint when handling the componenti operation. An authenticated attacker can inject malicious SQL code through the options[matricola] parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69216 | OpenSTAManager has an SQL Injection in Scadenzario Print Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69216</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. In 2.9.8 and earlier, an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in OpenSTAManager's Scadenzario (Payment Schedule) print template allows any authenticated user to extract sensitive data from the database, including admin credentials, customer information, and financial records. The vulnerability exists in templates/scadenzario/init.php, where the id_anagrafica parameter is directly concatenated into an SQL query without proper sanitization. The vulnerability enables complete database read access through error-based SQL injection techniques.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24050 | Zulip affected by Stored XSS in user profile modal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24050</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. From 5.0 to before 11.5, some administrative actions on the user profile were susceptible to stored XSS in group names or channel names. Exploiting these vulnerabilities required the user explicitly interacting with the problematic object. This vulnerability is fixed in 11.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24416 | OpenSTAManager has a Time-Based Blind SQL Injection in Article Pricing Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24416</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. OpenSTAManager v2.9.8 and earlier contain a critical Time-Based Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in the article pricing completion handler. The application fails to properly sanitize the idarticolo parameter before using it in SQL queries, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands and extract sensitive data through time-based Boolean inference.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24417 | OpenSTAManager has a Time-Based Blind SQL Injection with Amplified Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24417</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. OpenSTAManager v2.9.8 and earlier contain a critical Time-Based Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in the global search functionality. The application fails to properly sanitize the term parameter before using it in SQL LIKE clauses across multiple module-specific search handlers, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands and extract sensitive data through time-based Boolean inference.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24418 | OpenSTAManager has an SQL Injection vulnerability in the Scadenzario bulk operations module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24418</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. OpenSTAManager v2.9.8 and earlier contain a critical Error-Based SQL Injection vulnerability in the bulk operations handler for the Scadenzario (Payment Schedule) module. The application fails to validate that elements of the id_records array are integers before using them in an SQL IN() clause, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands and extract sensitive data through XPATH error messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24419 | OpenSTAManager has an SQL Injection in the Prima Nota  module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24419</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. OpenSTAManager v2.9.8 and earlier contain a critical Error-Based SQL Injection vulnerability in the Prima Nota (Journal Entry) module's add.php file. The application fails to validate that comma-separated values from the id_documenti GET parameter are integers before using them in SQL IN() clauses, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands and extract sensitive data through XPATH error messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24776 | OpenProject has an IDOR on MeetingAgendaItems allows cross-project meeting agenda item transfer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24776</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to 17.0.2, the drag&amp;amp;drop handler moving an agenda item to a different section was not properly checking if the target meeting section is part of the same meeting (or is the backlog, in case of recurring meetings). This allowed an attacker to move a meeting agenda item into a different meeting. The attacker did not get access to meetings, but they could add arbitrary agenda items, that could cause confusions. The vulnerability is fixed in 17.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24851 | OpenFGA Improper Policy Enforcement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24851</link><description>OpenFGA is a high-performance and flexible authorization/permission engine built for developers and inspired by Google Zanzibar. OpenFGA v1.8.5 to v1.11.2 ( openfga-0.2.22&lt;= Helm chart &lt;= openfga-0.2.51, v.1.8.5 &lt;= docker &lt;= v.1.11.2) are vulnerable to improper policy enforcement when certain Check calls are executed. The vulnerability requires a model that has a a relation directly assignable by a type bound public access and assignable by type bound non-public access, a tuple assigned for the relation that is a type bound public access, a tuple assigned for the same object with the same relation that is not type bound public access, and a tuple assigned for a different object that has an object ID lexicographically larger with the same user and relation which is not type bound public access. This vulnerability is fixed in v1.11.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25722 | Claude Code Vulnerable to Command Injection via Directory Change Bypasses Write Protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25722</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.0.57, Claude Code failed to properly validate directory changes when combined with write operations to protected folders. By using the cd command to navigate into sensitive directories like .claude, it was possible to bypass write protection and create or modify files without user confirmation. Reliably exploiting this required the ability to add untrusted content into a Claude Code context window. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.57.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25723 | Claude Code Vulnerable to Command Injection via Piped sed Command Bypasses File Write Restrictions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25723</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.0.55, Claude Code failed to properly validate commands using piped sed operations with the echo command, allowing attackers to bypass file write restrictions. This vulnerability enabled writing to sensitive directories like the .claude folder and paths outside the project scope. Exploiting this required the ability to execute commands through Claude Code with the "accept edits" feature enabled. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.55.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25724 | Claude Code Has Permission Deny Bypass Through Symbolic Links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25724</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.1.7, Claude Code failed to strictly enforce deny rules configured in settings.json when accessing files through symbolic links. If a user explicitly denied Claude Code access to a file (such as /etc/passwd) and Claude Code had access to a symbolic link pointing to that file, it was possible for Claude Code to read the restricted file through the symlink without triggering deny rule enforcement. This issue has been patched in version 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25725 | Claude Code Has Sandbox Escape via Persistent Configuration Injection in settings.json</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25725</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.1.2, Claude Code's bubblewrap sandboxing mechanism failed to properly protect the .claude/settings.json configuration file when it did not exist at startup. While the parent directory was mounted as writable and .claude/settings.local.json was explicitly protected with read-only constraints, settings.json was not protected if it was missing. This allowed malicious code running inside the sandbox to create this file and inject persistent hooks (such as SessionStart commands) that would execute with host privileges when Claude Code was restarted. This issue has been patched in version 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2061 | D-Link DIR-823X set_ipv6 sub_424D20 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2061</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is the function sub_424D20 of the file /goform/set_ipv6. Executing a manipulation can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64175 | Gogs Vulnerable to 2FA Bypass via Recovery Code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64175</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In version 0.13.3 and prior, Gogsâ€™ 2FA recovery code validation does not scope codes by user, enabling cross-account bypass. If an attacker knows a victimâ€™s username and password, they can use any unused recovery code (e.g., from their own account) to bypass the victimâ€™s 2FA. This enables full account takeover and renders 2FA ineffective in all environments where it's enabled.. This issue has been patched in versions 0.13.4 and 0.14.0+dev.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70963 | Gophish &lt;=0.12.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The administrative dashboard exposes each userâ€™s long-lived API key directly ins...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70963</link><description>Gophish &lt;=0.12.1 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The administrative dashboard exposes each userâ€™s long-lived API key directly inside the rendered HTML/JavaScript of the page on every login. This makes permanent API credentials accessible to any script running in the browser context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22592 | Gogs is Vulnerable to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22592</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In version 0.13.3 and prior, an authenticated user can cause a DOS attack. If one of the repo files is deleted before synchronization, it will cause the application to crash. This issue has been patched in versions 0.13.4 and 0.14.0+dev.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23632 | Gogs user can update repository content with read-only permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23632</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In version 0.13.3 and prior, the endpoint "PUT /repos/:owner/:repo/contents/*" does not require write permissions and allows access with read permission only via repoAssignment(). After passing the permission check, PutContents() invokes UpdateRepoFile(), which results in commit creation and the execution of git push. As a result, a token with read-only permission can be used to modify repository contents. This issue has been patched in versions 0.13.4 and 0.14.0+dev.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23633 | Gogs has arbitrary file read/write via path traversal in Git hook editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23633</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In version 0.13.3 and prior, there is an arbitrary file read/write via path traversal in Git hook editing. This issue has been patched in versions 0.13.4 and 0.14.0+dev.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24135 | Gogs vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion via path traversal in wiki page update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24135</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In version 0.13.3 and prior, a path traversal vulnerability exists in the updateWikiPage function of Gogs. The vulnerability allows an authenticated user with write access to a repository's wiki to delete arbitrary files on the server by manipulating the old_title parameter in the wiki editing form. This issue has been patched in versions 0.13.4 and 0.14.0+dev.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24903 | OrcaStatLLM Researcher Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Log Message Injection in Session Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24903</link><description>OrcaStatLLM Researcher is an LLM Based Research Paper Generator. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the  Log Message in the Session Page in OrcaStatLLM-Researcher that allows attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code in victims' browsers through malicious research topic inputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2060 | code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System editcampaignform.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2060</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /simpleblooddonor/editcampaignform.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1769 | Stored XSS on Xerox CentreWare Web 7.0.6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1769</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xerox CentreWare on Windows allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CentreWare: through 7.0.6.Â 

Consider 
upgrading XeroxÂ® CentreWare WebÂ® to v7.2.2.25 via the software available on Xerox.com</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64111 | Gogs&amp;#x27;s update .git/config file allows remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64111</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. In version 0.13.3 and prior, due to the insufficient patch for CVE-2024-56731, it's still possible to update files in the .git directory and achieve remote command execution. This issue has been patched in versions 0.13.4 and 0.14.0+dev.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2059 | SourceCodester Medical Center Portal Management System emp_edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2059</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Medical Center Portal Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /emp_edit1.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25266 | Wondershare Application Framework Service 2.4.3.231 - &amp;#x27;WsAppService&amp;#x27; Unquote Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25266</link><description>Wondershare Application Framework Service 2.4.3.231 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path by placing malicious executables in specific directory locations to hijack the service's execution context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25292 | Alps HID Monitor Service 8.1.0.10 - &amp;#x27;ApHidMonitorService&amp;#x27; Unquote Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25292</link><description>Alps HID Monitor Service 8.1.0.10 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files\Apoint2K\HidMonitorSvc.exe to inject malicious executables and gain system-level access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25293 | Blue Stacks App Player 2.4.44.62.57 - &amp;quot;BstHdLogRotatorSvc&amp;quot; Unquote Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25293</link><description>BlueStacks App Player 2.4.44.62.57 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the BstHdLogRotatorSvc service that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\Bluestacks\HD-LogRotatorService.exe to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25294 | html5_snmp 1.11 - &amp;#x27;Remark&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25294</link><description>html5_snmp 1.11 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts through the 'Remark' parameter in add_router_operation.php. Attackers can craft a POST request with a script payload in the Remark field to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers when the page is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25298 | html5_snmp 1.11 - &amp;#x27;Router_ID&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25298</link><description>html5_snmp 1.11 contains multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities that allow attackers to manipulate database queries through Router_ID and Router_IP parameters. Attackers can exploit error-based, time-based, and union-based injection techniques to potentially extract or modify database information by sending crafted payloads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25299 | rimbalinux AhadPOS 1.11 - &amp;#x27;alamatCustomer&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25299</link><description>RimbaLinux AhadPOS 1.11 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the 'alamatCustomer' parameter that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through crafted POST requests. Attackers can exploit time-based and boolean-based blind SQL injection techniques to extract information or potentially interact with the underlying database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25300 | thejshen Globitek CMS 1.4 - &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25300</link><description>thejshen Globitek CMS 1.4 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the 'id' GET parameter. Attackers can exploit boolean-based, time-based, and UNION-based SQL injection techniques to potentially extract or modify database information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25301 | thrsrossi Millhouse-Project 1.414 - &amp;#x27;content&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25301</link><description>Millhouse-Project 1.414 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability in the comment submission functionality that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can post comments with embedded JavaScript through the 'content' parameter in add_comment_sql.php to execute arbitrary scripts in victim browsers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25302 | Acer Launch Manager 6.1.7600.16385 - &amp;#x27;DsiWMIService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25302</link><description>Acer Launch Manager 6.1.7600.16385 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the DsiWMIService that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\Launch Manager\dsiwmis.exe to insert malicious code that would execute with system-level permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25303 | TheJshen contentManagementSystem 1.04 - &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25303</link><description>TheJshen ContentManagementSystem 1.04 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate database queries through the 'id' GET parameter. Attackers can exploit boolean-based, time-based, and UNION-based SQL injection techniques to extract or manipulate database information by crafting malicious query payloads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25304 | Intelligent Security System SecurOS Enterprise 10.2 - &amp;#x27;SecurosCtrlService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25304</link><description>SecurOS Enterprise 10.2 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the SecurosCtrlService that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files (x86)\ISS\SecurOS\ to insert malicious code that would execute with system-level permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25305 | JumpStart 0.6.0.0 - &amp;#x27;jswpbapi&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25305</link><description>JumpStart 0.6.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the jswpbapi service running with LocalSystem privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path containing spaces to inject and execute malicious code with elevated system permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23738 | The Asterisk embedded web server &amp;#x27;s /httpstatus page echos user supplied values(cookie and query string) without sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23738</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2, user supplied/control values for Cookies and any GET variable query Parameter are directly interpolated into the HTML of the page using ast_str_append. The endpoint at GET /httpstatus is the potential vulnerable endpoint relating to asterisk/main /http.c. This issue has been patched in versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23739 | Asterisk xml.c uses unsafe XML_PARSE_NOENT leading to potential XXE Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23739</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2, the ast_xml_open() function in xml.c parses XML documents using libxml with unsafe parsing options that enable entity expansion and XInclude processing. Specifically, it invokes xmlReadFile() with the XML_PARSE_NOENT flag and later processes XIncludes via xmlXIncludeProcess().If any untrusted or user-supplied XML file is passed to this function, it can allow an attacker to trigger XML External Entity (XXE) or XInclude-based local file disclosure, potentially exposing sensitive files from the host system. This can also be triggered in other cases in which the user is able to supply input in xml format that triggers the asterisk process to parse it. This issue has been patched in versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23740 | Asterisk vulnerable to potential privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23740</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2, when ast_coredumper writes its gdb init and output files to a directory that is world-writable (for example /tmp), an attacker with write permission(which is all users on a linux system) to that directory can cause root to execute arbitrary commands or overwrite arbitrary files by controlling the gdb init file and output paths. This issue has been patched in versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23741 | ast_coredumper running as root sources ast_debug_tools.conf from /etc/asterisk; potentially leading to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23741</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2, the asterisk/contrib/scripts/ast_coredumper runs as root, as noted by the NOTES tag on line 689 of the ast_coredumper file. The script will source the contents of /etc/asterisk/ast_debug_tools.conf, which resides in a folder that is writeable by the asterisk user:group. Due to the /etc/asterisk/ast_debug_tools.conf file following bash semantics and it being loaded; an attacker with write permissions may add or modify the file such that when the root ast_coredumper is run; it would source and thereby execute arbitrary bash code found in the /etc/asterisk/ast_debug_tools.conf. This issue has been patched in versions 20.7-cert9, 20.18.2, 21.12.1, 22.8.2, and 23.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2058 | mathurvishal CloudClassroom-PHP-Project Post Query Details postquerypublic.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2058</link><description>A flaw has been found in mathurvishal CloudClassroom-PHP-Project up to 5dadec098bfbbf3300d60c3494db3fb95b66e7be. This impacts an unknown function of the file /postquerypublic.php of the component Post Query Details Page. This manipulation of the argument gnamex causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery. Therefore, version details for affected or updated releases cannot be specified. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2103 | Use of Hard-Coded Cryptographic Key for Password Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2103</link><description>Infor SyteLine ERP uses hard-coded static cryptographic keys to encrypt stored credentials, including user passwords, database connection strings, and API keys. The encryption keys are identical across all installations. An attacker with access to the application binary and database can decrypt all stored credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25556 | MuPDF &amp;lt;= 1.27.0 Barcode Decoding Double Free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25556</link><description>MuPDF versions 1.23.0 through 1.27.0 contain a double-free vulnerability in fz_fill_pixmap_from_display_list() when an exception occurs during display list rendering. The function accepts a caller-owned fz_pixmap pointer but incorrectly drops the pixmap in its error handling path before rethrowing the exception. Callers (including the barcode decoding path in fz_decode_barcode_from_display_list) also drop the same pixmap in cleanup, resulting in a double-free that can corrupt the heap and crash the process. This issue affects applications that enable and use MuPDF barcode decoding and can be triggered by processing crafted input that causes a rendering-time error while decoding barcodes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13523 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Unescaped Display Names in Mattermost Confluence Plugin OAuth2 Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13523</link><description>Mattermost Confluence plugin version &lt;1.7.0 fails to properly escape user-controlled display names in HTML template rendering which allows authenticated Confluence users with malicious display names to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers via sending a specially crafted OAuth2 connection link that, when visited, renders the attacker's display name without proper sanitization. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00557</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2057 | SourceCodester Medical Center Portal Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2057</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Medical Center Portal Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument User results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2056 | D-Link DIR-605L/DIR-619L DHCP Connection Status wan_connection_status.asp information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2056</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-605L and DIR-619L 2.06B01/2.13B01. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /wan_connection_status.asp of the component DHCP Connection Status Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13818 | Local privilege escalation in ESET Management Agent for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13818</link><description>Local privilege escalation vulnerability via insecure temporary batch file execution in ESET Management Agent</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1337 | Insufficient escaping of unicode characters in query log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1337</link><description>Insufficient escaping of unicode characters in query log in Neo4j Enterprise and Community editions prior to 2026.01 can lead to XSS if the user opens the logs in a tool that treats them as HTML. There is no security impact on Neo4j products, but this advisory is released as a precaution to treat the logs as plain text if using versions prior to 2026.01.

Proof of concept exploit:Â  https://github.com/JoakimBulow/CVE-2026-1337</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2055 | D-Link DIR-605L/DIR-619L DHCP Client Information information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2055</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-605L and DIR-619L 2.06B01/2.13B01. The affected element is an unknown function of the component DHCP Client Information Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2054 | D-Link DIR-605L/DIR-619L Wifi Setting information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2054</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-605L and DIR-619L 2.06B01/2.13B01. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Wifi Setting Handler. Performing a manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2018 | itsourcecode School Management System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2018</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ramonsys/settings/controller.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1293 | Yoast SEO &amp;lt;= 26.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;yoast-schema&amp;#x27; Block Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1293</link><description>The Yoast SEO â€“ Advanced SEO with real-time guidance and built-in AI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the the `yoast-schema` block attribute in all versions up to, and including, 26.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2017 | IP-COM W30AP POST Request wx3auth R7WebsSecurityHandler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2017</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in IP-COM W30AP up to 1.0.0.11(1340). Affected by this issue is the function R7WebsSecurityHandler of the file /goform/wx3auth of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument data results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2016 | happyfish100 libfastcommon base64.c base64_decode stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2016</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in happyfish100 libfastcommon up to 1.0.84. Affected by this vulnerability is the function base64_decode of the file src/base64.c. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 82f66af3e252e3e137dba0c3891570f085e79adf. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2015 | Portabilis i-Educar Final Status Import FinalStatusImportService.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2015</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file FinalStatusImportService.php of the component Final Status Import. Executing a manipulation of the argument school_id can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2014 | itsourcecode Student Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2014</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/billing/index.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2013 | itsourcecode Student Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2013</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/soa/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24920 | Permission control vulnerability in the AMS module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24920</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the AMS module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24924 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the print module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24924</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the print module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24927 | Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the frequency modulation module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect avai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24927</link><description>Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the frequency modulation module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24928 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the file system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24928</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the file system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 10:05:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24916 | Identity authentication bypass vulnerability in the window module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24916</link><description>Identity authentication bypass vulnerability in the window module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24917 | UAF vulnerability in the security module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24917</link><description>UAF vulnerability in the security module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24919 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the DFX module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24919</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the DFX module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24931 | Vulnerability of improper criterion security check in the card module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24931</link><description>Vulnerability of improper criterion security check in the card module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2012 | itsourcecode Student Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2012</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/facultyloading/index.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1252 | Events Listing Widget &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Event URL Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1252</link><description>The Events Listing Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Event URL' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1499 | WP Duplicate &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload via &amp;#x27;process_add_site&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1499</link><description>The WP Duplicate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization leading to Arbitrary File Upload in all versions up to and including 1.1.8. This is due to a missing capability check on the `process_add_site()` AJAX action combined with path traversal in the file upload functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated (subscriber-level) attackers to set the internal `prod_key_random_id` option, which can then be used by an unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication checks and write arbitrary files to the server via the `handle_upload_single_big_file()` function, ultimately leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1785 | Code Snippets &amp;lt;= 3.9.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Cloud Snippet Download/Update Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1785</link><description>The Code Snippets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.4. This is due to missing nonce validation on the cloud snippet download and update actions in the Cloud_Search_List_Table class. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to force logged-in administrators to download or update cloud snippets without their consent via a crafted request, granted they can trick an administrator into visiting a malicious page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24914 | Type confusion vulnerability in the camera module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24914</link><description>Type confusion vulnerability in the camera module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24915 | Out-of-bounds read issue in the media subsystem.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confiden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24915</link><description>Out-of-bounds read issue in the media subsystem.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24918 | Address read vulnerability in the communication module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24918</link><description>Address read vulnerability in the communication module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24921 | Address read vulnerability in the HDC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24921</link><description>Address read vulnerability in the HDC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24922 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the HDC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24922</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the HDC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24923 | Permission control vulnerability in the HDC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24923</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the HDC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24929 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the graphics module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24929</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the graphics module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24930 | UAF concurrency vulnerability in the graphics module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24930</link><description>UAF concurrency vulnerability in the graphics module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2011 | itsourcecode Student Management System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2011</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/enrollment/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21643 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an sql command ('sql injection') vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientEMS 7.4.4 may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21643</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an sql command ('sql injection') vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientEMS 7.4.4 may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24925 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the image module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24925</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the image module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24926 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the camera module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24926</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the camera module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2010 | Sanluan PublicCMS Trade Payment TradePaymentService.java paid improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2010</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 4.0.202506.d/5.202506.d/6.202506.d. Impacted is the function Paid of the file publiccms-parent/publiccms-trade/src/main/java/com/publiccms/logic/service/trade/TradePaymentService.java of the component Trade Payment Handler. The manipulation of the argument paymentId leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 7329437e1288540336b1c66c114ed3363adcba02. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 08:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21626 | Extension - stackideas.com - Information disclosure in post custom fields in EasyDiscuss 1.0.0-5.0.15 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21626</link><description>Access control settings for forum post custom fields are not applied to the JSON output type, leading to an ACL violation vector an information disclosure</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1279 | Employee Directory &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;form_title&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1279</link><description>The Employee Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'form_title' parameter in the `search_employee_directory` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2009 | SourceCodester Gas Agency Management System createUser.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2009</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Gas Agency Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /gasmark/php_action/createUser.php. Executing a manipulation can lead to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2008 | abhiphile fermat-mcp eqn_chart.py eqn_chart code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2008</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in abhiphile fermat-mcp up to 47f11def1cd37e45dd060f30cdce346cbdbd6f0a. This vulnerability affects the function eqn_chart of the file fmcp/mpl_mcp/core/eqn_chart.py. Performing a manipulation of the argument equations results in code injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10753 | OAuth Single Sign On â€“ SSO (OAuth Client) &amp;lt;= 6.26.14 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10753</link><description>The OAuth Single Sign On â€“ SSO (OAuth Client) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access in all versions up to, and including, 6.26.14. This is due to missing capability checks and authentication verification on the OAuth redirect functionality accessible via the 'oauthredirect' option parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to set the global redirect URL option via the redirect_url parameter granted they can access the site directly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1401 | Tune Library &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via CSV Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1401</link><description>The Tune Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via CSV import in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected page. The vulnerability exists because the CSV import functionality lacks authorization checks and doesn't sanitize imported data, which is later rendered without escaping through the [tune-library] shortcode.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1808 | Orange Confort+ accessibility toolbar for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1808</link><description>The Orange Confort+ accessibility toolbar for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'style' parameter of the ocplus_button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1888 | Docus &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1888</link><description>The Docus â€“ YouTube Video Playlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'docusplaylist' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1909 | WaveSurfer-WP &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;src&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1909</link><description>The WaveSurfer-WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's audio shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'src' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2000 | DCN DCME-320 Web Management Backend bridge_cfg.php apply_config command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DCN DCME-320 up to 20260121. Impacted is the function apply_config of the file /function/system/basic/bridge_cfg.php of the component Web Management Backend. Performing a manipulation of the argument ip_list results in command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0521 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in PDF Export Error Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0521</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the PDF export functionality of the TYDAC AG MAP+ solution allows unauthenticated attackers to craft a malicious URL, that if visited by a victim, will execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim's context. Such a URL could be delivered through various means, for instance, by sending a link or by tricking victims to visit a page crafted by the attacker.



This issue was verified in MAP+: 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1998 | micropython runtime.c mp_import_all memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1998</link><description>A flaw has been found in micropython up to 1.27.0. This vulnerability affects the function mp_import_all of the file py/runtime.c. This manipulation causes memory corruption. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. Patch name: 570744d06c5ba9dba59b4c3f432ca4f0abd396b6. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0598 | Ansible-lightspeed: broken object level authorization leading to cross-user ai conversation context injection in ansible lightspeed api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0598</link><description>A security flaw was identified in the Ansible Lightspeed API conversation endpoints that handle AI chat interactions. The APIs do not properly verify whether a conversation identifier belongs to the authenticated user making the request. As a result, an attacker with valid credentials could access or influence conversations owned by other users. This exposes sensitive conversation data and allows unauthorized manipulation of AI-generated outputs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1991 | libuvc UVC Descriptor device.c uvc_scan_streaming null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1991</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in libuvc up to 0.0.7. Affected is the function uvc_scan_streaming of the file src/device.c of the component UVC Descriptor Handler. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1990 | oatpp Type.hpp ObjectWrapper null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1990</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in oatpp up to 1.3.1. This impacts the function oatpp::data::type::ObjectWrapper::ObjectWrapper of the file src/oatpp/data/type/Type.hpp. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1978 | kalyan02 NanoCMS User Information pagesdata.txt direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1978</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in kalyan02 NanoCMS up to 0.4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /data/pagesdata.txt of the component User Information Handler. Performing a manipulation results in direct request. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. You should change the configuration settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1979 | mruby JMPNOT-to-JMPIF Optimization vm.c mrb_vm_exec use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1979</link><description>A flaw has been found in mruby up to 3.4.0. This affects the function mrb_vm_exec of the file src/vm.c of the component JMPNOT-to-JMPIF Optimization. Executing a manipulation can lead to use after free. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called e50f15c1c6e131fa7934355eb02b8173b13df415. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15566 | ingress-nginx auth-proxy-set-headers nginx configuration injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15566</link><description>A security issue was discovered in ingress-nginxÂ where the `nginx.ingress.kubernetes.io/auth-proxy-set-headers` Ingress annotation can be used to inject configuration into nginx. This can lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the ingress-nginx controller, and disclosure of Secrets accessible to the controller. (Note that in the default installation, the controller can access all Secrets cluster-wide.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1977 | isaacwasserman mcp-vegalite-server visualize_data eval code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1977</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in isaacwasserman mcp-vegalite-server up to 16aefed598b8cd897b78e99b907f6e2984572c61. Affected by this vulnerability is the function eval of the component visualize_data. Such manipulation of the argument vegalite_specification leads to code injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 05:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1228 | Timeline Block &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Private Timeline Exposure via Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1228</link><description>The Timeline Block â€“ Beautiful Timeline Builder for WordPress (Vertical &amp; Horizontal Timelines) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 via the tlgb_shortcode() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to disclose private timeline content via the id attribute supplied to the 'timeline_block' shortcode.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1975 | Free5GC pfcp_reports.go identityTriggerType null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1975</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Free5GC up to 4.1.0. This impacts the function identityTriggerType of the file pfcp_reports.go. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1976 | Free5GC SMF SessionDeletionResponse null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1976</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Free5GC up to 4.1.0. Affected is the function SessionDeletionResponse of the component SMF. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1973 | Free5GC SMF establishPfcpSession null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1973</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Free5GC up to 4.1.0. The impacted element is the function establishPfcpSession of the component SMF. Executing a manipulation can lead to null pointer dereference. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1974 | Free5GC SMF datapath.go ResolveNodeIdToIp denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1974</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Free5GC up to 4.1.0. This affects the function ResolveNodeIdToIp of the file internal/sbi/processor/datapath.go of the component SMF. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1972 | Edimax BR-6208AC auth_check_userpass2 default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1972</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Edimax BR-6208AC 2_1.02. The affected element is the function auth_check_userpass2. Performing a manipulation of the argument Username/Password results in use of default credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor confirms that the affected product is end-of-life. They confirm that they "will issue a consolidated Security Advisory on our official support website." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1971 | Edimax BR-6288ACL wiz_WISP24gmanual.asp wiz_WISP24gmanual cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1971</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Edimax BR-6288ACL up to 1.12. Impacted is the function wiz_WISP24gmanual of the file wiz_WISP24gmanual.asp. Such manipulation of the argument manualssid leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor confirms that the affected product is end-of-life. They confirm that they "will issue a consolidated Security Advisory on our official support website." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>