<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:55:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-12931 | SourceCodester Food Ordering System edit-orders.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12931</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /routers/edit-orders.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59777 | NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59777</link><description>NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the master branch of the libmicrohttpd Git repository, after the v1.0.2 tag. A specially crafted packet sent by an attacker could cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62689 | NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62689</link><description>NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the master branch of the libmicrohttpd Git repository, after the v1.0.2 tag. A specially crafted packet sent by an attacker could cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12930 | SourceCodester Food Ordering System view-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12930</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12929 | SourceCodester Survey Application System LoginRegistration.php update_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12929</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Survey Application System 1.0. This impacts the function save_user/update_user of the file /LoginRegistration.php. Executing manipulation of the argument fullname can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12867 | Hundred Plus｜EIP Plus - Arbitrary File Uplaod</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12867</link><description>EIP Plus developed by Hundred Plus has an Arbitrary File Uplaod vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12868 | CyberTutor｜New Site Server - Use of Client-Side Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12868</link><description>New Site Server developed by CyberTutor has a Use of Client-Side Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to modify the frontend code to gain administrator privileges on the website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12928 | code-projects Online Job Search Engine login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12928</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Online Job Search Engine 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument username/phone results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12866 | Hundred Plus｜EIP Plus - Weak Password Recovery Mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12866</link><description>EIP Plus developed by Hundred Plus has a Weak Password Recovery Mechanism vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attacker to predict or brute-force the 'forgot password' link, thereby successfully resetting any user's password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12927 | DedeBIZ archives_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12927</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/archives_add.php. Such manipulation of the argument flags[] leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12864 | e-Excellence｜U-Office Force - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12864</link><description>U-Office Force developed by e-Excellence has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attacker to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12865 | e-Excellence｜U-Office Force - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12865</link><description>U-Office Force developed by e-Excellence has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attacker to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12926 | SourceCodester Farm Management System review.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12926</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Farm Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /review.php. This manipulation of the argument pid causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12924 | rymcu forest BankController.java GlobalResult authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12924</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in rymcu forest up to de53ce79db9faa2efc4e79ce1077a302c42a1224. This issue affects the function GlobalResult of the file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/web/api/bank/BankController.java. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12925 | rymcu forest UserDicController.java deleteDic authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12925</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in rymcu forest up to de53ce79db9faa2efc4e79ce1077a302c42a1224. Impacted is the function getAll/addDic/getAllDic/deleteDic of the file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/lucene/api/UserDicController.java. The manipulation results in missing authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12922 | OpenClinica Community Edition CRF Data Import ImportCRFData path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12922</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenClinica Community Edition up to 3.12.2/3.13. This affects an unknown part of the file /ImportCRFData?action=confirm of the component CRF Data Import. Performing manipulation of the argument xml_file results in path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 01:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12923 | liweiyi ChestnutCMS download resourceDownload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12923</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in liweiyi ChestnutCMS up to 1.5.8. This vulnerability affects the function resourceDownload of the file /dev-api/common/download. Executing manipulation of the argument path can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 01:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12921 | OpenClinica Community Edition CRF Data Import ImportCRFData xml injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12921</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in OpenClinica Community Edition up to 3.12.2/3.13. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ImportCRFData?action=confirm of the component CRF Data Import. Such manipulation of the argument xml_file leads to xml injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12920 | qianfox FoxCMS Product.php edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12920</link><description>A flaw has been found in qianfox FoxCMS up to 1.2.16. Affected by this vulnerability is the function add/edit of the file app/admin/controller/Product.php. This manipulation of the argument Title causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12919 | EverShop Order Order.resolvers.js resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12919</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in EverShop up to 2.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/modules/oms/graphql/types/Order/Order.resolvers.js of the component Order Handler. The manipulation of the argument uuid results in improper control of resource identifiers. The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12918 | yungifez Skuul School Management System View Fee Invoice fee-invoices resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12918</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yungifez Skuul School Management System up to 2.6.5. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/fees/fee-invoices/ of the component View Fee Invoice. Performing manipulation of the argument invoice_id results in improper control of resource identifiers. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12917 | TOZED ZLT T10 Reboot proc_post denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12917</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in TOZED ZLT T10 T10PLUS_3.04.15. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /reqproc/proc_post of the component Reboot Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 07:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40108 | serial: qcom-geni: Fix blocked task</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40108</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

serial: qcom-geni: Fix blocked task

Revert commit 1afa70632c39 ("serial: qcom-geni: Enable PM runtime for
serial driver") and its dependent commit 86fa39dd6fb7 ("serial:
qcom-geni: Enable Serial on SA8255p Qualcomm platforms") because the
first one causes regression - hang task on Qualcomm RB1 board (QRB2210)
and unable to use serial at all during normal boot:

  INFO: task kworker/u16:0:12 blocked for more than 42 seconds.
        Not tainted 6.17.0-rc1-00004-g53e760d89498 #9
  "echo 0 &gt; /proc/sys/kernel/hung_task_timeout_secs" disables this message.
  task:kworker/u16:0   state:D stack:0     pid:12    tgid:12    ppid:2      task_flags:0x4208060 flags:0x00000010
  Workqueue: async async_run_entry_fn
  Call trace:
   __switch_to+0xe8/0x1a0 (T)
   __schedule+0x290/0x7c0
   schedule+0x34/0x118
   rpm_resume+0x14c/0x66c
   rpm_resume+0x2a4/0x66c
   rpm_resume+0x2a4/0x66c
   rpm_resume+0x2a4/0x66c
   __pm_runtime_resume+0x50/0x9c
   __driver_probe_device+0x58/0x120
   driver_probe_device+0x3c/0x154
   __driver_attach_async_helper+0x4c/0xc0
   async_run_entry_fn+0x34/0xe0
   process_one_work+0x148/0x290
   worker_thread+0x2c4/0x3e0
   kthread+0x118/0x1c0
   ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20

The issue was reported on 12th of August and was ignored by author of
commits introducing issue for two weeks.  Only after complaining author
produced a fix which did not work, so if original commits cannot be
reliably fixed for 5 weeks, they obviously are buggy and need to be
dropped.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40109 | crypto: rng - Ensure set_ent is always present</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40109</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: rng - Ensure set_ent is always present

Ensure that set_ent is always set since only drbg provides it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 04:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12916 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System Frontend portal_login command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12916</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System 3.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /fort/portal_login of the component Frontend. This manipulation of the argument loginUrl causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Upgrading to version 3.0.11 and 3.0.12 is recommended to address this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12915 | 70mai X200 Init Script file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12915</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 70mai X200 up to 20251019. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Init Script Handler. The manipulation results in file inclusion. The attack requires a local approach. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12914 | aaPanel BaoTa Backend database sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12914</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in aaPanel BaoTa up to 11.1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /database?action=GetDatabaseAccess of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 21:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12913 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site roomdel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12913</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/roomdel.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 20:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11448 | Gallery Plugin for WordPress – Envira Photo Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.11.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Gallery Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11448</link><description>The Gallery Plugin for WordPress – Envira Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the '/envira-convert/v1/bulk-convert' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to convert galleries to Envira galleries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11967 | Mail Mint &amp;lt;= 1.18.10 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11967</link><description>The Mail Mint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the process_contact_attribute_import function in all versions up to, and including, 1.18.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11980 | Quick Featured Images &amp;lt;= 13.7.3 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection via delete_orphaned</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11980</link><description>The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'delete_orphaned' function in all versions up to, and including, 13.7.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database, granted they can convince an author-level user or higher to add a malicious custom field value.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12092 | CYAN Backup &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12092</link><description>The CYAN Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'delete' functionality in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12399 | Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12399</link><description>The Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the /wp-json/srr/v1/app/upload/file REST endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12643 | Saphali LiqPay for donate &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12643</link><description>The Saphali LiqPay for donate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'saphali_liqpay' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12837 | aThemes Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Call To Action Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12837</link><description>The aThemes Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Call To Action widget in versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12098 | Academy LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;enqueue_social_login_script&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12098</link><description>The Academy LMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for Complete eLearning Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.8 via the 'enqueue_social_login_script' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including the Facebook App Secret if Facebook Social Login is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 08:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12099 | Academy LMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for Complete eLearning Solution &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection via &amp;#x27;import_all_courses&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12099</link><description>The Academy LMS – WordPress LMS Plugin for Complete eLearning Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.8 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'import_all_courses' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 08:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12621 | Flexible Refund and Return Order for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.42 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Refund Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12621</link><description>The Flexible Refund and Return Order for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'create_refund' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.42. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update the status of refund requests, including approving and refusing refunds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 07:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12498 | EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Booking Note Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12498</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized booking note creation due to a missing capability check on the 'booking_add_notes' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to add a note to the backend view of any booking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9334 | Better Find and Replace &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9334</link><description>The Better Find and Replace – AI-Powered Suggestions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Limited Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.7. This is due to insufficient input validation and restriction on the 'rtafar_ajax' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to call arbitrary plugin functions and execute code within those functions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:18:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11748 | Groups &amp;lt;= 6.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Group Join</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11748</link><description>The Groups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.0 via the 'group_id' parameter of the group_join function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to register for groups other than ones set in the shortcode.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11972 | Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI &amp;lt;= 3.40.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11972</link><description>The Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post_types' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.40.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12000 | WPFunnels &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12000</link><description>The WPFunnels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the wpfnl_delete_log() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12042 | Course Booking System &amp;lt;= 6.1.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Booking Data Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12042</link><description>The Course Booking System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check in the csv-export.php file in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to directly access the file and obtain an export of all booking data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12064 | WP2Social Auto Publish &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12064</link><description>The WP2Social Auto Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via PostMessage in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12112 | Insert Headers and Footers Code – HT Script &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12112</link><description>The Insert Headers and Footers Code – HT Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via adding scripts in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 due to insufficient capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12125 | HTML Forms &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12125</link><description>The HTML Forms – Simple WordPress Forms Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12161 | Smart Auto Upload Images &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12161</link><description>The Smart Auto Upload Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the auto-image creation functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12167 | Contact Form 7 AWeber Extension &amp;lt;= 0.1.42 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12167</link><description>The Contact Form 7 AWeber Extension plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_aweber_logreset' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.42. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the AWeber logs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12177 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.30 - Unauthenticated Cron Trigger due to Hardcoded Cron Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12177</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a hardcoded Cron key used in the deleteExpired() and clearTempDataCPCron() functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.30. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger these cron jobs leading to deletion of expired posts and clearing cache.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12193 | Mang Board WP &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12193</link><description>The Mang Board WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mp' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12353 | WPFunnels &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Unauthorized User Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12353</link><description>The WPFunnels – The Easiest Funnel Builder For WordPress And WooCommerce To Collect Leads And Increase Sales plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized user registration in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2. This is due to the plugin relying on a user controlled value 'optin_allow_registration' to determine if user registration is allowed, instead of the site-specific setting. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register new user accounts, even when user registration is disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7663 | Ovatheme Events Manager &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7663</link><description>The Ovatheme Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several functions in the /class-ovaem-ajax.php file in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete ticket files, download tickets, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11452 | Asgaros Forum &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11452</link><description>The Asgaros Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the '$_COOKIE['asgarosforum_unread_exclude']' cookie in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12583 | Simple Downloads List &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12583</link><description>The Simple Downloads List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_neofix_sdl_edit' AJAX endpoint along with many others in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to alter many of the plugin's settings/downloads and inject malicious web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64492 | SuiteCRM is Vulnerable to Authenticated Time Based Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64492</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 8.9.0 and below contain a time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to infer data from the database by measuring response times, potentially leading to the extraction of sensitive information. It is possible for an attacker to enumerate database, table, and column names, extract sensitive data, or escalate privileges. This is fixed in version 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64493 | SuiteCRM is Vulnerable to Authenticated Blind SQL Injection via GraphQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64493</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions 8.6.0 through 8.9.0, there is an authenticated, blind (time-based) SQL-injection inside the appMetadata-operation of the GraphQL-API. This allows extraction of arbitrary data from the database, and does not require administrative access. This issue is fixed in version 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64494 | Soft Serve does not sanitize ANSI escape sequences in user input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64494</link><description>Soft Serve is a self-hostable Git server for the command line. In versions prior to 0.10.0, there are several places where the user can insert data (e.g. names) and ANSI escape sequences are not being removed, which can then be used, for example, to show fake alerts. In the same token, git messages, when printed, are also not being sanitized. This issue is fixed in version 0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64495 | Open WebUI vulnerable to Stored DOM XSS via prompts when &amp;#x27;Insert Prompt as Rich Text&amp;#x27; is enabled resulting in ATO/RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64495</link><description>Open WebUI is a self-hosted artificial intelligence platform designed to operate entirely offline. In versions 0.6.34 and below, the functionality that inserts custom prompts into the chat window is vulnerable to DOM XSS when 'Insert Prompt as Rich Text' is enabled, since the prompt body is assigned to the DOM sink .innerHtml without sanitisation. Any user with permissions to create prompts can abuse this to plant a payload that could be triggered by other users if they run the corresponding / command to insert the prompt. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.35.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64496 | Open WebUI Affected by an External Model Server (Direct Connections) Code Injection via SSE Events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64496</link><description>Open WebUI is a self-hosted artificial intelligence platform designed to operate entirely offline. Versions 0.6.224 and prior contain a code injection vulnerability in the Direct Connections feature that allows malicious external model servers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victim browsers via Server-Sent Event (SSE) execute events. This leads to authentication token theft, complete account takeover, and when chained with the Functions API, enables remote code execution on the backend server. The attack requires the victim to enable Direct Connections (disabled by default) and add the attacker's malicious model URL, achievable through social engineering of the admin and subsequent users. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.35.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64491 | SuiteCRM is vulnerable to unauthenticated reflected XSS through its Login page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64491</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.7 and below allow unauthenticated reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). Successful exploitation could lead to full account takeover, for example by altering the login form to send credentials to an attacker-controlled server. As a reflected XSS issue, exploitation requires the victim to open a crafted malicious link, which can be delivered via phishing, social media, or other communication channels. This issue is fixed in version 7.14.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64489 | SuiteCRM: Privilege Escalation via Improper Session Invalidation and Inactive User Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64489</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.7 and prior, 8.0.0-beta.1 through 8.9.0 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability where user sessions are not invalidated upon account deactivation. An inactive user with an active session can continue to access the application and, critically, can self-reactivate their account. This undermines administrative controls and allows unauthorized persistence. This issue is fixed in versions 7.14.8 and 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64490 | SuiteCRM&amp;#x27;s Inconsistent RBAC Enforcement Enables Access Control Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64490</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. Versions 7.14.7 and prior, 8.0.0-beta.1 through 8.9.0 allow a low-privileged user with a restrictive role to view and create work items through the Resource Calendar and project screens, even when the related modules (Projects, Project Tasks, Tasks, Leads, Accounts, Meetings, Calls) are explicitly set to Disabled/None in Role Management. This indicates inconsistent ACL/RBAC enforcement across modules and views, resulting in unauthorized data exposure and modification. This issue is fixed in versions 7.14.8 and 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64488 | SuiteCRM: Authenticated SQL Injection Possible in Reschedule Call Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64488</link><description>SuiteCRM is an open-source, enterprise-ready Customer Relationship Management (CRM) software application. In versions 7.14.7 and below and 8.0.0-beta.1 through 8.9.0 8.0.0-beta.1, an attacker can craft a malicious call_id that alters the logic of the SQL query or injects arbitrary SQL. An attack can lead to unauthorized data access and data ex-filtration, complete database compromise, and other various issues. This issue is fixed in versions 7.14.8 and 8.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>