<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:17:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-4737 | Insufficient encryption vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.aivoiceassistant) may lead to the risk of sensitive informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4737</link><description>Insufficient encryption vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.aivoiceassistant) may lead to the risk of sensitive information leakage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27525 | Information Exposure vulnerability in JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27525</link><description>Information Exposure vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager on Windows.This issue affects JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager: from 12-00 before 12-00-08, from 11-10 through 11-10-08, from 11-00 through 11-00-05, from 10-50 through 10-50-06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27523 | XXE vulnerability in JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27523</link><description>XXE vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager on Windows.This issue affects JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager: from 12-00 before 12-00-08, from 11-10 through 11-10-08, from 11-00 through 11-00-05, from 10-50 through 10-50-06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27524 | Weak encryption vulnerability in JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27524</link><description>Weak encryption vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager on Windows.This issue affects JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager: from 12-00 before 12-00-08, from 11-10 through 11-10-08, from 11-00 through 11-00-05, from 10-50 through 10-50-06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3742 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt; 2.5.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3742</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery WordPress plugin before 2.5.1 does not validate and escape some of its attributes before outputting them back in a page/post, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13914 | File Manager Advanced Shortcode &amp;lt;= Multiple Versions - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local JavaScript File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13914</link><description>The File Manager Advanced Shortcode WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 (file-manager-advanced-shortcode) and 2.5.6 (advanced-file-manager-pro-premium), via the 'file_manager_advanced' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary JavaScript files on the server. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. Sites currently using 2.5.4 (file-manager-advanced-shortcode) should be updated to 2.6.0 (advanced-file-manager-pro-premium).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48027 | The HttpAuth plugin in pGina.Fork through 3.9.9.12 allows authentication bypass when an adversary controls DNS resolution for pginaloginserv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48027</link><description>The HttpAuth plugin in pGina.Fork through 3.9.9.12 allows authentication bypass when an adversary controls DNS resolution for pginaloginserver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3053 | UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.07 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3053</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.07 via the uip_process_form_input() function. This is due to the function taking user supplied inputs to execute arbitrary functions with arbitrary data, and does not have any sort of capability check. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48024 | In BlueWave Checkmate before 2.1, an authenticated regular user can access sensitive application secrets via the /api/v1/settings endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48024</link><description>In BlueWave Checkmate before 2.1, an authenticated regular user can access sensitive application secrets via the /api/v1/settings endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3917 | 百度站长SEO合集(支持百度/神马/Bing/头条推送) &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3917</link><description>The 百度站长SEO合集(支持百度/神马/Bing/头条推送) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the download_remote_image_to_media_library function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4126 | EG-Series &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4126</link><description>The EG-Series plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [series] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes in the shortcode_title function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers - with contributor-level access and above, on sites with the Classic Editor plugin activated - to inject arbitrary JavaScript code in the titletag attribute that will execute whenever a user access an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4589 | Bon Toolkit &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4589</link><description>The Bon Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bt-map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4591 | Weluka Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4591</link><description>The Weluka Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'weluka-map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4579 | WP Content Security Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via CSP-Report Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4579</link><description>The WP Content Security Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blocked-uri and effective-directive  parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46836 | net-tools Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46836</link><description>net-tools is a collection of programs that form the base set of the NET-3 networking distribution for the Linux operating system. Inn versions up to and including 2.10, the Linux network utilities (like ifconfig) from the net-tools package do not properly validate the structure of /proc files when showing interfaces. `get_name()` in `interface.c` copies interface labels from `/proc/net/dev` into a fixed 16-byte stack buffer without bounds checking, leading to possible arbitrary code execution or crash. The known attack path does not require privilege but also does not provide privilege escalation in this scenario. A patch is available and expected to be part of version 2.20.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47783 | label-studio vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (Reflected) via the label_config parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47783</link><description>Label Studio is a multi-type data labeling and annotation tool. A vulnerability in versions prior to 1.18.0 allows an attacker to inject a malicious script into the context of a web page, which can lead to data theft, session hijacking, unauthorized actions on behalf of the user, and other attacks. The vulnerability is reproducible when sending a properly formatted request to the `POST /projects/upload-example/` endpoint. In the source code, the vulnerability is located at `label_studio/projects/views.py`. Version 1.18.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32421 | Next.js Race Condition to Cache Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32421</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. Versions prior to 14.2.24 and 15.1.6 have a race-condition vulnerability. This issue only affects the Pages Router under certain misconfigurations, causing normal endpoints to serve `pageProps` data instead of standard HTML. This issue was patched in versions 15.1.6 and 14.2.24 by stripping the `x-now-route-matches` header from incoming requests. Applications hosted on Vercel's platform are not affected by this issue, as the platform does not cache responses based solely on `200 OK` status without explicit `cache-control` headers. Those who self-host Next.js deployments and are unable to upgrade immediately can mitigate this vulnerability by stripping the `x-now-route-matches` header from all incoming requests at the content development network and setting `cache-control: no-store` for all responses under risk. The maintainers of Next.js strongly recommend only caching responses with explicit cache-control headers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 23:13:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45067 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Gaudi(R) software installers before version 1.18 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45067</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Gaudi(R) software installers before version 1.18 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29686 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29686</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the title parameter at /inform/InformManageController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29688 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29688</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the title parameter at /daymanager/daymanageabilitycontroller.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29689 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29689</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the password parameter at /mail/MailController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29690 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29690</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the outtype parameter at /address/AddrController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:25:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29691 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29691</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OA System before v2025.01.01 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the userName parameter at /login/LoginsController.java.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44879 | WS-WN572HP3 V230525 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the component /www/cgi-bin/upload.cgi. This vulnerability allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44879</link><description>WS-WN572HP3 V230525 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow in the component /www/cgi-bin/upload.cgi. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44024 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the Pichome system v2.1.0 and before. The vulnerability exists due to insufficien...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44024</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the Pichome system v2.1.0 and before. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient sanitization of user input in the login form. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into the username or password fields during the login process</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55569 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55569</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56427 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56427</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds access via malformed RRC packets to the target.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26783 | An issue was discovered in RRC in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26783</link><description>An issue was discovered in RRC in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, W1000, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. Incorrect handling of undefined values leads to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47884 | In Jenkins OpenID Connect Provider Plugin 96.vee8ed882ec4d and earlier the generation of build ID Tokens uses potentially overridden values ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47884</link><description>In Jenkins OpenID Connect Provider Plugin 96.vee8ed882ec4d and earlier the generation of build ID Tokens uses potentially overridden values of environment variables, in conjunction with certain other plugins allowing attackers able to configure jobs to craft a build ID Token that impersonates a trusted job, potentially gaining unauthorized access to external services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47885 | Jenkins Health Advisor by CloudBees Plugin 374.v194b_d4f0c8c8 and earlier does not escape responses from the Jenkins Health Advisor server, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47885</link><description>Jenkins Health Advisor by CloudBees Plugin 374.v194b_d4f0c8c8 and earlier does not escape responses from the Jenkins Health Advisor server, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to control Jenkins Health Advisor server responses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47886 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins Cadence vManager Plugin 4.0.1-286.v9e25a_740b_a_48 and earlier allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47886</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins Cadence vManager Plugin 4.0.1-286.v9e25a_740b_a_48 and earlier allows attackers to connect to an attacker-specified URL using attacker-specified username and password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47887 | Missing permission checks in Jenkins Cadence vManager Plugin 4.0.1-286.v9e25a_740b_a_48 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47887</link><description>Missing permission checks in Jenkins Cadence vManager Plugin 4.0.1-286.v9e25a_740b_a_48 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to connect to an attacker-specified URL using attacker-specified username and password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47888 | Jenkins DingTalk Plugin 2.7.3 and earlier unconditionally disables SSL/TLS certificate and hostname validation for connections to the config...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47888</link><description>Jenkins DingTalk Plugin 2.7.3 and earlier unconditionally disables SSL/TLS certificate and hostname validation for connections to the configured DingTalk webhooks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47889 | In Jenkins WSO2 Oauth Plugin 1.0 and earlier, authentication claims are accepted without validation by the "WSO2 Oauth" security realm, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47889</link><description>In Jenkins WSO2 Oauth Plugin 1.0 and earlier, authentication claims are accepted without validation by the "WSO2 Oauth" security realm, allowing unauthenticated attackers to log in to controllers using this security realm using any username and any password, including usernames that do not exist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27891 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27891</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds reads via malformed NAS packets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57096 | An issue in wps office before v.19302 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57096</link><description>An issue in wps office before v.19302 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25370 | An issue in realme GT 2 (RMX3311) running Android 14 with realme UI 5.0 allows a physically proximate attacker to obtain sensitive informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25370</link><description>An issue in realme GT 2 (RMX3311) running Android 14 with realme UI 5.0 allows a physically proximate attacker to obtain sensitive information via the show app only setting function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58101 | Samsung Galaxy Buds and Galaxy Buds 2 audio devices are Bluetooth pairable by default without user input nor a way to stop this mode. As a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58101</link><description>Samsung Galaxy Buds and Galaxy Buds 2 audio devices are Bluetooth pairable by default without user input nor a way to stop this mode. As a consequence, audio playback takeover or even microphone recording without user consent or notification is achieved. Note: This is considered a low severity vulnerability by the vendor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32363 | mediDOK before 2.5.18.43 allows remote attackers to achieve remote code execution on a target system via deserialization of untrusted data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32363</link><description>mediDOK before 2.5.18.43 allows remote attackers to achieve remote code execution on a target system via deserialization of untrusted data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45516 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0.0 before Patch 43, 10.0.x before 10.0.12, 10.1.x before 10.1.4, and 8.8.15 before ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45516</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0.0 before Patch 43, 10.0.x before 10.0.12, 10.1.x before 10.1.4, and 8.8.15 before Patch 47. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Zimbra Classic UI allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript within the victim's session, potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information. This issue arises from insufficient sanitization of HTML content, including malformed &lt;img /&gt; tags with embedded JavaScript. The vulnerability is triggered when the victim views a specially crafted email in the Classic UI, causing the malicious script to execute. No further user interaction is required beyond viewing the email.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33104 | CWE-79</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33104</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2900 | IBM Semeru Runtime denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2900</link><description>IBM Semeru Runtime 8.0.302.0 through 8.0.442.0, 11.0.12.0 through 11.0.26.0, 17.0.0.0 through 17.0.14.0, and 21.0.0.0 through 12.0.6.0 is vulnerable to a denial of service caused by a buffer overflow and subsequent crash, due to a defect in its native AES/CBC encryption implementation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0131 | GlobalProtect App: Incorrect Privilege Management Vulnerability in OPSWAT MetaDefender Endpoint Security SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0131</link><description>An incorrect privilege management vulnerability in the OPSWAT MetaDefender Endpoint Security SDK used by the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect™ app on Windows devices allows a locally authenticated non-administrative Windows user to escalate their privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. However, execution requires that the local user also successfully exploits a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0132 | Cortex XDR Broker VM: Unauthenticated User Can Disable Internal Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0132</link><description>A missing authentication vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR® Broker VM allows an unauthenticated user to disable certain internal services on the Broker VM. 

The attacker must have network access to the Broker VM to exploit this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0133 | PAN-OS: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in GlobalProtect Gateway and Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0133</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect™ gateway and portal features of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS® software enables execution of malicious JavaScript in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user's browser when they click on a specially crafted link. The primary risk is phishing attacks that can lead to credential theft—particularly if you enabled Clientless VPN.

There is no availability impact to GlobalProtect features or GlobalProtect users. Attackers cannot use this vulnerability to tamper with or modify contents or configurations of the GlobalProtect portal or gateways. The integrity impact of this vulnerability is limited to enabling an attacker to create phishing and credential-stealing links that appear to be hosted on the GlobalProtect portal.



For GlobalProtect users with Clientless VPN enabled, there is a limited impact on confidentiality due to inherent risks of Clientless VPN that facilitate credential theft. You can read more about this risk in the informational bulletin  PAN-SA-2025-0005 https://security.paloaltonetworks.com/PAN-SA-2025-0005   https://security.paloaltonetworks.com/PAN-SA-2025-0005 . There is no impact to confidentiality for GlobalProtect users if you did not enable (or you disable) Clientless VPN.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0134 | Cortex XDR Broker VM: Authenticated Code Injection Vulnerability in Broker VM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0134</link><description>A code injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR® Broker VM allows an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the host operating system running Broker VM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0135 | GlobalProtect App on macOS: Non Admin User Can Disable the GlobalProtect App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0135</link><description>An incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect™ App on macOS devices enables a locally authenticated non administrative user to disable the app.

The GlobalProtect app on Windows, Linux, iOS, Android, Chrome OS and GlobalProtect UWP app are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0136 | PAN-OS: Unencrypted Data Transfer when using AES-128-CCM on Intel-based hardware devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0136</link><description>Using the AES-128-CCM algorithm for IPSec on certain Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS® firewalls (PA-7500, PA-5400, PA-5400f, PA-3400, PA-1600, PA-1400, and PA-400 Series) leads to unencrypted data transfer to devices that are connected to the PAN-OS firewall through IPSec.

This issue does not affect Cloud NGFWs, Prisma® Access instances, or  PAN-OS VM-Series firewalls.

NOTE: The AES-128-CCM encryption algorithm is not recommended for use.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0137 | PAN-OS: Improper Neutralization of Input in the Management Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0137</link><description>An improper input neutralization vulnerability in the management web interface of the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS® software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to impersonate another legitimate authenticated PAN-OS administrator.


The attacker must have network access to the management web interface to exploit this issue. You greatly reduce the risk of this issue by restricting access to the management web interface to only trusted internal IP addresses according to our recommended  critical deployment guidelines https://live.paloaltonetworks.com/t5/community-blogs/tips-amp-tricks-how-to-secure-the-management-access-of-your-palo/ba-p/464431 .</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0138 | Prisma Cloud Compute Edition: Insufficient Session Expiration Vulnerability in the Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0138</link><description>Web sessions in the web interface of Palo Alto Networks Prisma® Cloud Compute Edition do not expire when users are deleted, which makes Prisma Cloud Compute Edition susceptible to unauthorized access.

Compute in Prisma Cloud Enterprise Edition is not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4640 | Out-of-bounds Write in pcl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4640</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in PointCloudLibrary pcl allows Overflow Buffers. Since version 1.14.0, PCL by default uses a zlib installation from the system, unless the user sets WITH_SYSTEM_ZLIB=FALSE. So this potential vulnerability is only relevant if the PCL version is older than 1.14.0 or the user specifically requests to not use the system zlib.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4641 | XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in WebDriverManager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4641</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in bonigarcia webdrivermanager WebDriverManager on Windows, MacOS, Linux (XML parsing components modules) allows Data Serialization External Entities Blowup. This vulnerability is associated with program files src/main/java/io/github/bonigarcia/wdm/WebDriverManager.java.

This issue affects webdrivermanager: from 1.0.0 before 6.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4638 | Improper Pointer Arithmetic in pcl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4638</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the inftrees.c component of the zlib library, which is bundled within the PointCloudLibrary (PCL). This issue may allow context-dependent attackers to cause undefined behavior by exploiting improper pointer arithmetic.

Since version 1.14.0, PCL by default uses a zlib installation from the system, unless the user sets WITH_SYSTEM_ZLIB=FALSE. So this potential vulnerability is only relevant if the PCL version is older than 1.14.0 or the user specifically requests to not use the system zlib.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4639 | Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference in Peergos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4639</link><description>CWE-611 Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference in the getDocumentBuilder() method of WebDav servlet in Peergos. This issue affects Peergos through version 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4637 | Divide By Zero in dlib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4637</link><description>Divide By Zero vulnerability in davisking dlib allows 

remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted file.

.This issue affects dlib: before &lt;19.24.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30668 | Zoom Workplace Apps - NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30668</link><description>Integer underflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46785 | Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows - Buffer Over-read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46785</link><description>Buffer over-read in some Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46786 | Zoom Workplace Apps  - Improper Neutralization of Special Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46786</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to impact app integrity via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4664 | Insufficient policy enforcement in Loader in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.113 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4664</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in Loader in Google Chrome prior to 136.0.7103.113 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0130 | PAN-OS: Firewall Denial-of-Service (DoS) in the Web-Proxy Feature via a Burst of Maliciously Crafted Packets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0130</link><description>A missing exception check in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS® software with the web proxy feature enabled allows an unauthenticated attacker to send a burst of maliciously crafted packets that causes the firewall to become unresponsive and eventually reboot. Repeated successful attempts to trigger this condition will cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode.

This issue does not affect Cloud NGFW or Prisma Access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30663 | Zoom Workplace Apps - Time-of-check Time-of-use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30663</link><description>Time-of-check time-of-use race condition in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30664 | Zoom Workplace Apps - Improper Neutralization of Special Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30664</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30665 | Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows - NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30665</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in some Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30666 | Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows - NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30666</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in some Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30667 | Zoom Workplace Apps - NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30667</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in some Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26784 | An issue was discovered in NAS in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26784</link><description>An issue was discovered in NAS in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47701 | Restrict route by IP - Critical - Cross Site Request Forgery - SA-CONTRIB-2025-047</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47701</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Drupal Restrict route by IP allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Restrict route by IP: from 0.0.0 before 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47702 | oEmbed Providers - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-048</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal oEmbed Providers allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects oEmbed Providers: from 0.0.0 before 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47703 | COOKiES Consent Management - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-049</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47703</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal COOKiES Consent Management allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects COOKiES Consent Management: from 0.0.0 before 1.2.14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47704 | Klaro Cookie &amp;amp; Consent Management - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-050</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47704</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Klaro Cookie &amp; Consent Management allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Klaro Cookie &amp; Consent Management: from 0.0.0 before 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47705 | IFrame Remove Filter - Moderately critical - Cross site scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-051</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47705</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal IFrame Remove Filter allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects IFrame Remove Filter: from 0.0.0 before 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47706 | Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-052</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47706</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability in Drupal Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal allows Remote Services with Stolen Credentials.This issue affects Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal: from 0.0.0 before 4.7.0, from 5.0.0 before 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47707 | Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal - Moderately critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-053</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47707</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal: from 0.0.0 before 4.7.0, from 5.0.0 before 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47708 | Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal - Critical - Cross Site Request Forgery - SA-CONTRIB-2025-054</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47708</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Drupal Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal: from 0.0.0 before 4.7.0, from 5.0.0 before 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47709 | Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal - Critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-055</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47709</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Drupal Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal: from 0.0.0 before 4.7.0, from 5.0.0 before 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47710 | Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal - Critical - Access bypass - SA-CONTRIB-2025-056</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47710</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Drupal Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Enterprise MFA - TFA for Drupal: from 0.0.0 before 4.7.0, from 5.0.0 before 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3875 | Thunderbird parses addresses in a way that can allow sender spoofing in case the server allows an invalid From address to be used. For examp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3875</link><description>Thunderbird parses addresses in a way that can allow sender spoofing in case the server allows an invalid From address to be used. For example, if the From header contains an (invalid) value "Spoofed Name  ", Thunderbird treats spoofed@example.com as the actual address. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.10.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3877 | A crafted HTML email using mailbox:/// links can trigger automatic, unsolicited downloads of .pdf files to the user's desktop or home direct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3877</link><description>A crafted HTML email using mailbox:/// links can trigger automatic, unsolicited downloads of .pdf files to the user's desktop or home directory without prompting, even if auto-saving is disabled. This behavior can be abused to fill the disk with garbage data (e.g. using /dev/urandom on Linux) or to leak Windows credentials via SMB links when the email is viewed in HTML mode. While user interaction is required to download the .pdf file, visual obfuscation can conceal the download trigger. Viewing the email in HTML mode is enough to load external content. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.10.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3909 | Thunderbird's handling of the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header can be exploited to execute JavaScript in the file:/// context. By cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3909</link><description>Thunderbird's handling of the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header can be exploited to execute JavaScript in the file:/// context. By crafting a nested email attachment (message/rfc822) and setting its content type to application/pdf, Thunderbird may incorrectly render it as HTML when opened, allowing the embedded JavaScript to run without requiring a file download. This behavior relies on Thunderbird auto-saving the attachment to /tmp and linking to it via the file:/// protocol, potentially enabling JavaScript execution as part of the HTML. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.10.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3932 | It was possible to craft an email that showed a tracking link as an attachment. If the user attempted to open the attachment, Thunderbird au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3932</link><description>It was possible to craft an email that showed a tracking link as an attachment. If the user attempted to open the attachment, Thunderbird automatically accessed the link. The configuration to block remote content did not prevent that. Thunderbird has been fixed to no longer allow access to web pages listed in the X-Mozilla-External-Attachment-URL header of an email. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.10.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 138.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40595 | A Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the SMA1000 Appliance Work Place interface. By using an encoded UR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40595</link><description>A Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the SMA1000 Appliance Work Place interface. By using an encoded URL, a remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially cause the appliance to make requests to unintended location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26785 | An issue was discovered in NAS in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26785</link><description>An issue was discovered in NAS in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, and Modem 5400. The lack of a length check leads to out-of-bounds writes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44186 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in /admin/Operation/User.php page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44186</link><description>SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in /admin/Operation/User.php page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44184 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/profile.php via the website_image,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44184</link><description>SourceCodester Best Employee Management System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/profile.php via the website_image, fname, lname, contact, username, and address parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47782 | motionEye vulnerable to RCE in add_camera Function Due to unsafe command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47782</link><description>motionEye is an online interface for the software motion, a video surveillance program with motion detection. In versions 0.43.1b1 through 0.43.1b3, using a constructed (camera) device path with the `add`/`add_camera` motionEye web API allows an attacker with motionEye admin user credentials to execute any command within a non-interactive shell as motionEye run user, `motion` by default. The vulnerability has been patched with motionEye v0.43.1b4. As a workaround, apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47781 | Rallly Insufficient Password Login Token Entropy Leads to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47781</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Versions up to and including 3.22.1 of the application features token based authentication. When a user attempts to login to the application, they insert their email and a 6 digit code is sent to their email address to complete the authentication. A token that consists of 6 digits only presents weak entropy however and when coupled with no token brute force protection, makes it possible for an unauthenticated attacker with knowledge of a valid email address to successfully brute force the token within 15 minutes (token expiration time) and take over the account associated with the targeted email address. All users on the Rallly applications are impacted. As long as an attacker knows the user's email address they used to register on the app, they can systematically take over any user account. For the authentication mechanism to be safe, the token would need to be assigned a complex high entropy value that cannot be bruteforced within reasonable time, and ideally rate limiting the /api/auth/callback/email endpoint to further make brute force attempts unreasonable within the 15 minutes time. As of time of publication, no patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47777 | 5ire Client Vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) and Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47777</link><description>5ire is a cross-platform desktop artificial intelligence assistant and model context protocol client. Versions prior to 0.11.1 are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting in chatbot responses due to insufficient sanitization. This, in turn, can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via unsafe Electron protocol handling and exposed Electron APIs. All users of 5ire client versions prior to patched releases, particularly those interacting with untrusted chatbots or pasting external content, are affected. Version 0.11.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47778 | Sulu vulnerable to XXE in SVG File upload Inspector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47778</link><description>Sulu is an open-source PHP content management system based on the Symfony framework. Starting in versions 2.5.21, 2.6.5, and 3.0.0-alpha1, an admin user can upload SVG which may load external data via XML DOM library. This can be used for insecure XML External Entity References. The problem has been patched in versions 2.6.9, 2.5.25, and 3.0.0-alpha3. As a workaround, one may patch the effect file `src/Sulu/Bundle/MediaBundle/FileInspector/SvgFileInspector.php` manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24969 | iTop portal user can see any other contact&amp;#x27;s picture</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24969</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. Prior to version 3.2.1, a portal user can see any other contacts picture by changing the picture ID in the URL. Version 3.2.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47775 | Bullfrog&amp;#x27;s DNS over TCP bypasses domain filtering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47775</link><description>Bullfrog is a GithHb Action to block unauthorized outbound traffic in GitHub workflows. Prior to version 0.8.4, using tcp breaks blocking and allows DNS exfiltration. This can result in sandbox bypass. Version 0.8.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24785 | iTop dashboard vulnerable to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24785</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. In version 3.2.0, an attacker may send a URL to the server to trigger a PHP error. The next user trying to load this dashboard would encounter a crashed start page. Version 3.2.1 fixes the issue by checking the provided layout_class before saving the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24022 | iTop server vulnerable to portal code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24022</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. Prior to versions 2.7.12, 3.1.3, and 3.2.1, server code execution is possible through the frontend of iTop's portal. This is fixed in versions 2.7.12, 3.1.3 and 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24026 | iTop Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24026</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. Versions prior to 3.2.1 are vulnerable to regular expression denial of service (ReDoS) that may, under some circumstances, affect iTop server. Version 3.2.1 doesn't use the affected variable in the regular expression. As a workaround, if iTop app_root_url is defined in the configuration file, then there is no possible way to exploit this ReDoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24021 | iTop doesn&amp;#x27;t have mass assignment of fields in the portal form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24021</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. Prior to versions 2.7.12, 3.1.3, and 3.2.1, anyone with an account having portal access can set value to object fields when they're not supposed to. Versions 2.7.12, 3.1.3, and 3.2.1 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56157 | iTop vulnerable to Self XSS in CSV Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56157</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. Prior to versions 3.1.3 and 3.2.1, by filling malicious code in a CSV content, a cross-site scripting attack can be performed when importing this content. The issue is fixed in versions 3.1.3 and 3.2.1. As a workaround, check CSV content before importing it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52601 | iTop portal Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52601</link><description>iTop is an web based IT Service Management tool. Prior to versions 2.7.12, 3.1.3, and 3.2.1, anyone with an account having portal access can have read access to objects they're not allowed to see by querying an unprotected route. Versions 2.7.12, 3.1.3, and 3.2.1 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10864 | SQL Injection vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Advanced Authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10864</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in OpenText Advance Authentication. This issue affects Advance Authentication versions before 6.5</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10865 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText Advanced Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10865</link><description>Improper Input validation leads to XSS or Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in OpenText Advance Authentication. This issue affects Advance Authentication version before 6.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54779 | Netgate pfSense CE (prior to 2.8.0 beta release) and corresponding Plus builds is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in widgets/log.wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54779</link><description>Netgate pfSense CE (prior to 2.8.0 beta release) and corresponding Plus builds is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in widgets/log.widget.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57273 | Netgate pfSense CE (prior to 2.8.0 beta release) and corresponding Plus builds is vulnerable to Cross-site scripting (XSS) in the Automatic ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57273</link><description>Netgate pfSense CE (prior to 2.8.0 beta release) and corresponding Plus builds is vulnerable to Cross-site scripting (XSS) in the Automatic Configuration Backup (ACB) service, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript, delete backups, or leak sensitive information via an unsanitized "reason" field and a derivable device key generated from the public SSH key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54780 | Netgate pfSense CE (prior to 2.8.0 beta release) and corresponding Plus builds are vulnerable to command injection in the OpenVPN widget due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54780</link><description>Netgate pfSense CE (prior to 2.8.0 beta release) and corresponding Plus builds are vulnerable to command injection in the OpenVPN widget due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input to the OpenVPN management interface. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary OpenVPN management commands via the remipp parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3600 | Unsafe Reflection Vulnerability in Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3600</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® UI for AJAX, versions 2011.2.712 to 2025.1.218, an unsafe reflection vulnerability exists that may lead to an unhandled exception resulting in a crash of the hosting process and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47436 | Apache ORC: Potential Heap Buffer Overflow during C++ LZO Decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47436</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Apache ORC.

A vulnerability has been identified in the ORC C++ LZO decompression logic, where specially crafted malformed ORC files can cause the decompressor to allocate a 250-byte buffer but then attempts to copy 295 bytes into it. It causes memory corruption.

This issue affects Apache ORC C++ library: through 1.8.8, from 1.9.0 through 1.9.5, from 2.0.0 through 2.0.4, from 2.1.0 through 2.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.9, 1.9.6, 2.0.5, and 2.1.2, which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53146 | media: dw2102: Fix null-ptr-deref in dw2102_i2c_transfer()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53146</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: dw2102: Fix null-ptr-deref in dw2102_i2c_transfer()

In dw2102_i2c_transfer, msg is controlled by user. When msg[i].buf
is null and msg[i].len is zero, former checks on msg[i].buf would be
passed. Malicious data finally reach dw2102_i2c_transfer. If accessing
msg[i].buf[0] without sanity check, null ptr deref would happen.
We add check on msg[i].len to prevent crash.

Similar commit:
commit 950e252cb469
("[media] dw2102: limit messages to buffer size")</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3931 | Yggdrasil: local privilege escalation in yggdrasil</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3931</link><description>A flaw was found in Yggdrasil, which acts as a system broker, allowing the processes to communicate to other children's "worker" processes through the DBus component. Yggdrasil creates a DBus method to dispatch messages to workers. However, it misses authentication and authorization checks, allowing every system user to call it. One available Yggdrasil worker acts as a package manager with capabilities to create and enable new repositories and install or remove packages. 

This flaw allows an attacker with access to the system to leverage the lack of authentication on the dispatch message to force the Yggdrasil worker to install arbitrary RPM packages. This issue results in local privilege escalation, enabling the attacker to access and modify sensitive system data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47445 | WordPress Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.26 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47445</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Themewinter Eventin allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Eventin: from n/a through 4.0.26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3769 | Latepoint &amp;lt;= 5.1.92 - Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3769</link><description>The LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.92 via the 'view_booking_summary_in_lightbox' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve appointment details such as customer names and email addresses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3834 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3834</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 8510 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in the OU History report.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3833 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3833</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus versions 6513 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in the MFA reports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24780 | Apache IoTDB: Remote Code Execution with untrusted URI of User-defined function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24780</link><description>Remote Code Execution with untrusted URI of UDF vulnerability in Apache IoTDB. The attacker who has privilege to create UDF can register malicious function from untrusted URI.

This issue affects Apache IoTDB: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.4, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26795 | Apache IoTDB JDBC driver: Exposure of Sensitive Information in IoTDB JDBC driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26795</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Apache IoTDB JDBC driver.

This issue affects iotdb-jdbc: from 0.10.0 through 1.3.3, from 2.0.1-beta before 2.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.2 and 1.3.4, which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26864 | Apache IoTDB: Exposure of Sensitive Information in IoTDB OpenID Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26864</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor, Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in the OpenIdAuthorizer of Apache IoTDB.

This issue affects Apache IoTDB: from 0.10.0 through 1.3.3, from 2.0.1-beta before 2.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.4 and 2.0.2, which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47292 | Cap Collectif vulnerable to insecure deserialization leading to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47292</link><description>Cap Collectif is an online decision making platform that integrates several tools. Before commit 812f2a7d271b76deab1175bdaf2be0b8102dd198, the `DebateAlternateArgumentsResolver` deserializes a `Cursor`, allowing any classes and which can be controlled by unauthenticated user. Exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to Remote Code Execution. The vulnerability is fixed in commit 812f2a7d271b76deab1175bdaf2be0b8102dd198.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4430 | Unauthorized file manipulation in EZD RP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4430</link><description>Unauthorized access to "/api/Token/gettoken" endpoint in EZD RP allows file manipulation.This issue affects EZD RP in versions before 20.19 (published on 22nd August 2024).</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2875 | CWE-610: Externally Controlled Reference to a Resource in Another Sphere vulnerability exists that could
cause a loss of confidentiality whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2875</link><description>CWE-610: Externally Controlled Reference to a Resource in Another Sphere vulnerability exists that could
cause a loss of confidentiality when an unauthenticated attacker manipulates controller’s webserver URL to
access resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13940 | Ninja Forms Webhooks &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Form Webhook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13940</link><description>The Ninja Forms Webhooks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7 via the form webhook functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8988 | PeepSo Core: File Uploads &amp;lt;= 6.4.6.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via file_download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8988</link><description>The PeepSo Core: File Uploads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.6.0 via the file_download REST API endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download files uploaded by others users and expose potentially sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0020 | ArcGIS Hidden Functionality Allows Insecure OAuth 2.0 Based Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0020</link><description>Violation of Secure Design Principles, Hidden Functionality, Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability in ArcGIS (Authentication) allows Privilege Abuse, Manipulating Hidden Fields, Configuration/Environment Manipulation.

The ArcGIS client_credentials OAuth 2.0 API implementation does not adhere to the RFC/standards; This hidden (known and by-design, but undocumented) functionality enables a requestor (Referred to as client in RFC 6749) to request an, undocumented, custom token expiration from ArcGIS (Referred to as authorization server in RFC 6749).</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52290 | Stored XSS in Configuration Key Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52290</link><description>LF Edge eKuiper is a lightweight internet of things (IoT) data analytics and stream processing engine. Prior to version 2.1.0 user with rights to modificate the service (e.g. kuiperUser role) can inject a cross-site scripting payload into Connection Configuration key `Name` (`confKey`) parameter. After this setup, when any user with access to this service (e.g. admin) tries to delete this key, a payload acts in the victim's browser. Version 2.1.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3623 | Uncanny Automator &amp;lt;= 6.4.0.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection in automator_api_decode_message Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3623</link><description>The Uncanny Automator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.0.1 via deserialization of untrusted input in the automator_api_decode_message() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to delete arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 03:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4520 | Uncanny Automator &amp;lt;= 6.4.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4520</link><description>The Uncanny Automator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX functions in versions up to, and including, 6.4.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions or above to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 03:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47905 | Varnish Cache before 7.6.3 and 7.7 before 7.7.1, and Varnish Enterprise before 6.0.13r14, allow client-side desync via HTTP/1 requests, beca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47905</link><description>Varnish Cache before 7.6.3 and 7.7 before 7.7.1, and Varnish Enterprise before 6.0.13r14, allow client-side desync via HTTP/1 requests, because the product incorrectly permits CRLF to be skipped to delimit chunk boundaries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4574 | Crossbeam-channel: crossbeam-channel vulnerable to double free on drop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4574</link><description>In crossbeam-channel rust crate, the internal `Channel` type's `Drop` method has a race condition which could, in some circumstances, lead to a double-free that could result in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26646 | .NET, Visual Studio, and Build Tools for Visual Studio Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26646</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28036 | Improper conditions check for some Intel(R) Arc™ GPU may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28036</link><description>Improper conditions check for some Intel(R) Arc™ GPU may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28954 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28954</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28956 | Exposure of Sensitive Information in Shared Microarchitectural Structures during Transient Execution for some Intel(R) Processors may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28956</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information in Shared Microarchitectural Structures during Transient Execution for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29222 | Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29222</link><description>Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31073 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Level Zero software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31073</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI Level Zero software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31150 | Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31150</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36292 | Improper buffer restrictions for some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Flex Series for Windows driver before version 31.0.101.4314 may allow an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36292</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions for some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Flex Series for Windows driver before version 31.0.101.4314 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39758 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) Arc™ &amp;amp; Iris(R) Xe graphics software before version 31.0.101.4032 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39758</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) Arc™ &amp;amp; Iris(R) Xe graphics software before version 31.0.101.4032 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39833 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) QAT software before version 2.3.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39833</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) QAT software before version 2.3.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43101 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Flex Series for Windows driver software before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43101</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Flex Series for Windows driver software before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43420 | Exposure of sensitive information caused by shared microarchitectural predictor state that influences transient execution for some Intel Ato...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43420</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information caused by shared microarchitectural predictor state that influences transient execution for some Intel Atom(R) processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45332 | Exposure of sensitive information caused by shared microarchitectural predictor state that influences transient execution in the indirect br...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45332</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information caused by shared microarchitectural predictor state that influences transient execution in the indirect branch predictors for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45333 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Flex Series for Windows driver before version 31.0.101.4314 may allow an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45333</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) Data Center GPU Flex Series for Windows driver before version 31.0.101.4314 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45371 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) Arc™ &amp;amp; Iris(R) Xe graphics software before version 32.0.101.6077 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45371</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) Arc™ &amp;amp; Iris(R) Xe graphics software before version 32.0.101.6077 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46895 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Arc™ &amp;amp; Iris(R) Xe graphics software before version 32.0.101.6083/32.0.101.5736 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46895</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Arc™ &amp;amp; Iris(R) Xe graphics software before version 32.0.101.6083/32.0.101.5736 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47550 | Incorrect default permissions for some Endurance Gaming Mode software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47550</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Endurance Gaming Mode software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47795 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software before version 2025.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47795</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software before version 2025.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47800 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47800</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48869 | Improper restriction of software interfaces to hardware features for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) 6 processor with E-cores when using Intel(R) Trus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48869</link><description>Improper restriction of software interfaces to hardware features for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) 6 processor with E-cores when using Intel(R) Trust Domain Extensions (Intel(R) TDX) or Intel(R) Software Guard Extensions (Intel(R) SGX) may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20003 | Improper link resolution before file access ('Link Following') for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software installers may allow an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20003</link><description>Improper link resolution before file access ('Link Following') for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software installers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20004 | Insufficient control flow management in the Alias Checking Trusted Module for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) 6 processor E-Cores firmware may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20004</link><description>Insufficient control flow management in the Alias Checking Trusted Module for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) 6 processor E-Cores firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20006 | Use after free for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20006</link><description>Use after free for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20008 | Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Simics(R) Package Manager software before version 1.12.0 may allow a privileged user to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20008</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Simics(R) Package Manager software before version 1.12.0 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20009 | Improper input validation in the UEFI firmware GenerationSetup module for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20009</link><description>Improper input validation in the UEFI firmware GenerationSetup module for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20012 | Incorrect behavior order for some Intel(R) Core™ Ultra Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20012</link><description>Incorrect behavior order for some Intel(R) Core™ Ultra Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via physical access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20013 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20013</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20015 | Uncontrolled search path element for some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection software before version 29.4 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20015</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element for some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection software before version 29.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20018 | Untrusted pointer dereference for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20018</link><description>Untrusted pointer dereference for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20022 | Insufficient control flow management for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a privileged user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20022</link><description>Insufficient control flow management for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20026 | Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20026</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20030 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20030</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20031 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20031</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20032 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow a privileged user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20032</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20034 | Improper input validation in the BackupBiosUpdate UEFI firmware SmiVariable driver for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards before v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20034</link><description>Improper input validation in the BackupBiosUpdate UEFI firmware SmiVariable driver for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards before version R01.02.0003 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20039 | Race condition for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20039</link><description>Race condition for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20041 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics software for Intel(R) Arc™ graphics and Intel(R) Iris(R) Xe graphics before version 32.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20041</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics software for Intel(R) Arc™ graphics and Intel(R) Iris(R) Xe graphics before version 32.0.101.6325/32.0.101.6252 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20043 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) RealSense™ SDK software before version 2.56.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20043</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) RealSense™ SDK software before version 2.56.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20046 | Use after free for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20046</link><description>Use after free for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20047 | Improper locking in the Intel(R) Integrated Connectivity I/O interface (CNVi) for some Intel(R) Core™ Ultra Processors may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20047</link><description>Improper locking in the Intel(R) Integrated Connectivity I/O interface (CNVi) for some Intel(R) Core™ Ultra Processors may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via physical access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20052 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) Graphics software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20052</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) Graphics software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20054 | Uncaught exception in the core management mechanism for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20054</link><description>Uncaught exception in the core management mechanism for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20057 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20057</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20062 | Use after free for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20062</link><description>Use after free for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20071 | NULL pointer dereference for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20071</link><description>NULL pointer dereference for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20076 | Improper access control for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an unauthenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20076</link><description>Improper access control for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20079 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Advisor software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20079</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Advisor software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20082 | Time-of-check time-of-use race condition in the UEFI firmware SmiVariable driver for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20082</link><description>Time-of-check time-of-use race condition in the UEFI firmware SmiVariable driver for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privileged user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20083 | Improper authentication in the firmware for the Intel(R) Slim Bootloader may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20083</link><description>Improper authentication in the firmware for the Intel(R) Slim Bootloader may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20084 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20084</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20095 | Incorrect Default Permissions for some Intel(R) RealSense™ SDK software before version 2.56.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20095</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions for some Intel(R) RealSense™ SDK software before version 2.56.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20100 | Improper access control in the memory controller configurations for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) 6 processor with E-cores may allow a privileged us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20100</link><description>Improper access control in the memory controller configurations for some Intel(R) Xeon(R) 6 processor with E-cores may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20101 | Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure or denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20101</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure or denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20103 | Insufficient resource pool in the core management mechanism for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20103</link><description>Insufficient resource pool in the core management mechanism for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20104 | Race condition in some Administrative Tools for some Intel(R) Network Adapters package before version 29.4 may allow an authenticated user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20104</link><description>Race condition in some Administrative Tools for some Intel(R) Network Adapters package before version 29.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20108 | Uncontrolled search path element for some Intel(R) Network Adapter Driver installers for Windows 11 before version 29.4 may allow an authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20108</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element for some Intel(R) Network Adapter Driver installers for Windows 11 before version 29.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20611 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20611</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20612 | Incorrect execution-assigned permissions for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20612</link><description>Incorrect execution-assigned permissions for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20616 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20616</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20618 | Stack-based buffer overflow for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow a privileged user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20618</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.100 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20623 | Exposure of sensitive information caused by shared microarchitectural predictor state that influences transient execution for some Intel(R) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20623</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information caused by shared microarchitectural predictor state that influences transient execution for some Intel(R) Core™ processors (10th Generation) may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20624 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20624</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20629 | Insecure inherited permissions in the NVM Update Utility for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Adapter E810 Series before version 4.60 may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20629</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in the NVM Update Utility for some Intel(R) Ethernet Network Adapter E810 Series before version 4.60 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21081 | Protection mechanism failure for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21081</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21094 | Improper input validation in the UEFI firmware DXE module for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privileged user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21094</link><description>Improper input validation in the UEFI firmware DXE module for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21099 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21099</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21100 | Improper initialization in the UEFI firmware for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privileged user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21100</link><description>Improper initialization in the UEFI firmware for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP boards may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22446 | Inadequate encryption strength for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22446</link><description>Inadequate encryption strength for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22448 | Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Simics(R) Package Manager software before version 1.12.0 may allow an authenticated user to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22448</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Simics(R) Package Manager software before version 1.12.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22843 | Incorrect execution-assigned permissions for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22843</link><description>Incorrect execution-assigned permissions for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22844 | Improper access control for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an unauthenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22844</link><description>Improper access control for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22848 | Improper conditions check for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22848</link><description>Improper conditions check for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22892 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some OpenVINO™ model server software maintained by Intel(R) before version 2024.4 may allow an unauthe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22892</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some OpenVINO™ model server software maintained by Intel(R) before version 2024.4 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22895 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22895</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23233 | Incorrect execution-assigned permissions for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23233</link><description>Incorrect execution-assigned permissions for some Edge Orchestrator software for Intel(R) Tiber™ Edge Platform may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24308 | Improper input validation in the UEFI firmware error handler for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP may allow a privileged user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24308</link><description>Improper input validation in the UEFI firmware error handler for the Intel(R) Server D50DNP and M50FCP may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24495 | Incorrect initialization of resource in the branch prediction unit for some Intel(R) Core™ Ultra Processors may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24495</link><description>Incorrect initialization of resource in the branch prediction unit for some Intel(R) Core™ Ultra Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43559 | ColdFusion | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43559</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms and execute code. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43560 | ColdFusion | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43560</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms and execute code. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43561 | ColdFusion | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43561</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication mechanisms and execute code. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43562 | ColdFusion | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command (&amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;) (CWE-78)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43562</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms and execute code. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43563 | ColdFusion | Improper Access Control (CWE-284)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43563</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in arbitrary file system read. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to access or modify sensitive data without proper authorization. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43564 | ColdFusion | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43564</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could result in arbitrary file system read. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to access or modify sensitive data without proper authorization. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43565 | ColdFusion | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43565</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security protections and execute code. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43566 | ColdFusion | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43566</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.1, 2023.13, 2021.19 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security protections and gain unauthorized read access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30314 | Adobe Connect | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30314</link><description>Adobe Connect versions 12.8 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30315 | Adobe Connect | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30315</link><description>Adobe Connect versions 12.8 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30316 | Adobe Connect | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30316</link><description>Adobe Connect versions 12.8 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43553 | Substance3D - Modeler | Uncontrolled Search Path Element (CWE-427)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43553</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.21.0 and earlier are affected by an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. If the application relies on a search path to locate critical resources such as libraries or executables, an attacker could manipulate the search path to load a malicious resource, potentially executing arbitrary code. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43554 | Substance3D - Modeler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43554</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.21.0 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43567 | Adobe Connect | Cross-site Scripting (Reflected XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43567</link><description>Adobe Connect versions 12.8 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. A successful attacker can abuse this to achieve session takeover, increasing the confidentiality and integrity impact as high.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43548 | Dimension | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43548</link><description>Dimension versions 4.1.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43549 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43549</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43551 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43551</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43568 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43568</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43569 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43569</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43570 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43570</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43571 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43571</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43572 | Dimension | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43572</link><description>Dimension versions 4.1.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45863 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the macstr parameter in the formMapDelDevice interface...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45863</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the macstr parameter in the formMapDelDevice interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3744 | Nomad Vulnerable To Violation Of Mandatory Sentinel Policies in Nomad Job Submissions via Policy Override</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3744</link><description>Nomad Enterprise (“Nomad”) jobs using the policy override option are bypassing the mandatory sentinel policies. This vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-3744, is fixed in Nomad Enterprise 1.10.1, 1.9.9, and 1.8.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45861 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the routername parameter in the formDnsv6 interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45861</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the routername parameter in the formDnsv6 interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45746 | In ZKT ZKBio CVSecurity 6.4.1_R an unauthenticated attacker can craft JWT token using the hardcoded secret to authenticate to the service co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45746</link><description>In ZKT ZKBio CVSecurity 6.4.1_R an unauthenticated attacker can craft JWT token using the hardcoded secret to authenticate to the service console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45865 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the dnsaddr parameter in the formDhcpv6s interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45865</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the dnsaddr parameter in the formDhcpv6s interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43545 | Bridge | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43545</link><description>Bridge versions 15.0.3, 14.1.6 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43546 | Bridge | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43546</link><description>Bridge versions 15.0.3, 14.1.6 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43547 | Bridge | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43547</link><description>Bridge versions 15.0.3, 14.1.6 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30330 | Illustrator | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30330</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.3, 28.7.5 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30328 | Animate | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30328</link><description>Animate versions 24.0.8, 23.0.11 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30329 | Animate | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30329</link><description>Animate versions 24.0.8, 23.0.11 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, causing disruption of service. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43555 | Animate | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43555</link><description>Animate versions 24.0.8, 23.0.11 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43556 | Animate | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43556</link><description>Animate versions 24.0.8, 23.0.11 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43557 | Animate | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43557</link><description>Animate versions 24.0.8, 23.0.11 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4660 | Remote Code Execution in Windows Secure Connector/ HPS Inspection Engine via Insecure Named Pipe Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4660</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the Windows agent component of SecureConnector due to improper access controls on a named pipe. The pipe is accessible to the Everyone group and does not restrict remote connections, allowing any network-based attacker to connect without authentication. By interacting with this pipe, an attacker can redirect the agent to communicate with a rogue server that can issue commands via the SecureConnector Agent. 



This does not impact Linux or OSX Secure Connector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30322 | Substance3D - Painter | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30322</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 11.0 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30324 | Photoshop Desktop | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30324</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 26.5, 25.12.2 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30325 | Photoshop Desktop | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30325</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 26.5, 25.12.2 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30326 | Photoshop Desktop | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30326</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 26.5, 25.12.2 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31358 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in the AMD Manageability API could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31358</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in the AMD Manageability API could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31359 | Incorrect default permissions in the AMD Manageability API could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31359</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in the AMD Manageability API could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27197 | Lightroom Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27197</link><description>Lightroom Desktop versions 8.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36321 | Unquoted search path within AIM-T Manageability Service can allow a local attacker to escalate privileges, potentially resulting in arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36321</link><description>Unquoted search path within AIM-T Manageability Service can allow a local attacker to escalate privileges, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0035 | Unquoted search path within AMD Cloud Manageability Service can allow a local attacker to escalate privileges, potentially resulting in arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0035</link><description>Unquoted search path within AMD Cloud Manageability Service can allow a local attacker to escalate privileges, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30318 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30318</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.5.2, ID20.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30319 | InDesign Desktop | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30319</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.5.2, ID20.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, causing a disruption in service. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30320 | InDesign Desktop | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30320</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID19.5.2, ID20.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, causing disruption in service. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47280 | Umbraco.Forms has HTML injection vulnerability in &amp;#x27;Send email&amp;#x27; workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47280</link><description>Umbraco Forms is a form builder that integrates with the Umbraco content management system. Starting in the 7.x branch and prior to versions 13.4.2 and 15.1.2, the 'Send email' workflow does not HTML encode the user-provided field values in the sent email message, making any form with this workflow configured vulnerable, as it allows sending the message from a trusted system and address, potentially bypassing spam and email client security systems. This issue affects all (supported) versions Umbraco Forms and is patched in 13.4.2 and 15.1.2. Unpatched or unsupported versions can workaround this issue by using the `Send email with template (Razor)` workflow instead or writing a custom workflow type. To avoid accidentally using the vulnerable workflow again, the `SendEmail` workflow type can be removed using a composer available in the GitHub Security Advisory for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36339 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in the AMD Optimizing CPU Libraries could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36339</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in the AMD Optimizing CPU Libraries could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6364 | Server Identity Validation Bypass in Absolute Persistence®</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6364</link><description>A vulnerability in Absolute Persistence® versions before 2.8 exists when it is not activated. This may allow a skilled attacker with both physical access to the device, and full hostile network control, to initiate OS commands on the device.  To remediate this vulnerability, update the device firmware to the latest available version. Please contact the device manufacturer for upgrade instructions or contact Absolute Security, see reference below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21264 | Visual Studio Code Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21264</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24063 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24063</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26677 | Windows Remote Desktop Gateway (RD Gateway) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26677</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26684 | Microsoft Defender Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26684</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26685 | Microsoft Defender for Identity Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26685</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27468 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27468</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27488 | Microsoft Windows Hardware Lab Kit (HLK) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27488</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29826 | Microsoft Dataverse Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29826</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29829 | Windows Trusted Runtime Interface Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29829</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29830 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29830</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29831 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29831</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29832 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29832</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29833 | Microsoft Virtual Machine Bus (VMBus) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29833</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29835 | Windows Remote Access Connection Manager Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29835</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29836 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29836</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29837 | Windows Installer Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29837</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29838 | Windows ExecutionContext Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29838</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29839 | Windows Multiple UNC Provider Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29839</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29840 | Windows Media Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29840</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29841 | Universal Print Management Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29841</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29842 | UrlMon Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29842</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29954 | Windows Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29954</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29955 | Windows Hyper-V Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29955</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29956 | Windows SMB Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29956</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29957 | Windows Deployment Services Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29957</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29958 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29958</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29959 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29959</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29960 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29960</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29961 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29961</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29962 | Windows Media Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29962</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29963 | Windows Media Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29963</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29964 | Windows Media Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29964</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29966 | Remote Desktop Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29966</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29967 | Remote Desktop Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29967</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29968 | Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29968</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29969 | MS-EVEN RPC Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29969</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29970 | Microsoft Brokering File System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29970</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29971 | Web Threat Defense (WTD.sys) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29971</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29973 | Microsoft Azure File Sync Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29973</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29974 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29974</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29975 | Microsoft PC Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29975</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29976 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29976</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29977 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29977</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29978 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29978</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29979 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29979</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30375 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30375</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30376 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30376</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30377 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30377</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30378 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30378</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30379 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30379</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30381 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30381</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30382 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30382</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30383 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30383</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30384 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30384</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30385 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30385</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30386 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30386</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30387 | Document Intelligence Studio On-Prem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30387</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30388 | Windows Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30388</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30393 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30393</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30394 | Windows Remote Desktop Gateway (RD Gateway) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30394</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30397 | Scripting Engine Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30397</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30400 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30400</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32701 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32701</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32702 | Visual Studio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32702</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32703 | Visual Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32703</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32704 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32704</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32705 | Microsoft Outlook Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32705</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32706 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32706</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32707 | NTFS Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32707</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32709 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32709</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21960 | Incorrect default permissions in the AMD Optimizing CPU Libraries (AOCL) installation directory could allow an attacker to achieve privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21960</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in the AMD Optimizing CPU Libraries (AOCL) installation directory could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30310 | Dreamweaver Desktop | Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type (&amp;#x27;Type Confusion&amp;#x27;) (CWE-843)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30310</link><description>Dreamweaver Desktop versions 21.4 and earlier are affected by an Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type ('Type Confusion') vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3757 | Authentication Bypass in OpenPubKey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3757</link><description>Versions of OpenPubkey library prior to 0.10.0  contained a vulnerability that would allow a specially crafted JWS to bypass signature verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4658 | Authentication Bypass in OPKSSH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4658</link><description>Versions of OpenPubkey library prior to 0.10.0  contained a vulnerability that would allow a specially crafted JWS to bypass signature verification. As OPKSSH depends on the OpenPubkey library for authentication, this vulnerability in OpenPubkey also applies to OPKSSH versions prior to 0.5.0 and would allow an attacker to bypass OPKSSH authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47204 | An issue was discovered in post.php in bootstrap-multiselect (aka Bootstrap Multiselect) 1.1.2. A PHP script in the source code echoes arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47204</link><description>An issue was discovered in post.php in bootstrap-multiselect (aka Bootstrap Multiselect) 1.1.2. A PHP script in the source code echoes arbitrary POST data. If a developer adopts this structure wholesale in a live application, it could create a Reflective Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable through Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47278 | Flask uses fallback key instead of current signing key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47278</link><description>Flask is a web server gateway interface (WSGI) web application framework. In Flask 3.1.0, the way fallback key configuration was handled resulted in the last fallback key being used for signing, rather than the current signing key. Signing is provided by the `itsdangerous` library. A list of keys can be passed, and it expects the last (top) key in the list to be the most recent key, and uses that for signing. Flask was incorrectly constructing that list in reverse, passing the signing key first. Sites that have opted-in to use key rotation by setting `SECRET_KEY_FALLBACKS` care likely to unexpectedly be signing their sessions with stale keys, and their transition to fresher keys will be impeded. Sessions are still signed, so this would not cause any sort of data integrity loss. Version 3.1.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45857 | EDIMAX CV7428NS v1.20 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the command parameter in the mp function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45857</link><description>EDIMAX CV7428NS v1.20 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the command parameter in the mp function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4427 | Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4427</link><description>An authentication bypass in the API component of Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile 12.5.0.0 and prior allows attackers to access protected resources without proper credentials via the API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4428 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4428</link><description>Remote Code Execution in API component in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile 12.5.0.0 and prior on unspecified platforms allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted API requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47276 | Actualizer Uses OpenSSL&amp;#x27;s  &amp;quot;-passwd&amp;quot; Function Which Uses SHA512 Under The Hood Instead of Proper Password Hasher like Yescript/Argon2i</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47276</link><description>Actualizer is a single shell script solution to allow developers and embedded engineers to create Debian operating systems (OS). Prior to version 1.2.0, Actualizer uses OpenSSL's  "-passwd" function, which uses SHA512 instead of a more suitable password hasher like Yescript/Argon2i. All Actualizer users building a full Debian Operating System are affected. Users should upgrade to version 1.2.0 of Actualizer. Existing OS deployment requires manual password changes against the alpha and root accounts. The change will deploy's Debian's yescript overriding the older SHA512 hash created by OpenSSL. As a workaround, users need to reset both `root` and "Alpha" users' passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46506 | NetAlertX 23.01.14 through 24.x before 24.10.12 allows unauthenticated command injection via settings update because function=savesettings l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46506</link><description>NetAlertX 23.01.14 through 24.x before 24.10.12 allows unauthenticated command injection via settings update because function=savesettings lacks an authentication requirement, as exploited in the wild in May 2025. This is related to settings.php and util.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56526 | An issue was discovered in OXID eShop before 7. CMS pages in combination with Smarty may display user information if a CMS page contains a S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56526</link><description>An issue was discovered in OXID eShop before 7. CMS pages in combination with Smarty may display user information if a CMS page contains a Smarty syntax error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28055 | upset-gal-web v7.1.0 /api/music/v1/cover.ts contains an arbitrary file read vulnerabilit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28055</link><description>upset-gal-web v7.1.0 /api/music/v1/cover.ts contains an arbitrary file read vulnerabilit</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31493 | Path traversal of collection names during file system lookup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31493</link><description>Kirby is an open-source content management system. A vulnerability in versions prior to 3.9.8.3, 3.10.1.2, and 4.7.1 affects all Kirby sites that use the `collection()` helper or `$kirby-&gt;collection()` method with a dynamic collection name (such as a collection name that depends on request or user data). Sites that only use fixed calls to the `collection()` helper/`$kirby-&gt;collection()` method (i.e. calls with a simple string for the collection name) are *not* affected. A missing path traversal check allowed attackers to navigate and access all files on the server that were accessible to the PHP process, including files outside of the collections root or even outside of the Kirby installation. PHP code within such files was executed. Such attacks first require an attack vector in the site code that is caused by dynamic collection names, such as `collection('tags-' . get('tags'))`. It generally also requires knowledge of the site structure and the server's file system by the attacker, although it can be possible to find vulnerable setups through automated methods such as fuzzing. In a vulnerable setup, this could cause damage to the confidentiality and integrity of the server. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.9.8.3, Kirby 3.10.1.2, and Kirby 4.7.1. In all of the mentioned releases, the maintainers of Kirby have added a check for the collection path that ensures that the resulting path is contained within the configured collections root. Collection paths that point outside of the collections root will not be loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45858 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the FUN_00459fdc function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45858</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the FUN_00459fdc function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46721 | nosurf vulnerable to CSRF due to non-functional same-origin request checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46721</link><description>nosurf is cross-site request forgery (CSRF) protection middleware for Go. A vulnerability in versions prior to 1.2.0 allows an attacker who controls content on the target site, or on a subdomain of the target site (either via XSS, or otherwise) to bypass CSRF checks and issue requests on user's behalf. Due to misuse of the Go `net/http` library, nosurf categorizes all incoming requests as plain-text HTTP requests, in which case the `Referer` header is not checked to have the same origin as the target webpage. If the attacker has control over HTML contents on either the target website (e.g. `example.com`), or on a website hosted on a subdomain of the target (e.g. `attacker.example.com`), they will also be able to manipulate cookies set for the target website. By acquiring the secret CSRF token from the cookie, or overriding the cookie with a new token known to the attacker, `attacker.example.com` is able to craft cross-site requests to `example.com`. A patch for the issue was released in nosurf 1.2.0. In lieu of upgrading to a patched version of nosurf, users may additionally use another HTTP middleware to ensure that a non-safe HTTP request is coming from the same origin (e.g. by requiring a `Sec-Fetch-Site: same-origin` header in the request).</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48766 | NetAlertX 24.7.18 before 24.10.12 allows unauthenticated file reading because an HTTP client can ignore a redirect, and because of factors r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48766</link><description>NetAlertX 24.7.18 before 24.10.12 allows unauthenticated file reading because an HTTP client can ignore a redirect, and because of factors related to strpos and directory traversal. This is related to components/logs.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22462 | An authentication bypass in Ivanti Neurons for ITSM (on-prem only) before 2023.4, 2024.2 and 2024.3 with the May 2025 Security Patch allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22462</link><description>An authentication bypass in Ivanti Neurons for ITSM (on-prem only) before 2023.4, 2024.2 and 2024.3 with the May 2025 Security Patch allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to gain administrative access to the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28056 | rebuild v3.9.0 through v3.9.3 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /admin/admin-cli/exec component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28056</link><description>rebuild v3.9.0 through v3.9.3 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /admin/admin-cli/exec component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30207 | Kirby vulnerable to path traversal in the router for PHP&amp;#x27;s built-in server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30207</link><description>Kirby is an open-source content management system. A vulnerability in versions prior to 3.9.8.3, 3.10.1.2, and 4.7.1 affects all Kirby setups that use PHP's built-in server. Such setups are commonly only used during local development. Sites that use other server software (such as Apache, nginx or Caddy) are not affected. A missing path traversal check allowed attackers to navigate all files on the server that were accessible to the PHP process, including files outside of the Kirby installation. The vulnerable implementation delegated all existing files to PHP, including existing files outside of the document root. This leads to a different response that allows attackers to determine whether the requested file exists. Because Kirby's router only delegates such requests to PHP and does not load or execute them, contents of the files were not exposed as PHP treats requests to files outside of the document root as invalid. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.9.8.3, Kirby 3.10.1.2, and Kirby 4.7.1. In all of the mentioned releases, the maintainers of Kirby have updated the router to check if existing static files are within the document root. Requests to files outside the document root are treated as page requests of the error page and will no longer allow to determine whether the file exists or not.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22460 | Default credentials in Ivanti Cloud Services Application before version 5.0.5 allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22460</link><description>Default credentials in Ivanti Cloud Services Application before version 5.0.5 allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28057 | owl-admin v3.2.2~ to v4.10.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin-api/system/admin_menus/save_order.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28057</link><description>owl-admin v3.2.2~ to v4.10.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin-api/system/admin_menus/save_order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30159 | Kirby vulnerable to path traversal of snippet names in the `snippet()` helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30159</link><description>Kirby is an open-source content management system. A vulnerability in versions prior to 3.9.8.3, 3.10.1.2, and 4.7.1 affects all Kirby sites that use the `snippet()` helper or `$kirby-&gt;snippet()` method with a dynamic snippet name (such as a snippet name that depends on request or user data). Sites that only use fixed calls to the `snippet()` helper/`$kirby-&gt;snippet()` method (i.e. calls with a simple string for the snippet name) are *not* affected. A missing path traversal check allowed attackers to navigate and access all files on the server that were accessible to the PHP process, including files outside of the snippets root or even outside of the Kirby installation. PHP code within such files was executed. Such attacks first require an attack vector in the site code that is caused by dynamic snippet names, such as `snippet('tags-' . get('tags'))`. It generally also requires knowledge of the site structure and the server's file system by the attacker, although it can be possible to find vulnerable setups through automated methods such as fuzzing. In a vulnerable setup, this could cause damage to the confidentiality and integrity of the server. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.9.8.3, Kirby 3.10.1.2, and Kirby 4.7.1. In all of the mentioned releases, Kirby maintainers have added a check for the snippet path that ensures that the resulting path is contained within the configured snippets root. Snippet paths that point outside of the snippets root will not be loaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44831 | EngineerCMS v1.02 through v2.0.5 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the /project/addproject interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44831</link><description>EngineerCMS v1.02 through v2.0.5 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the /project/addproject interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12533 | Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Phoenix SecureCore Technology 4 allows Input Data Manipulation.This is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12533</link><description>Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Phoenix SecureCore Technology 4 allows Input Data Manipulation.This issue affects SecureCore Technology 4: from 4.0.1.0 before 4.0.1.1018, from 4.1.0.1 before 4.1.0.573, from 4.2.0.1 before 4.2.0.338, from 4.2.1.1 before 4.2.1.300, from 4.3.0.1 before 4.3.0.244, from 4.3.1.1 before 4.3.1.187, from 4.4.0.1 before 4.4.0.299, from 4.5.0.1 before 4.5.0.231, from 4.5.1.1 before 4.5.1.103, from 4.5.5.1 before 4.5.5.36, from 4.6.0.1 before 4.6.0.67.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45864 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the addrPoolStart parameter in the formDhcpv6s interfa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45864</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the addrPoolStart parameter in the formDhcpv6s interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45866 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the addrPoolEnd parameter in the formDhcpv6s interface...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45866</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the addrPoolEnd parameter in the formDhcpv6s interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45867 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the static_dns1 parameter in the formIpv6Setup interfa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45867</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the static_dns1 parameter in the formIpv6Setup interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35281 | An improper isolation or compartmentalization vulnerability [CWE-653] in FortiClientMac version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.8 and below, 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35281</link><description>An improper isolation or compartmentalization vulnerability [CWE-653] in FortiClientMac version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.8 and below, 7.0 all versions and FortiVoiceUCDesktop 3.0 all versions desktop application may allow an authenticated attacker to inject code via Electron environment variables.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22859 | A Relative Path Traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiClientEMS 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and FortiClientEMS Cloud 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22859</link><description>A Relative Path Traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiClientEMS 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and FortiClientEMS Cloud 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to perform a limited arbitrary file write on the system via upload requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32756 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability [CWE-121] in Fortinet FortiVoice versions 7.2.0, 7.0.0 through 7.0.6, 6.4.0 through 6.4.10, Fort...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32756</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability [CWE-121] in Fortinet FortiVoice versions 7.2.0, 7.0.0 through 7.0.6, 6.4.0 through 6.4.10, FortiRecorder versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.0.0 through 7.0.5, 6.4.0 through 6.4.5, FortiMail versions 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, 7.0.0 through 7.0.8, FortiNDR versions 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.6, FortiCamera versions 2.1.0 through 2.1.3, 2.0 all versions, 1.1 all versions, allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via sending HTTP requests with specially crafted hash cookie.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45859 | TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the bandstr parameter in the formMapDelDevice interfac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45859</link><description>TOTOLINK A3002R v4.0.0-B20230531.1404 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the bandstr parameter in the formMapDelDevice interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44039 | CP-XR-DE21-S -4G Router Firmware version 1.031.022 was discovered to contain insecure protections for its UART console. This vulnerability a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44039</link><description>CP-XR-DE21-S -4G Router Firmware version 1.031.022 was discovered to contain insecure protections for its UART console. This vulnerability allows local attackers to connect to the UART port via a serial connection, read all boot sequence, and revealing internal system details and sensitive information without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36340 | A  junction point vulnerability within AMD uProf can allow a local low-privileged attacker to create junction points, potentially resulting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36340</link><description>A  junction point vulnerability within AMD uProf can allow a local low-privileged attacker to create junction points, potentially resulting in arbitrary file deletion or disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42446 | TOCTOU in SmmWhea</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42446</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition by local means. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4649 | ACL are not correctly taken into account in the display of the &amp;quot;event logs&amp;quot; page. This page requiring, high privileges, will display all available logs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4649</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Centreon web allows Privilege Escalation.
ACL are not correctly taken into account in the display of the "event logs" page. This page requiring, high privileges, will display all available logs.


This issue affects web: from 24.10.3 before 24.10.4, from 24.04.09 before 24.04.10, from 23.10.19 before 23.10.21, from 23.04.24 before 23.04.26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32917 | Privilege escalation in jar_signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32917</link><description>Privilege escalation in jar_signature agent plugin in Checkmk versions &lt;2.4.0b7 (beta), &lt;2.3.0p32, &lt;2.2.0p42, and 2.1.0p49 (EOL) allow user with write access to JAVA_HOME/bin directory to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4648 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS by altering the content of a SVG media during the submit request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4648</link><description>Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability in Centreon web allows Reflected XSS.
A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS by altering the content of a SVG media during the submit request.
This issue affects web: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.5, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.11, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.22, from 23.04.0 before 23.04.27, from 22.10.0 before 22.10.29.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23815 | A vulnerability has been identified in Desigo CC (All versions if access from Installed Clients to Desigo CC server is allowed from networks...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23815</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Desigo CC (All versions if access from Installed Clients to Desigo CC server is allowed from networks outside of a highly protected zone), Desigo CC (All versions if access from Installed Clients to Desigo CC server is only allowed within highly protected zones). The affected server application fails to authenticate specific client requests. Modification of the client binary could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the server database via the event port (default: 4998/tcp)</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51444 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.4). The application insufficientl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51444</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.4). The application insufficiently validates user input for database read queries. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct an SQL injection attack that bypasses authorization controls and allows to download any data from the application's database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51445 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.4). The affected application cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51445</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.4). The affected application contains a XML External Entity Injection (XXE) vulnerability in the docx import feature. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to read arbitrary data from the application server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51446 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.4). The file upload feature of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51446</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.4). The file upload feature of the affected application improperly sanitizes xml files. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting attack by uploading specially crafted xml files that are later downloaded and viewed by other users of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51447 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.2). The login implementation of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51447</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2310 (All versions), Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.2). The login implementation of the affected application contains an observable response discrepancy vulnerability when validating usernames. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to distinguish between valid and invalid usernames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24007 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIRIUS 3RK3 Modular Safety System (MSS) (All versions), SIRIUS Safety Relays 3SK2 (All versions). Aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24007</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIRIUS 3RK3 Modular Safety System (MSS) (All versions), SIRIUS Safety Relays 3SK2 (All versions). Affected devices only provide weak password obfuscation. An attacker with network access could retrieve and de-obfuscate the safety password used for protection against inadvertent operating errors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24008 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIRIUS 3RK3 Modular Safety System (MSS) (All versions), SIRIUS Safety Relays 3SK2 (All versions). The...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24008</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIRIUS 3RK3 Modular Safety System (MSS) (All versions), SIRIUS Safety Relays 3SK2 (All versions). The affected devices do not encrypt data in transit. An attacker with network access could eavesdrop the connection and retrieve sensitive information, including obfuscated safety passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24009 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIRIUS 3RK3 Modular Safety System (MSS) (All versions), SIRIUS Safety Relays 3SK2 (All versions). The...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24009</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIRIUS 3RK3 Modular Safety System (MSS) (All versions), SIRIUS Safety Relays 3SK2 (All versions). The affected devices do not require authentication to access critical resources. An attacker with network access could retrieve sensitive information from certain data records, including obfuscated safety passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24510 | A vulnerability has been identified in MS/TP Point Pickup Module (All versions). Affected devices improperly handle specific incoming BACnet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24510</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in MS/TP Point Pickup Module (All versions). Affected devices improperly handle specific incoming BACnet MSTP messages. This could allow an attacker residing in the same BACnet network to send a specially crafted MSTP message that results in a denial of service condition of the targeted device. A power cycle is required to restore the device's normal operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26389 | A vulnerability has been identified in OZW672 (All versions &lt; V8.0), OZW772 (All versions &lt; V8.0). The web service in affected devices does ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26389</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OZW672 (All versions &lt; V8.0), OZW772 (All versions &lt; V8.0). The web service in affected devices does not sanitize the input parameters required for the `exportDiagramPage` endpoint. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26390 | A vulnerability has been identified in OZW672 (All versions &lt; V6.0), OZW772 (All versions &lt; V6.0). The web service of affected devices is vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26390</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OZW672 (All versions &lt; V6.0), OZW772 (All versions &lt; V6.0). The web service of affected devices is vulnerable to SQL injection when checking authentication data. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to bypass the check and authenticate as
Administrator user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30174 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30174</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), SINEMA Remote Connect (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V17 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V18 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V19 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V20 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.1). Affected products contain a out of bound read buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30175 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30175</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), SINEMA Remote Connect (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V17 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V18 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V19 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V20 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.1). Affected products contain a out of bound write buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30176 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30176</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), SINEMA Remote Connect (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V17 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V18 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V19 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V20 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.1). Affected products contain a out of bound read buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31929 | A vulnerability has been identified in IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket (8EM1310-2EH04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket/ shutter (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31929</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket (8EM1310-2EH04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket/ shutter (8EM1310-2EN04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent cable 7m (8EM1310-2EJ04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent cable 7m incl. SIM (8EM1310-2EJ04-3GA2) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket (8EM1310-2EH04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket incl. SIM (8EM1310-2EH04-3GA2) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket/ shutter (8EM1310-2EN04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket/ shutter SIM (8EM1310-2EN04-3GA2) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3EJ04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Child socket (8EM1310-3EH04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Child socket/ shutter (8EM1310-3EN04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent cable 7m (8EM1310-3EJ04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent cable 7m incl. SIM (8EM1310-3EJ04-3GA2) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket (8EM1310-3EH04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket incl. SIM (8EM1310-3EH04-3GA2) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket/ shutter (8EM1310-3EN04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket/ shutter SIM (8EM1310-3EN04-3GA2) (All versions), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3FJ04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3FJ04-0GA1) (All versions), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3FJ04-0GA2) (All versions), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child socket (8EM1310-3FH04-0GA0) (All versions), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Parent socket (8EM1310-3FH04-3GA1) (All versions), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Parent socket incl. SI (8EM1310-3FH04-3GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Cellular 48A NTEP (8EM1310-5HF14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Child 40A w/ 15118 HW (8EM1310-4CF14-0GA0) (All versions), UL Commercial Child 48A BA Compliant (8EM1315-5CG14-0GA0) (All versions), UL Commercial Child 48A w/ 15118 HW (8EM1310-5CF14-0GA0) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 40A with Simcard (8EM1310-4CF14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A (USPS) (8EM1317-5CG14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A BA Compliant (8EM1315-5CG14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A with Simcard BA (8EM1310-5CF14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A, 15118, 25ft (8EM1310-5CG14-1GA1) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A, 15118, 25ft (8EM1314-5CG14-2FA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A, 15118, 25ft (8EM1315-5HG14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Commercial Parent 48A,15118 25ft Sim (8EM1310-5CG14-1GA2) (All versions), UL Resi High End 40A w/15118 Hw (8EM1312-4CF18-0FA3) (All versions), UL Resi High End 48A w/15118 Hw (8EM1312-5CF18-0FA3) (All versions), VersiCharge Blue™ 80A AC Cellular (8EM1315-7BG16-1FH2) (All versions). Affected devices do not contain an Immutable Root of Trust in M0 Hardware. An attacker with physical access to the device could use this to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31930 | A vulnerability has been identified in IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket (8EM1310-2EH04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket/ ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31930</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket (8EM1310-2EH04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Child socket/ shutter (8EM1310-2EN04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent cable 7m (8EM1310-2EJ04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent cable 7m incl. SIM (8EM1310-2EJ04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket (8EM1310-2EH04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket incl. SIM (8EM1310-2EH04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket/ shutter (8EM1310-2EN04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 1Ph 7.4kW Parent socket/ shutter SIM (8EM1310-2EN04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3EJ04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Child socket (8EM1310-3EH04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Child socket/ shutter (8EM1310-3EN04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent cable 7m (8EM1310-3EJ04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent cable 7m incl. SIM (8EM1310-3EJ04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket (8EM1310-3EH04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket incl. SIM (8EM1310-3EH04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket/ shutter (8EM1310-3EN04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC 3Ph 22kW Parent socket/ shutter SIM (8EM1310-3EN04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3FJ04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3FJ04-0GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child cable 7m (8EM1310-3FJ04-0GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Child socket (8EM1310-3FH04-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Parent socket (8EM1310-3FH04-3GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), IEC ERK 3Ph 22 kW Parent socket incl. SI (8EM1310-3FH04-3GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Cellular 48A NTEP (8EM1310-5HF14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Child 40A w/ 15118 HW (8EM1310-4CF14-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Child 48A BA Compliant (8EM1315-5CG14-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Child 48A w/ 15118 HW (8EM1310-5CF14-0GA0) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 40A with Simcard (8EM1310-4CF14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A (USPS) (8EM1317-5CG14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A BA Compliant (8EM1315-5CG14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A with Simcard BA (8EM1310-5CF14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A, 15118, 25ft (8EM1310-5CG14-1GA1) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A, 15118, 25ft (8EM1314-5CG14-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A, 15118, 25ft (8EM1315-5HG14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), UL Commercial Parent 48A,15118 25ft Sim (8EM1310-5CG14-1GA2) (All versions &lt; V2.135), VersiCharge Blue™ 80A AC Cellular (8EM1315-7BG16-1FH2) (All versions &lt; V2.135). Affected devices contain Modbus service enabled by default. This could allow an attacker connected to the same network to remotely control the EV charger.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32454 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.14), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32454</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.14), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0010), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0008), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0004). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32469 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32469</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1400 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1500 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1501 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1510 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1511 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1512 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1524 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1536 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5). The 'ping' tool in the web interface of affected devices is vulnerable to command injection due to missing server side input sanitation. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33024 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33024</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1400 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1500 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1501 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1510 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1511 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1512 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1524 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1536 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5). The 'tcpdump' tool in the web interface of affected devices is vulnerable to command injection due to missing server side input sanitation. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33025 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33025</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX MX5000RE (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1400 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1500 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1501 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1510 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1511 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1512 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1524 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX1536 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5), RUGGEDCOM ROX RX5000 (All versions &lt; V2.16.5). The 'traceroute' tool in the web interface of affected devices is vulnerable to command injection due to missing server side input sanitation. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40555 | A vulnerability has been identified in APOGEE PXC+TALON TC Series (BACnet) (All versions). Affected devices start sending unsolicited BACnet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40555</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in APOGEE PXC+TALON TC Series (BACnet) (All versions). Affected devices start sending unsolicited BACnet broadcast messages after processing a specific BACnet createObject request. This could allow an attacker residing in the same BACnet network to send a specially crafted message that results in a partial denial of service condition of the targeted device, and potentially reduce the availability of BACnet network. A power cycle is required to restore the device's normal operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40556 | A vulnerability has been identified in BACnet ATEC 550-440 (All versions), BACnet ATEC 550-441 (All versions), BACnet ATEC 550-445 (All vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40556</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in BACnet ATEC 550-440 (All versions), BACnet ATEC 550-441 (All versions), BACnet ATEC 550-445 (All versions), BACnet ATEC 550-446 (All versions). Affected devices improperly handle specific incoming BACnet MSTP messages. This could allow an attacker residing in the same BACnet network to send a specially crafted MSTP message that results in a denial of service condition of the targeted device. A power cycle is required to restore the device's normal operation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40566 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions &lt; V4.1 Update 3), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions &lt; V5.0 Update...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40566</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions &lt; V4.1 Update 3), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions &lt; V5.0 Update 1). Affected products do not correctly invalidate user sessions upon user logout. This could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker, who has obtained the session token by other means, to re-use a legitimate user's session even after logout.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40571 | A vulnerability has been identified in Mendix OIDC SSO (Mendix 10 compatible) (All versions &lt; V4.0.0), Mendix OIDC SSO (Mendix 9 compatible)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40571</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Mendix OIDC SSO (Mendix 10 compatible) (All versions &lt; V4.0.0), Mendix OIDC SSO (Mendix 9 compatible) (All versions). The Mendix OIDC SSO module grants read and write access to all tokens exclusively to the Administrator role and could result in privilege misuse by an adversary modifying the module during Mendix development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40572 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly assign permiss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40572</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly assign permissions to critical ressources.
This could allow a non-privileged local attacker to access sensitive information stored on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40573 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices are vulnerable to path travers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40573</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices are vulnerable to path traversal attacks.
This could allow a privileged local attacker to restore backups that are outside the backup folder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40574 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly assign permiss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40574</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly assign permissions to critical ressources.
This could allow a non-privileged local attacker to interact with the backupmanager service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40575 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate incom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40575</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate incoming Profinet packets.
An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this flaw by sending a specially crafted malicious packet, which leads to a crash of the dcpd
process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40576 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate incom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40576</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate incoming Profinet packets.
An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this flaw by sending a specially crafted malicious packet, which leads to a crash of the dcpd process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40577 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate incom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40577</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate incoming Profinet packets.
An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this flaw by sending a specially crafted malicious packet, which leads to a crash of the dcpd process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40578 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly handle multipl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40578</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly handle multiple incoming Profinet packets received in rapid succession.
An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this flaw by sending multiple packets in a very short time frame, which leads to a crash of the dcpd process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40579 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices are vulnerable to a stack-base...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40579</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices are vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow.
This could allow a non-privileged local attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device or to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40580 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices are vulnerable to a stack-base...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40580</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions). Affected devices are vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow.
This could allow a non-privileged local attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device or to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40581 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions with SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client installed)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40581</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions with SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client installed). Affected devices are vulnerable to an authentication bypass.
This could allow a non-privileged local attacker to bypass the authentication of the SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client, and to read and modify the configuration parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40582 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions with SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client installed)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40582</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions with SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client installed). Affected devices do not properly sanitize configuration parameters.
This could allow a non-privileged local attacker to execute root commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40583 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions with SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client installed)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40583</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions with SINEMA Remote Connect Edge Client installed). Affected devices do transmit sensitive information in cleartext.
This could allow a privileged local attacker to retrieve this sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40628 | SQL Injection in DomainsPRO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40628</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in DomainsPRO 1.2. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases via the “d” parameter in the “/article.php” endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4647 | A user with elevated privileges can bypass sanitization measures by replacing the content of an existing SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon web allows Reflected XSS.

A user with elevated privileges can bypass sanitization measures by replacing the content of an existing SVG.

This issue affects web: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.5, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.11, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.22, from 23.04.0 before 23.04.27, from 22.10.0 before 22.10.29.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22248 | [pgpool] Unauthenticated access to postgres through pgpool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22248</link><description>The bitnami/pgpool Docker image, and the bitnami/postgres-ha k8s chart, under default configurations, comes with an 'repmgr' user that allows unauthenticated access to the database inside the cluster. The PGPOOL_SR_CHECK_USER is the user that Pgpool itself uses to perform streaming replication checks against nodes, and should not be at trust level. This allows to log into a PostgreSQL database using the repgmr user without authentication. If Pgpool is exposed externally, a potential attacker could use this user to get access to the service. This is also present within the bitnami/postgres-ha Kubernetes Helm chart.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4646 | A high privilege user is able to create and use a valid admin API token in centreon-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4646</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Centreon web (API Token creation form modules) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects web: from 24.04.0 before 24.04.10, from 24.10.0 before 24.10.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41645 | SMA: Sunny Portal demo system privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41645</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker could use a demo account of the portal to hijack devices that were created in that account by mistake.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3916 | CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability exists that could cause local attackers being able to
exploit these issues to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3916</link><description>CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability exists that could cause local attackers being able to
exploit these issues to potentially execute arbitrary code while the end user opens a malicious project file (SSD
file) provided by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27696 | Apache Superset: Improper authorization leading to resource ownership takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27696</link><description>Improper Authorization vulnerability in Apache Superset allows ownership takeover of dashboards, charts or datasets by authenticated users with read permissions.

This issue affects Apache Superset: through 4.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.1.2 or above, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3107 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3107</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4317 | TheGem &amp;lt;= 5.10.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4317</link><description>The TheGem theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the thegem_get_logo_url() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:52:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4339 | TheGem &amp;lt;= 5.10.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Theme Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4339</link><description>The TheGem theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajaxApi() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary theme options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4473 | Frontend Dashboard 1.5.10 - 2.2.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via ajax_request Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4473</link><description>The Frontend Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the ajax_request() function in versions 1.0 to 2.2.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to control where the plugin sends outgoing emails. By pointing SMTP to their own server, attackers could capture password reset emails intended for administrators, and elevate their privileges for full site takeover.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4474 | Frontend Dashboard 1.0 - 2.2.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via fed_admin_setting_form_function Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4474</link><description>The Frontend Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the fed_admin_setting_form_function() function in versions 1.0 to 2.2.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the plugin’s 'register' role setting to make new user registrations default to the administrator role, leading to an elevation of privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4632 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory vulnerability in Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server version before 21.1052 allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4632</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory vulnerability in Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server version before 21.1052 allows attackers to write arbitrary file as system authority.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22246 | CVE-2025-22246 – UAA Private Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22246</link><description>Cloud Foundry UAA release versions from v77.21.0 to v7.31.0 are vulnerable to a private key exposure in logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22249 | VMSA-2025-0008: VMware Aria automation updates address a DOM based Cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2025-22249)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22249</link><description>VMware Aria automation contains a DOM based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A malicious actor may exploit this issue to steal the access token of a logged in user of VMware Aria automation appliance by tricking the user into clicking a malicious crafted payload URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4396 | Relevanssi &amp;lt;= 4.24.4 (Free) and &amp;lt;= 2.27.4 (Premium) - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4396</link><description>The Relevanssi – A Better Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the cats and tags query parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.4 (Free) and &lt;= 2.27.4 (Premium) due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries to already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35471 | conda-forge openssl-feedstock writable OPENSSLDIR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35471</link><description>conda-forge openssl-feedstock before 066e83c (2024-05-20), on Microsoft Windows, configures OpenSSL to use an OPENSSLDIR file path that can be written to by non-privilged local users. By writing a specially crafted openssl.cnf file in OPENSSLDIR, a non-privileged local user can execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the user or process loading openssl-feedstock DLLs. Miniforge before 24.5.0 is also affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26662 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SAP Data Services Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26662</link><description>The Data Services Management Console does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, allowing an attacker to inject malicious script. When a targeted victim, who is already logged in, clicks on the compromised link, the injected script gets executed within the scope of victim�s browser. This potentially leads to an impact on confidentiality and integrity. Availability is not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30009 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Live Auction Cockpit)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30009</link><description>he Live Auction Cockpit in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SRM) uses a deprecated java applet component within the affected SRM packages which allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious script in the victim�s browser. This vulnerability has low impact on confidentiality and integrity within the scope of that victim�s browser, with no effect on availability of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30010 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Live Auction Cockpit)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30010</link><description>The Live Auction Cockpit in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SRM) uses a deprecated java applet component within the affected SRM packages which allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a malicious link, which when clicked by a victim, redirects the browser to a malicious site. On successful exploitation, the attacker could cause low impact on confidentiality and integrity with no impact on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30011 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Live Auction Cockpit)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30011</link><description>The Live Auction Cockpit in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SRM) uses a deprecated java applet component within the affected SRM packages which allows an unauthenticated attacker to send an malicious request to the application, which could disclose the internal version details of the affected system. This vulnerability has low impact on confidentiality, with no effect on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30012 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Live Auction Cockpit)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30012</link><description>The Live Auction Cockpit in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SRM) uses a deprecated java applet component within the affected SRM stack to accept binary Java objects in specific encoding format. On successful exploitation, an authenticated attacker with high privileges could send malicious payload request and receive an outbound DNS request, resulting in deserialization of data in the application. This vulnerability has low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30018 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Live Auction Cockpit)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30018</link><description>The Live Auction Cockpit in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (SRM) allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit an application servlet request with a crafted XML file which when parsed, enables the attacker to access sensitive files and data. This vulnerability has a high impact on the application's confidentiality, with no effect on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31329 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31329</link><description>SAP NetWeaver is vulnerable to an Information Disclosure vulnerability caused by the injection of malicious instructions into user configuration settings. An attacker with administrative privileges can craft these instructions so that when accessed by the victim, sensitive information such as user credentials is exposed. These credentials may then be used to gain unauthorized access to local or adjacent systems. This results in high impact to Confidentiality, with no significant effect on Integrity or Availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42997 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Gateway Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42997</link><description>Under certain conditions, SAP Gateway Client allows a high-privileged user to access restricted information beyond the scope of the application. Due to the possibility of influencing application behavior or performance through misuse of the exposed data, this may potentially lead to low impact on confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42999 | Insecure Deserialization in SAP NetWeaver (Visual Composer development server)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42999</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer Metadata Uploader is vulnerable when a privileged user can upload untrusted or malicious content which, when deserialized, could potentially lead to a compromise of confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the host system.Note: Customers who have implemented the security note 3594142 should also implement this security note 3604119.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43000 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (PMW)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43000</link><description>Under certain conditions Promotion Management Wizard (PMW) allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.This has High impact on Confidentiality with Low impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43002 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S4/HANA (OData meta-data property)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43002</link><description>SAP S4CORE OData meta-data property allows an authenticated attacker to access restricted information due to missing authorization check. This could cause a low impact on confidentiality but integrity and availability of the application are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43003 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA (Private Cloud &amp;amp; On-Premise)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43003</link><description>SAP S/4 HANA allows an authenticated attacker with user privileges to configure a field not intended for their access and create a custom UI layout displaying this field. On performing this step the attacker could gain access to highly sensitive information. This could cause a high impact on confidentiality and minimal impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43004 | Security Misconfiguration Vulnerability in SAP Digital Manufacturing (Production Operator Dashboard)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43004</link><description>Due to a security misconfiguration vulnerability, customers can develop Production Operator Dashboards (PODs) that enable outside users to access customer data when they access these dashboards. Since no mechanisms exist to enforce authentication, malicious unauthenticated users can view non-sensitive customer information. However, this does not affect data integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43005 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP GUI for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43005</link><description>SAP GUI for Windows allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit insecure obfuscation algorithms used by the GuiXT application to store user credentials. While this issue does not impact the Integrity or Availability of the application, it may have a Low impact on the Confidentiality of data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43006 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Master Data Management Catalog)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43006</link><description>SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Master Data Management Catalogue) allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious scripts in the application, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application, but it can have some minor impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43007 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Service Parts Management (SPM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43007</link><description>SAP Service Parts Management (SPM) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing an attacker to escalate privileges. This has low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43008 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4HANA HCM Portugal and SAP ERP HCM Portugal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43008</link><description>Due to missing authorization check, an unauthorized user can view the files of other company. This might lead to disclosure of personal data of employees. There is no impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43009 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Service Parts Management (SPM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43009</link><description>SAP Service Parts Management (SPM) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing an attacker to escalate privileges. This has low impact on Confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43010 | Code injection vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition or On Premise(SCM Master Data Layer (MDL))</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43010</link><description>SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition or on Premise (SCM Master Data Layer (MDL)) allows an authenticated attacker with SAP standard authorization to execute a certain function module remotely and replace arbitrary ABAP programs, including SAP standard programs. This is due to lack of input validation and no authorization checks. This has low Confidentiality impact but high impact on integrity and availability to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43011 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP Landscape Transformation (PCL Basis)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43011</link><description>Under certain conditions, SAP Landscape Transformation's PCL Basis module does not perform the necessary authorization checks, allowing authenticated users to access restricted functionalities or data. This can lead to a high impact on confidentiality with no impact on the integrity or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>