<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:40:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-0547 | Ability FTP Server APPE Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0547</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Ability FTP Server 2.34 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component APPE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0548 | FreeFloat FTP Server SIZE Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0548</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component SIZE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250718 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0545 | CodeCanyon RISE Rise Ultimate Project Manager signin redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0545</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CodeCanyon RISE Rise Ultimate Project Manager 3.5.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php/signin. The manipulation of the argument redirect with the input http://evil.com leads to open redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250714 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0546 | EasyFTP LIST Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0546</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in EasyFTP 1.7.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component LIST Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250715.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0543 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System propertydetail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0543</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file propertydetail.php. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250713 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0541 | Tenda W9 httpd formAddSysLogRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0541</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formAddSysLogRule of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument sysRulenEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250711. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0542 | Tenda W9 httpd formWifiMacFilterGet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0542</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formWifiMacFilterGet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250712. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0539 | Tenda W9 httpd formQosManage_user stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0539</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formQosManage_user of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250709 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0540 | Tenda W9 httpd formOfflineSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0540</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formOfflineSet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250710 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0537 | Tenda W9 httpd setWrlBasicInfo stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0537</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). This affects the function setWrlBasicInfo of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250707. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0538 | Tenda W9 httpd formQosManage_auto stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0538</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formQosManage_auto of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250708. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0552 | Intumit inc. SmartRobot - Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0552</link><description>Intumit inc. SmartRobot's web framwork has a remote code execution vulnerability. An unauthorized remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0536 | Tenda W9 httpd setWrlAccessList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0536</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). Affected by this issue is the function setWrlAccessList of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250706 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 03:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0535 | Tenda PA6 httpd portmap cgiPortMapAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0535</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda PA6 1.0.1.21. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgiPortMapAdd of the file /portmap of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument groupName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250705 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 03:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48383 | NetVision Information airPASS - Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48383</link><description>NetVision

Information 

 airPASS has a path traversal vulnerability within its parameter in a specific URL. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0533 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface SetOnlineDevName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0533</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250703. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0534 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface SetOnlineDevName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0534</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250704. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0531 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface setBlackRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0531</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250701 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0532 | Tenda A15 Web-based Management Interface WifiExtraSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0532</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet of the component Web-based Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto2_4g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250702 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0530 | CXBSoft Post-Office HTTP POST Request reg_go.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0530</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CXBSoft Post-Office up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /apps/reg_go.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username_reg leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250700. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0529 | CXBSoft Post-Office HTTP POST Request login_auth.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0529</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CXBSoft Post-Office up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /apps/login_auth.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username_login leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250699. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0527 | CXBSoft Url-shorting HTTP POST Request update_go.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0527</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/pages/update_go.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument version leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250697 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0528 | CXBSoft Post-Office HTTP POST Request update_go.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0528</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CXBSoft Post-Office 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/pages/update_go.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument version leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0526 | CXBSoft Url-shorting HTTP POST Request short_to_long.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0526</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pages/short_to_long.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument shorturl leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250696. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0524 | CXBSoft Url-shorting index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0524</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250694 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0525 | CXBSoft Url-shorting HTTP POST Request long_s_short.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0525</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CXBSoft Url-shorting up to 1.3.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/long_s_short.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument longurl leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250695. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0522 | Allegro RomPager HTTP POST Request cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0522</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Allegro RomPager 4.01. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file usertable.htm?action=delete of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 4.30 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250692. NOTE: The vendor explains that this is a very old issue that got fixed 20 years ago but without a public disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0523 | CmsEasy language_admin.php getslide_child_action sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0523</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CmsEasy up to 7.7.7. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getslide_child_action in the library lib/admin/language_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250693 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0510 | HaoKeKeJi YiQiNiu Api.php http_post server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0510</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in HaoKeKeJi YiQiNiu up to 3.1. Affected by this issue is the function http_post of the file /application/pay/controller/Api.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250652.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 22:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0505 | ZhongFuCheng3y Austin Upload Material Menu MaterialController.java getFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZhongFuCheng3y Austin 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function getFile of the file com/java3y/austin/web/controller/MaterialController.java of the component Upload Material Menu. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250619.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0504 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System Make a Reservation Page add_reserve.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0504</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file add_reserve.php of the component Make a Reservation Page. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Lastname with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250618 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0503 | code-projects Online FIR System registercomplaint.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0503</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online FIR System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file registercomplaint.php. The manipulation of the argument Name/Address leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250611.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 20:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0502 | SourceCodester House Rental Management System Edit User manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0502</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file manage_user.php of the component Edit User. The manipulation of the argument id/name/username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250610 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 20:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0501 | SourceCodester House Rental Management System Manage Invoice Details cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0501</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Manage Invoice Details. The manipulation of the argument Invoice leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250609 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 19:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0500 | SourceCodester House Rental Management System Manage Tenant Details cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0500</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Manage Tenant Details. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250608.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 19:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0499 | SourceCodester House Rental Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0499</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250607.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0498 | Project Worlds Lawyer Management System searchLawyer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0498</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Lawyer Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file searchLawyer.php. The manipulation of the argument experience leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250603.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0497 | Campcodes Student Information System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0497</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Student Information System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 17:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0496 | Kashipara Billing Software HTTP POST Request item_list_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0496</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file item_list_edit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250601 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0495 | Kashipara Billing Software HTTP POST Request party_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0495</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_submit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250600.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 16:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0494 | Kashipara Billing Software HTTP POST Request material_bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0494</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file material_bill.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument itemtypeid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250599.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 16:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0493 | Kashipara Billing Software HTTP POST Request submit_delivery_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0493</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file submit_delivery_list.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument customer_details leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 15:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0492 | Kashipara Billing Software HTTP POST Request buyer_detail_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0492</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file buyer_detail_submit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument gstn_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250597 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 15:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0491 | Huaxia ERP UserController.java password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0491</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Huaxia ERP up to 3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/com/jsh/erp/controller/UserController.java. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250596.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 14:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0490 | Huaxia ERP getAllList information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0490</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Huaxia ERP up to 3.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/getAllList. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250595.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 14:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0489 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System edit_chicken.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0489</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/action/edit_chicken.php. The manipulation of the argument ref leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0488 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System new-feed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/action/new-feed.php. The manipulation of the argument type_feed leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250593 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0487 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System delete-vaccine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0487</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/action/delete-vaccine.php. The manipulation of the argument ref leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250592.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 12:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0486 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System add_con.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0486</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/action/add_con.php. The manipulation of the argument chicken leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250591.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 12:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0485 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System add_con.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0485</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/pages/tables/add_con.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250590 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 11:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0484 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System update_mother.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0484</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/action/update_mother.php. The manipulation of the argument age_mother leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250589 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0483 | Taokeyun HTTP POST Request Task.php index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0483</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. This vulnerability affects the function index of the file application/index/controller/app/Task.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250588.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0482 | Taokeyun HTTP POST Request Video.php index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0482</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. This affects the function index of the file application/index/controller/app/Video.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250587.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0481 | Taokeyun HTTP POST Request Goods.php shopGoods sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0481</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function shopGoods of the file application/index/controller/app/store/Goods.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250586 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21640 | OOB Access in CefVideoConsumerOSR::OnFrameCaptured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21640</link><description>Chromium Embedded Framework (CEF) is a simple framework for embedding Chromium-based browsers in other applications.`CefVideoConsumerOSR::OnFrameCaptured` does not check `pixel_format` properly, which leads to out-of-bounds read out of the sandbox. This vulnerability was patched in commit 1f55d2e.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22209 | XBlock custom auth does not respect JWT Scopes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22209</link><description>Open edX Platform is a service-oriented platform for authoring and delivering online learning. A user with a JWT and more limited scopes could call endpoints exceeding their access. This vulnerability has been patched in commit 019888f.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0251 | The Advanced Woo Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search parameter in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0251</link><description>The Advanced Woo Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.96 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This only affects sites when the Dynamic Content for Elementor plugin is also installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0480 | Taokeyun HTTP POST Request Drs.php index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0480</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function index of the file application/index/controller/m/Drs.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250585 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0479 | Taokeyun HTTP POST Request User.php login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0479</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function login of the file application/index/controller/m/User.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250584.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0478 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System edit_chicken.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0478</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/pages/edit_chicken.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250583.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 06:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0477 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System update-deworm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0477</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/action/update-deworm.php. The manipulation of the argument usage_deworm leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250582 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0476 | Blood Bank &amp;amp; Donor Management request-received-bydonar.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0476</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Blood Bank &amp; Donor Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file request-received-bydonar.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250581 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52288 | An issue was discovered in the flaskcode package through 0.0.8 for Python. An unauthenticated directory traversal, exploitable with a GET re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52288</link><description>An issue was discovered in the flaskcode package through 0.0.8 for Python. An unauthenticated directory traversal, exploitable with a GET request to a /resource-data/&lt;file_path&gt;.txt URI (from views.py), allows attackers to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52289 | An issue was discovered in the flaskcode package through 0.0.8 for Python. An unauthenticated directory traversal, exploitable with a POST r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52289</link><description>An issue was discovered in the flaskcode package through 0.0.8 for Python. An unauthenticated directory traversal, exploitable with a POST request to a /update-resource-data/&lt;file_path&gt; URI (from views.py), allows attackers to write to arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51062 | An unauthenticated log file read in the component log-smblog-save of QStar Archive Solutions RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51062</link><description>An unauthenticated log file read in the component log-smblog-save of QStar Archive Solutions RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows attackers to disclose the SMB Log contents via executing a crafted command.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51063 | QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 was discovered to contain a DOM Based Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51063</link><description>QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 was discovered to contain a DOM Based Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability within the component qnme-ajax?method=tree_level.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51064 | QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 was discovered to contain a DOM Based reflected XSS vulnerability within the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51064</link><description>QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 was discovered to contain a DOM Based reflected XSS vulnerability within the component qnme-ajax?method=tree_table.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51065 | Incorrect access control in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows unauthenticated attackers to obtain system ba...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51065</link><description>Incorrect access control in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows unauthenticated attackers to obtain system backups and other sensitive information from the QStar Server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51066 | An authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows attackers to arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51066</link><description>An authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows attackers to arbitrarily execute commands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51067 | An unauthenticated reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51067</link><description>An unauthenticated reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary javascript on a victim's browser via a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51068 | An authenticated reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51068</link><description>An authenticated reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary javascript on a victim's browser via a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51070 | An access control issue in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily adjus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51070</link><description>An access control issue in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily adjust sensitive SMB settings on the QStar Server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51071 | An access control issue in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily disab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51071</link><description>An access control issue in QStar Archive Solutions Release RELEASE_3-0 Build 7 Patch 0 allows unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily disable the SMB service on a victim's Qstar instance by executing a specific command in a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 04:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33472 | An issue was discovered in Scada-LTS v2.7.5.2 build 4551883606 and before, allows remote attackers with low-level authentication to escalate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33472</link><description>An issue was discovered in Scada-LTS v2.7.5.2 build 4551883606 and before, allows remote attackers with low-level authentication to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, and obtain sensitive information via Event Handlers function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46942 | Lack of authentication in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46942</link><description>Lack of authentication in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via improper authorization in GraphQL endpoints.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46943 | An issue was discovered in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8. The HMAC secret used for generating tokens is hardcod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46943</link><description>An issue was discovered in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8. The HMAC secret used for generating tokens is hardcoded as "secret". A weak HMAC secret poses a risk because attackers can use the predictable secret to create valid JSON Web Tokens (JWTs), allowing them access to important information and actions within the application.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51804 | An issue in rymcu forest v.0.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via manipulation of the HTTP body URL in the com.ry...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51804</link><description>An issue in rymcu forest v.0.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via manipulation of the HTTP body URL in the com.rymcu.forest.web.api.common.UploadController file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51805 | SQL Injection vulnerability in TDuckCLoud tduck-platform v.4.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the getFormKey p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51805</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in TDuckCLoud tduck-platform v.4.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the getFormKey parameter in the search function of FormDataMysqlService.java file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50072 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in OpenKM version 7.1.40 (dbb6e88) With Professional Extension that allows an authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50072</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in OpenKM version 7.1.40 (dbb6e88) With Professional Extension that allows an authenticated user to upload a note on a file which acts as a stored XSS payload. Any user who opens the note of a document file will trigger the XSS.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 01:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0475 | code-projects Dormitory Management System modifyuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0475</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file modifyuser.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250580.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 01:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>