<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10357 | Clever Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10357</link><description>The Clever Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 via the getTemplateContent function in src/widgets/class-clever-widget-base.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9116 | Monkee-Boy Essentials &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9116</link><description>The Monkee-Boy Essentials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9772 | Uix Shortcodes – Compatible with Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9772</link><description>The The Uix Shortcodes – Compatible with Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8392 | WordPress Post Grid Layouts with Pagination – Sogrid &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8392</link><description>The WordPress Post Grid Layouts with Pagination – Sogrid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the 'tab' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. This can also be exploited via CSRF techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9637 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.10 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Teacher+) Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9637</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.10. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9642 | Editor Custom Color Palette &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9642</link><description>The Editor Custom Color Palette plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9853 | ID-SK Toolkit &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9853</link><description>The ID-SK Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9967 | WP show more &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via show_more Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9967</link><description>The WP show more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's show_more shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0127 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the GPU kernel driver of the vGPU Manager for all supported hypervisors, where a user of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0127</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the GPU kernel driver of the vGPU Manager for all supported hypervisors, where a user of the guest OS can cause an improper input validation by compromising the guest OS kernel. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0128 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager that allows a user of the guest OS to access global resources. A su...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0128</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager that allows a user of the guest OS to access global resources. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0117 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0117</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0118 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0118</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0119 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0119</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0120 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0120</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0121 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0121</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0126 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow a privileged attacker to escalate permissions. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0126</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability which could allow a privileged attacker to escalate permissions. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 08:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10092 | Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 5.0.12 - Missing Authorization to API Key Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10092</link><description>The Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_handle_api_key_actions function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to revoke existing API keys and generate new ones.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 07:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9456 | WP Awesome Login &amp;lt;= 0.4.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9456</link><description>The WP Awesome Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 04:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8870 | Forms for Mailchimp by Optin Cat – Grow Your MailChimp List &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8870</link><description>The Forms for Mailchimp by Optin Cat – Grow Your MailChimp List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10091 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Comparison Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10091</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Comparison Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9454 | PriPre &amp;lt;= 0.4.11 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9454</link><description>The PriPre plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9613 | FormFacade – WordPress plugin for Google Forms &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9613</link><description>The FormFacade – WordPress plugin for Google Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'userId' and 'publishId' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9462 | Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls &amp;lt;= 5.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Poll Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9462</link><description>The Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via poll settings in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9475 | Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls &amp;lt;= 5.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via Order_by Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9475</link><description>The Poll Maker – Versus Polls, Anonymous Polls, Image Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the order_by parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.6  due to insufficient escaping on the user-supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9626 | Editorial Assistant by Sovrn &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Attachment Upload and Set Post Featured Image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9626</link><description>The Editorial Assistant by Sovrn plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_zemanta_set_featured_image' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload attachment files (such as jpg, png, txt, zip), and set the post featured image.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9890 | User Toolkit &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9890</link><description>The User Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This is due to an improper capability check in the 'switchUser' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9930 | Extensions by HocWP Team &amp;lt;= 0.2.3.2 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9930</link><description>The Extensions by HocWP Team plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 0.2.3.2. This is due to missing validation on the user being supplied in the 'verify_email' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator. The vulnerability is in the Account extension.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9931 | Wux Blog Editor &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authentication Bypass to Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9931</link><description>The Wux Blog Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to missing validation on the token being supplied during the autologin through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in to the first administrator user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9932 | Wux Blog Editor &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9932</link><description>The Wux Blog Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'wuxbt_insertImageNew' function in versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9933 | WatchTowerHQ &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - Authentication Bypass to Administrator due to Missing Empty Value Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9933</link><description>The WatchTowerHQ plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.9.6. This is due to the 'watchtower_ota_token' default value is empty, and the not empty check is missing in the 'Password_Less_Access::login' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in to the WatchTowerHQ client administrator user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47821 | pyLoad vulnerable to remote code execution by download to /.pyload/scripts using /flashgot API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47821</link><description>pyLoad is a free and open-source Download Manager. The folder `/.pyload/scripts` has scripts which are run when certain actions are completed, for e.g. a download is finished. By downloading a executable file to a folder in /scripts and performing the respective action, remote code execution can be achieved in versions on the 0.5 branch prior to 0.5.0b3.dev87. A file can be downloaded to such a folder by changing the download folder to a folder in `/scripts` path and using the `/flashgot` API to download the file. This vulnerability allows an attacker with access to change the settings on a pyload server to execute arbitrary code and completely compromise the system. Version 0.5.0b3.dev87 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 23:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48237 | WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in \Common\Controller\HomebaseController.class.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48237</link><description>WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in \Common\Controller\HomebaseController.class.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48238 | WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the edit_post method of /Admin\Controller\NavControl.class.php via the parentid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48238</link><description>WTCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the edit_post method of /Admin\Controller\NavControl.class.php via the parentid parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48239 | An issue was discovered in WTCMS 1.0. In the plupload method in \AssetController.class.php, the app parameters aren't processed, resulting i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48239</link><description>An issue was discovered in WTCMS 1.0. In the plupload method in \AssetController.class.php, the app parameters aren't processed, resulting in Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48228 | An issue was found in funadmin 5.0.2. The selectfiles method in \backend\controller\sys\Attachh.php directly stores the passed parameters an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48228</link><description>An issue was found in funadmin 5.0.2. The selectfiles method in \backend\controller\sys\Attachh.php directly stores the passed parameters and values into the param parameter without filtering, resulting in Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48234 | An issue was discovered in mipjz 5.0.5. In the push method of app\tag\controller\ApiAdminTag.php the value of the postAddress parameter is n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48234</link><description>An issue was discovered in mipjz 5.0.5. In the push method of app\tag\controller\ApiAdminTag.php the value of the postAddress parameter is not processed and is directly passed into curl_exec execution and output, resulting in Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that can read server files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48235 | An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the save method of the TemplateController.java file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48235</link><description>An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the save method of the TemplateController.java file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48236 | An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the FileOutputStream function in the write String method of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48236</link><description>An issue in ofcms 1.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the FileOutputStream function in the write String method of the ofcms-admin\src\main\java\com\ofsoft\cms\core\uitle\FileUtils.java file</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 21:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48229 | funadmin 5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the Curd one click command mode plugin.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48229</link><description>funadmin 5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the Curd one click command mode plugin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48230 | funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the parentField parameter in the index method of \backend\controller\auth\Auth.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48230</link><description>funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the parentField parameter in the index method of \backend\controller\auth\Auth.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48232 | An issue was found in mipjz 5.0.5. In the mipPost method of \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminTool.php, the value of the postAddress parameter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48232</link><description>An issue was found in mipjz 5.0.5. In the mipPost method of \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminTool.php, the value of the postAddress parameter is not processed and is directly passed into curl_exec execution and output, resulting in a Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that can read server files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48233 | mipjz 5.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminSetting.php via the ICP parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48233</link><description>mipjz 5.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in \app\setting\controller\ApiAdminSetting.php via the ICP parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48396 | AIML Chatbot 1.0 (fixed in 2.0) is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability is exploited through the message input field,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48396</link><description>AIML Chatbot 1.0 (fixed in 2.0) is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability is exploited through the message input field, where attackers can inject malicious HTML or JavaScript code. The chatbot fails to sanitize these inputs, leading to the execution of malicious scripts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48218 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48218</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48222 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/edit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48222</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/edit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48223 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/fieldlist.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48223</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has a SQL injection vulnerability in /curd/table/fieldlist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48224 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in /curd/index/editfile.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48224</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file read vulnerability in /curd/index/editfile.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48225 | Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in /curd/index/delfile.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48225</link><description>Funadmin v5.0.2 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in /curd/index/delfile.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48226 | Funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in curd/table/savefield.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48226</link><description>Funadmin 5.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in curd/table/savefield.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48227 | Funadmin 5.0.2 has a logical flaw in the Curd one click command deletion function, which can result in a Denial of Service (DOS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48227</link><description>Funadmin 5.0.2 has a logical flaw in the Curd one click command deletion function, which can result in a Denial of Service (DOS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 20:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49767 | Werkzeug possible resource exhaustion when parsing file data in forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49767</link><description>Werkzeug is a Web Server Gateway Interface web application library. Applications using `werkzeug.formparser.MultiPartParser` corresponding to a version of Werkzeug prior to 3.0.6 to parse `multipart/form-data` requests (e.g. all flask applications) are vulnerable to a relatively simple but effective resource exhaustion (denial of service) attack. A specifically crafted form submission request can cause the parser to allocate and block 3 to 8 times the upload size in main memory. There is no upper limit; a single upload at 1 Gbit/s can exhaust 32 GB of RAM in less than 60 seconds. Werkzeug version 3.0.6 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 19:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49766 | Werkzeug safe_join not safe on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49766</link><description>Werkzeug is a Web Server Gateway Interface web application library. On Python &lt; 3.11 on Windows, os.path.isabs() does not catch UNC paths like //server/share. Werkzeug's safe_join() relies on this check, and so can produce a path that is not safe, potentially allowing unintended access to data. Applications using Python &gt;= 3.11, or not using Windows, are not vulnerable. Werkzeug version 3.0.6 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 19:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37845 | MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Active Process Command fea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37845</link><description>MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Active Process Command feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37846 | MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain a Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability via the Platform Management Edit page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37846</link><description>MangoOS before 5.2.0 was discovered to contain a Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability via the Platform Management Edit page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37847 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.1.4 and Mango API before 4.5.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37847</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.1.4 and Mango API before 4.5.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48450 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48450</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML file into chat group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37844 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37844</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MangoOS before 5.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48448 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48448</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Huly Platform v0.6.295 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted HTML file into the tracker comments page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48700 | Kliqqi-CMS has a background arbitrary code execution vulnerability that attackers can exploit to implant backdoors or getShell via the edit_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48700</link><description>Kliqqi-CMS has a background arbitrary code execution vulnerability that attackers can exploit to implant backdoors or getShell via the edit_page.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9584 | Image Map Pro &amp;lt;= 6.0.20 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Map Project Add/Update/Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9584</link><description>The Image Map Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the AJAX functions in versions up to, and including, 6.0.20. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level privileges or above, to add, update or delete map projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9585 | Image Map Pro &amp;lt;= 6.0.20 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9585</link><description>The Image Map Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'save_project' function with an arbitrary shortcode in versions up to, and including, 6.0.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48343 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in ESAFENET CDG 5 and earlier allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter of the dataSea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48343</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in ESAFENET CDG 5 and earlier allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter of the dataSearch.jsp page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10386 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk ThinManager Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10386</link><description>CVE-2024-10386 IMPACT



An authentication
vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability could allow a
threat actor with network access to send crafted messages to the device, potentially
resulting in database manipulation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10387 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk ThinManager Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10387</link><description>CVE-2024-10387 IMPACT



A Denial-of-Service
vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability could allow a
threat actor with network access to send crafted messages to the device,
potentially resulting in Denial-of-Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8036 | Unauthorized Modifications of Firmware and Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8036</link><description>ABB is aware of privately reported vulnerabilities in the product versions referenced in this CVE. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a specially crafted firmware or configuration to the system node, causing the node to stop, become inaccessible, or allowing the attacker to take control of the node.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 17:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48655 | An issue in Total.js CMS v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the func.js file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48655</link><description>An issue in Total.js CMS v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the func.js file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48743 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Sentry v.6.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the z parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48743</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Sentry v.6.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the z parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48654 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Blood Bank v.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48654</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Blood Bank v.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30359 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserList. Authentication i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30359</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserList. Authentication is required. The information disclosed is associated with the all registered users, including user ID, status, email address, role(s), user type, license type, and personal details such as first name, last name, gender, and user preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30360 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by multiple Stored XSS (AKA Persistent or Type II) vulnerabilities via a POST request to /profile/u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30360</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by multiple Stored XSS (AKA Persistent or Type II) vulnerabilities via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the slackid or phone parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30361 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserType. No authenticatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30361</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserType. No authentication is required. The information disclosed is associated with the registered user ID, status, email address, role(s), user type, license type, and personal details such as first name, last name, gender, and user preferences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48459 | A command execution vulnerability exists in the AX2 Pro home router produced by Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co., Ltd. (Jixiang Tenda) v.DI_700...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48459</link><description>A command execution vulnerability exists in the AX2 Pro home router produced by Shenzhen Tenda Technology Co., Ltd. (Jixiang Tenda) v.DI_7003G-19.12.24A1V16.03.29.50;V16.03.29.50;V16.03.29.50. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by constructing a malicious payload to execute commands and further obtain shell access to the router's file system with the highest privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30356 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Privilege Escalation vulnerability via a POST request to /user/assignuserrole via the userid a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30356</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Privilege Escalation vulnerability via a POST request to /user/assignuserrole via the userid and role parameters . Authentication is required with OE_ADMIN role privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30357 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30357</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId and email parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30358 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /user/updatePassword via the userId and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30358</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /user/updatePassword via the userId and newPsw parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30354 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserWithTeam. Authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30354</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability via a GET request to /user/getUserWithTeam. Authentication is required. The information disclosed is associated with all registered user ID numbers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-30355 | OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30355</link><description>OvalEdge 5.2.8.0 and earlier is affected by an Account Takeover vulnerability via a POST request to /profile/updateProfile via the userId and email parameters. Authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48204 | SQL injection vulnerability in Hanzhou Haobo network management system 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48204</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Hanzhou Haobo network management system 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 16:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48580 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the email ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48580</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the email parameter of the login request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48579 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Best House rental management system project in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48579</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Best House rental management system project in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the username parameter of the login request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48581 | File Upload vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the admin_cl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48581</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Best courier management system in php v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the admin_class.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26248 | The Kademlia DHT (go-libp2p-kad-dht 0.20.0 and earlier) used in IPFS (0.18.1 and earlier) assigns routing information for content (i.e., inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26248</link><description>The Kademlia DHT (go-libp2p-kad-dht 0.20.0 and earlier) used in IPFS (0.18.1 and earlier) assigns routing information for content (i.e., information about who holds the content) to be stored by peers whose peer IDs have a small DHT distance from the content ID. This allows an attacker to censor content by generating many Sybil peers whose peer IDs have a small distance from the content ID, thus hijacking the content resolution process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48428 | An issue in Olive VLE allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reset password function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48428</link><description>An issue in Olive VLE allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reset password function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49757 | Zitadel User Registration Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49757</link><description>The open-source identity infrastructure software Zitadel allows administrators to disable the user self-registration. Due to a missing security check in versions prior to 2.64.0, 2.63.5, 2.62.7, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7, disabling the "User Registration allowed" option only hid the registration button on the login page. Users could bypass this restriction by directly accessing the registration URL (/ui/login/loginname) and register a user that way. Versions 2.64.0, 2.63.5, 2.62.7, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49753 | Denied Host Validation Bypass in Zitadel Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49753</link><description>Zitadel is open-source identity infrastructure software. Versions prior to 2.64.1, 2.63.6, 2.62.8, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 have a flaw in the URL validation mechanism of Zitadel actions allows bypassing restrictions intended to block requests to localhost (127.0.0.1). The isHostBlocked check, designed to prevent such requests, can be circumvented by creating a DNS record that resolves to 127.0.0.1. This enables actions to send requests to localhost despite the intended security measures. This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized access to unsecured internal endpoints, which may contain sensitive information or functionalities. Versions 2.64.1, 2.63.6, 2.62.8, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49380 | Plenti arbitrary file write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49380</link><description>Plenti, a static site generator, has an arbitrary file write vulnerability in versions prior to 0.7.2. The `/postLocal` endpoint is vulnerable to an arbitrary file write vulnerability when a plenti user serves their website. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution. Version 0.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49381 | Plenti arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49381</link><description>Plenti, a static site generator, has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in versions prior to 0.7.2. The `/postLocal` endpoint is vulnerable to an arbitrary file write deletion when a plenti user serves their website. This issue may lead to information loss. Version 0.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10380 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software ajax_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10380</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax_product.php. The manipulation of the argument drop_services leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49376 | Autolab Has Misconfigured Reset Password Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49376</link><description>Autolab, a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments, has misconfigured reset password permissions in version 3.0.0. For email-based accounts, users with insufficient privileges could reset and theoretically access privileged users' accounts by resetting their passwords. This issue is fixed in version 3.0.1. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49378 | smartUp Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49378</link><description>smartUp, a web browser mouse gestures extension, has a universal cross-site scripting issue in the Edge and Firefox versions of smartUp 7.2.622.1170. The vulnerability allows another extension to execute arbitrary code in the context of the user’s tab. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10381 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in Matrix Door Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10381</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Matrix Door Controller Cosec Vega FAXQ due to improper implementation of session management at the web-based management interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted http request on the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote attacker to gain unauthorized access and take complete control of the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9991 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information Vulnerability in Philips Lighting Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9991</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Philips lighting devices due to storage of Wi-Fi credentials in plain text within the device firmware. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and analyzing the binary data to obtain the plaintext Wi-Fi credentials stored on the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain unauthorized access to the Wi-Fi network to which vulnerable device is connected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10378 | ESAFENET CDG CDGRenewApplicationService.java actionViewCDGRenewFile sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10378</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected is the function actionViewCDGRenewFile of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/CDGRenewApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument CDGRenewFileId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10379 | ESAFENET CDG DecryptApplicationService.java actionViewDecyptFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10379</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function actionViewDecyptFile of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/DecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument decryptFileId with the input ../../../Windows/System32/drivers/etc/hosts leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The affected function has a typo and is missing an R. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10374 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.4.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpmem_loginout Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10374</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpmem_loginout shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10376 | ESAFENET CDG AutoSignService.java actionPassOrNotAutoSign sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10376</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function actionPassOrNotAutoSign of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/service/processsign/AutoSignService.java. The manipulation of the argument UniqueId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10377 | ESAFENET CDG DecryptApplicationService.java actionPassDecryptApplication1 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function actionPassDecryptApplication1 of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/DecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This is a different issue than CVE-2024-10069. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47483 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0 and 1.1.0.0, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47483</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0 and 1.1.0.0, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47481 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, 1.1.0., contain(s) an Improper Access Control vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47481</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, 1.1.0., contain(s) an Improper Access Control vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44098 | In lwis_device_event_states_clear_locked of lwis_event.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a double free. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44098</link><description>In lwis_device_event_states_clear_locked of lwis_event.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a double free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44099 | There is a possible Local bypass of user interaction due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44099</link><description>There is a possible Local bypass of user interaction due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44100 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44100</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44101 | there is a possible Null Pointer Dereference (modem crash) due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44101</link><description>there is a possible Null Pointer Dereference (modem crash) due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47012 | In mm_GetMobileIdIndexForNsUpdate of mm_GmmPduCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47012</link><description>In mm_GetMobileIdIndexForNsUpdate of mm_GmmPduCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47013 | In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible arbitrary write due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47013</link><description>In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible arbitrary write due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47014 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47014</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47015 | In ProtocolMiscHwConfigChangeAdapter::GetData() of protocolmiscadapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47015</link><description>In ProtocolMiscHwConfigChangeAdapter::GetData() of protocolmiscadapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47016 | there is a possible privilege escalation due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47016</link><description>there is a possible privilege escalation due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47017 | In ufshc_scsi_cmd of ufs.c, there is a possible stack variable use after free due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47017</link><description>In ufshc_scsi_cmd of ufs.c, there is a possible stack variable use after free due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47018 | In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47018</link><description>In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47019 | In ProtocolEmbmsSaiListAdapter::Init() of protocolembmsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47019</link><description>In ProtocolEmbmsSaiListAdapter::Init() of protocolembmsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47020 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47020</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47021 | In sms_ExtractCbLanguage of sms_CellBroadcast.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47021</link><description>In sms_ExtractCbLanguage of sms_CellBroadcast.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47022 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47022</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47023 | there is a possible man-in-the-middle attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47023</link><description>there is a possible man-in-the-middle attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47024 | In vring_size of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47024</link><description>In vring_size of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47025 | In ppmp_protect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible information disclosure due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47025</link><description>In ppmp_protect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible information disclosure due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47026 | In gsc_gsa_rescue of gsc_gsa.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47026</link><description>In gsc_gsa_rescue of gsc_gsa.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47027 | In sm_mem_compat_get_vmm_obj of lib/sm/shared_mem.c, there is a possible arbitrary physical memory access due to improper input validation. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47027</link><description>In sm_mem_compat_get_vmm_obj of lib/sm/shared_mem.c, there is a possible arbitrary physical memory access due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47028 | In ffu_flash_pack of ffu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47028</link><description>In ffu_flash_pack of ffu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47029 | In TrustySharedMemoryManager::GetSharedMemory of ondevice/trusty/trusty_shared_memory_manager.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47029</link><description>In TrustySharedMemoryManager::GetSharedMemory of ondevice/trusty/trusty_shared_memory_manager.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47030 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47030</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47031 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47031</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47033 | In lwis_allocator_free of lwis_allocator.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47033</link><description>In lwis_allocator_free of lwis_allocator.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47034 | there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47034</link><description>there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47035 | In vring_init of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47035</link><description>In vring_init of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47041 | In valid_address of syscall.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47041</link><description>In valid_address of syscall.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10016 | File Upload Types by WPForms &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10016</link><description>The File Upload Types by WPForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10112 | Simple News &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via news Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10112</link><description>The Simple News plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'news' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10343 | Beek Widget Extention &amp;lt;= 0.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10343</link><description>The Beek Widget Extention plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 0.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8666 | Shoutcast Icecast HTML5 Radio Player &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8666</link><description>The Shoutcast Icecast HTML5 Radio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'html5radio' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45785 | MUSASI version 3 contains an issue with use of client-side authentication. If this vulnerability is exploited, other users' credential and s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45785</link><description>MUSASI version 3 contains an issue with use of client-side authentication. If this vulnerability is exploited, other users' credential and sensitive information may be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47158 | N-LINE 2.0.6 and prior versions contain a code injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47158</link><description>N-LINE 2.0.6 and prior versions contain a code injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed on the instructor's browser, or the instructor may be directed to a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10150 | Bamazoo – Button Generator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via dgs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10150</link><description>The Bamazoo – Button Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's dgs shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10341 | League of Legends Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10341</link><description>The League of Legends Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10342 | League of Legends Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10342</link><description>The League of Legends Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9598 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.0.99.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9598</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.99.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'proxy' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send the logged in user's cookies to their own server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9628 | WPS Telegram Chat &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Unauthorized Access to Telegram Bot API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9628</link><description>The WPS Telegram Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'Wps_Telegram_Chat_Admin::checkСonnection' function in versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to have full access to the Telegram Bot API endpoint and communicate with it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9630 | WPS Telegram Chat &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Missing Authorization to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9630</link><description>The WPS Telegram Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check when accessing messages in versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the messages that are sent through the Telegram Bot API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50583 | Whale browser Installer before 3.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute a malicious DLL in the user environment due to improper permission sett...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50583</link><description>Whale browser Installer before 3.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute a malicious DLL in the user environment due to improper permission settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10011 | BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 14.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10011</link><description>The BuddyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 14.1.0 via the id parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform actions on files outside of the originally intended directory and enables file uploads to directories outside of the web root. Depending on server configuration it may be possible to upload files with double extensions. This vulnerability only affects Windows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10148 | Awesome buttons &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via btn2 Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10148</link><description>The Awesome buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's btn2 shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9235 | Mapster WP Maps &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9235</link><description>The Mapster WP Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to an insufficient capability check on the mapster_wp_maps_set_option_from_js() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9302 | App Builder – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Flight &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Privilege Escalation and Account Takeover via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9302</link><description>The App Builder – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Flight plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.7. This is due to the verify_otp_forgot_password() and update_password() functions not having enough controls to prevent a successful brute force attack of the OTP to change a password, or verify that a password reset request came from an authorized user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate and brute force an OTP that makes it possible to change any users passwords, including an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9607 | 10Web Social Post Feed &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9607</link><description>The 10Web Social Post Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note this is only exploitable when the leave a review notice is present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42420 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs contain multiple Out-of-bounds Read vulnerabilities, due to improper processing of keyword search input and impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42420</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs contain multiple Out-of-bounds Read vulnerabilities, due to improper processing of keyword search input and improper processing of SOAP messages.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43424 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP request headers, resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.&#13;
Crafted HTTP requests...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43424</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP request headers, resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45829 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide the web page to download data, where query parameters in HTTP requests are improperly processed and resul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45829</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide the web page to download data, where query parameters in HTTP requests are improperly processed and resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45842 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process URI data in HTTP PUT requests resulting in a path Traversal vulnerability.&#13;
Unintended interna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45842</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process URI data in HTTP PUT requests resulting in a path Traversal vulnerability.
Unintended internal files may be retrieved when processing crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47005 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide configuration related APIs. They are expected to be called by administrative users only, but insufficient...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47005</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide configuration related APIs. They are expected to be called by administrative users only, but insufficiently restricted.
A non-administrative user may execute some configuration APIs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47406 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP authentication requests, resulting in an authentication bypass vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47406</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP authentication requests, resulting in an authentication bypass vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47549 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, which may allow contamination of unintended data to HTTP re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47549</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, which may allow contamination of unintended data to HTTP response headers.
Accessing a crafted URL which points to an affected product may cause malicious script executed on the web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47801 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47801</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability.
Accessing a crafted URL which points to an affected product may cause malicious script executed on the web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48870 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly validate input data in URI data registration, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48870</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly validate input data in URI data registration, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability.
If crafted input is stored by an administrative user, malicious script may be executed on the web browsers of other victim users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9109 | UPS Live Rates and Access Points &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Missing Authorization to Plugin API key reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9109</link><description>The WooCommerce UPS Shipping – Live Rates and Access Points plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_oauth_data function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's API key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9488 | Comments – wpDiscuz &amp;lt;= 7.6.24 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9488</link><description>The Comments – wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.24. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9686 | Order Notification for Telegram &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Send Telegram Test Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9686</link><description>The Order Notification for Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized test message sending due to a missing capability check on the 'nktgnfw_send_test_message' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send a test message via the Telegram Bot API to the user configured in the settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10372 | chidiwilliams buzz model_loader.py download_model temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10372</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in chidiwilliams buzz 1.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function download_model of the file buzz/model_loader.py. The manipulation leads to insecure temporary file. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 02:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10368 | Codezips Sales Management System addstock.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addstock.php. The manipulation of the argument prodtype leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10369 | Codezips Sales Management System addcustcom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /addcustcom.php. The manipulation of the argument refno leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10370 | Codezips Sales Management System addcustind.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addcustind.php. The manipulation of the argument refno leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10371 | SourceCodester Payroll Management System main login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10371</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Payroll Management System 1.0. This affects the function login of the file main. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10354 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10354</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/print.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10355 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10355</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10351 | Tenda RX9 Pro POST Request setMacFilterCfg sub_424CE0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10351</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX9 Pro 22.03.02.20. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function sub_424CE0 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10353 | SourceCodester Online Exam System admin-dashboard access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10353</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Exam System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-dashboard. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This affects a different product and is a different issue than CVE-2024-40480.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10350 | code-projects Hospital Management System add-doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-doctor.php. The manipulation of the argument docname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10348 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System Manage Tenant Details index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?page=tenants of the component Manage Tenant Details. The manipulation of the argument Last Name/First Name/Middle Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only shows the field "Last Name" to be affected. Other fields might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10349 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System ajax.php delete_tenant sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10349</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function delete_tenant of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_tenant. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49750 | Snowflake Connector for Python has sensitive data in logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49750</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Prior to version 3.12.3, when the logging level was set by the user to DEBUG, the Connector could have logged Duo passcodes (when specified via the `passcode` parameter) and Azure SAS tokens. Additionally, the SecretDetector logging formatter, if enabled, contained bugs which caused it to not fully redact JWT tokens and certain private key formats. Snowflake released version 3.12.3 of the Snowflake Connector for Python, which fixes the issue. In addition to upgrading, users should review their logs for any potentially sensitive information that may have been captured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41617 | Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The `redirect_if_not_loggedin` function in `...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41617</link><description>Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The `redirect_if_not_loggedin` function in `functions_security.php` fails to terminate script execution after redirecting unauthenticated users. This flaw allows an unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, potentially leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41618 | Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the `transaction_delete_group` function. The vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41618</link><description>Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the `transaction_delete_group` function. The vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user input in the `TrDeleteArr` parameter, which is directly incorporated into an SQL query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49762 | Pterodactyl Panel has plain-text logging of user passwords when two-factor authentication is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49762</link><description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel. When a user disables two-factor authentication via the Panel, a `DELETE` request with their current password in a query parameter will be sent.  While query parameters are encrypted when using TLS, many webservers (including ones officially documented for use with Pterodactyl) will log query parameters in plain-text, storing a user's password in plain text. Prior to version 1.11.8, if a malicious user obtains access to these logs they could potentially authenticate against a user's account; assuming they are able to discover the account's email address or username separately. This problem has been patched in version 1.11.8. There are no workarounds at this time. There is not a direct vulnerability within the software as it relates to logs generated by intermediate components such as web servers or Layer 7 proxies. Updating to `v1.11.8` or adding the linked patch manually are the only ways to avoid this problem. As this vulnerability relates to historical logging of sensitive data, users who have ever disabled 2FA on a Panel (self-hosted or operated by a company) should change their passwords and consider enabling 2FA if it was left disabled. While it's unlikely that their account swill be compromised by this vulnerability, it's not impossible. Panel administrators should consider clearing any access logs that may contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49359 | ZimaOS vulnerable to Directory Listing via Parameter Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49359</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http:///v2_1/file` in ZimaOS is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack, allowing authenticated users to list the contents of any directory on the server. By manipulating the path parameter, attackers can access sensitive system directories such as `/etc`, potentially exposing critical configuration files and increasing the risk of further attacks. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49760 | OpenRefine has a path traversal in LoadLanguageCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49760</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. The load-language command expects a `lang` parameter from which it constructs the path of the localization file to load, of the form `translations-$LANG.json`. But when doing so in versions prior to 3.8.3, it does not check that the resulting path is in the expected directory, which means that this command could be exploited to read other JSON files on the file system. Version 3.8.3 addresses this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49357 | ZimaOS (Installed Applications and System Information) has Unauthorized Sensitive Data Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49357</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoints in ZimaOS, such as `http:///v1/users/image?path=/var/lib/casaos/1/app_order.json` and `http:///v1/users/image?path=/var/lib/casaos/1/system.json`, expose sensitive data like installed applications and system information without requiring any authentication or authorization. This sensitive data leak can be exploited by attackers to gain detailed knowledge about the system setup, installed applications, and other critical information. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49358 | ZimaOS vulnerable to Username Enumeration via API Responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49358</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http:///v1/users/login` in ZimaOS returns distinct responses based on whether a username exists or the password is incorrect. This behavior can be exploited for username enumeration, allowing attackers to determine whether a user exists in the system or not. Attackers can leverage this information in further attacks, such as credential stuffing or targeted password brute-forcing. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48423 | An issue in assimp v.5.4.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the CallbackToLogRedirector function within the Assimp libr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48423</link><description>An issue in assimp v.5.4.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the CallbackToLogRedirector function within the Assimp library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48932 | ZimaOS Unauthenticated API Discloses Usernames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48932</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http:///v1/users/name` allows unauthenticated users to access sensitive information, such as usernames, without any authorization. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to enumerate usernames and leverage them for further attacks, such as brute-force or phishing campaigns. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48424 | A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability has been identified in the OpenDDLParser::parseStructure function within the Assimp library, specifical...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48424</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability has been identified in the OpenDDLParser::parseStructure function within the Assimp library, specifically during the processing of OpenGEX files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48426 | A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the SortByPTypeProcess::Execute function in the Assimp library during fuzz testing with AddressS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48426</link><description>A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the SortByPTypeProcess::Execute function in the Assimp library during fuzz testing with AddressSanitizer. The crash occurred due to a read access to an invalid memory address (0x1000c9714971).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48931 | ZimaOS Arbitrary File Read via Parameter Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48931</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the ZimaOS API endpoint `http:///v3/file?token=&amp;amp;files=` is vulnerable to arbitrary file reading due to improper input validation. By manipulating the `files` parameter, authenticated users can read sensitive system files, including `/etc/shadow`, which contains password hashes for all users. This vulnerability exposes critical system data and poses a high risk for privilege escalation or system compromise. The vulnerability occurs because the API endpoint does not validate or restrict file paths provided via the `files` parameter. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the file path to access sensitive files outside the intended directory. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48425 | A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the Assimp::SplitLargeMeshesProcess_Triangle::UpdateNode function within the Assimp library duri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48425</link><description>A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the Assimp::SplitLargeMeshesProcess_Triangle::UpdateNode function within the Assimp library during fuzz testing using AddressSanitizer. The crash occurs due to a read access violation at address 0x000000000460, which points to the zero page, indicating a null or invalid pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47882 | OpenRefine&amp;#x27;s error page lacks escaping, leading to potential Cross-site Scripting on import of malicious project</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47882</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, the built-in "Something went wrong!" error page includes the exception message and exception traceback without escaping HTML tags, enabling injection into the page if an attacker can reliably produce an error with an attacker-influenced message. It appears that the only way to reach this code in OpenRefine itself is for an attacker to somehow convince a victim to import a malicious file, which may be difficult.  However, out-of-tree extensions may add their own calls to `respondWithErrorPage`. Version 3.8.3 has a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47883 | Butterfly has path/URL confusion in resource handling leading to multiple weaknesses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47883</link><description>The OpenRefine fork of the MIT Simile Butterfly server is a modular web application framework. The Butterfly framework uses the `java.net.URL` class to refer to (what are expected to be) local resource files, like images or templates. This works: "opening a connection" to these URLs opens the local file. However, prior to version 1.2.6, if a `file:/` URL is directly given where a relative path (resource name) is expected, this is also accepted in some code paths; the app then fetches the file, from a remote machine if indicated, and uses it as if it was a trusted part of the app's codebase. This leads to multiple weaknesses and potential weaknesses. An attacker that has network access to the application could use it to gain access to files, either on the the server's filesystem (path traversal) or shared by nearby machines (server-side request forgery with e.g. SMB). An attacker that can lead or redirect a user to a crafted URL belonging to the app could cause arbitrary attacker-controlled JavaScript to be loaded in the victim's browser (cross-site scripting). If an app is written in such a way that an attacker can influence the resource name used for a template, that attacker could cause the app to fetch and execute an attacker-controlled template (remote code execution). Version 1.2.6 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47881 | OpenRefine&amp;#x27;s SQLite integration allows filesystem access, remote code execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47881</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Starting in version 3.4-beta and prior to version 3.8.3, in the `database` extension, the "enable_load_extension" property can be set for the SQLite integration, enabling an attacker to load (local or remote) extension DLLs and so run arbitrary code on the server. The attacker needs to have network access to the OpenRefine instance. Version 3.8.3 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10327 | A vulnerability in Okta Verify for iOS versions 9.25.1 (beta) and 9.27.0 (including beta) allows push notification responses through the iOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10327</link><description>A vulnerability in Okta Verify for iOS versions 9.25.1 (beta) and 9.27.0 (including beta) allows push notification responses through the iOS ContextExtension feature allowing the authentication to proceed regardless of the user’s selection. When a user long-presses the notification banner and selects an option, both options allow the authentication to succeed. 
The ContextExtension feature is one of several push mechanisms available when using Okta Verify Push on iOS devices. The vulnerable flows include: 
* When a user is presented with a notification on a locked screen, the user presses on the notification directly and selects their reply without unlocking the device; 
* When a user is presented with a notification on the home screen and drags the notification down and selects their reply; 
* When an Apple Watch is used to reply directly to a notification. 

 A pre-condition for this vulnerability is that the user must have enrolled in Okta Verify while the Okta customer was using Okta Classic. This applies irrespective of whether the organization has since upgraded to Okta Identity Engine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45260 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. Users who belong to unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45260</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. Users who belong to unauthorized groups can invoke any interface of the device, thereby gaining complete control over it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45261 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The SID generated for a spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45261</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The SID generated for a specific user is not tied to that user itself, which allows other users to potentially use it for authentication. Once an attacker bypasses the application's authentication procedures, they can generate a valid SID, escalate privileges, and gain full control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45262 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The params parameter in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45262</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The params parameter in the call method of the /rpc endpoint is vulnerable to arbitrary directory traversal, which enables attackers to execute scripts under any path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45263 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The upload interface allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45263</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The upload interface allows the uploading of arbitrary files to the device. Once the device executes the files, it can lead to information leakage, enabling complete control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47878 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability (XSS) in GData extension (authorized.vt)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47878</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, the `/extension/gdata/authorized` endpoint includes the `state` GET parameter verbatim in a `</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47879 | OpenRefine&amp;#x27;s PreviewExpressionCommand, which is eval, lacks protection against cross-site request forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47879</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, lack of cross-site request forgery protection on the `preview-expression` command means that visiting a malicious website could cause an attacker-controlled expression to be executed. The expression can contain arbitrary Clojure or Python code. The attacker must know a valid project ID of a project that contains at least one row, and the attacker must convince the victim to open a malicious webpage. Version 3.8.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47880 | OpenRefine has a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability from POST request in ExportRowsCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47880</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, the `export-rows` command can be used in such a way that it reflects part of the request verbatim, with a Content-Type header also taken from the request. An attacker could lead a user to a malicious page that submits a form POST that contains  embedded JavaScript code. This code would then be included in the response, along with an attacker-controlled `Content-Type` header, and so potentially executed in the victim's browser as if it was part of OpenRefine. The attacker-provided code can do anything the user can do, including deleting projects, retrieving database passwords, or executing arbitrary Jython or Closure expressions, if those extensions are also present. The attacker must know a valid project ID of a project that contains at least one row. Version 3.8.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48208 | pure-ftpd before 1.0.52 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is an out of bounds read in the domlsd() function of the ls.c file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48208</link><description>pure-ftpd before 1.0.52 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is an out of bounds read in the domlsd() function of the ls.c file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7763 | WhatsUp Gold getReport Missing Authentication Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7763</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.0, 

an Authentication Bypass issue exists which allows an attacker to obtain encrypted user credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45242 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT A8J-ENH1350EXT devices through 3.9.3.2_c1.9.51 allow (blind) OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters to the Ping o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45242</link><description>EnGenius ENH1350EXT A8J-ENH1350EXT devices through 3.9.3.2_c1.9.51 allow (blind) OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters to the Ping or Speed Test utility. During the time of initial setup, the device creates an open unsecured network whose admin panel is configured with the default credentials of admin/admin. An unauthorized attacker in proximity to the Wi-Fi network can exploit this window of time to execute arbitrary OS commands with root-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45259 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. By intercepting an HTTP req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45259</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. By intercepting an HTTP request and changing the filename property in the download interface, any file on the device can be deleted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47173 | Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface denial of service vulnerability in SaaS and marketplace setups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47173</link><description>Aimeos is an e-commerce framework. All SaaS and marketplace setups using the Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface version from 2024.04 up to 2024.07.1 are affected by a potential denial of service attack. Version 2024.07.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48427 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Sourcecodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48427</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Sourcecodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter in /mpms/admin/?page=services/manage_service&amp;id</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46998 | baserCMS has a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Edit Email Form Settings Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46998</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Edit Email Form Settings Feature. Version 5.1.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48144 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Fusion Chat Chat AI Assistant Ask Me Anything v1.2.4.0 allows attackers to access and exf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48144</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Fusion Chat Chat AI Assistant Ask Me Anything v1.2.4.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48145 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Netangular Technologies ChatNet AI Version v1.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48145</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Netangular Technologies ChatNet AI Version v1.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46996 | baserCMS has a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Blog posts Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46996</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Blog posts feature. Version 5.1.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48140 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica Your AI Copilot powered by ChatGPT4 v6.3.0 allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48140</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica Your AI Copilot powered by ChatGPT4 v6.3.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48141 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Zhipu AI CodeGeeX v2.17.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48141</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Zhipu AI CodeGeeX v2.17.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48142 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica ChatGPT AI Assistant v2.4.0 allows attackers to access an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48142</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica ChatGPT AI Assistant v2.4.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48143 | A lack of rate limiting in the OTP validation component of Digitory Multi Channel Integrated POS v1.0 allows attackers to gain access to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48143</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the OTP validation component of Digitory Multi Channel Integrated POS v1.0 allows attackers to gain access to the ordering system and place an excessive amount of food orders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46994 | baserCMS has Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in Blog posts and Contents list Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46994</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Blog posts and Contents list Feature. Version 5.1.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46995 | baserCMS has Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in HTTP 400 Bad Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46995</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in HTTP 400 Bad Request. Version 5.1.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48139 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Blackbox AI v1.3.95 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48139</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Blackbox AI v1.3.95 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48454 | An issue in SourceCodester Purchase Order Management System v1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /admin?page=user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48454</link><description>An issue in SourceCodester Purchase Order Management System v1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /admin?page=user component</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10337 | SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10337</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/home.php?con=add. The manipulation of the argument cat/subcat/ t1/t2/text leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10338 | SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10338</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/home.php. The manipulation of the argument view/view1 leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48442 | Incorrect access control in Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48442</link><description>Incorrect access control in Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 allows attackers to access the SSH protocol without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48514 | php-heic-to-jpg &lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to remote code execution. An attacker who can upload heic images is able to execute code on the remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48514</link><description>php-heic-to-jpg &lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to remote code execution. An attacker who can upload heic images is able to execute code on the remote server via the file name. As a result, the CIA is no longer guaranteed. This affects php-heic-to-jpg 1.0.5 and below.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10295 | Gateway: apicast basic auth bypass via malformed base64 headerssending non-base64 &amp;#x27;basic&amp;#x27; auth with special characters causes apicast to incorrectly authenticate a request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10295</link><description>A flaw was found in Gateway. Sending a non-base64 'basic' auth with special characters can cause APICast to incorrectly authenticate a request. A malformed basic authentication header containing special characters bypasses authentication and allows unauthorized access to the backend. This issue can occur due to a failure in the base64 decoding process, which causes APICast to skip the rest of the authentication checks and proceed with routing the request upstream.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48440 | Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 was discovered to contain a command ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48440</link><description>Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the component at_command.asp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48441 | Wuhan Tianyu Information Industry Co., Ltd Tianyu CPE Router CommonCPExCPETS_v3.2.468.11.04_P4 was discovered to contain a command injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48441</link><description>Wuhan Tianyu Information Industry Co., Ltd Tianyu CPE Router CommonCPExCPETS_v3.2.468.11.04_P4 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the component at_command.asp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10313 | iniNet Solutions SpiderControl SCADA PC HMI Editor Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10313</link><description>iniNet Solutions SpiderControl SCADA PC HMI Editor has a path traversal 
vulnerability. When the software loads a malicious ‘ems' project 
template file constructed by an attacker, it can write files to 
arbitrary directories. This can lead to overwriting system files, 
causing system paralysis, or writing to startup items, resulting in 
remote control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46478 | HTMLDOC v1.9.18 contains a buffer overflow in parse_pre function,ps-pdf.cxx:5681.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46478</link><description>HTMLDOC v1.9.18 contains a buffer overflow in parse_pre function,ps-pdf.cxx:5681.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38314 | IBM Maximo Application Suite - Monitor Component information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38314</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite - Monitor Component 8.10, 8.11, and 9.0 could disclose information in the form of the hard-coded cryptographic key to an attacker that has compromised environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48547 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of DreamCatcher Life v1.8.7 allows attackers to access sensitive info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48547</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of DreamCatcher Life v1.8.7 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48548 | The APK file in Cloud Smart Lock v2.0.1 has a leaked a URL that can call an API for binding physical devices. This vulnerability allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48548</link><description>The APK file in Cloud Smart Lock v2.0.1 has a leaked a URL that can call an API for binding physical devices. This vulnerability allows attackers to arbitrarily construct a request to use the app to bind to unknown devices by finding a valid serial number via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40810 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. An app may be able to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40810</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. An app may be able to cause a coprocessor crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44141 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. A person with physical access to an unlocked Mac may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44141</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. A person with physical access to an unlocked Mac may be able to gain root code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44185 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, watchOS 10.6, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44185</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, watchOS 10.6, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6, macOS Sonoma 14.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44205 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.8, macOS Monte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44205</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.8, macOS Monterey 12.7.6, iOS 16.7.9 and iPadOS 16.7.9, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6, macOS Sonoma 14.6. A sandboxed app may be able to access sensitive user data in system logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44206 | An issue in the handling of URL protocols was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, wa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44206</link><description>An issue in the handling of URL protocols was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, watchOS 10.6, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6, macOS Sonoma 14.6. A user may be able to bypass some web content restrictions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48544 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Sylvania Smart Home v3.0.3 allows attackers to access sensitive in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48544</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Sylvania Smart Home v3.0.3 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48545 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of IVY Smart v4.5.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48545</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of IVY Smart v4.5.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10335 | SourceCodester Garbage Collection Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10335</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Garbage Collection Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "username" to be affected. But it must be assumed that the parameter "password" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10336 | SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System Admin Login Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10336</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php of the component Admin Login Page. The manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48542 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Yamaha Headphones Controller v1.6.7 allows attackers to access sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48542</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Yamaha Headphones Controller v1.6.7 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48546 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Wear Sync v1.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48546</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Wear Sync v1.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48539 | Neye3C v4.5.2.0 was discovered to contain a hardcoded encryption key in the firmware update mechanism.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48539</link><description>Neye3C v4.5.2.0 was discovered to contain a hardcoded encryption key in the firmware update mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48540 | Incorrect access control in XIAO HE Smart 4.3.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48540</link><description>Incorrect access control in XIAO HE Smart 4.3.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48541 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Ruochan Smart v4.4.7 allows attackers to access sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48541</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Ruochan Smart v4.4.7 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9692 | Improper Access Control in Input in VIMESA VHF/FM Transmitter Blue Plus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9692</link><description>VIMESA VHF/FM Transmitter Blue Plus is suffering from a Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can issue an unauthorized HTTP GET request to the unprotected endpoint 'doreboot' and restart the transmitter operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48538 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Neye3C v4.5.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48538</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Neye3C v4.5.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45031 | Apache Syncope: Stored XSS in Console and Enduser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45031</link><description>When editing objects in the Syncope Console, incomplete HTML tags could be used to bypass HTML sanitization. This made it possible to inject stored XSS payloads which would trigger for other users during ordinary usage of the application.
XSS payloads could also be injected in Syncope Enduser when editing “Personal Information” or “User Requests”: such payloads would trigger for administrators in Syncope Console, thus enabling session hijacking.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.9, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10180 | Contact Form 7 - Repeatable Fields &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via field_group Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10180</link><description>The Contact Form 7 – Repeatable Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's field_group shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49693 | WordPress Mega Elements – Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kraftplugins Mega Elements allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mega Elements: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49695 | WordPress WP Flow Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins WP Flow Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Flow Plus: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49696 | WordPress Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.21 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RoboSoft Robo Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Robo Gallery: from n/a through 3.2.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10332 | A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in Janto v4.3r11 from Impronta. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10332</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in Janto v4.3r11 from Impronta. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending the victim a malicious URL using the endpoint “/abonados/public/janto/main.php”.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49702 | WordPress myCred Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in myCRED myCred Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects myCred Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49681 | WordPress WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49681</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SWIT WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49691 | WordPress Product Filter by WBW plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49691</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Woobewoo Product Filter by WBW allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Product Filter by WBW: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49703 | WordPress WpEvently plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49703</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MagePeople Team Event Manager for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Event Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49682 | WordPress Simple Membership plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49682</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in smp7, wp.Insider Simple Membership allows Phishing.This issue affects Simple Membership: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49683 | WordPress Schema &amp;amp; Structured Data for WP &amp;amp; AMP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49683</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5608 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5608</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8121 are vulnerable to SQL Injection in the technician reports feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8959 | WP Adminify – Best WordPress Custom Dashboard Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8959</link><description>The WP Adminify – Custom WordPress Dashboard, Login and Admin Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10176 | Compact WP Audio Player &amp;lt;= 1.9.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sc_embed_player Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10176</link><description>The Compact WP Audio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 
sc_embed_player shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10331 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System search-vehicle.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10331</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinputdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9214 | Extra Product Options Builder for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.133 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9214</link><description>The Extra Product Options Builder for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'RednaoSerializedFields' parameter during the creation of a signature file in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.133 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9650 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 9.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;tooltip&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9650</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tooltip’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6826 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6826</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.2 before 17.3.6, 17.4 before 17.4.3, and 17.5 before 17.5.1. A denial of service could occur via importing a malicious crafted XML manifest file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 09:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8312 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8312</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.10 before 17.3.6, 17.4 before 17.4.3, and 17.5 before 17.5.1. An attacker could inject HTML into the Global Search field on a diff view leading to XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 09:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10050 | Elementor Header &amp;amp; Footer Builder &amp;lt;= 1.6.43 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Disclosure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10050</link><description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.43 via the hfe_template shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to view the contents of Draft, Private and Password-protected posts they do not own.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 08:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8717 | PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook, PDF embed, PDF viewer – DearFlip &amp;lt;= 2.3.32 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8717</link><description>The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook, PDF embed, PDF viewer – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pdf_source' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6049 | Unauthenticated Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6049</link><description>The web server of Lawo AG vsm LTC Time Sync (vTimeSync) is affected by a "..." (triple dot) path traversal vulnerability. By sending a specially crafted HTTP request, an unauthenticated remote attacker could download arbitrary files from the operating system. As a limitation, the exploitation is only possible if the requested file has some file extension, e. g. .exe or .txt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8667 | HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.10.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Publication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8667</link><description>The HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post publication due to a missing capability check on the activateCampaign() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to publish arbitrary posts like ones they have submitted for review, or a site administrator has in draft.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9531 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Missing Authorization to Forged Vendor Profile Deletion Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9531</link><description>The MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mvx_sent_deactivation_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to send a canned email to the site's administrator asking to delete the profile of an arbitrary vendor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9943 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Vendor Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9943</link><description>The MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions in api/class-mvx-rest-controller.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update vendor account details, create vendor accounts, and delete arbitrary users via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9864 | EventPrime – Modern Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.0.4.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9864</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ticket names in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when front-end users can submit new events with tickets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9865 | EventPrime – Modern Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.0.4.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Transaction Log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9865</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ep_booking_attendee_fields’ fields in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the transaction log for a booking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40595 | An authentication-bypass issue in the RDP component of One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Sessions (SPS) On Premise before 7.5.1 (and LTS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40595</link><description>An authentication-bypass issue in the RDP component of One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Sessions (SPS) On Premise before 7.5.1 (and LTS before 7.0.5.1) allows man-in-the-middle attackers to obtain access to privileged sessions on target resources by intercepting cleartext RDP protocol information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 05:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9374 | Terms descriptions &amp;lt;= 3.4.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9374</link><description>The Terms descriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 04:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>