<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 06:28:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-3239 | PostX &amp;lt; 4.0.2 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3239</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks and WordPress Blog Plugin  WordPress plugin before 4.0.2 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 06:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43040 | IBM Spectrum Fusion HCI improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43040</link><description>IBM Spectrum Fusion HCI 2.5.2 through 2.7.2 could allow an attacker to perform unauthorized actions in RGW for Ceph due to improper bucket access.  IBM X-Force ID:  266807.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 02:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29212 | Due to an  unsafe de-serialization method used by the Veeam Service Provider Console(VSPC) server in communication between the management ag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29212</link><description>Due to an  unsafe de-serialization method used by the Veeam Service Provider Console(VSPC) server in communication between the management agent and its components, under certain conditions, it is possible to perform Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the VSPC server machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 02:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35205 | The WPS Office (aka cn.wps.moffice_eng) application before 17.0.0 for Android fails to properly sanitize file names before processing them t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35205</link><description>The WPS Office (aka cn.wps.moffice_eng) application before 17.0.0 for Android fails to properly sanitize file names before processing them through external application interactions, leading to a form of path traversal. This potentially enables any application to dispatch a crafted library file, aiming to overwrite an existing native library utilized by WPS Office. Successful exploitation could result in the execution of arbitrary commands under the guise of WPS Office's application ID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:04:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4809 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System setting.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4809</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file setting.php. The manipulation of the argument logo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263929 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:04:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35204 | Veritas System Recovery before 23.2_Hotfix has incorrect permissions for the Veritas System Recovery folder, and thus low-privileged users c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35204</link><description>Veritas System Recovery before 23.2_Hotfix has incorrect permissions for the Veritas System Recovery folder, and thus low-privileged users can conduct attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:04:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4808 | Kashipara College Management System delete_faculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4808</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file delete_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263928.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:04:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4806 | Kashipara College Management System each_extracurricula_activities.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4806</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file each_extracurricula_activities.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263926 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4807 | Kashipara College Management System delete_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4807</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file delete_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263927.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4804 | Kashipara College Management System edit_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4804</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file edit_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263924.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4805 | Kashipara College Management System edit_faculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4805</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file edit_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263925 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4802 | Kashipara College Management System submit_extracurricular_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4802</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file submit_extracurricular_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument activity_datetime leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4803 | Kashipara College Management System submit_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4803</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file submit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263923.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4801 | Kashipara College Management System submit_new_faculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4801</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file submit_new_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263921 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4800 | Kashipara College Management System submit_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4800</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file submit_student.php. The manipulation of the argument date_of_birth leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263920.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 21:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2299 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Profile Picture Upload in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2299</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application due to improper validation of uploaded files in the profile picture upload functionality. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious HTML files containing JavaScript code, which is executed when the file is accessed. This vulnerability is remotely exploitable via Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), allowing attackers to perform actions on behalf of authenticated users and potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information within the Lollms-webui application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 20:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4799 | Kashipara College Management System view_each_faculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4799</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file view_each_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263919.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 18:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4798 | SourceCodester Online Computer and Laptop Store manage_brand.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4798</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Computer and Laptop Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/maintenance/manage_brand.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263918 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4797 | Campcodes Online Laundry Management System ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument name/customer_name/username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263896.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4796 | Campcodes Online Laundry Management System manage_inv.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4796</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /manage_inv.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263895.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4795 | Campcodes Online Laundry Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4795</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263894 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 05:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4794 | Campcodes Online Laundry Management System manage_receiving.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4794</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_receiving.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263893 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4793 | Campcodes Online Laundry Management System manage_laundry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4793</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_laundry.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263892.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 03:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4792 | Campcodes Online Laundry Management System admin_class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4792</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument id/delete_category/delete_inv/delete_laundry/delete_supply/delete_user/login/save_inv/save_user leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263891.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4791 | Contemporary Control System BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B Application Protocol Data Unit denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4791</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Contemporary Control System BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B 2.7.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Application Protocol Data Unit. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263890 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4790 | DedeCMS path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4790</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DedeCMS 5.7.114. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys_verifies.php?action=view. The manipulation of the argument filename with the input ../../../../../etc/passwd leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263889 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47711 | IBM Security Guardium denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47711</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, and 12.0 could allow an authenticated user to upload files that would cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  271526.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47712 | IBM Security Guardium privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47712</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, and 12.0 could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges on the system due to improper permissions control.  IBM X-Force ID:  271527.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47709 | IBM Security Guardium command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47709</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, and 12.0 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending a specially crafted request.  IBM X-Force ID:  271524.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28760 | IBM App Connect Enterprise denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28760</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise 11.0.0.1 through 11.0.0.25 and 12.0.1.0 through 12.0.12.0 dashboard is vulnerable to a denial of service due to improper restrictions of resource allocation.  IBM X-Force ID:  285244.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28761 | IBM App Connect Enterprise HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28761</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise 11.0.0.1 through 11.0.0.25 and 12.0.1.0 through 12.0.12.0 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.  IBM X-Force ID:  285245.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52721 | The WindowManager module has a vulnerability in permission control.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect confide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52721</link><description>The WindowManager module has a vulnerability in permission control.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32999 | Cracking vulnerability in the OS security module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32999</link><description>Cracking vulnerability in the OS security module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4046 | Cracking vulnerability in the OS security module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4046</link><description>Cracking vulnerability in the OS security module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52720 | Race condition vulnerability in the soundtrigger module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52720</link><description>Race condition vulnerability in the soundtrigger module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32995 | Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the AMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32995</link><description>Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the AMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32996 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the account module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32996</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the account module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32997 | Race condition vulnerability in the binder driver module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32997</link><description>Race condition vulnerability in the binder driver module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32998 | NULL pointer access vulnerability in the clock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32998</link><description>NULL pointer access vulnerability in the clock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52384 | Double-free vulnerability in the RSMC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52384</link><description>Double-free vulnerability in the RSMC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52719 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the PMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52719</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the PMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32993 | Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the memory module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32993</link><description>Out-of-bounds access vulnerability in the memory module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52383 | Double-free vulnerability in the RSMC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52383</link><description>Double-free vulnerability in the RSMC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 09:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32992 | Insufficient verification vulnerability in the baseband module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32992</link><description>Insufficient verification vulnerability in the baseband module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 09:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32989 | Insufficient verification vulnerability in the system sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32989</link><description>Insufficient verification vulnerability in the system sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 09:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32990 | Permission verification vulnerability in the system sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32990</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the system sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 09:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32991 | Permission verification vulnerability in the wpa_supplicant module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32991</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the wpa_supplicant module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 09:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4487 | Blocksy Companion &amp;lt;= 2.0.45 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4487</link><description>The Blocksy Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG uploads in versions up to, and including, 2.0.45 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4329 | Thim Elementor Kit &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4329</link><description>The Thim Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 06:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4560 | Kognetiks Chatbot for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via chatbot_chatgpt_upload_file_to_assistant Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4560</link><description>The Kognetiks Chatbot for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the chatbot_chatgpt_upload_file_to_assistant function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers, with to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 05:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4630 | Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp;amp; Beaver Builder Templates &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4630</link><description>The Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_upload_mimes’ function in versions up to, and including, 4.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 04:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5447 | Use-After-Free in Service for Hardware Support App for Fingerprint Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5447</link><description>Missing lock check in SynHsaService may create a use-after-free condition which causes abnormal termination of the service, resulting in denial of service for the Synaptics Hardware Support App.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 02:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4209 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features &amp;lt;= 3.2.36 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Timer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4209</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown timer in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 02:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>