<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:57:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-13507 | Time-series operations may cause internal BSON size limit to be exceed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13507</link><description>Inconsistent object size validation in time series processing logic may result in later processing of oversized BSON documents leading to an assert failing and process termination. 
This issue impacts MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.26, v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.16 and MongoDB server v8.2 versions prior to 8.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13068 | Telegram Bot &amp;amp; Channel &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Telegram Username</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13068</link><description>The Telegram Bot &amp; Channel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Telegram username in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13558 | Blog2Social &amp;lt;= 8.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Trashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13558</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'deleteUserCcDraftPost' function in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the status of arbitrary posts to trash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13559 | EduKart Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13559</link><description>The EduKart Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the 'edukart_pro_register_user_front_end' function not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62497 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W versions prior to Ver.2.8.0. If a user accesses a specially crafted webpage wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62497</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W versions prior to Ver.2.8.0. If a user accesses a specially crafted webpage while logged in, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64730 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W all versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64730</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in SNC-CX600W all versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64304 | "FOD" App uses hard-coded cryptographic keys, which may allow a local unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the cryptographic keys.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64304</link><description>"FOD" App uses hard-coded cryptographic keys, which may allow a local unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the cryptographic keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 04:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10646 | Search Exclude &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 – Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Search Settings Modification via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10646</link><description>The Search Exclude plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a insufficient capability check on the Base::get_rest_permission() method in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to modify plugin settings, such as adding arbitrary posts to the search exclusion list.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 03:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6389 | Sneeit Framework &amp;lt;= 8.3 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution in sneeit_articles_pagination_callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6389</link><description>The Sneeit Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 8.3 via the sneeit_articles_pagination_callback() function. This is due to the function accepting user input and then passing that through call_user_func(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server which can be leveraged to inject backdoors or, for example, create new administrative user accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 03:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59373 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in 

 the restore mechanism of 

ASUS System Control Interface. It can be triggered when a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59373</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in 

 the restore mechanism of 

ASUS System Control Interface. It can be triggered when an unprivileged actor copies files without proper validation into protected system paths, potentially leading to arbitrary files being executed as SYSTEM.
For more information, please refer to section Security Update for MyAsus in the ASUS Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 03:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64761 | OpenBao Privileged Operator Identity Group Root Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64761</link><description>OpenBao is an open source identity-based secrets management system. Prior to version 2.4.4, a privileged operator could use the identity group subsystem to add a root policy to a group identity group, escalating their or another user's permissions in the system. Specifically this is an issue when: an operator in the root namespace has access to identity/groups endpoints and an operator does not have policy access. Otherwise, an operator with policy access could create or modify an existing policy to grant root-equivalent permissions through the sudo capability. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65944 | Sentry-Javascript deals with leaked sensitive headers when `sendDefaultPii` is set to `true`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65944</link><description>Sentry-Javascript is an official Sentry SDKs for JavaScript. From version 10.11.0 to before 10.27.0, when a Node.js application using the Sentry SDK has sendDefaultPii: true it is possible to inadvertently send certain sensitive HTTP headers, including the Cookie header, to Sentry. Those headers would be stored within a Sentry organization as part of the associated trace. A person with access to the Sentry organization could then view and use these sensitive values to impersonate or escalate their privileges within the application. This issue has been patched in version 10.27.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65951 | Inside Track / Entropy Derby Timelock Encryption Bypassed via Pre-Computed VDF Output Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65951</link><description>Inside Track / Entropy Derby is a research-grade horse-racing betting engine. Prior to commit 2d38d2f, the VDF-based timelock encryption system fails to enforce sequential delay against the betting operator. Bettors pre-compute the entire Wesolowski VDF and include vdfOutputHex in their encrypted bet ticket, allowing the house to decrypt immediately using fast proof verification instead of expensive VDF evaluation. This issue has been patched via commit 2d38d2f.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9803 | Improper Authentication in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9803</link><description>lunary-ai/lunary version 1.9.34 is vulnerable to an account takeover due to improper authentication in the Google OAuth integration. The application fails to verify the 'aud' (audience) field in the access token issued by Google, which is crucial for ensuring the token is intended for the application. This oversight allows attackers to use tokens issued to malicious applications to gain unauthorized access to user accounts. The issue is resolved in version 1.9.35.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 02:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62155 | QuantumNous New API Has SSRF Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62155</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. Prior to version 0.9.6, a recently patched SSRF vulnerability contains a bypass method that can bypass the existing security fix and still allow SSRF to occur.
Because the existing fix only applies security restrictions to the first URL request, a 302 redirect can bypass existing security measures and successfully access the intranet. This issue has been patched in version 0.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65018 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow in `png_combine_row` triggered via `png_image_finish_read`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65018</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From version 1.6.0 to before 1.6.51, there is a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the libpng simplified API function png_image_finish_read when processing 16-bit interlaced PNGs with 8-bit output format. Attacker-crafted interlaced PNG files cause heap writes beyond allocated buffer bounds. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64720 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a buffer overflow in `png_image_read_composite` via incorrect palette premultiplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64720</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From version 1.6.0 to before 1.6.51, an out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in png_image_read_composite when processing palette images with PNG_FLAG_OPTIMIZE_ALPHA enabled. The palette compositing code in png_init_read_transformations incorrectly applies background compositing during premultiplication, violating the invariant component ≤ alpha × 257 required by the simplified PNG API. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64505 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow in `png_do_quantize` via malformed palette index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64505</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. Prior to version 1.6.51, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in libpng's png_do_quantize function when processing PNG files with malformed palette indices. The vulnerability occurs when palette_lookup array bounds are not validated against externally-supplied image data, allowing an attacker to craft a PNG file with out-of-range palette indices that trigger out-of-bounds memory access. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64506 | LIBPNG is vulnerable to a heap buffer over-read in `png_write_image_8bit` with grayscale+alpha or RGB/RGBA images</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64506</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From version 1.6.0 to before 1.6.51, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in libpng's png_write_image_8bit function when processing 8-bit images through the simplified write API with convert_to_8bit enabled. The vulnerability affects 8-bit grayscale+alpha, RGB/RGBA, and images with incomplete row data. A conditional guard incorrectly allows 8-bit input to enter code expecting 16-bit input, causing reads up to 2 bytes beyond allocated buffer boundaries. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.51.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10144 | Perfect Brands for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10144</link><description>The Perfect Brands for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the `brands` attribute of the `products` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47856 | In RSA Authentication Agent before 7.4.7, service paths and shortcut paths may be vulnerable to path interception if the path has one or mor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47856</link><description>In RSA Authentication Agent before 7.4.7, service paths and shortcut paths may be vulnerable to path interception if the path has one or more spaces and is not surrounded by quotation marks. An adversary can place an executable in a higher-level directory of the path, and Windows will resolve that executable instead of the intended executable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54338 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54338</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows an attacker to disclose user hashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54341 | A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There are Hard-coded configurati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54341</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2. There are Hard-coded configuration values.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54563 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54563</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows Incorrect Access Control, leading to Remote Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63674 | An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.1227.472.2926 allows local physical attackers to execute arbitrary code via overriding t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63674</link><description>An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.1227.472.2926 allows local physical attackers to execute arbitrary code via overriding the bootloader on the SD card.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54347 | A Directory Traversal vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54347</link><description>A Directory Traversal vulnerability was found in the Application Server of Desktop Alert PingAlert version 6.1.0.11 to 6.1.1.2 which allows an attacker to write arbitrary files under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29933 | Improper input validation within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to write out of bounds, potentially resulting in a crash or denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29933</link><description>Improper input validation within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to write out of bounds, potentially resulting in a crash or denial of service</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48511 | Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to write to an arbitrary physical address, potentially resulting in cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48511</link><description>Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to write to an arbitrary physical address, potentially resulting in crash or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48510 | Improper return value within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to bypass KSLR, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48510</link><description>Improper return value within AMD uProf can allow a local attacker to bypass KSLR, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52538 | Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52538</link><description>Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25126 | TVT NVMS-9000 Hard-coded API Credentials &amp;amp; Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25126</link><description>Shenzhen TVT Digital Technology Co., Ltd. NVMS-9000 firmware (used by many white-labeled DVR/NVR/IPC products) contains hardcoded API credentials and an OS command injection flaw in its configuration services. The web/API interface accepts HTTP/XML requests authenticated with a fixed vendor credential string and passes user-controlled fields into shell execution contexts without proper argument sanitization. An unauthenticated remote attacker can leverage the hard-coded credential to access endpoints such as /editBlackAndWhiteList and inject shell metacharacters inside XML parameters, resulting in arbitrary command execution as root. The same vulnerable backend is also reachable in some models through a proprietary TCP service on port 4567 that accepts a magic GUID preface and base64-encoded XML, enabling the same command injection sink. Firmware releases from mid-February 2018 and later are reported to have addressed this issue. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-01-28 UTC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7330 | Ruijie Networks NBR Routers Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via fileupload.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7330</link><description>Ruijie NBR series routers contain an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability via /ddi/server/fileupload.php. The endpoint accepts attacker-supplied values in the name and uploadDir parameters and saves the provided multipart file content without adequate validation or sanitization of file type, path, or extension. A remote attacker can upload a crafted PHP file and then access it from the web root, resulting in arbitrary code execution in the context of the web service. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-01-14 UTC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14007 | TVT NVMS-9000 &amp;lt; 1.3.4 Unauthenticated Administrative Queries &amp;amp; Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14007</link><description>Shenzhen TVT Digital Technology Co., Ltd. NVMS-9000 firmware (used by many white-labeled DVR/NVR/IPC products) versions prior to 1.3.4 contain an authentication bypass in the NVMS-9000 control protocol. By sending a single crafted TCP payload to an exposed NVMS-9000 control port, an unauthenticated remote attacker can invoke privileged administrative query commands without valid credentials. Successful exploitation discloses sensitive information including administrator usernames and passwords in cleartext, network and service configuration, and other device details via commands such as queryBasicCfg, queryUserList, queryEmailCfg, queryPPPoECfg, and queryFTPCfg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0003 | Inadequate lock protection within Xilinx Run time may allow a local attacker to trigger a Use-After-Free condition potentially resulting in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0003</link><description>Inadequate lock protection within Xilinx Run time may allow a local attacker to trigger a Use-After-Free condition potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality or availability</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0007 | Insufficient validation within Xilinx Run Time framework could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges from user space to kernel space...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0007</link><description>Insufficient validation within Xilinx Run Time framework could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges from user space to kernel space, potentially compromising confidentiality, integrity, and/or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36150 | IBM Concert Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36150</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63498 | alinto SOGo 5.12.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "userName" parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63498</link><description>alinto SOGo 5.12.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "userName" parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56400 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the OAuth implementation of the Tuya SDK 6.5.0 for Android and iOS, affects the Tuya Smar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56400</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the OAuth implementation of the Tuya SDK 6.5.0 for Android and iOS, affects the Tuya Smart and Smartlife mobile applications, as well as other third-party applications that integrate the SDK, allows an attacker to link their own Amazon Alexa account to a victim's Tuya account. The applications fail to validate the OAuth state parameter during the account linking flow, enabling a cross-site request forgery (CSRF)-like attack. By tricking the victim into clicking a crafted authorization link, an attacker can complete the OAuth flow on the victim's behalf, resulting in unauthorized Alexa access to the victim's Tuya-connected devices. This affects users regardless of prior Alexa linkage and does not require the Tuya application to be active at the time. Successful exploitation may allow remote control of devices such as cameras, doorbells, door locks, or alarms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0005 | Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0005</link><description>Improper input validation within the XOCL driver may allow a local attacker to generate an integer overflow condition, potentially resulting in crash or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64048 | YCCMS 3.4 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the article management functionality. The vulnerability exists in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64048</link><description>YCCMS 3.4 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the article management functionality. The vulnerability exists in the add() and getPost() functions within the ArticleAction.class.php file due to improper neutralization of user input in the article title field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52539 | A buffer overflow with Xilinx Run Time Environment may allow a local attacker to read or corrupt data from the advanced extensible interface...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52539</link><description>A buffer overflow with Xilinx Run Time Environment may allow a local attacker to read or corrupt data from the advanced extensible interface (AXI), potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality, integrity, and/or availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64047 | OpenRapid RapidCMS 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /user/user-move.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64047</link><description>OpenRapid RapidCMS 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /user/user-move.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63914 | An issue was discovered in Cinnamon kotaemon 0.11.0. The _may_extract_zip function in the \libs\ktem\ktem\index\file\ui.py file does not che...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63914</link><description>An issue was discovered in Cinnamon kotaemon 0.11.0. The _may_extract_zip function in the \libs\ktem\ktem\index\file\ui.py file does not check the contents of uploaded ZIP files. Although the contents are extracted into a temporary folder that is cleared before each extraction, successfully uploading a ZIP bomb could still cause the server to consume excessive resources during decompression. Moreover, if no further files are uploaded afterward, the extracted data could occupy disk space and potentially render the system unavailable. Anyone with permission to upload files can carry out this attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13466 | body-parser vulnerable to denial of service when url encoding is used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13466</link><description>body-parser 2.2.0 is vulnerable to denial of service due to inefficient handling of URL-encoded bodies with very large numbers of parameters. An attacker can send payloads containing thousands of parameters within the default 100KB request size limit, causing elevated CPU and memory usage. This can lead to service slowdown or partial outages under sustained malicious traffic.
This issue is addressed in version 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36112 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36112</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.7 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5 and 6.2.1.1 could reveal sensitive server IP configuration information to an unauthorized user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13609 | Keylime: keylime: registrar allows identity takeover via duplicate uuid registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13609</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in keylime where an attacker can exploit this flaw by registering a new agent using a different Trusted Platform Module (TPM) device but claiming an existing agent's unique identifier (UUID). This action overwrites the legitimate agent's identity, enabling the attacker to impersonate the compromised agent and potentially bypass security controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63434 | The update mechanism in Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is insecure. The application downloads and extracts up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63434</link><description>The update mechanism in Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is insecure. The application downloads and extracts update packages containing executable code without performing a cryptographic integrity or authenticity check on their contents. An attacker who can control the update metadata can serve a malicious package, which the application will accept, extract, and later execute, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63435 | Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 is Missing Authentication for Critical Function. The server-side endpoint responsible fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63435</link><description>Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 is Missing Authentication for Critical Function. The server-side endpoint responsible for serving update packages for the application does not require any authentication. This allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to freely download official update packages..</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63432 | Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is Missing SSL Certificate Validation. The application fails to properly valid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63432</link><description>Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior is Missing SSL Certificate Validation. The application fails to properly validate the TLS certificate from its update server. An attacker on the same network can exploit this vulnerability by performing a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack to intercept, decrypt, and modify traffic between the application and the update server. This serves as the basis for further attacks, including Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63433 | Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior uses a hardcoded cryptographic key and IV to decrypt update metadata. The key ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63433</link><description>Xtooltech Xtool AnyScan Android Application 4.40.40 and prior uses a hardcoded cryptographic key and IV to decrypt update metadata. The key is stored as a static value within the application's code. An attacker with the ability to intercept network traffic can use this hardcoded key to decrypt, modify, and re-encrypt the update manifest, allowing them to direct the application to download a malicious update package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63958 | MILLENSYS Vision Tools Workspace 6.5.0.2585 exposes a sensitive configuration endpoint (/MILLENSYS/settings) that is accessible without auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63958</link><description>MILLENSYS Vision Tools Workspace 6.5.0.2585 exposes a sensitive configuration endpoint (/MILLENSYS/settings) that is accessible without authentication. This page leaks plaintext database credentials, file share paths, internal license server configuration, and software update parameters. An unauthenticated attacker can retrieve this information by accessing the endpoint directly, potentially leading to full system compromise. The vulnerability is due to missing access controls on a privileged administrative function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63952 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /mwapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63952</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /mwapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily create accounts via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63953 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /usapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63953</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the /usapi?method=add-user component of Magewell Pro Convert v1.2.213 allows attackers to arbitrarily create accounts via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40213 | Bluetooth: MGMT: fix crash in set_mesh_sync and set_mesh_complete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40213</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: MGMT: fix crash in set_mesh_sync and set_mesh_complete

There is a BUG: KASAN: stack-out-of-bounds in set_mesh_sync due to
memcpy from badly declared on-stack flexible array.

Another crash is in set_mesh_complete() due to double list_del via
mgmt_pending_valid + mgmt_pending_remove.

Use DEFINE_FLEX to declare the flexible array right, and don't memcpy
outside bounds.

As mgmt_pending_valid removes the cmd from list, use mgmt_pending_free,
and also report status on error.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60638 | An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Nnssf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60638</link><description>An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Nnssf_NSSAIAvailability API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60632 | An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Npcf_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60632</link><description>An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via crafted POST request to the Npcf_BDTPolicyControl API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60633 | An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via the Nudm_SubscriberDataManagement...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60633</link><description>An issue was discovered in Free5GC v4.0.0 and v4.0.1 allowing an attacker to cause a denial of service via the Nudm_SubscriberDataManagement API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60917 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60917</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the color parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10554 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Requirements in ENOVIA Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10554</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Requirements in ENOVIA Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10555 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Service Items Management in DELMIA Service Process Engineer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10555</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Service Items Management in DELMIA Service Process Engineer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60915 | An issue in the size query parameter (/views/file.py) of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60915</link><description>An issue in the size query parameter (/views/file.py) of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to execute a path traversal via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60916 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60916</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /overview/network/ endpoint of Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the charge parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44018 | A firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in the OTA Update functionality of GL-Inet GL-AXT1800 4.7.0. A specially crafted .tar file can lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44018</link><description>A firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in the OTA Update functionality of GL-Inet GL-AXT1800 4.7.0. A specially crafted .tar file can lead to a firmware downgrade. An attacker can perform a man-in-the-middle attack to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56401 | ZIRA Group WBRM 7.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in referenceLookupsByTableNameAndColumnName.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56401</link><description>ZIRA Group WBRM 7.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in referenceLookupsByTableNameAndColumnName.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56423 | An issue in Austrian Academy of Sciences (AW) Austrian Archaeological Institute OpenAtlas v.8.12.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56423</link><description>An issue in Austrian Academy of Sciences (AW) Austrian Archaeological Institute OpenAtlas v.8.12.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the login error messages</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60914 | Incorrect access control in Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60914</link><description>Incorrect access control in Austrian Archaeological Institute Openatlas before v8.12.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information via sending a crafted GET request to the /display_logo endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12969 | CVE-2025-12969</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12969</link><description>Fluent Bit in_forward input plugin does not properly enforce the security.users authentication mechanism under certain configuration conditions. This allows remote attackers with network access to the Fluent Bit instance exposing the forward input to send unauthenticated data. By bypassing authentication controls, attackers can inject forged log records, flood alerting systems, or manipulate routing decisions, compromising the authenticity and integrity of ingested logs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12970 | CVE-2025-12970</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12970</link><description>The extract_name function in Fluent Bit in_docker input plugin copies container names into a fixed size stack buffer without validating length. An attacker who can create containers or control container names, can supply a long name that overflows the buffer, leading to process crash or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12972 | CVE-2025-12972</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12972</link><description>Fluent Bit out_file plugin does not properly sanitize tag values when deriving output file names. When the File option is omitted, the plugin uses untrusted tag input to construct file paths. This allows attackers with network access to craft tags containing path traversal sequences that cause Fluent Bit to write files outside the intended output directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12977 | CVE-2025-12977</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12977</link><description>Fluent Bit in_http, in_splunk, and in_elasticsearch input plugins fail to sanitize tag_key inputs. An attacker with network access or the ability to write records into Splunk or Elasticsearch can supply tag_key values containing special characters such as newlines or ../ that are treated as valid tags. Because tags influence routing and some outputs derive filenames or contents from tags, this can allow newline injection, path traversal, forged record injection, or log misrouting, impacting data integrity and log routing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12978 | CVE-2025-12978</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12978</link><description>Fluent Bit in_http, in_splunk, and in_elasticsearch input plugins contain a flaw in the tag_key validation logic that fails to enforce exact key-length matching. This allows crafted inputs where a tag prefix is incorrectly treated as a full match. A remote attacker with authenticated or exposed access to these input endpoints can exploit this behavior to manipulate tags and redirect records to unintended destinations. This compromises the authenticity of ingested logs and can allow injection of forged data, alert flooding and routing manipulation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11921 | iStat Menus 7.10.4 - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11921</link><description>iStats contains an insecure XPC service that allows local, unprivileged users to escalate their privileges to root via command injection.This issue affects iStats: 7.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65493 | NULL pointer dereference in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65493</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS/TLS connection that triggers BIO_get_data() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65494 | NULL pointer dereference in get_san_or_cn_from_cert() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65494</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in get_san_or_cn_from_cert() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted X.509 certificate that causes sk_GENERAL_NAME_value() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65495 | Integer signedness error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65495</link><description>Integer signedness error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted TLS certificate that causes i2d_X509() to return -1 and be misused as a malloc() size parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65496 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65496</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65497 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65497</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65498 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65498</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65499 | Array index error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65499</link><description>Array index error in tls_verify_call_back() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_ex_data_X509_STORE_CTX_idx() to return -1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65500 | NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65500</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in coap_dtls_generate_cookie() in src/coap_openssl.c in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted DTLS handshake that triggers SSL_get_SSL_CTX() to return NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65501 | Null pointer dereference in coap_dtls_info_callback() in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a DTLS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65501</link><description>Null pointer dereference in coap_dtls_info_callback() in OISM libcoap 4.3.5 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a DTLS handshake where SSL_get_app_data() returns NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65502 | Null pointer dereference in add_ca_certs() in Cesanta Mongoose before 7.2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via TLS initi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65502</link><description>Null pointer dereference in add_ca_certs() in Cesanta Mongoose before 7.2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via TLS initialization where SSL_CTX_get_cert_store() returns NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65503 | Use after free in endpoint destructors in Redboltz async_mqtt 10.2.5 allows local users to cause a denial of service via triggering SSL init...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65503</link><description>Use after free in endpoint destructors in Redboltz async_mqtt 10.2.5 allows local users to cause a denial of service via triggering SSL initialization failure that results in incorrect destruction order between io_context and endpoint objects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65998 | Apache Syncope: Default AES key used for internal password encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65998</link><description>Apache Syncope can be configured to store the user password values in the internal database with AES encryption, though this is not the default option.

When AES is configured, the default key value, hard-coded in the source code, is always used. This allows a malicious attacker, once obtained access to the internal database content, to reconstruct the original cleartext password values.
This is not affecting encrypted plain attributes, whose values are also stored using AES encryption.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.15 / 4.0.3, which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12628 | WP 2FA &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Second Factor Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12628</link><description>The WP 2FA WordPress plugin does not generate backup codes with enough entropy, which could allow attackers to bypass the second factor by brute forcing them</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40212 | nfsd: fix refcount leak in nfsd_set_fh_dentry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40212</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfsd: fix refcount leak in nfsd_set_fh_dentry()

nfsd exports a "pseudo root filesystem" which is used by NFSv4 to find
the various exported filesystems using LOOKUP requests from a known root
filehandle.  NFSv3 uses the MOUNT protocol to find those exported
filesystems and so is not given access to the pseudo root filesystem.

If a v3 (or v2) client uses a filehandle from that filesystem,
nfsd_set_fh_dentry() will report an error, but still stores the export
in "struct svc_fh" even though it also drops the reference (exp_put()).
This means that when fh_put() is called an extra reference will be dropped
which can lead to use-after-free and possible denial of service.

Normal NFS usage will not provide a pseudo-root filehandle to a v3
client.  This bug can only be triggered by the client synthesising an
incorrect filehandle.

To fix this we move the assignments to the svc_fh later, after all
possible error cases have been detected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41016 | Multiple vulnerabilities in DFUSION by Davantis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41016</link><description>Inadequate access control vulnerability in Davantis DFUSION v6.177.7, which allows unauthorised actors to extract images and videos related to alarm events through access to “/alarms//”, where the “MEDIA” parameter can take the value of “snapshot” or “video.mp4”. These media files contain images recorded by security cameras in response to triggered alerts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41017 | Multiple vulnerabilities in DFUSION by Davantis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41017</link><description>Inadequate access control vulnerability in Davantis DDFUSION v6.177.7, which allows unauthorised actors to retrieve perspective parameters from security camera settings by accessing “/cameras//perspective”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12740 | Remote Command Execution in Looker via IBM DB2 JDBC drive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12740</link><description>A Looker user with a Developer role could create a database connection using IBM DB2 driver and, by manipulating LookML, cause Looker to execute a malicious command, due to inadequate filtering of the driver's parameters.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  25.0.93+
  *  25.6.84+

  *  25.12.42+
  *  25.14.50+
  *  25.16.44+</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12741 | Arbitrary File Write in Denodo dialect of Looker allows Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12741</link><description>A Looker user with Developer role could create a database connection using Denodo driver and, by manipulating LookML, cause Looker to execute a malicious command.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.108+
  *  24.18.200+
  *  25.0.78+
  *  25.6.65+
  *  25.8.47+
  *  25.12.10+
  *  25.14+</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41087 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) stored in Taclia&amp;#x27;s web application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41087</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability stored in tha Taclia web application, where the uploaded SVG images are not properly sanitized. This allows to the attackers to embed malicious scripts in SVG files such as image profiles, which are then stored on the server and executed in the context of any user who accesses the compromised resource.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41729 | DoS via Modbus Read Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41729</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can send a specially crafted Modbus read command to the device which leads to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12739 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Looker&amp;#x27;s Extension Loader leading to Admin Account Compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12739</link><description>An attacker with viewer permissions in Looker could craft a malicious URL that, when opened by a Looker admin, would execute an attacker-supplied script. Exploitation required at least one Looker extension installed on the instance.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :  *  24.18.201+
  *  25.0.79+
  *  25.6.66+
  *  25.12.7+
  *  25.16.0+
  *  25.18.0+
  *  25.20.0+</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 09:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13596 | Improper Error Handling Leading to Sensitive Information Disclosure in CIGES ≤ 2.15.6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13596</link><description>A sensitive information disclosure vulnerability exists in the error handling component of ATISoluciones CIGES Application version 2.15.6 and earlier. When certain unexpected conditions trigger unhandled exceptions, the application returns detailed error messages and stack traces to the client. This may expose internal filesystem paths, SQL queries, database connection details, or environment configuration data to remote unauthenticated attackers. This issue allows information gathering and reconnaissance but does not enable direct system compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13588 | lKinderBueno Streamity Xtream IPTV Player proxy.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13588</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lKinderBueno Streamity Xtream IPTV Player up to 2.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file public/proxy.php. Performing manipulation results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 2.8.1 is sufficient to resolve this issue. The patch is named c70bfb8d36b47bfd64c5ec73917e1d9ddb97af92. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13586 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System changepassword.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13586</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Admin/changepassword.php. This manipulation of the argument txtconfirm_password causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-14015 | Studiocart &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14015</link><description>The WordPress eCommerce Plugin  WordPress plugin through 2.9.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12394 | Backup Migration &amp;lt; 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Backup Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12394</link><description>The Backup Migration WordPress plugin before 2.0.0 does not properly generate its backup path in certain server configurations, allowing unauthenticated users to fetch a log that discloses the backup filename. The backup archive is then downloadable without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12569 | WP Front User Submit &amp;lt; 5.0.0 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12569</link><description>The Guest posting / Frontend Posting / Front Editor  WordPress plugin before 5.0.0 does not validate a parameter before redirecting the user to its value, leading to an Open Redirect issue</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12629 | Broken Link Manager &amp;lt;= 0.6.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12629</link><description>The Broken Link Manager WordPress plugin through 0.6.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 06:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13585 | code-projects COVID Tracking System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13585</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects COVID Tracking System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument code results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13584 | Eigenfocus Description cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13584</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Eigenfocus up to 1.4.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Description Handler. The manipulation of the argument entry.description/time_entry.description leads to cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.4.1 is able to resolve this issue. The identifier of the patch is 7dec94c9d1f3e513e0ee38ba68caaba628e08582. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7402 | Ads Pro Plugin - Multi-Purpose WordPress Advertising Manager &amp;lt;= 4.95 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via site_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7402</link><description>The Ads Pro Plugin - Multi-Purpose WordPress Advertising Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘site_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.95 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:01:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13583 | code-projects Question Paper Generator POST Parameter signupscript.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13583</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Question Paper Generator 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /signupscript.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument Fname can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 04:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13582 | code-projects Jonnys Liquor GET Parameter detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13582</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Jonnys Liquor 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /detail.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument Product results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 04:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13581 | itsourcecode Student Information System schedule_edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13581</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Information System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /schedule_edit1.php. Such manipulation of the argument schedule_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13589 | Otsuka Information Technology｜FMS - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13589</link><description>FMS developed by Otsuka Information Technology has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13579 | code-projects Library System return.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /return.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13580 | code-projects Library System mail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13580</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Library System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /mail.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13578 | code-projects Library System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13578</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Library System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13577 | PHPGurukul Hostel Management System register-complaint.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13577</link><description>A flaw has been found in PHPGurukul Hostel Management System 2.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /register-complaint.php. Executing manipulation of the argument cdetails can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13576 | code-projects Blog Site admin.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13576</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Blog Site 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin.php. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13575 | code-projects Blog Site Category blog.php category_exists sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13575</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Blog Site 1.0. Impacted is the function category_exists of the file /resources/functions/blog.php of the component Category Handler. Such manipulation of the argument name/field leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13574 | code-projects Online Bidding System addcategory.php categoryadd unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13574</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Bidding System 1.0. This issue affects the function categoryadd of the file /administrator/addcategory.php. This manipulation of the argument catimage causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 02:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13573 | projectworlds can pass malicious payloads add_book.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13573</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in projectworlds can pass malicious payloads up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add_book.php. The manipulation of the argument image results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 23:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13572 | projectworlds Advanced Library Management System delete_admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13572</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in projectworlds Advanced Library Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /delete_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 23:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12800 | WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.4.5 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12800</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.4.5 via the su_shortcode_csv_table function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. If the 'Unsafe features' option is explicitly enabled by an administrator, this issue becomes exploitable by Contributor+ attackers</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 22:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13571 | code-projects Simple Food Ordering System listorder.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13571</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Simple Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /listorder.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 22:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13570 | itsourcecode COVID Tracking System page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode COVID Tracking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/?page=state. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 21:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13569 | itsourcecode COVID Tracking System page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13569</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode COVID Tracking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=city. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 21:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13568 | itsourcecode COVID Tracking System page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13568</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode COVID Tracking System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=people. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13567 | itsourcecode COVID Tracking System page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13567</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode COVID Tracking System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=establishment. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13566 | jarun nnn nnn.c run_cmd_as_plugin double free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13566</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in jarun nnn up to 5.1. The impacted element is the function show_content_in_floating_window/run_cmd_as_plugin of the file nnn/src/nnn.c. The manipulation leads to double free. An attack has to be approached locally. The identifier of the patch is 2f07ccdf21e705377862e5f9dfa31e1694979ac7. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 19:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13565 | SourceCodester Inventory Management System resetPassword.php password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13565</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Inventory Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /model/user/resetPassword.php. Executing manipulation can lead to weak password recovery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13564 | SourceCodester Pre-School Management System FilehelperController.php removefile denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13564</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Pre-School Management System 1.0. Impacted is the function removefile of the file app/controllers/FilehelperController.php. Performing manipulation of the argument filepath results in denial of service. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13562 | D-Link DIR-852 gena.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13562</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-852 1.00. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /gena.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument service leads to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 18:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13561 | SourceCodester Company Website CMS index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13561</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Company Website CMS 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54515 | The Secure Flag passed to Versal™ Adaptive SoC’s Arm® Trusted Firmware for Cortex®-A processors (TF-A) for Arm’s Power State Coordination In...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54515</link><description>The Secure Flag passed to Versal™ Adaptive SoC’s Arm® Trusted Firmware for Cortex®-A processors (TF-A) for Arm’s Power State Coordination Interface (PSCI) commands were incorrectly set to secure instead of using the processor’s actual security state. This would allow the PSCI requests to appear they were from processors in the secure state instead of the non-secure state.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48507 | The security state of the calling processor into Arm® Trusted Firmware (TF-A) is not used and could potentially allow non-secure processors ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48507</link><description>The security state of the calling processor into Arm® Trusted Firmware (TF-A) is not used and could potentially allow non-secure processors access to secure memories, access to crypto operations, and the ability to turn on and off subsystems within the SOC.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13560 | SourceCodester Company Website CMS reset-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13560</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Company Website CMS 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/reset-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21922 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in AMD StoreMI™ could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21922</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in AMD StoreMI™ could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21923 | Incorrect default permissions in AMD StoreMI™ could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation potentially resulting in arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21923</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in AMD StoreMI™ could allow an attacker to achieve privilege escalation potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13557 | Campcodes Online Polling System registeracc.php Nusẽtɔwo aɖe le be wotsɔe ɖe agbe. sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13557</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Polling System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registeracc.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13556 | Campcodes Online Polling System checklogin.php Nusẽtɔwo aɖe le be wotsɔe ɖe agbe. sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13556</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Online Polling System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/checklogin.php. Executing manipulation of the argument myusername can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13555 | Campcodes School File Management System Login index.php Nusẽtɔwo aɖe le be wotsɔe ɖe agbe. sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13555</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes School File Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php of the component Login. Performing manipulation of the argument stud_no results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13554 | Campcodes Supplier Management System Login index.php Nusẽtɔwo aɖe le be wotsɔe ɖe agbe. sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13554</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /index.php of the component Login. Such manipulation of the argument txtUsername leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13553 | D-Link DWR-M920 formPinManageSetup sub_41C7FC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13553</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DWR-M920 1.1.50. This affects the function sub_41C7FC of the file /boafrm/formPinManageSetup. This manipulation of the argument submit-url causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13552 | D-Link DIR-822K/DWR-M920 formWlEncrypt buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13552</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-822K and DWR-M920 1.00_20250513164613/1.1.50. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formWlEncrypt. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13551 | D-Link DIR-822K/DWR-M920 formWanConfigSetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13551</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-822K and DWR-M920 1.00_20250513164613/1.1.50. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formWanConfigSetup. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13550 | D-Link DIR-822K/DWR-M920 formVpnConfigSetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13550</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-822K and DWR-M920 1.00_20250513164613/1.1.50. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formVpnConfigSetup. Executing manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13549 | D-Link DIR-822K formNtp sub_455524 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13549</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-822K 1.00. This issue affects the function sub_455524 of the file /boafrm/formNtp. Performing manipulation of the argument submit-url results in buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13548 | D-Link DIR-822K/DWR-M920 formFirewallAdv buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13548</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-822K and DWR-M920 1.00_20250513164613/1.1.50. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formFirewallAdv. Such manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 11:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13547 | D-Link DIR-822K/DWR-M920 formDdns memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13547</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DIR-822K and DWR-M920 1.00_20250513164613/1.1.50. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formDdns. This manipulation of the argument submit-url causes memory corruption. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 11:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13546 | ashraf-kabir travel-agency Search results.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13546</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ashraf-kabir travel-agency up to 1f25aa03544bc5fb7a9e846f8a7879cecdb0cad3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /results.php of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument user_query results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13545 | ashraf-kabir travel-agency index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13545</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ashraf-kabir travel-agency up to 1f25aa03544bc5fb7a9e846f8a7879cecdb0cad3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin_area/index.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_pack leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13544 | ashraf-kabir travel-agency customer_register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13544</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ashraf-kabir travel-agency up to 1f25aa03544bc5fb7a9e846f8a7879cecdb0cad3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /customer_register.php. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>