<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 23:12:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10745 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal deferred_table.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10745</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/deferred_table.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 23:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10744 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal complex_header_2.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10744</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/media/unit_testing/templates/complex_header_2.php. The manipulation of the argument scripts leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 22:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10743 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal editable_ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10743</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /shopping/admin/assets/plugins/DataTables/examples/examples_support/editable_ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument value leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 21:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10742 | code-projects Wazifa System control.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10742</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/control.php. The manipulation of the argument to leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 21:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10741 | code-projects E-Health Care System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10741</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Users/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument f_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 20:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10740 | code-projects E-Health Care System consulting_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10740</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects E-Health Care System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/consulting_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument consulting_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 19:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10739 | code-projects E-Health Care System adminlogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10739</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects E-Health Care System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/adminlogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email/admin_pswd as part of String leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "email" to be affected. But it must be assumed that parameter "admin_pswd" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 17:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10738 | itsourcecode Farm Management System manage-breed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10738</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Farm Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage-breed.php. The manipulation of the argument breed leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 17:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10737 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10737</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10736 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /student.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 14:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10735 | Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System editNominee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /editNominee.php. The manipulation of the argument nominee_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 14:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10734 | Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System editPayment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10734</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /editPayment.php. The manipulation of the argument recipt_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 13:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10733 | code-projects Restaurant Order System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Order System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10732 | Tongda OA 2017 index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10732</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /module/word_model/view/index.php. The manipulation of the argument query_str leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10731 | Tongda OA check_seal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10731</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pda/appcenter/check_seal.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 10:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10730 | Tongda OA web_show.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10730</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.6. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pda/appcenter/web_show.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 08:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10702 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10702</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 18:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10701 | PHPGurukul Car Rental Portal search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10701</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Car Rental Portal 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 17:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10700 | code-projects University Event Management System submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10700</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects University Event Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file submit.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email/title/Year/gender/fromdate/todate/people leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "name" to be affected. But it must be assumed that a variety of other parameters is affected too.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10699 | code-projects Wazifa System logincontrol.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10699</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /controllers/logincontrol.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 14:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10698 | Tenda AC6 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10698</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.19 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 13:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10697 | Tenda AC6 API Endpoint WriteFacMac formWriteFacMac command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10697</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.19 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formWriteFacMac of the file /goform/WriteFacMac of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument The leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 12:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9896 | BBP Core – Expand bbPress powered forums with useful features &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via add_query_arg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9896</link><description>The BBP Core – Expand bbPress powered forums with useful features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 07:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51774 | qBittorrent before 5.0.1 proceeds with use of https URLs even after certificate validation errors.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51774</link><description>qBittorrent before 5.0.1 proceeds with use of https URLs even after certificate validation errors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 05:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10310 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.10.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Gallery Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10310</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom Gallery Widget 'image_title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 02:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10540 | Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.16 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10540</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'service' parameter of the bookingpress_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 02:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8739 | ReCaptcha Integration for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8739</link><description>The ReCaptcha Integration for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 02:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9868 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.10.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Age Gate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9868</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Age Gate Widget 'url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 02:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9191 | The Okta Device Access features, provided by the Okta Verify agent for Windows, provides access to the OktaDeviceAccessPipe, which enables a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9191</link><description>The Okta Device Access features, provided by the Okta Verify agent for Windows, provides access to the OktaDeviceAccessPipe, which enables attackers in a compromised device to retrieve passwords associated with Desktop MFA passwordless logins. The vulnerability was discovered via routine penetration testing.

Note: A precondition of this vulnerability is that the user must be using the Okta Device Access passwordless feature. Okta Device Access users not using passwordless are not affected, and customers only using Okta Verify on platforms other than Windows, or only using FastPass are not affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 21:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44232 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, visionOS 2.1, watchOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44232</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, visionOS 2.1, watchOS 11.1, tvOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. Parsing a maliciously crafted video file may lead to unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 20:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44233 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, visionOS 2.1, watchOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44233</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, visionOS 2.1, watchOS 11.1, tvOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. Parsing a maliciously crafted video file may lead to unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 20:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44234 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, visionOS 2.1, watchOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44234</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1, visionOS 2.1, watchOS 11.1, tvOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1. Parsing a maliciously crafted video file may lead to unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 20:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51252 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51252</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the restore function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48353 | Yealink Meeting Server before V26.0.0.67 allows attackers to obtain static key information from a front-end JS file and decrypt the plaintex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48353</link><description>Yealink Meeting Server before V26.0.0.67 allows attackers to obtain static key information from a front-end JS file and decrypt the plaintext passwords based on the obtained key information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48352 | Yealink Meeting Server before V26.0.0.67 is vulnerable to sensitive data exposure in the server response via sending HTTP request with enter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48352</link><description>Yealink Meeting Server before V26.0.0.67 is vulnerable to sensitive data exposure in the server response via sending HTTP request with enterprise ID.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51247 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51247</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doPPPo function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51248 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51248</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the modifyrow function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41744 | IBM CICS TX Standard cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41744</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard 11.1 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48217 | An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in the dashboard of SiSMART v7.4.0 allows attackers to execute a horizontal-privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48217</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in the dashboard of SiSMART v7.4.0 allows attackers to execute a horizontal-privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41745 | IBM CICS TX Standard cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41745</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41738 | IBM TXSeries for Multiplatforms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41738</link><description>IBM TXSeries for Multiplatforms 10.1 could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information from the query string of an HTTP GET method to process a request which could be obtained using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41741 | IBM TXSeries for Multiplatforms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41741</link><description>IBM TXSeries for Multiplatforms 10.1 could allow an attacker to determine valid usernames due to an observable timing discrepancy which could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48410 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Camtrace v.9.16.2.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48410</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Camtrace v.9.16.2.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49770 | oak&amp;#x27;s path traversal allows transfer of hidden files within the served root directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49770</link><description>`oak` is a middleware framework for Deno's native HTTP server, Deno Deploy, Node.js 16.5 and later, Cloudflare Workers and Bun. By default `oak` does not allow transferring of hidden files with `Context.send` API. However, prior to version 17.1.3, this can be bypassed by encoding `/` as its URL encoded form `%2F`. For an attacker this has potential to read sensitive user data or to gain access to server secrets. Version 17.1.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51483 | changedetection.io Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51483</link><description>changedetection.io is free, open source web page change detection software. Prior to version 0.47.5, when a WebDriver is used to fetch files, `source:file:///etc/passwd` can be used to retrieve local system files, where the more traditional `file:///etc/passwd` gets blocked. Version 0.47.5 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51492 | Zusam vulnerable to stored XSS, allowing token theft via crafted SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51492</link><description>Zusam is a free and open-source way to self-host private forums. Prior to version 0.5.6, specially crafted SVG files uploaded to the service as images allow for unrestricted script execution on (raw) image load. With certain payloads, theft of the target user’s long-lived session token is possible. Note that Zusam, at the time of writing, uses a user’s static API key as a long-lived session token, and these terms can be used interchangeably on the platform. This session token/API key remains valid indefinitely, so long as the user doesn’t expressly request a new one via their Settings page. Version 0.5.6 fixes the cross-site scripting vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51244 | In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51244</link><description>In Draytek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the doIPSec function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51245 | In DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51245</link><description>In DrayTek Vigor3900 1.5.1.3, attackers can inject malicious commands into mainfunction.cgi and execute arbitrary commands by calling the rename_table function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51431 | LB-LINK BL-WR 1300H v.1.0.4 contains hardcoded credentials stored in /etc/shadow which are easily guessable.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51431</link><description>LB-LINK BL-WR 1300H v.1.0.4 contains hardcoded credentials stored in /etc/shadow which are easily guessable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10661 | Tenda AC15 SetDlnaCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10661</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC15 15.03.05.19 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function SetDlnaCfg of the file /goform/SetDlnaCfg. The manipulation of the argument scanList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10662 | Tenda AC15 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10662</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC15 15.03.05.19 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22733 | TP Link MR200 V4 Firmware version 210201 was discovered to contain a null-pointer-dereference in the web administration panel on /cgi/login ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22733</link><description>TP Link MR200 V4 Firmware version 210201 was discovered to contain a null-pointer-dereference in the web administration panel on /cgi/login via the sign, Action or LoginStatus query parameters which could lead to a denial of service by a local or remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51432 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in FiberHome HG6544C RP2743 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the SSID field in the WIFI C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51432</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in FiberHome HG6544C RP2743 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the SSID field in the WIFI Clients List not being sanitized</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28265 | IBOS v4.5.5 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability via \system\modules\dashboard\controllers\LoginController.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28265</link><description>IBOS v4.5.5 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability via \system\modules\dashboard\controllers\LoginController.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51398 | Altai Technologies Ltd Altai X500 Indoor 22 802.11ac Wave 2 AP web Management Weak password leakage in the background may lead to unauthoriz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51398</link><description>Altai Technologies Ltd Altai X500 Indoor 22 802.11ac Wave 2 AP web Management Weak password leakage in the background may lead to unauthorized access, data theft, and network attacks, seriously threatening network security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51399 | Altai Technologies Ltd Altai IX500 Indoor 22 802.11ac Wave 2 AP After login, there are file reads in the background, and attackers can obtai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51399</link><description>Altai Technologies Ltd Altai IX500 Indoor 22 802.11ac Wave 2 AP After login, there are file reads in the background, and attackers can obtain sensitive information such as user credentials, system configuration, and database connection strings, which can lead to data breaches and identity theft.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10659 | ESAFENET CDG CDGAuthoriseTempletService.java delSystemEncryptPolicy sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10659</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected by this issue is the function delSystemEncryptPolicy of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/document/CDGAuthoriseTempletService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10660 | ESAFENET CDG HookService.java deleteHook sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10660</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This affects the function deleteHook of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/HookService.java. The manipulation of the argument hookId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40490 | An issue in Sourcebans++ before v.1.8.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted XAJAX call to the Forgot Pass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40490</link><description>An issue in Sourcebans++ before v.1.8.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted XAJAX call to the Forgot Password function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51377 | An issue in Ladybird Web Solution Faveo Helpdesk &amp; Servicedesk (On-Premise and Cloud) 9.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51377</link><description>An issue in Ladybird Web Solution Faveo Helpdesk &amp; Servicedesk (On-Premise and Cloud) 9.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Subject and Identifier fields</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10657 | Tongda OA prcs_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10657</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pda/approve_center/prcs_info.php. The manipulation of the argument RUN_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10658 | Tongda OA check_seal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10658</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pda/approve_center/check_seal.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27525 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27525</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the filename parameter of the home.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27524 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27524</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the filename parameter of the new_ticket.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10656 | Tongda OA 2017 apply.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10656</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pda/meeting/apply.php. The manipulation of the argument mr_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48289 | An issue in the Bluetooth Low Energy implementation of Cypress Bluetooth SDK v3.66 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48289</link><description>An issue in the Bluetooth Low Energy implementation of Cypress Bluetooth SDK v3.66 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying a crafted LL_PAUSE_ENC_REQ packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37095 | WordPress Envira Photo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.7.3 - Missing Authorization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37095</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Envira Gallery Team Envira Photo Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Envira Photo Gallery: from n/a through 1.8.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37096 | WordPress Popup box plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37096</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Popup Box Team Popup allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Popup box: from n/a through 4.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37106 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt; 3.26.7 - Unautenticated Plugin Settings Change Leading to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37106</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WishList Products WishList Member X allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.26.6</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37108 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt; 3.26.7 - Authenticated Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37108</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WishList Products WishList Member X allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.26.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37119 | WordPress Uncanny Automator Pro plugin &amp;lt; 5.3.0.1 - Unauthenticated License Settings Reset vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37119</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Automator Pro: from n/a through 5.3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37123 | WordPress Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37123</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VowelWeb Ibtana allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ibtana: from n/a through 1.2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37201 | WordPress Woocommerce Customers Order History plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37201</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in javmah Woocommerce Customers Order History allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Woocommerce Customers Order History: from n/a through 5.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37203 | WordPress Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37203</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Laybuy Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37204 | WordPress PropertyHive plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37204</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PropertyHive allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37207 | WordPress Demo Awesome plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37207</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Theme4Press Demo Awesome allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Demo Awesome: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37209 | WordPress User Rights Access Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37209</link><description>Access Control vulnerability in Prism IT Systems User Rights Access Manager allows .

This issue affects User Rights Access Manager: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37214 | WordPress AliExpress Dropshipping with AliNext Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37214</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dropshipping Guru Ali2Woo Lite Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels, Stored XSS.This issue affects Ali2Woo Lite: from n/a through 3.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37218 | WordPress Page Builder Sandwich &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37218</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WordPress Page Builder Sandwich Team Page Builder Sandwich – Front-End Page Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Page Builder Sandwich – Front-End Page Builder: from n/a through 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37220 | WordPress Optinly plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37220</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OptinlyHQ Optinly allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Optinly: from n/a through 1.0.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37226 | WordPress Kanban Boards for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.21 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37226</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kanban for WordPress Kanban Boards for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Kanban Boards for WordPress: from n/a through 2.5.21.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37232 | WordPress Hercules Core  plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Settings Change/Access vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37232</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hercules Design Hercules Core allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Hercules Core: from n/a through 6.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37249 | WordPress Advanced Custom Fields Pro plugin &amp;lt; 6.3.2 - Contributor+ Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37249</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEngine Inc. Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO: from n/a through 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37250 | WordPress Advanced Custom Fields Pro plugin &amp;lt; 6.3.2 - Subscriber+ Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37250</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEngine Inc. Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO: from n/a through 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37254 | WordPress WP File Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37254</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in mndpsingh287 File Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects File Manager: from n/a through 7.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37255 | WordPress ElementsKit Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37255</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpmet Elements kit Elementor addons allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Elements kit Elementor addons: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37269 | WordPress Masterstudy Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37269</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes Masterstudy Elementor Widgets allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Masterstudy Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37276 | WordPress Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37276</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in fifu.App Featured Image from URL allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Image from URL: from n/a through 4.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37277 | WordPress Paid Memberships Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37277</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro: from n/a through 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37411 | WordPress Progress Planner plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37411</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team Emilia Projects Progress Planner allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Progress Planner: from n/a through 0.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37415 | WordPress E2Pdf plugin &amp;lt;= 1.20.27 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37415</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in E2Pdf.Com allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects e2pdf: from n/a through 1.20.27.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37423 | WordPress Newspack Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Directory Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37423</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Blocks allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Newspack Blocks: from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37425 | WordPress Newspack Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37425</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Blocks newspack-blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newspack Blocks: from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37427 | WordPress Timetics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37427</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arraytics Timetics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Timetics: from n/a through 1.0.21.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37439 | WordPress Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.4.1 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Post/Page Duplication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37439</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash: from n/a through 4.1.4.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37440 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37440</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 4.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37443 | WordPress WP Job Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37443</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic WP Job Manager - Resume Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Job Manager - Resume Manager: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37444 | WordPress Defender plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37444</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPMU DEV Defender Security allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Defender Security: from n/a through 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37453 | WordPress ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37453</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ProfileGrid User Profiles ProfileGrid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ProfileGrid: from n/a through 5.8.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37456 | WordPress Simple Newsletter Plugin – Noptin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37456</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Noptin Newsletter Noptin allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Noptin: from n/a through 3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37463 | WordPress CRM Perks Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37463</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CRM Perks CRM Perks Forms allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects CRM Perks Forms: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37468 | WordPress Newsmatic theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37468</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in blazethemes Newsmatic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newsmatic: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37470 | WordPress Woffice Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.8 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37470</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice Core allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Woffice Core: from n/a through 5.4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37475 | WordPress Newspack Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 2.13.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37475</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Newsletters allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Newspack Newsletters: from n/a through 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37477 | WordPress Newspack Content Converter plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37477</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Content Converter allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newspack Content Converter: from n/a through 0.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37481 | WordPress The Post Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37481</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects The Post Grid: from n/a through 7.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37482 | WordPress The Post Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37482</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Post Grid: from n/a through 7.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37483 | WordPress The Post Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37483</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Post Grid: from n/a through 7.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37505 | WordPress Business One Page theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Broken Access Control on Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37505</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rara Themes Business One Page allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Business One Page: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37506 | WordPress Donation Forms by Charitable plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37506</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Charitable Donations &amp; Fundraising Team Charitable allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Charitable: from n/a through 1.8.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37510 | WordPress Donation Forms by Charitable plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37510</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Charitable Donations &amp; Fundraising Team Charitable allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Charitable: from n/a through 1.8.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37516 | WordPress Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37516</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in fifu.App Featured Image from URL allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Image from URL: from n/a through 4.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37517 | WordPress Spectra plugin &amp;lt;= 2.13.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37517</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Spectra allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Spectra: from n/a through 2.13.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37921 | WordPress Chained Quiz plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37921</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Chained Quiz allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Chained Quiz: from n/a through 1.3.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37926 | WordPress WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.2.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37926</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alex Volkov WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Accessibility Helper (WAH): from n/a through 0.6.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37929 | WordPress User Activity Log Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Subscriber+ Multiple Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37929</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in solwin User Activity Log Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects User Activity Log Pro: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38690 | WordPress iPanorama 360 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38690</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Avirtum iPanorama 360 WordPress Virtual Tour Builder allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects iPanorama 360 WordPress Virtual Tour Builder: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38695 | WordPress WP GoToWebinar plugin &amp;lt;= 15.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38695</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP GoToWebinar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP GoToWebinar: from n/a through 15.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38702 | WordPress Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38702</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38707 | WordPress EmbedPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38707</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects EmbedPress: from n/a through 4.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38714 | WordPress WP Fast Total Search  &amp;lt;= 1.68.232 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38714</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Epsiloncool WP Fast Total Search allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Fast Total Search: from n/a through 1.68.232.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38719 | WordPress Auto Featured Image plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38719</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Creative Motion Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail): from n/a through 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38721 | WordPress EazyDocs plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38721</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in spider-themes EazyDocs allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects EazyDocs: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38726 | WordPress Product Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.33 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38726</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PickPlugins Product Designer allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Product Designer: from n/a through 1.0.33.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38727 | WordPress Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38727</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Seraphinite Solutions Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Seraphinite Post .DOCX Source: from n/a through 2.16.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38733 | WordPress Meks Video Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38733</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Meks Meks Video Importer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Meks Video Importer: from n/a through 1.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38737 | WordPress ReDi Restaurant Reservation plugin &amp;lt;= 24.0422 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38737</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Reservation Diary ReDi Restaurant Reservation allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects ReDi Restaurant Reservation: from n/a through 24.0422.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38740 | WordPress Packlink PRO shipping module plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38740</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Packlink Shipping S.L. Packlink PRO shipping module allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Packlink PRO shipping module: from n/a through 3.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38743 | WordPress Plum: Spin Wheel &amp;amp; Email Pop-up plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38743</link><description>Access Control vulnerability in Upqode Plum: Spin Wheel &amp; Email Pop-up allows .

This issue affects Plum: Spin Wheel &amp; Email Pop-up: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38744 | WordPress Plum: Spin Wheel &amp;amp; Email Pop-up plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Broken Access Control to Unauth Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38744</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Upqode Plum: Spin Wheel &amp; Email Pop-up allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs, Stored XSS.This issue affects Plum: Spin Wheel &amp; Email Pop-up: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38745 | WordPress Wholesale Suite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38745</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rymera Web Co Wholesale Suite allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Wholesale Suite: from n/a through 2.1.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38748 | WordPress EleForms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38748</link><description>Access Control vulnerability in TheInnovs EleForms allows .

This issue affects EleForms: from n/a through 2.9.9.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38769 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38769</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Arconix Shortcodes allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38771 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38771</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Atarim allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through 4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38774 | WordPress Security Optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38774</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SiteGround SiteGround Security allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SiteGround Security: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38777 | WordPress Titan Anti-spam &amp;amp; Security plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38777</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CreativeMotion Titan Anti-spam &amp; Security allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Titan Anti-spam &amp; Security: from n/a through 7.3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38783 | WordPress Arconix FAQ plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38783</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Arconix FAQ allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Arconix FAQ: from n/a through 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38792 | WordPress ConveyThis Translate plugin &amp;lt;= 234 - Non-arbitrary Options Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38792</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ConveyThis Translate Team Language Translate Widget for WordPress – ConveyThis allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Language Translate Widget for WordPress – ConveyThis: from n/a through 234.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38794 | WordPress Custom Query Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38794</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MediaRon LLC Custom Query Blocks allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Custom Query Blocks: from n/a through 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39625 | WordPress Icegram Engage plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.24 - Unauthenticated Message Duplication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39625</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in icegram Icegram allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Icegram: from n/a through 3.1.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39635 | WordPress Youzify  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39635</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in KaineLabs Youzify allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Youzify: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39639 | WordPress File Upload plugin &amp;lt;= 4.24.7 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39639</link><description>Broken Access Control vulnerability in Nickolas Bossinas WordPress File Upload allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WordPress File Upload: from n/a through 4.24.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39640 | WordPress Social Feed Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39640</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuadLayers WP Social Feed Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Social Feed Gallery: from n/a through 4.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39650 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Vouchers plugin &amp;lt; 4.9.5 - Unauthenticated Multiple Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39650</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPWeb Elite WooCommerce PDF Vouchers allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Vouchers: from n/a through 4.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39654 | WordPress Sign-up Sheets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39654</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fetch Designs Sign-up Sheets allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sign-up Sheets: from n/a through 2.2.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39664 | WordPress Filter &amp;amp; Grids plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.32 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39664</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YMC Filter &amp; Grids allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Filter &amp; Grids: from n/a through 2.8.33.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43118 | WordPress Hummingbird plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43118</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPMU DEV Hummingbird allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Hummingbird: from n/a through 3.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43119 | WordPress Aruba HiSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43119</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Aruba.It Aruba HiSpeed Cache allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Aruba HiSpeed Cache: from n/a through 2.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43120 | WordPress TypeSquare Webfonts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43120</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in XSERVER Inc. TypeSquare Webfonts allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects TypeSquare Webfonts: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43122 | WordPress Robin image optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43122</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Creative Motion Robin image optimizer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Robin image optimizer: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43134 | WordPress Waitlist Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43134</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in xootix Waitlist Woocommerce ( Back in stock notifier ) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Waitlist Woocommerce ( Back in stock notifier ): from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43136 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43136</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Sunshine Sunshine Photo Cart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: from n/a through 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43142 | WordPress Tutor LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43142</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeum Tutor LMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Tutor LMS: from n/a through 2.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43143 | WordPress Registrations for the Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43143</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Roundup WP Registrations for the Events Calendar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Registrations for the Events Calendar: from n/a through 2.12.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43146 | WordPress Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.96.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43146</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ahmed Kaludi, Mohammed Kaludi AMP for WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AMP for WP: from n/a through 1.0.96.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43154 | WordPress Advanced Cron Manager – debug &amp;amp; control plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43154</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BracketSpace Advanced Cron Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced Cron Manager – debug &amp; control: from n/a through 2.5.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43157 | WordPress FormCraft plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43157</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in nCrafts FormCraft allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects FormCraft: from n/a through 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43158 | WordPress Masteriyo LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43158</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Masteriyo Masteriyo - LMS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Masteriyo - LMS: from n/a through 1.11.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43159 | WordPress Masteriyo LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43159</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Masteriyo Masteriyo - LMS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Masteriyo - LMS: from n/a through 1.11.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43162 | WordPress Easy Digital Downloads plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43162</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Easy Digital Downloads allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Digital Downloads: from n/a through 3.2.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43208 | WordPress Send Emails with Mandrill plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43208</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Miller Media ( Matt Miller ) Send Emails with Mandrill allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Send Emails with Mandrill: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43209 | WordPress Bitly&amp;#x27;s WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43209</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bitly allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Bitly: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43211 | WordPress MailChimp Subscribe Form plugin &amp;lt;=4.0.9.8 - Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43211</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PluginOps MailChimp Subscribe Forms allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MailChimp Subscribe Forms: from n/a through 4.0.9.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43212 | WordPress WpTravelly plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43212</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MagePeople Team WpTravelly allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WpTravelly: from n/a through 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43215 | WordPress Social Slider Feed plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43215</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in creativemotion Social Slider Feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Social Slider Feed: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43219 | WordPress Persian WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43219</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ووکامرس فارسی Persian WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Persian WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43223 | WordPress EventPrime plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43223</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EventPrime Events EventPrime allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects EventPrime: from n/a through 4.0.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43229 | WordPress WP Search Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43229</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cornel Raiu WP Search Analytics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Search Analytics: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43235 | WordPress Meta Box plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43235</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MetaBox.Io Meta Box – WordPress Custom Fields Framework allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Meta Box – WordPress Custom Fields Framework: from n/a through 5.9.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43253 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43253</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Smart Online Order for Clover: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43254 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43254</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Smart Online Order for Clover: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43260 | WordPress Clearfy Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43260</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Creative Motion Clearfy Cache allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Clearfy Cache: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43268 | WordPress Backup and Restore WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.50 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43268</link><description>Access Control vulnerability in WPBackItUp Backup and Restore WordPress allows .

This issue affects Backup and Restore WordPress: from n/a through 1.50.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43270 | WordPress Backup and Restore WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.50 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43270</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPBackItUp Backup and Restore WordPress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Backup and Restore WordPress: from n/a through 1.50.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43273 | WordPress Icegram Collect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43273</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in icegram Icegram Collect plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Icegram Collect plugin: from n/a through 1.3.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43274 | WordPress JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43274</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JS Help Desk JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 2.8.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43277 | WordPress UsersWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43277</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AyeCode Ltd UsersWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects UsersWP: from n/a through 1.2.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43285 | WordPress Presto Player plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43285</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Presto Made, Inc Presto Player allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Presto Player: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43290 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43290</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Atarim allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43293 | WordPress Recipe Card Blocks for Gutenberg &amp;amp; Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43293</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPZOOM Recipe Card Blocks for Gutenberg &amp; Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Recipe Card Blocks for Gutenberg &amp; Elementor: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43296 | WordPress HTML5 Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.30 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43296</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins LLC Flash &amp; HTML5 Video allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Flash &amp; HTML5 Video: from n/a through 2.5.30.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43297 | WordPress Clone plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43297</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Migrate Clone allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Clone: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43298 | WordPress Clone plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43298</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Migrate Clone allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Clone: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43302 | WordPress Fonts plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43302</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fonts Plugin Fonts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Fonts: from n/a through 3.7.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43310 | WordPress Print Labels with Barcodes. Create price tags, product labels, order labels for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43310</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UkrSolution Print Barcode Labels for your WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Print Barcode Labels for your WooCommerce products/orders: from n/a through 3.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43312 | WordPress WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43312</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPClever WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43314 | WordPress Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43314</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gabe Livan Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster: from n/a through 1.3.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43323 | WordPress ReviewX plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.28 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43323</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ReviewX allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects ReviewX: from n/a through 1.6.28.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43332 | WordPress Photo Engine plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43332</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jordy Meow Photo Engine allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Photo Engine: from n/a through 6.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43341 | WordPress Hello Agency theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43341</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CozyThemes Hello Agency allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Hello Agency: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43343 | WordPress Order Tracking – WordPress Status Tracking Plugin plugin &amp;lt; 3.3.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43343</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Etoile Web Design Order Tracking allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Order Tracking: from n/a through 3.3.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43355 | WordPress JoomSport plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43355</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BearDev JoomSport allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JoomSport: from n/a through 5.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43919 | WordPress Yet Another Related Posts Plugin (YARPP) plugin &amp;lt;= 5.30.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43919</link><description>Access Control vulnerability in YARPP YARPP allows .

This issue affects YARPP: from n/a through 5.30.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43923 | WordPress Timetics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.23 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43923</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arraytics Timetics allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Timetics: from n/a through 1.0.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43925 | WordPress Envira Gallery Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43925</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Envira Gallery Team Envira Photo Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Envira Photo Gallery: from n/a through 1.8.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43928 | WordPress JobSearch WP Job Board WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43928</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in eyecix JobSearch allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JobSearch: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43929 | WordPress JobSearch WP Job Board WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43929</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in eyecix JobSearch allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects JobSearch: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43932 | WordPress The Plus Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43932</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in POSIMYTH The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite: from n/a through 5.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43937 | WordPress WP Crowdfunding plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.10 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43937</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeum WP Crowdfunding allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Crowdfunding: from n/a through 2.1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43956 | WordPress MemberPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.34 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43956</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Caseproof, LLC Memberpress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Memberpress: from n/a through 1.11.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43962 | WordPress LWS Affiliation plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43962</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LWS LWS Affiliation allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects LWS Affiliation: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43968 | WordPress Newspack plugin &amp;lt; 3.8.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43968</link><description>Broken Access Control vulnerability in Automattic Newspack allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newspack: from n/a through 3.8.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43973 | WordPress Payment forms, Buy now buttons and Invoicing System plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43973</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AyeCode Ltd GetPaid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects GetPaid: from n/a through 2.8.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43974 | WordPress ReviveNews theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43974</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CozyThemes ReviveNews allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects ReviveNews: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43979 | WordPress Blockbooster theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43979</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CozyThemes Blockbooster allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Blockbooster: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43980 | WordPress FotaWP theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43980</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CozyThemes Fota WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Fota WP: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43981 | WordPress GeoDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.70 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43981</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AyeCode – WP Business Directory Plugins GeoDirectory allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects GeoDirectory: from n/a through 2.3.70.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43982 | WordPress Login As Users plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Broken Access Control to Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43982</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Geek Code Lab Login As Users allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Login As Users: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43998 | WordPress Blogpoet theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43998</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebsiteinWP Blogpoet allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Blogpoet: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44006 | WordPress WooCommerce Multilingual &amp;amp; Multicurrency plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44006</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OnTheGoSystems WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency multilingual allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency: from n/a through 5.3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44019 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Campaign Monitor Extension plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.67 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44019</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Renzo Johnson Contact Form 7 Campaign Monitor Extension allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Campaign Monitor Extension: from n/a through 0.4.67.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44020 | WordPress WP Free SSL plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44020</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Prasad Kirpekar WP Free SSL – Free SSL Certificate for WordPress and force HTTPS allows .

This issue affects WP Free SSL – Free SSL Certificate for WordPress and force HTTPS: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44021 | WordPress Truepush plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44021</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Truepush allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Truepush: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44031 | WordPress JoomSport plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44031</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BearDev JoomSport allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JoomSport: from n/a through 5.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44038 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44038</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Sunshine Sunshine Photo Cart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: from n/a through 3.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44052 | WordPress HelloAsso plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44052</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HelloAsso allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HelloAsso: from n/a through 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47302 | WordPress Fluent Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Broken Access Control on Email Verification vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47302</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPManageNinja LLC Fluent Support allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Fluent Support: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47308 | WordPress Templately plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47308</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Templately allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Templately: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47311 | WordPress Wheel of Life plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47311</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kraft Plugins Wheel of Life allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Wheel of Life: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47314 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47314</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Sunshine Sunshine Photo Cart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: from n/a through 3.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47317 | WordPress Ads by WPQuads plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.84 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47317</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Quads Ads by WPQuads – Adsense Ads, Banner Ads, Popup Ads allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ads by WPQuads – Adsense Ads, Banner Ads, Popup Ads: from n/a through 2.0.84.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47318 | WordPress PWA for WP &amp;amp; AMP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.72 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47318</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Magazine3 PWA for WP &amp; AMP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PWA for WP &amp; AMP: from n/a through 1.7.72.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47321 | WordPress WP Datepicker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47321</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood WP Datepicker allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Datepicker: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47358 | WordPress Popup Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.19.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47358</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Popup Maker allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Popup Maker: from n/a through 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47359 | WordPress Depicter plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47359</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Depicter Slider and Popup by Averta Depicter Slider allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47361 | WordPress Elementor Addon Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47361</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPVibes Elementor Addon Elements allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Elementor Addon Elements: from n/a through 1.13.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47362 | WordPress Strong Testimonials plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47362</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPChill Strong Testimonials allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Strong Testimonials: from n/a through 3.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48039 | WordPress CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48039</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CubeWP CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework: from n/a through 1.1.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48044 | WordPress ShortPixel Image Optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48044</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ShortPixel – Convert WebP/AVIF &amp; Optimize Images ShortPixel Image Optimizer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ShortPixel Image Optimizer: from n/a through 5.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48045 | WordPress Happy Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.12.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48045</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leevio Happy Addons for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Happy Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 3.12.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49256 | WordPress Htaccess File Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49256</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in WPChill Htaccess File Editor allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.

This issue affects Htaccess File Editor: from n/a through 1.0.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51407 | Floodlight SDN OpenFlow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to construct false broadcast ports causing inter-host communic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51407</link><description>Floodlight SDN OpenFlow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to construct false broadcast ports causing inter-host communication anomalies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37094 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37094</link><description>Access Control vulnerability in StylemixThemes MasterStudy LMS allows .

This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through 3.2.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 13:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10655 | Tongda OA 2017 new.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10655</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pda/reportshop/new.php. The manipulation of the argument repid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 13:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51406 | Floodlight SDN Open Flow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to build fake LLDP packets that allow specific clusters to be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51406</link><description>Floodlight SDN Open Flow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to build fake LLDP packets that allow specific clusters to be missed by Floodlight, which in turn leads to missed hosts inside and outside the cluster.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 13:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48270 | An issue in the component /logins of oasys v1.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a burst attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48270</link><description>An issue in the component /logins of oasys v1.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a burst attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 13:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7456 | SQL Injection in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7456</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `/api/v1/external-users` route of lunary-ai/lunary version v1.4.2. The `order by` clause of the SQL query uses `sql.unsafe` without prior sanitization, allowing for SQL injection. The `orderByClause` variable is constructed without server-side validation or sanitization, enabling an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands. Successful exploitation can lead to complete data loss, modification, or corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10654 | TOTOLINK LR350 formLoginAuth.htm authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10654</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 up to 9.3.5u.6369 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /formLoginAuth.htm. The manipulation of the argument authCode with the input 1 leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10367 | Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp;amp; FSE &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10367</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 11:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10652 | CHANGING Information Technology IDExpert - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10652</link><description>IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a parameter for a specific functionality, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject JavsScript code and perform Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10653 | CHANGING Information Technology IDExpert - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10653</link><description>IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a specific parameter in the administrator interface, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to inject and execute OS commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10651 | CHANGING Information Technology IDExpert - Arbitrary File Read through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10651</link><description>IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a specific parameter in the administrator interface, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10232 | AtomChat &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via atomchat Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10232</link><description>The Group Chat &amp; Video Chat by AtomChat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's atomchat shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7424 | Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7424</link><description>The Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of and access to data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to invoke those functions intended for admin use resulting in subscribers being able to upload csv files and view the contents of MPG projects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 07:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9655 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Icon Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9655</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 07:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0106 | NVIDIA ConnectX Host Firmware for the BlueField Data Processing Unit (DPU) contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0106</link><description>NVIDIA ConnectX Host Firmware for the BlueField Data Processing Unit (DPU) contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper handling of insufficient privileges issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, data tampering, and limited information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0105 | NVIDIA ConnectX Firmware contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper handling of insufficient privileges issue. A succe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0105</link><description>NVIDIA ConnectX Firmware contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper handling of insufficient privileges issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, data tampering, and limited information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:48:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21510 | Versions of the package sinatra from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision via the X-Forwarded-Host (X...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21510</link><description>Versions of the package sinatra from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision via the X-Forwarded-Host (XFH) header. When making a request to a method with redirect applied, it is possible to trigger an Open Redirect Attack by inserting an arbitrary address into this header. If used for caching purposes, such as with servers like Nginx, or as a reverse proxy, without handling the X-Forwarded-Host header, attackers can potentially exploit Cache Poisoning or Routing-based SSRF.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10620 | knightliao Disconf Configuration Center list improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10620</link><description>A vulnerability was found in knightliao Disconf 2.6.36. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/config/list of the component Configuration Center. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47939 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in multiple Ricoh laser printers and MFPs which implement Web Image Monitor. If this vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47939</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in multiple Ricoh laser printers and MFPs which implement Web Image Monitor. If this vulnerability is exploited, receiving a specially crafted request created and sent by an attacker may lead to arbitrary code execution and/or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. As for the details of affected product names and versions, refer to the information provided by the vendor under [References].</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49501 | Sysmac Studio provided by OMRON Corporation contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49501</link><description>Sysmac Studio provided by OMRON Corporation contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may access the program which is protected by Data Protection function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10619 | Tongda OA 2017 next_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10619</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pda/reportshop/next_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument repid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10617 | Tongda OA check_seal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10617</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pda/workflow/check_seal.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10618 | Tongda OA 2017 record_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10618</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pda/reportshop/record_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument repid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10616 | Tongda OA webSignSubmit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10616</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /pda/workflow/webSignSubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument saleId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10612 | ESAFENET CDG HookInvalidCourseService.java removeHookInvalidCourse sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10612</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function removeHookInvalidCourse of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/HookInvalidCourseService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10613 | ESAFENET CDG SystemEncryptPolicyService.java delSystemEncryptPolicy sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10613</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delSystemEncryptPolicy of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/SystemEncryptPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10615 | Tongda OA 2017 delete_data_attach.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10615</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /general/approve_center/query/list/input_form/delete_data_attach.php. The manipulation of the argument RUN_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10610 | ESAFENET CDG ProtocolService.java delProtocol sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10610</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function delProtocol of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/ProtocolService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10611 | ESAFENET CDG PrintScreenListService.java delProtocol sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10611</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function delProtocol of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/PrintScreenListService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10609 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System Project typeadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10609</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System Project 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file typeadd.php. The manipulation of the argument sex leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10608 | code-projects Courier Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10608</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument txtusername leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10607 | code-projects Courier Management System track-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10607</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /track-result.php. The manipulation of the argument Consignment leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>