<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:41:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-14205 | code-projects Chamber of Commerce Membership Management System Your Info membership_profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14205</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chamber of Commerce Membership Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /membership_profile.php of the component Your Info Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument Full Name/Address/City/State results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14204 | TykoDev cherry-studio-TykoFork OAuth Server Discovery oauth-authorization-server redirectToAuthorization os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14204</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TykoDev cherry-studio-TykoFork 0.1. This issue affects the function redirectToAuthorization of the file /.well-known/oauth-authorization-server of the component OAuth Server Discovery. Such manipulation of the argument authorizationUrl leads to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14203 | code-projects Question Paper Generator selectquestionuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14203</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Question Paper Generator up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /selectquestionuser.php. This manipulation of the argument subid causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14201 | alokjaiswal Hotel-Management-services-using-MYSQL-and-php dishsub.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14201</link><description>A vulnerability was found in alokjaiswal Hotel-Management-services-using-MYSQL-and-php up to 5f8b60a7aa6c06a5632de569d4e3f6a8cd82f76f. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dishsub.php. The manipulation of the argument item.name results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14200 | alokjaiswal Hotel-Management-services-using-MYSQL-and-php Request Pending usersub.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14200</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in alokjaiswal Hotel-Management-services-using-MYSQL-and-php up to 5f8b60a7aa6c06a5632de569d4e3f6a8cd82f76f. Affected is an unknown function of the file /usersub.php of the component Request Pending Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14199 | Verysync 微力同步 Web Administration text.txt unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14199</link><description>A flaw has been found in Verysync 微力同步 up to 2.21.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /rest/f/api/resources/f96956469e7be39d/tmp/text.txt?override=false of the component Web Administration Module. Executing manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14198 | Verysync 微力同步 Web Administration download information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14198</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Verysync 微力同步 2.21.3. This affects an unknown function of the file /safebrowsing/clientreport/download?key=dummytoken of the component Web Administration Module. Performing manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14197 | Verysync 微力同步 Web Administration f96956469e7be39d information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14197</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Verysync 微力同步 up to 2.21.3. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /rest/f/api/resources/f96956469e7be39d of the component Web Administration Module. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14196 | H3C Magic B1 aspForm sub_44de0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14196</link><description>A weakness has been identified in H3C Magic B1 up to 100R004. The affected element is the function sub_44de0 of the file /goform/aspForm. This manipulation of the argument param causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14195 | code-projects Employee Profile Management System add_file_query.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14195</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Employee Profile Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /profiling/add_file_query.php. The manipulation of the argument per_file results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14194 | code-projects Employee Profile Management System view_personnel.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14194</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Employee Profile Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view_personnel.php. The manipulation of the argument per_address/dr_school/other_school leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 14:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14193 | code-projects Employee Profile Management System view_personnel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14193</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Employee Profile Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view_personnel.php. Executing manipulation of the argument per_id can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 14:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14192 | RashminDungrani online-banking auth_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14192</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RashminDungrani online-banking up to 2337ad552ea9d385b4e07b90e6f32d011b7c68a2. This affects an unknown part of the file /site/dist/auth_login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14191 | UTT 进取 512W formP2PLimitConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14191</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT 进取 512W up to 1.7.7-171114. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formP2PLimitConfig. Such manipulation of the argument except leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14190 | Chanjet TPlus sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14190</link><description>A flaw has been found in Chanjet TPlus up to 20251121. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tplus/ajaxpro/Ufida.T.SM.UIP.MultiCompanySettingController,Ufida.T.SM.UIP.ashx?method=Load. This manipulation of the argument currentAccId causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14189 | Chanjet CRM jxf_dump_table_demo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14189</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Chanjet CRM up to 20251121. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tools/jxf_dump_table_demo.php. The manipulation of the argument gblOrgID results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14188 | UGREEN DH2100+ nas_svr create handler_file_backup_create command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14188</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UGREEN DH2100+ up to 5.3.0.251125. This impacts the function handler_file_backup_create of the file /v1/file/backup/create of the component nas_svr. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14187 | UGREEN DH2100+ nas_svr create handler_file_backup_create buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14187</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UGREEN DH2100+ up to 5.3.0.251125. This affects the function handler_file_backup_create of the file /v1/file/backup/create of the component nas_svr. Executing manipulation of the argument path can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 08:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14186 | Grandstream GXP1625 Network Status api.values.post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14186</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Grandstream GXP1625 1.0.7.4. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/api.values.post of the component Network Status Page. Performing manipulation of the argument vpn_ip results in basic cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 07:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14185 | Yonyou U8 Cloud AppServletService.class sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14185</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Yonyou U8 Cloud 5.0/5.0sp/5.1/5.1sp. The affected element is an unknown function of the file nc/pubitf/erm/mobile/appservice/AppServletService.class. Such manipulation of the argument usercode leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14184 | SGAI Space1 NAS N1211DS gsaiagent JSONAPI NGNIX_UPLOAD command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14184</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SGAI Space1 NAS N1211DS up to 1.0.915. Impacted is the function RENAME_FILE/OPERATE_FILE/NGNIX_UPLOAD of the file /cgi-bin/JSONAPI of the component gsaiagent. This manipulation causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14183 | SGAI Space1 NAS N1211DS gsaiagent JSONAPI GET_USER_INFO credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14183</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SGAI Space1 NAS N1211DS up to 1.0.915. This issue affects the function GET_FACTORY_INFO/GET_USER_INFO of the file /cgi-bin/JSONAPI of the component gsaiagent. The manipulation results in unprotected storage of credentials. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 03:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14182 | Sobey Media Convergence System upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14182</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sobey Media Convergence System 2.0/2.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /sobey-mchEditor/watermark/upload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 02:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40267 | io_uring/rw: ensure allocated iovec gets cleared for early failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40267</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/rw: ensure allocated iovec gets cleared for early failure

A previous commit reused the recyling infrastructure for early cleanup,
but this is not enough for the case where our internal caches have
overflowed. If this happens, then the allocated iovec can get leaked if
the request is also aborted early.

Reinstate the previous forced free of the iovec for that situation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40268 | cifs: client: fix memory leak in smb3_fs_context_parse_param</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40268</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cifs: client: fix memory leak in smb3_fs_context_parse_param

The user calls fsconfig twice, but when the program exits, free() only
frees ctx-&gt;source for the second fsconfig, not the first.
Regarding fc-&gt;source, there is no code in the fs context related to its
memory reclamation.

To fix this memory leak, release the source memory corresponding to ctx
or fc before each parsing.

syzbot reported:
BUG: memory leak
unreferenced object 0xffff888128afa360 (size 96):
  backtrace (crc 79c9c7ba):
    kstrdup+0x3c/0x80 mm/util.c:84
    smb3_fs_context_parse_param+0x229b/0x36c0 fs/smb/client/fs_context.c:1444

BUG: memory leak
unreferenced object 0xffff888112c7d900 (size 96):
  backtrace (crc 79c9c7ba):
    smb3_fs_context_fullpath+0x70/0x1b0 fs/smb/client/fs_context.c:629
    smb3_fs_context_parse_param+0x2266/0x36c0 fs/smb/client/fs_context.c:1438</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40269 | ALSA: usb-audio: Fix potential overflow of PCM transfer buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40269</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: usb-audio: Fix potential overflow of PCM transfer buffer

The PCM stream data in USB-audio driver is transferred over USB URB
packet buffers, and each packet size is determined dynamically.  The
packet sizes are limited by some factors such as wMaxPacketSize USB
descriptor.  OTOH, in the current code, the actually used packet sizes
are determined only by the rate and the PPS, which may be bigger than
the size limit above.  This results in a buffer overflow, as reported
by syzbot.

Basically when the limit is smaller than the calculated packet size,
it implies that something is wrong, most likely a weird USB
descriptor.  So the best option would be just to return an error at
the parameter setup time before doing any further operations.

This patch introduces such a sanity check, and returns -EINVAL when
the packet size is greater than maxpacksize.  The comparison with
ep-&gt;packsize[1] alone should suffice since it's always equal or
greater than ep-&gt;packsize[0].</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40270 | mm, swap: fix potential UAF issue for VMA readahead</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40270</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm, swap: fix potential UAF issue for VMA readahead

Since commit 78524b05f1a3 ("mm, swap: avoid redundant swap device
pinning"), the common helper for allocating and preparing a folio in the
swap cache layer no longer tries to get a swap device reference
internally, because all callers of __read_swap_cache_async are already
holding a swap entry reference.  The repeated swap device pinning isn't
needed on the same swap device.

Caller of VMA readahead is also holding a reference to the target entry's
swap device, but VMA readahead walks the page table, so it might encounter
swap entries from other devices, and call __read_swap_cache_async on
another device without holding a reference to it.

So it is possible to cause a UAF when swapoff of device A raced with
swapin on device B, and VMA readahead tries to read swap entries from
device A.  It's not easy to trigger, but in theory, it could cause real
issues.

Make VMA readahead try to get the device reference first if the swap
device is a different one from the target entry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40271 | fs/proc: fix uaf in proc_readdir_de()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40271</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/proc: fix uaf in proc_readdir_de()

Pde is erased from subdir rbtree through rb_erase(), but not set the node
to EMPTY, which may result in uaf access.  We should use RB_CLEAR_NODE()
set the erased node to EMPTY, then pde_subdir_next() will return NULL to
avoid uaf access.

We found an uaf issue while using stress-ng testing, need to run testcase
getdent and tun in the same time.  The steps of the issue is as follows:

1) use getdent to traverse dir /proc/pid/net/dev_snmp6/, and current
   pde is tun3;

2) in the [time windows] unregister netdevice tun3 and tun2, and erase
   them from rbtree.  erase tun3 first, and then erase tun2.  the
   pde(tun2) will be released to slab;

3) continue to getdent process, then pde_subdir_next() will return
   pde(tun2) which is released, it will case uaf access.

CPU 0                                      |    CPU 1
-------------------------------------------------------------------------
traverse dir /proc/pid/net/dev_snmp6/      |   unregister_netdevice(tun-&gt;dev)   //tun3 tun2
sys_getdents64()                           |
  iterate_dir()                            |
    proc_readdir()                         |
      proc_readdir_de()                    |     snmp6_unregister_dev()
        pde_get(de);                       |       proc_remove()
        read_unlock(&amp;amp;proc_subdir_lock);    |         remove_proc_subtree()
                                           |           write_lock(&amp;amp;proc_subdir_lock);
        [time window]                      |           rb_erase(&amp;amp;root-&gt;subdir_node, &amp;amp;parent-&gt;subdir);
                                           |           write_unlock(&amp;amp;proc_subdir_lock);
        read_lock(&amp;amp;proc_subdir_lock);      |
        next = pde_subdir_next(de);        |
        pde_put(de);                       |
        de = next;    //UAF                |

rbtree of dev_snmp6
                        |
                    pde(tun3)
                     /    \
                  NULL  pde(tun2)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40272 | mm/secretmem: fix use-after-free race in fault handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40272</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/secretmem: fix use-after-free race in fault handler

When a page fault occurs in a secret memory file created with
`memfd_secret(2)`, the kernel will allocate a new folio for it, mark the
underlying page as not-present in the direct map, and add it to the file
mapping.

If two tasks cause a fault in the same page concurrently, both could end
up allocating a folio and removing the page from the direct map, but only
one would succeed in adding the folio to the file mapping.  The task that
failed undoes the effects of its attempt by (a) freeing the folio again
and (b) putting the page back into the direct map.  However, by doing
these two operations in this order, the page becomes available to the
allocator again before it is placed back in the direct mapping.

If another task attempts to allocate the page between (a) and (b), and the
kernel tries to access it via the direct map, it would result in a
supervisor not-present page fault.

Fix the ordering to restore the direct map before the folio is freed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40273 | NFSD: free copynotify stateid in nfs4_free_ol_stateid()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40273</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

NFSD: free copynotify stateid in nfs4_free_ol_stateid()

Typically copynotify stateid is freed either when parent's stateid
is being close/freed or in nfsd4_laundromat if the stateid hasn't
been used in a lease period.

However, in case when the server got an OPEN (which created
a parent stateid), followed by a COPY_NOTIFY using that stateid,
followed by a client reboot. New client instance while doing
CREATE_SESSION would force expire previous state of this client.
It leads to the open state being freed thru release_openowner-&gt;
nfs4_free_ol_stateid() and it finds that it still has copynotify
stateid associated with it. We currently print a warning and is
triggerred

WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 8858 at fs/nfsd/nfs4state.c:1550 nfs4_free_ol_stateid+0xb0/0x100 [nfsd]

This patch, instead, frees the associated copynotify stateid here.

If the parent stateid is freed (without freeing the copynotify
stateids associated with it), it leads to the list corruption
when laundromat ends up freeing the copynotify state later.

[ 1626.839430] Internal error: Oops - BUG: 00000000f2000800 [#1]  SMP
[ 1626.842828] Modules linked in: nfnetlink_queue nfnetlink_log bluetooth cfg80211 rpcrdma rdma_cm iw_cm ib_cm ib_core nfsd nfs_acl lockd grace nfs_localio ext4 crc16 mbcache jbd2 overlay uinput snd_seq_dummy snd_hrtimer qrtr rfkill vfat fat uvcvideo snd_hda_codec_generic videobuf2_vmalloc videobuf2_memops snd_hda_intel uvc snd_intel_dspcfg videobuf2_v4l2 videobuf2_common snd_hda_codec snd_hda_core videodev snd_hwdep snd_seq mc snd_seq_device snd_pcm snd_timer snd soundcore sg loop auth_rpcgss vsock_loopback vmw_vsock_virtio_transport_common vmw_vsock_vmci_transport vmw_vmci vsock xfs 8021q garp stp llc mrp nvme ghash_ce e1000e nvme_core sr_mod nvme_keyring nvme_auth cdrom vmwgfx drm_ttm_helper ttm sunrpc dm_mirror dm_region_hash dm_log iscsi_tcp libiscsi_tcp libiscsi scsi_transport_iscsi fuse dm_multipath dm_mod nfnetlink
[ 1626.855594] CPU: 2 UID: 0 PID: 199 Comm: kworker/u24:33 Kdump: loaded Tainted: G    B   W           6.17.0-rc7+ #22 PREEMPT(voluntary)
[ 1626.857075] Tainted: [B]=BAD_PAGE, [W]=WARN
[ 1626.857573] Hardware name: VMware, Inc. VMware20,1/VBSA, BIOS VMW201.00V.24006586.BA64.2406042154 06/04/2024
[ 1626.858724] Workqueue: nfsd4 laundromat_main [nfsd]
[ 1626.859304] pstate: 61400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO +DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[ 1626.860010] pc : __list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x148/0x200
[ 1626.860601] lr : __list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x148/0x200
[ 1626.861182] sp : ffff8000881d7a40
[ 1626.861521] x29: ffff8000881d7a40 x28: 0000000000000018 x27: ffff0000c2a98200
[ 1626.862260] x26: 0000000000000600 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: ffff8000881d7b20
[ 1626.862986] x23: ffff0000c2a981e8 x22: 1fffe00012410e7d x21: ffff0000920873e8
[ 1626.863701] x20: ffff0000920873e8 x19: ffff000086f22998 x18: 0000000000000000
[ 1626.864421] x17: 20747562202c3839 x16: 3932326636383030 x15: 3030666666662065
[ 1626.865092] x14: 6220646c756f6873 x13: 0000000000000001 x12: ffff60004fd9e4a3
[ 1626.865713] x11: 1fffe0004fd9e4a2 x10: ffff60004fd9e4a2 x9 : dfff800000000000
[ 1626.866320] x8 : 00009fffb0261b5e x7 : ffff00027ecf2513 x6 : 0000000000000001
[ 1626.866938] x5 : ffff00027ecf2510 x4 : ffff60004fd9e4a3 x3 : 0000000000000000
[ 1626.867553] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : ffff000096069640 x0 : 000000000000006d
[ 1626.868167] Call trace:
[ 1626.868382]  __list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x148/0x200 (P)
[ 1626.868876]  _free_cpntf_state_locked+0xd0/0x268 [nfsd]
[ 1626.869368]  nfs4_laundromat+0x6f8/0x1058 [nfsd]
[ 1626.869813]  laundromat_main+0x24/0x60 [nfsd]
[ 1626.870231]  process_one_work+0x584/0x1050
[ 1626.870595]  worker_thread+0x4c4/0xc60
[ 1626.870893]  kthread+0x2f8/0x398
[ 1626.871146]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[ 1626.871422] Code: aa1303e1 aa1403e3 910e8000 97bc55d7 (d4210000)
[ 1626.871892] SMP: stopping secondary CPUs</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40274 | KVM: guest_memfd: Remove bindings on memslot deletion when gmem is dying</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40274</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: guest_memfd: Remove bindings on memslot deletion when gmem is dying

When unbinding a memslot from a guest_memfd instance, remove the bindings
even if the guest_memfd file is dying, i.e. even if its file refcount has
gone to zero.  If the memslot is freed before the file is fully released,
nullifying the memslot side of the binding in kvm_gmem_release() will
write to freed memory, as detected by syzbot+KASAN:

  ==================================================================
  BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in kvm_gmem_release+0x176/0x440 virt/kvm/guest_memfd.c:353
  Write of size 8 at addr ffff88807befa508 by task syz.0.17/6022

  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 6022 Comm: syz.0.17 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
  Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/02/2025
  Call Trace:
   
   dump_stack_lvl+0x189/0x250 lib/dump_stack.c:120
   print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
   print_report+0xca/0x240 mm/kasan/report.c:482
   kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:595
   kvm_gmem_release+0x176/0x440 virt/kvm/guest_memfd.c:353
   __fput+0x44c/0xa70 fs/file_table.c:468
   task_work_run+0x1d4/0x260 kernel/task_work.c:227
   resume_user_mode_work include/linux/resume_user_mode.h:50 [inline]
   exit_to_user_mode_loop+0xe9/0x130 kernel/entry/common.c:43
   exit_to_user_mode_prepare include/linux/irq-entry-common.h:225 [inline]
   syscall_exit_to_user_mode_work include/linux/entry-common.h:175 [inline]
   syscall_exit_to_user_mode include/linux/entry-common.h:210 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0x2bd/0xfa0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:100
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
  RIP: 0033:0x7fbeeff8efc9
   

  Allocated by task 6023:
   kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:56 [inline]
   kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:77
   poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:397 [inline]
   __kasan_kmalloc+0x93/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:414
   kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:262 [inline]
   __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x3e2/0x700 mm/slub.c:5758
   kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:957 [inline]
   kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1094 [inline]
   kvm_set_memory_region+0x747/0xb90 virt/kvm/kvm_main.c:2104
   kvm_vm_ioctl_set_memory_region+0x6f/0xd0 virt/kvm/kvm_main.c:2154
   kvm_vm_ioctl+0x957/0xc60 virt/kvm/kvm_main.c:5201
   vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
   __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:597 [inline]
   __se_sys_ioctl+0xfc/0x170 fs/ioctl.c:583
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xfa/0xfa0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

  Freed by task 6023:
   kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:56 [inline]
   kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:77
   kasan_save_free_info+0x46/0x50 mm/kasan/generic.c:584
   poison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:252 [inline]
   __kasan_slab_free+0x5c/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:284
   kasan_slab_free include/linux/kasan.h:234 [inline]
   slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:2533 [inline]
   slab_free mm/slub.c:6622 [inline]
   kfree+0x19a/0x6d0 mm/slub.c:6829
   kvm_set_memory_region+0x9c4/0xb90 virt/kvm/kvm_main.c:2130
   kvm_vm_ioctl_set_memory_region+0x6f/0xd0 virt/kvm/kvm_main.c:2154
   kvm_vm_ioctl+0x957/0xc60 virt/kvm/kvm_main.c:5201
   vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
   __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:597 [inline]
   __se_sys_ioctl+0xfc/0x170 fs/ioctl.c:583
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xfa/0xfa0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Deliberately don't acquire filemap invalid lock when the file is dying as
the lifecycle of f_mapping is outside the purview of KVM.  Dereferencing
the mapping is *probably* fine, but there's no need to invalidate anything
as memslot deletion is responsible for zapping SPTEs, and the only code
that can access the dying file is kvm_gmem_release(), whose core code is
mutual
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40275 | ALSA: usb-audio: Fix NULL pointer dereference in snd_usb_mixer_controls_badd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40275</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: usb-audio: Fix NULL pointer dereference in snd_usb_mixer_controls_badd

In snd_usb_create_streams(), for UAC version 3 devices, the Interface
Association Descriptor (IAD) is retrieved via usb_ifnum_to_if(). If this
call fails, a fallback routine attempts to obtain the IAD from the next
interface and sets a BADD profile. However, snd_usb_mixer_controls_badd()
assumes that the IAD retrieved from usb_ifnum_to_if() is always valid,
without performing a NULL check. This can lead to a NULL pointer
dereference when usb_ifnum_to_if() fails to find the interface descriptor.

This patch adds a NULL pointer check after calling usb_ifnum_to_if() in
snd_usb_mixer_controls_badd() to prevent the dereference.

This issue was discovered by syzkaller, which triggered the bug by sending
a crafted USB device descriptor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40276 | drm/panthor: Flush shmem writes before mapping buffers CPU-uncached</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40276</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/panthor: Flush shmem writes before mapping buffers CPU-uncached

The shmem layer zeroes out the new pages using cached mappings, and if
we don't CPU-flush we might leave dirty cachelines behind, leading to
potential data leaks and/or asynchronous buffer corruption when dirty
cachelines are evicted.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40277 | drm/vmwgfx: Validate command header size against SVGA_CMD_MAX_DATASIZE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40277</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Validate command header size against SVGA_CMD_MAX_DATASIZE

This data originates from userspace and is used in buffer offset
calculations which could potentially overflow causing an out-of-bounds
access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40278 | net: sched: act_ife: initialize struct tc_ife to fix KMSAN kernel-infoleak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40278</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: sched: act_ife: initialize struct tc_ife to fix KMSAN kernel-infoleak

Fix a KMSAN kernel-infoleak detected  by the syzbot .

[net?] KMSAN: kernel-infoleak in __skb_datagram_iter

In tcf_ife_dump(), the variable 'opt' was partially initialized using a
designatied initializer. While the padding bytes are reamined
uninitialized. nla_put() copies the entire structure into a
netlink message, these uninitialized bytes leaked to userspace.

Initialize the structure with memset before assigning its fields
to ensure all members and padding are cleared prior to beign copied.

This change silences the KMSAN report and prevents potential information
leaks from the kernel memory.

This fix has been tested and validated by syzbot. This patch closes the
bug reported at the following syzkaller link and ensures no infoleak.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40279 | net: sched: act_connmark: initialize struct tc_ife to fix kernel leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40279</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: sched: act_connmark: initialize struct tc_ife to fix kernel leak

In tcf_connmark_dump(), the variable 'opt' was partially initialized using a
designatied initializer. While the padding bytes are reamined
uninitialized. nla_put() copies the entire structure into a
netlink message, these uninitialized bytes leaked to userspace.

Initialize the structure with memset before assigning its fields
to ensure all members and padding are cleared prior to beign copied.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40280 | tipc: Fix use-after-free in tipc_mon_reinit_self().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40280</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tipc: Fix use-after-free in tipc_mon_reinit_self().

syzbot reported use-after-free of tipc_net(net)-&gt;monitors[]
in tipc_mon_reinit_self(). [0]

The array is protected by RTNL, but tipc_mon_reinit_self()
iterates over it without RTNL.

tipc_mon_reinit_self() is called from tipc_net_finalize(),
which is always under RTNL except for tipc_net_finalize_work().

Let's hold RTNL in tipc_net_finalize_work().

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __raw_spin_lock_irqsave include/linux/spinlock_api_smp.h:110 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0xa7/0xf0 kernel/locking/spinlock.c:162
Read of size 1 at addr ffff88805eae1030 by task kworker/0:7/5989

CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 5989 Comm: kworker/0:7 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT_{RT,(full)}
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 08/18/2025
Workqueue: events tipc_net_finalize_work
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x189/0x250 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0xca/0x240 mm/kasan/report.c:482
 kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:595
 __kasan_check_byte+0x2a/0x40 mm/kasan/common.c:568
 kasan_check_byte include/linux/kasan.h:399 [inline]
 lock_acquire+0x8d/0x360 kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5842
 __raw_spin_lock_irqsave include/linux/spinlock_api_smp.h:110 [inline]
 _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0xa7/0xf0 kernel/locking/spinlock.c:162
 rtlock_slowlock kernel/locking/rtmutex.c:1894 [inline]
 rwbase_rtmutex_lock_state kernel/locking/spinlock_rt.c:160 [inline]
 rwbase_write_lock+0xd3/0x7e0 kernel/locking/rwbase_rt.c:244
 rt_write_lock+0x76/0x110 kernel/locking/spinlock_rt.c:243
 write_lock_bh include/linux/rwlock_rt.h:99 [inline]
 tipc_mon_reinit_self+0x79/0x430 net/tipc/monitor.c:718
 tipc_net_finalize+0x115/0x190 net/tipc/net.c:140
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3236 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xade/0x17b0 kernel/workqueue.c:3319
 worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3400
 kthread+0x70e/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:463
 ret_from_fork+0x439/0x7d0 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:148
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:245
 

Allocated by task 6089:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:388 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x93/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:405
 kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:260 [inline]
 __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x1a8/0x320 mm/slub.c:4407
 kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:905 [inline]
 kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1039 [inline]
 tipc_mon_create+0xc3/0x4d0 net/tipc/monitor.c:657
 tipc_enable_bearer net/tipc/bearer.c:357 [inline]
 __tipc_nl_bearer_enable+0xe16/0x13f0 net/tipc/bearer.c:1047
 __tipc_nl_compat_doit net/tipc/netlink_compat.c:371 [inline]
 tipc_nl_compat_doit+0x3bc/0x5f0 net/tipc/netlink_compat.c:393
 tipc_nl_compat_handle net/tipc/netlink_compat.c:-1 [inline]
 tipc_nl_compat_recv+0x83c/0xbe0 net/tipc/netlink_compat.c:1321
 genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x215/0x300 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1115
 genl_family_rcv_msg net/netlink/genetlink.c:1195 [inline]
 genl_rcv_msg+0x60e/0x790 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1210
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x208/0x470 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2552
 genl_rcv+0x28/0x40 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1219
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1320 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x846/0xa10 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1346
 netlink_sendmsg+0x805/0xb30 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1896
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:714 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0x21c/0x270 net/socket.c:729
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x508/0x820 net/socket.c:2614
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x21f/0x2a0 net/socket.c:2668
 __sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2700 [inline]
 __do_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2705 [inline]
 __se_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2703 [inline]
 __x64_sys_sendmsg+0x1a1/0x260 net/socket.c:2703
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xfa/0x3b0 arch/
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40281 | sctp: prevent possible shift-out-of-bounds in sctp_transport_update_rto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40281</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sctp: prevent possible shift-out-of-bounds in sctp_transport_update_rto

syzbot reported a possible shift-out-of-bounds [1]

Blamed commit added rto_alpha_max and rto_beta_max set to 1000.

It is unclear if some sctp users are setting very large rto_alpha
and/or rto_beta.

In order to prevent user regression, perform the test at run time.

Also add READ_ONCE() annotations as sysctl values can change under us.

[1]

UBSAN: shift-out-of-bounds in net/sctp/transport.c:509:41
shift exponent 64 is too large for 32-bit type 'unsigned int'
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 16704 Comm: syz.2.2320 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/02/2025
Call Trace:
 
  __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
  dump_stack_lvl+0x16c/0x1f0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
  ubsan_epilogue lib/ubsan.c:233 [inline]
  __ubsan_handle_shift_out_of_bounds+0x27f/0x420 lib/ubsan.c:494
  sctp_transport_update_rto.cold+0x1c/0x34b net/sctp/transport.c:509
  sctp_check_transmitted+0x11c4/0x1c30 net/sctp/outqueue.c:1502
  sctp_outq_sack+0x4ef/0x1b20 net/sctp/outqueue.c:1338
  sctp_cmd_process_sack net/sctp/sm_sideeffect.c:840 [inline]
  sctp_cmd_interpreter net/sctp/sm_sideeffect.c:1372 [inline]</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40282 | Bluetooth: 6lowpan: reset link-local header on ipv6 recv path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40282</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: 6lowpan: reset link-local header on ipv6 recv path

Bluetooth 6lowpan.c netdev has header_ops, so it must set link-local
header for RX skb, otherwise things crash, eg. with AF_PACKET SOCK_RAW

Add missing skb_reset_mac_header() for uncompressed ipv6 RX path.

For the compressed one, it is done in lowpan_header_decompress().

Log: (BlueZ 6lowpan-tester Client Recv Raw - Success)
------
kernel BUG at net/core/skbuff.c:212!
Call Trace:

...
packet_rcv (net/packet/af_packet.c:2152)
...

__local_bh_enable_ip (kernel/softirq.c:407)
netif_rx (net/core/dev.c:5648)
chan_recv_cb (net/bluetooth/6lowpan.c:294 net/bluetooth/6lowpan.c:359)
------</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40283 | Bluetooth: btusb: reorder cleanup in btusb_disconnect to avoid UAF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40283</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: btusb: reorder cleanup in btusb_disconnect to avoid UAF

There is a KASAN: slab-use-after-free read in btusb_disconnect().
Calling "usb_driver_release_interface(&amp;amp;btusb_driver, data-&gt;intf)" will
free the btusb data associated with the interface. The same data is
then used later in the function, hence the UAF.

Fix by moving the accesses to btusb data to before the data is free'd.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40284 | Bluetooth: MGMT: cancel mesh send timer when hdev removed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40284</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: MGMT: cancel mesh send timer when hdev removed

mesh_send_done timer is not canceled when hdev is removed, which causes
crash if the timer triggers after hdev is gone.

Cancel the timer when MGMT removes the hdev, like other MGMT timers.

Should fix the BUG: sporadically seen by BlueZ test bot
(in "Mesh - Send cancel - 1" test).

Log:
------
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in run_timer_softirq+0x76b/0x7d0
...
Freed by task 36:
 kasan_save_stack+0x24/0x50
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30
 __kasan_save_free_info+0x3a/0x60
 __kasan_slab_free+0x43/0x70
 kfree+0x103/0x500
 device_release+0x9a/0x210
 kobject_put+0x100/0x1e0
 vhci_release+0x18b/0x240
------</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40285 | smb/server: fix possible refcount leak in smb2_sess_setup()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40285</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb/server: fix possible refcount leak in smb2_sess_setup()

Reference count of ksmbd_session will leak when session need reconnect.
Fix this by adding the missing ksmbd_user_session_put().</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40286 | smb/server: fix possible memory leak in smb2_read()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40286</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb/server: fix possible memory leak in smb2_read()

Memory leak occurs when ksmbd_vfs_read() fails.
Fix this by adding the missing kvfree().</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40287 | exfat: fix improper check of dentry.stream.valid_size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40287</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

exfat: fix improper check of dentry.stream.valid_size

We found an infinite loop bug in the exFAT file system that can lead to a
Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition. When a dentry in an exFAT filesystem is
malformed, the following system calls — SYS_openat, SYS_ftruncate, and
SYS_pwrite64 — can cause the kernel to hang.

Root cause analysis shows that the size validation code in exfat_find()
does not check whether dentry.stream.valid_size is negative. As a result,
the system calls mentioned above can succeed and eventually trigger the DoS
issue.

This patch adds a check for negative dentry.stream.valid_size to prevent
this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40288 | drm/amdgpu: Fix NULL pointer dereference in VRAM logic for APU devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40288</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Fix NULL pointer dereference in VRAM logic for APU devices

Previously, APU platforms (and other scenarios with uninitialized VRAM managers)
triggered a NULL pointer dereference in `ttm_resource_manager_usage()`. The root
cause is not that the `struct ttm_resource_manager *man` pointer itself is NULL,
but that `man-&gt;bdev` (the backing device pointer within the manager) remains
uninitialized (NULL) on APUs—since APUs lack dedicated VRAM and do not fully
set up VRAM manager structures. When `ttm_resource_manager_usage()` attempts to
acquire `man-&gt;bdev-&gt;lru_lock`, it dereferences the NULL `man-&gt;bdev`, leading to
a kernel OOPS.

1. **amdgpu_cs.c**: Extend the existing bandwidth control check in
   `amdgpu_cs_get_threshold_for_moves()` to include a check for
   `ttm_resource_manager_used()`. If the manager is not used (uninitialized
   `bdev`), return 0 for migration thresholds immediately—skipping VRAM-specific
   logic that would trigger the NULL dereference.

2. **amdgpu_kms.c**: Update the `AMDGPU_INFO_VRAM_USAGE` ioctl and memory info
   reporting to use a conditional: if the manager is used, return the real VRAM
   usage; otherwise, return 0. This avoids accessing `man-&gt;bdev` when it is
   NULL.

3. **amdgpu_virt.c**: Modify the vf2pf (virtual function to physical function)
   data write path. Use `ttm_resource_manager_used()` to check validity: if the
   manager is usable, calculate `fb_usage` from VRAM usage; otherwise, set
   `fb_usage` to 0 (APUs have no discrete framebuffer to report).

This approach is more robust than APU-specific checks because it:
- Works for all scenarios where the VRAM manager is uninitialized (not just APUs),
- Aligns with TTM's design by using its native helper function,
- Preserves correct behavior for discrete GPUs (which have fully initialized
  `man-&gt;bdev` and pass the `ttm_resource_manager_used()` check).

v4: use ttm_resource_manager_used(&amp;amp;adev-&gt;mman.vram_mgr.manager) instead of checking the adev-&gt;gmc.is_app_apu flag (Christian)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40289 | drm/amdgpu: hide VRAM sysfs attributes on GPUs without VRAM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40289</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: hide VRAM sysfs attributes on GPUs without VRAM

Otherwise accessing them can cause a crash.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14141 | UTT 进取 520W formArpBindConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14141</link><description>A flaw has been found in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formArpBindConfig. Executing manipulation of the argument pools can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 16:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14140 | UTT 进取 520W websHostFilter strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14140</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The affected element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/websHostFilter. Performing manipulation of the argument addHostFilter results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14139 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigDnsFilterGlobal strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14139</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigDnsFilterGlobal. Such manipulation of the argument timeRangeName leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14136 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 mod_form.so stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14136</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This vulnerability affects the function RE2000v2Repeater_get_wired_clientlist_setClientsName of the file mod_form.so. The manipulation of the argument clientsname_0 results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 13:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14135 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 mod_form.so AP_get_wired_clientlist_setClientsName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14135</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This affects the function AP_get_wired_clientlist_setClientsName of the file mod_form.so. The manipulation of the argument clientsname_0 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14134 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 mod_form.so stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14134</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. Affected by this issue is the function RE2000v2Repeater_get_wireless_clientlist_setClientsName of the file mod_form.so. Executing manipulation of the argument clientsname_0 can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14133 | Linksys RE6500/RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE7000/RE9000 mod_form.so AP_get_wireless_clientlist_setClientsName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14133</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6500, RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. Affected by this vulnerability is the function AP_get_wireless_clientlist_setClientsName of the file mod_form.so. Performing manipulation of the argument clientsname_0 results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14126 | TOZED ZLT M30S/ZLT M30S PRO Web hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14126</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOZED ZLT M30S and ZLT M30S PRO 1.47/3.09.06. Affected is an unknown function of the component Web Interface. Such manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 10:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12966 | All-in-One Video Gallery 4.5.4 - 4.5.7 – Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via Import ZIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12966</link><description>The All-in-One Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the resolve_import_directory() function in versions 4.5.4 to 4.5.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13065 | Starter Templates &amp;lt;= 4.4.41 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via WXR Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13065</link><description>The Starter Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.41. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting WXR files, allowing double extension files to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid WXR file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12499 | Rich Shortcodes for Google Reviews &amp;lt;= 6.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Google Review</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12499</link><description>The Rich Shortcodes for Google Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the contents of a Google Review in all versions up to, and including, 6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially patched in version 6.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 07:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13377 | 10Web Booster &amp;lt;= 2.32.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Folder Deletion via two_clear_page_cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13377</link><description>The 10Web Booster – Website speed optimization, Cache &amp; Page Speed optimizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary folder deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the get_cache_dir_for_page_from_url() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.32.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary folders on the server, which can easily lead to a loss of data or a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13748 | Fluent Forms &amp;lt;= 6.1.7 - Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference to Payment Status Tampering via submission_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13748</link><description>The Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Conversational Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7 via the 'submission_id' parameter due to missing validation on a user controlled key within the confirmScaPayment() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to mark arbitrary submissions as failed via crafted requests to the endpoint granted they can guess or enumerate a valid submission identifier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12091 | Search, Filters &amp;amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.0.63 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12091</link><description>The Search, Filters &amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wcis_save_email' endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.63. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to deactivate the plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12574 | Listar – Directory Listing &amp;amp; Classifieds WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12574</link><description>The Listar – Directory Listing &amp; Classifieds WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the '/wp-json/listar/v1/place/delete' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12577 | Listar – Directory Listing &amp;amp; Classifieds WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Listing Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12577</link><description>The Listar – Directory Listing &amp; Classifieds WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the '/wp-json/listar/v1/place/save' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update listing details.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12673 | Flex QR Code Generator &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12673</link><description>The Flex QR Code Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the update_qr_code() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12715 | Canadian Nutrition Facts Label &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Nutrition Label Custom Post Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12715</link><description>The Canadian Nutrition Facts Label plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'percentage' field in the Nutrition Label custom post type in all versions up to, and including, 3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12717 | List Attachments Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.4.1a - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via list-attachments Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12717</link><description>The List Attachments Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'before_list' parameter in the [list-attachments] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.1a due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12720 | g-FFL Cockpit &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Improper Authorization to Unauthenticated Product Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12720</link><description>The g-FFL Cockpit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to IP-based authorization that can be spoofed in the handle_enqueue_only() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary products.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12721 | g-FFL Cockpit &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12721</link><description>The g-FFL Cockpit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 via the /server_status REST API endpoint due to a lack of capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract information about the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13137 | Live Sales Notification for Woocommerce – Woomotiv &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13137</link><description>The Live Sales Notification for Woocommerce – Woomotiv plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'woomotiv_limit' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13308 | Application Passwords &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via reject_url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13308</link><description>The Application Passwords plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'reject_url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URLs, which allows javascript: URI schemes to be embedded in the reject_url parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute when a user clicks the "No, I do not approve of this connection" button, granted they can successfully trick the victim into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13309 | Accessiy By CodeConfig Accessibility – Easy One-Click Accessibility Toolbar That Truly Matters &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Modify Accessibility Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13309</link><description>The Accessiy By CodeConfig Accessibility – Easy One-Click Accessibility Toolbar That Truly Matters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access and above to modify the plugin’s global accessibility settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13358 | Accessiy By CodeConfig Accessibility &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Page Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13358</link><description>The Accessiy By CodeConfig Accessibility plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized page creation due to missing authorization checks in versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to the plugin not performing capability checks in the `Settings::createPage()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary published pages on the site via the `ccpcaCreatePage` AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13626 | myLCO &amp;lt;= 0.8.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13626</link><description>The myLCO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13629 | WP Landing Page &amp;lt;= 0.9.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Post Meta Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13629</link><description>The WP Landing Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.3. This is due to missing nonce validation on the 'wplp_api_update_text' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary post meta via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13656 | Cute News Ticker &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;color&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13656</link><description>The Cute News Ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'color' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13666 | Helloprint &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Order Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13666</link><description>The Helloprint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to the plugin registering a public REST API endpoint without implementing authorization checks to verify request authenticity. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily modify WooCommerce order statuses via the /wp-json/helloprint/v1/complete_order_from_helloprint_callback endpoint by providing a valid order reference ID.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13856 | Extra Post Images &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13856</link><description>The Extra Post Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter of the extra-images shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13857 | Yet Another WebClap for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13857</link><description>The Yet Another WebClap for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'text' parameter of the webclap_button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13863 | RevInsite &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13863</link><description>The RevInsite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `token` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13894 | CSV Sumotto &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13894</link><description>The CSV Sumotto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` variable in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13896 | Social Feed Gallery Portfolio &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13896</link><description>The Social Feed Gallery Portfolio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter of the [igp-wp] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13898 | Ultra Skype Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;btn_id&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13898</link><description>The Ultra Skype Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'btn_id' parameter of the [ultra_skype] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13899 | TR Timthumb &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13899</link><description>The TR Timthumb plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13907 | CSS3 Buttons &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13907</link><description>The CSS3 Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14117 | fit2cloud Halo cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14117</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in fit2cloud Halo 2.21.10. Impacted is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13292 | Improper access control in Google Cloud Apigee-X allows cross-tenant Analytics modification and log data access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13292</link><description>A vulnerability in Apigee-X allowed an attacker to gain unauthorized read and write access to Apigee Analytics (AX) data and access logs belonging to other Apigee customer organizations.

Apigee-X was found to be vulnerable.

This vulnerability was patched in version 1-16-0-apigee-3. No user action is required for this.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12505 | weDocs &amp;lt;= 2.1.14 - Missing Authorization to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12505</link><description>The weDocs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.14. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the create_item_permissions_check function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify global plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 04:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13922 | Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI &amp;lt;= 3.40.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via ORDER BY Clause</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13922</link><description>The Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager – AI Autotagger with OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'existing_terms_orderby' parameter in the AI preview AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.40.1. This is due to insufficient escaping on user-supplied parameters and lack of SQL query parameterization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above who have AI metabox permissions, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database, cause performance degradation, or enable data inference through time-based techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 04:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11263 | Link Whisper Free &amp;lt;= 0.8.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11263</link><description>The Link Whisper Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the type parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 03:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12510 | Widgets for Google Reviews &amp;lt;= 13.2.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Google Reviews</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12510</link><description>The Widgets for Google Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 13.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on Google Reviews data imported by the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that will execute in the admin panel (and potentially on the frontend) whenever a user accesses imported reviews, granted they can add a malicious review to a Google Place that is connected to the vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 03:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66629 | HedgeDoc is missing state parameter in OAuth2 flows could lead to CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66629</link><description>HedgeDoc is an open source, real-time, collaborative, markdown notes application. Prior to 1.10.4, some of HedgeDoc's OAuth2 endpoints for social login providers such as Google, GitHub, GitLab, Facebook or Dropbox lack CSRF protection, since they don't send a state parameter and verify the response using this parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14111 | Rarlab RAR App com.rarlab.rar path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14111</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Rarlab RAR App up to 7.11 Build 127 on Android. This affects an unknown part of the component com.rarlab.rar. Such manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 7.20 build 128 is able to mitigate this issue. You should upgrade the affected component. The vendor responded very professional: "This is the real vulnerability affecting RAR for Android only. WinRAR and Unix RAR versions are not affected. We already fixed it in RAR for Android 7.20 build 128 and we publicly mentioned it in that version changelog. (...) To avoid confusion among users, it would be useful if such disclosure emphasizes that it is RAR for Android only issue and WinRAR isn't affected."</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14116 | xerrors Yuxi-Know embed.py OtherEmbedding.aencode server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14116</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in xerrors Yuxi-Know up to 0.4.0. This vulnerability affects the function OtherEmbedding.aencode of the file /src/models/embed.py. Performing manipulation of the argument health_url results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The patch is named 0ff771dc1933d5a6b78f804115e78a7d8625c3f3. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The vendor responded with a vulnerability confirmation and a list of security measures they have established already (e.g. disabled URL parsing, disabled URL upload mode, removed URL-to-markdown conversion).</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34291 | Langflow &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 CORS Misconfiguration to Token Hijack &amp;amp; RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34291</link><description>Langflow versions up to and including 1.6.9 contain a chained vulnerability that enables account takeover and remote code execution. An overly permissive CORS configuration (allow_origins='*' with allow_credentials=True) combined with a refresh token cookie configured as SameSite=None allows a malicious webpage to perform cross-origin requests that include credentials and successfully call the refresh endpoint. An attacker-controlled origin can therefore obtain fresh access_token / refresh_token pairs for a victim session. Obtained tokens permit access to authenticated endpoints — including built-in code-execution functionality — allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary code and achieve full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14108 | ZSPACE Q2C NAS HTTP POST Request open zfilev2_api.OpenSafe command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14108</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ZSPACE Q2C NAS up to 1.1.0210050. Affected by this issue is the function zfilev2_api.OpenSafe of the file /v2/file/safe/open of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument safe_dir causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 22:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14106 | ZSPACE Q2C NAS HTTP POST Request close zfilev2_api.CloseSafe command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14106</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ZSPACE Q2C NAS up to 1.1.0210050. Affected is the function zfilev2_api.CloseSafe of the file /v2/file/safe/close of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument safe_dir leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14107 | ZSPACE Q2C NAS HTTP POST Request status zfilev2_api.SafeStatus command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14107</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in ZSPACE Q2C NAS up to 1.1.0210050. Affected by this vulnerability is the function zfilev2_api.SafeStatus of the file /v2/file/safe/status of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument safe_dir results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13426 | Improper Sandboxing in Google Apigee&amp;#x27;s JavaCallout Policy Allows for Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13426</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Google  Apigee's JavaCallout policy https://docs.apigee.com/api-platform/reference/policies/java-callout-policy  that allows for remote code execution.

It is possible for a user to write a JavaCallout that injected a malicious object into the MessageContext to execute arbitrary Java code and system commands at runtime, leading to unauthorized access to data, lateral movement within the network, and access to backend systems.

The Apigee hybrid versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability:
  *  Hybrid_1.11.2+
  *  Hybrid_1.12.4+
  *  Hybrid_1.13.3+
  *  Hybrid_1.14.1+
  *  OPDK_5202+
  *  OPDK_5300+</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14105 | TOZED ZLT M30S/ZLT M30S PRO Web proc_post denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14105</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in TOZED ZLT M30S and ZLT M30S PRO 1.47/3.09.06. This impacts an unknown function of the file /reqproc/proc_post of the component Web Interface. Executing manipulation of the argument goformId with the input REBOOT_DEVICE can lead to denial of service. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8148 | CVE-2025-8148 Improper Access Control in SFTP service of GoAnywhere MFT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8148</link><description>An Improper Access Control in the SFTP service in Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT prior to version 7.9.0 allows Web Users with an Authentication Alias and a valid SSH key but limited to Password authentication for SFTP to still login using their SSH key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 21:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46603 | Dell CloudBoost Virtual Appliance, versions 19.13.0.0 and prior, contains an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46603</link><description>Dell CloudBoost Virtual Appliance, versions 19.13.0.0 and prior, contains an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66644 | Array Networks ArrayOS AG before 9.4.5.9 allows command injection, as exploited in the wild in August through December 2025.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66644</link><description>Array Networks ArrayOS AG before 9.4.5.9 allows command injection, as exploited in the wild in August through December 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66581 | Frappe LMS is Missing Server-Side Authorization in Business Logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66581</link><description>Frappe Learning Management System (LMS) is a learning system that helps users structure their content. Prior to 2.41.0, a flaw in the server-side authorization logic allowed authenticated users to perform actions beyond their assigned roles across multiple features. Because the affected endpoints relied on client-side or UI-level checks instead of enforcing permissions on the server, users with low-privileged roles (such as students) could perform operations intended only for instructors or administrators via directly using the API's. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.41.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66623 | Strimzi allows unrestricted access to all Secrets in the same Kubernetes namespace from Kafka Connect and MirrorMaker 2 operands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66623</link><description>Strimzi provides a way to run an Apache Kafka cluster on Kubernetes or OpenShift in various deployment configurations. From 0.47.0 and prior to 0.49.1, in some situations, Strimzi creates an incorrect Kubernetes Role which grants the Apache Kafka Connect and Apache Kafka MirrorMaker 2 operands the GET access to all Kubernetes Secrets that exist in the given Kubernetes namespace. The issue is fixed in Strimzi 0.49.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66624 | BACnet-stack MS/TP reply matcher OOB read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66624</link><description>BACnet Protocol Stack library provides a BACnet application layer, network layer and media access (MAC) layer communications services. Prior to 1.5.0.rc2, The npdu_is_expected_reply function in src/bacnet/npdu.c indexes request_pdu[offset+2/3/5] and reply_pdu[offset+1/2/4] without verifying that those APDU bytes exist. bacnet_npdu_decode() can return offset == 2 for a 2-byte NPDU, so tiny PDUs pass the version check and then get read out of bounds. On ASan/MPU/strict builds this is an immediate crash (DoS). On unprotected builds it is undefined behavior and can mis-route replies; RCE is unlikely because only reads occur, but DoS is reliable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66570 | cpp-httplib Untrusted HTTP Header Handling: Internal Header Shadowing (REMOTE*/LOCAL*)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66570</link><description>cpp-httplib is a C++11 single-file header-only cross platform HTTP/HTTPS library. Prior to 0.27.0, a vulnerability allows attacker-controlled HTTP headers to influence server-visible metadata, logging, and authorization decisions. An attacker can inject headers named REMOTE_ADDR, REMOTE_PORT, LOCAL_ADDR, LOCAL_PORT that are parsed into the request header multimap via read_headers() in httplib.h (headers.emplace), then the server later appends its own internal metadata using the same header names in Server::process_request without erasing duplicates. Because Request::get_header_value returns the first entry for a header key (id == 0) and the client-supplied headers are parsed before server-inserted headers, downstream code that uses these header names may inadvertently use attacker-controlled values. Affected files/locations: cpp-httplib/httplib.h (read_headers, Server::process_request, Request::get_header_value, get_header_value_u64) and cpp-httplib/docker/main.cc (get_client_ip, nginx_access_logger, nginx_error_logger). Attack surface: attacker-controlled HTTP headers in incoming requests flow into the Request.headers multimap and into logging code that reads forwarded headers, enabling IP spoofing, log poisoning, and authorization bypass via header shadowing. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66577 | cpp-httplib Untrusted HTTP Header Handling: X-Forwarded-For/X-Real-IP Trust</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66577</link><description>cpp-httplib is a C++11 single-file header-only cross platform HTTP/HTTPS library. Prior to 0.27.0, a vulnerability allows attacker-controlled HTTP headers to influence server-visible metadata, logging, and authorization decisions. An attacker can supply X-Forwarded-For or X-Real-IP headers which get accepted unconditionally by get_client_ip() in docker/main.cc, causing access and error logs (nginx_access_logger / nginx_error_logger) to record spoofed client IPs (log poisoning / audit evasion). This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66558 | Nextcloud Twofactor WebAuthn app was updated based on public key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66558</link><description>Nextcloud Twofactor WebAuthn is the WebAuthn Two-Factor Provider for Nextcloud. Prior to 1.4.2 and 2.4.1, a missing ownership check allowed an attack to take-away a 2FA webauthn device when correctly guessing a 80-128 character long random string of letters, numbers and symbols. The victim would then be prompted to register a new device on the next login. The attacker can not authenticate as the victim. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.2 and 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66562 | TUUI vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via XSS in Markdown ECharts Rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66562</link><description>TUUI is a desktop MCP client designed as a tool unitary utility integration. Prior to 1.3.4, a critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in Tuui due to an unsafe Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) flaw in the Markdown rendering component. Tuui allows the execution of arbitrary JavaScript within ECharts code blocks. Combined with an exposed IPC interface that allows spawning processes, an attacker can execute arbitrary system commands on the victim's machine simply by having them view a malicious Markdown message. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66566 | yawkat LZ4 Java has a possible information leak in Java safe decompressor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66566</link><description>yawkat LZ4 Java provides LZ4 compression for Java. Insufficient clearing of the output buffer in Java-based decompressor implementations in lz4-java 1.10.0 and earlier allows remote attackers to read previous buffer contents via crafted compressed input. In applications where the output buffer is reused without being cleared, this may lead to disclosure of sensitive data. JNI-based implementations are not affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66556 | Nextcloud talk allows participants to blindly delete poll drafts of other users by ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66556</link><description>Nextcloud talk is a video &amp; audio conferencing app for Nextcloud. Prior to 20.1.8 and 21.1.2, a participant with chat permissions was able to delete poll drafts of other participants within the conversation based on their numeric ID. This vulnerability is fixed in 20.1.8 and 21.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66554 | Nextcloud Contacts vulnerable to Stored XSS in contacts app via organisation and title field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66554</link><description>Contacts app for Nextcloud easily syncs contacts from various devices with your Nextcloud and allows editing. Prior to 5.5.4, 6.0.6, and 7.2.5, a malicious user was able to modify their organisation and title field to load additional CSS files. Javascript and other options were correctly blocked by the content security policy of the Nextcloud Server code. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.5.4, 6.0.6, and 7.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66545 | Nextcloud Groupfolders users with read-only permissions for team folder can restore deleted files from trash bin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66545</link><description>Nextcloud Groupfolders provides admin-configured folders shared by everyone in a group or team. Prior to 14.0.11, 15.3.12, 16.0.15, 17.0.14, 18.1.8, 19.1.8, and 20.1.2, a user with read-only permission can restore a file from the trash bin. This vulnerability is fixed in 14.0.11, 15.3.12, 16.0.15, 17.0.14, 18.1.8, 19.1.8, and 20.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66549 | Nextcloud Desktop discloses information when attempting to lock a file inside a end-to-end encrypted directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66549</link><description>Nextcloud Desktop is the desktop sync client for Nextcloud. Prior to 3.16.5, when trying to manually lock a file inside an end-to-end encrypted directory, the path of the file was sent to the server unencrypted, making it possible for administrators to see it in log files. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.16.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36882 | Flexsense DiskBoss Application Crash Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36882</link><description>Flexsense DiskBoss 7.7.14 allows unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via /Command/Search Files/Directory field, leading to a denial of service by crashing the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66515 | Nextcloud Approval app allows users to request approval for other users file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66515</link><description>The Nextcloud Approval app allows approval or disapproval of files in the sidebar. Prior to 1.3.1 and 2.5.0, an authenticated user listed as a requester in a workflow can set another user’s file into the “pending approval” without access to the file by using the numeric file id. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.3.1 and 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66514 | Nextcloud Mail stored HTML injection in subject text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66514</link><description>Nextcloud Mail is the mail app for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to 5.5.3, a stored HTML injection in the Mail app's message list allowed an authenticated user to inject HTML into the email subjects. Javascript was correctly blocked by the content security policy of the Nextcloud Server code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66548 | Nextcloud Deck app allows to spoof file extensions by using RTLO characters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66548</link><description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. Prior to 1.12.7, 1.14.4, and 1.15.1, file extension can be spoofed by using RTLO characters, tricking users into download files with a different extension than what is displayed. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.12.7, 1.14.4, and 1.15.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66557 | Nextcloud Deck app allowed user with &amp;quot;Can share&amp;quot; permission to modify permissions of other non-owners</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66557</link><description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. Prior to 1.14.6 and 1.15.2, a bug in the permission logic allowed users with "Can share" permission to modify the permissions of other recipients. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.14.6 and 1.15.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36876 | ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Server &amp;lt;= 7.0.3 Debug Log Disclosure2020</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36876</link><description>ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Server versions 7.0.3.4968 (Pro), 7.0.2.4954, 6.5.2.4954, 6.4.2.4681, 6.3.2.4203, and 2.0.1.823 allows unauthenticated attackers to disclose the webserver's Python debug log file containing system information, credentials, paths, processes and command arguments running on the device. Attackers can access sensitive information by visiting the message_log page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36877 | ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Server &amp;lt;= 7.0.3 code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36877</link><description>ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Server 7.0.3 contains an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands as the web server user. Attackers can upload PHP executable files via the Quick File Uploader page, resulting in remote code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36878 | ReQuest Serious Play F3 Media Player &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 Directory Traversal File Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36878</link><description>ReQuest Serious Play Media Player 3.0 contains an unauthenticated file disclosure vulnerability when input passed through the 'file' parameter in and script is not properly verified before being used to read web log files. Attackers can exploit this to disclose contents of files from local resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36879 | Flexsense DiskBoss Service Unquoted Service Path Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36879</link><description>Flexsense DiskBoss 11.7.28 allows unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges using any of its services, enabling remote code execution during startup or reboot with escalated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path vulnerability by specifying a malicious service name in the 'sc qc' command, allowing them to execute arbitrary system commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36880 | Flexsense DiskBoss &amp;#x27;Reports and Data Directory&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36880</link><description>Flexsense DiskBoss 7.7.14 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the 'Reports and Data Directory' field that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36881 | Flexsense DiskBoss &amp;#x27;Add Input Directory&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36881</link><description>Flexsense DiskBoss 7.7.14 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the 'Input Directory' component that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on the system. Attackers can exploit this by pasting a specially crafted directory path into the 'Add Input Directory' field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34256 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Hard-coded JWT Key Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34256</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a hard-coded cryptographic key vulnerability. The product uses a static HS512 HMAC secret for signing EIRMMToken JWTs across all installations. The server accepts forged JWTs that need only contain a valid email claim, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to generate arbitrary tokens and impersonate any DeviceOn account, including the root super admin. Successful exploitation permits full administrative control of the DeviceOn instance and can be leveraged to execute code on managed agents through DeviceOn’s remote management features.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34257 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via action/defined</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34257</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/action/defined endpoint. When an authenticated user creates a task, the defined_name value is stored and later rendered in the Overview page without HTML sanitization. An attacker can inject malicious script into defined_name, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view the affected task, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34258 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via devicemap/plan</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34258</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/devicemap/plan endpoint. When an authenticated user adds an area to a map entry, the name parameter is stored and later rendered in the map list without HTML sanitization. An attacker can inject malicious script into the area name, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected map entry, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34259 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via devicemap/building</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34259</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/devicemap/building endpoint. When an authenticated user creates a map entry, the name parameter is stored and later rendered in the map list UI without HTML sanitzation. An attacker can inject malicious script into the map entry name, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected map entry, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34260 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via action/schedule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34260</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/action/schedule endpoint. When an authenticated user adds a schedule to an existing task, the schedule name is stored and later rendered in schedule listings without HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into the schedule name, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected schedule, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34261 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via devicegroups/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34261</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/devicegroups/ endpoint. When an authenticated user creates a device group, the name and description values are stored and later rendered in device group listings without proper HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into either field, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected device group, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34262 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via devices/name/{agent_id}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34262</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/devices/name/{agent_id} endpoint. When an authenticated user renames a device, the new_name value is stored and later rendered in device listings or detail views without proper HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into the device name, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected device, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34263 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via plugin-config/dashboards/menus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34263</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/plugin-config/dashboards/menus endpoint. When an authenticated user adds or edits a dashboard entry, the label and path values are stored in plugin configuration data and later rendered in the dashboard UI without proper HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into either field, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected dashboard, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34264 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via dog/{agentId}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34264</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/dog/{agentId} endpoint. When an authenticated user adds or edits Software Watchdog process rules for an agent, the monitored process name is stored in the settings array and later rendered in the Software Watchdog UI without proper HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into the process name, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected rules, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34265 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via rule-engines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34265</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/rule-engines endpoint. When an authenticated user creates or updates a rule for an agent, the rule fields min, max, and unit are stored and later rendered in rule listings or detail views without proper HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into one or more of these fields, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected rule, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34266 | Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server &amp;lt; 5.4 Authenticated Stored XSS via plugin-config/addins/menus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34266</link><description>Advantech WISE-DeviceOn Server versions prior to 5.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rmm/v1/plugin-config/addins/menus endpoint. When an authenticated user adds or edits an AddIns menu entry, the label and path values are stored in plugin configuration data and later rendered in the AddIns UI without proper HTML sanitation. An attacker can inject malicious script into either field, which is then executed in the browser context of users who view or interact with the affected AddIns entry, potentially enabling session compromise and unauthorized actions as the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66513 | Nextcloud Tables app share information not limited to relevant users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66513</link><description>Nextcloud Tables allows you to create your own tables with individual columns. Prior to 0.8.9, 0.9.6, and 1.0.1, the information which table (numeric ID) is shared with which groups or users and the respective permissions was not limited to privileged users. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.9, 0.9.6, and 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66551 | Nextcloud Tables is missing an ownership check which allows moving columns into tables of other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66551</link><description>Nextcloud Tables allows you to create your own tables with individual columns. Prior to 0.8.6 and 0.9.3, a malicious user was able to create their own table and then move a column to a victims table. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.6 and 0.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66553 | Nextcloud Tables app allowed users to view columns metadata information of any table</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66553</link><description>Nextcloud Tables allows you to create your own tables with individual columns. Prior to 0.8.7 and 0.9.4, authenticated users were able to view meta data of columns in other tables of the Tables app by modifying the numeric ID in a request. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.7 and 0.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14094 | Edimax BR-6478AC V3 formSysCmd sub_44CCE4 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14094</link><description>A flaw has been found in Edimax BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15. The affected element is the function sub_44CCE4 of the file /boafrm/formSysCmd. This manipulation of the argument sysCmd causes os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66550 | Nextcloud Calendar attachments of local files are offered to downloaded</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66550</link><description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Prior to 4.7.17 and 5.2.4, when a malicious user creates a calendar event with a crafted attachment that links to a download link of a file on the same Nextcloud server, the file would be downloaded without the user confirming the action. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.7.17 and 5.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66546 | Nextcloud Calendar app allowed booking appointments without the generated token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66546</link><description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Prior to 4.7.19, 5.5.6, and 6.0.1, the calendar app allowed blindly booking appointments with a squential ID without known the appointment token. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.7.19, 5.5.6, and 6.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9183 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9183</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 18.4 prior to 18.4.5, 18.5 prior to 18.5.3, and 18.6 prior to 18.6.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to obtain credentials from higher-privileged users and perform actions in their context under specific conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14093 | Edimax BR-6478AC V3 formTracerouteDiagnosticRun sub_416990 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14093</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Edimax BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15. Impacted is the function sub_416990 of the file /boafrm/formTracerouteDiagnosticRun. The manipulation of the argument host results in os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66511 | Nextcloud Calendar app used predictable proposal participant tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66511</link><description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Prior to 6.0.3, the Calendar app generates participant tokens for meeting proposals using a hash function, allowing an attacker to compute valid participant tokens, which allowed them to request details and submit dates in meeting proposals. The tokens are not purely random generated. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66547 | Nextcloud Server users can modify tags on files that do not belong to them</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66547</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server and Enterprise Server prior to 31.0.1, non-privileged users can modify tags on files they should not have access to via bulk tagging. This vulnerability is fixed in 31.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66552 | Nextcloud Server admin_audit does not log all actions on files in groupfolders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66552</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server and Enterprise Server prior to 30.0.9 and 31.0.1, incorrect path handling with groupfolders caused the admin_audit app to not properly log all actions on files and folders inside groupfolders. This vulnerability is fixed in Nextcloud Server and Enterprise Server prior to 30.0.9 and 31.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14104 | Util-linux: util-linux: heap buffer overread in setpwnam() when processing 256-byte usernames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14104</link><description>A flaw was found in util-linux. This vulnerability allows a heap buffer overread when processing 256-byte usernames, specifically within the `setpwnam()` function, affecting SUID (Set User ID) login-utils utilities writing to the password database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65878 | The warehouse management system version 1.2 contains an arbitrary file read vulnerability. The endpoint `/file/showImageByPath` does not san...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65878</link><description>The warehouse management system version 1.2 contains an arbitrary file read vulnerability. The endpoint `/file/showImageByPath` does not sanitize user-controlled path parameters. An attacker could exploit directory traversal to read arbitrary files on the server's file system. This could lead to the leakage of sensitive system information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66510 | Nextcloud Server Contacts Search allowed users to retrieve contact information of other users beyond their contact list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66510</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server prior to 31.0.10 and 32.0.1 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 28.0.14.11, 29.0.16.8, 30.0.17.3, and 31.0.10, contacts search allowed to retrieve personal data of other users (emails, names, identifiers) without proper access control. This allows an authenticated user to retrieve information about accounts that are not related or added as contacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66512 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to XSS in SVG images when opened outside of Nextcloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66512</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server and Server Enterprise prior to 31.0.12 and 32.0.3, a missing sanitization allowed malicious users to circumvent the content security policy when a malicious user manages to trick a user it viewing an uploaded SVG outside of the Nextcloud Servers web page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65036 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the confluence details summary macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65036</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Prior to 1.27.1, the macro executes Velocity from the details pages without checking for permissions, which can lead to remote code execution. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.27.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65879 | Warehouse Management System 1.2 contains an authenticated arbitrary file deletion vulnerability. The /goods/deleteGoods endpoint accepts a u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65879</link><description>Warehouse Management System 1.2 contains an authenticated arbitrary file deletion vulnerability. The /goods/deleteGoods endpoint accepts a user-controlled goodsimg parameter, which is directly concatenated with the server's UPLOAD_PATH and passed to File.delete() without validation. A remote authenticated attacker can delete arbitrary files on the server by supplying directory traversal payloads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66471 | urllib3 Streaming API improperly handles highly compressed data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66471</link><description>urllib3 is a user-friendly HTTP client library for Python. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to 2.6.0, the Streaming API improperly handles highly compressed data. urllib3's streaming API is designed for the efficient handling of large HTTP responses by reading the content in chunks, rather than loading the entire response body into memory at once. When streaming a compressed response, urllib3 can perform decoding or decompression based on the HTTP Content-Encoding header (e.g., gzip, deflate, br, or zstd). The library must read compressed data from the network and decompress it until the requested chunk size is met. Any resulting decompressed data that exceeds the requested amount is held in an internal buffer for the next read operation. The decompression logic could cause urllib3 to fully decode a small amount of highly compressed data in a single operation. This can result in excessive resource consumption (high CPU usage and massive memory allocation for the decompressed data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14091 | TrippWasTaken PHP-Guitar-Shop Product Details product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14091</link><description>A weakness has been identified in TrippWasTaken PHP-Guitar-Shop up to 6ce0868889617c1975982aae6df8e49555d0d555. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /product.php of the component Product Details Page. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14092 | Edimax BR-6478AC V3 formDebugDiagnosticRun sub_416898 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14092</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Edimax BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15. This issue affects the function sub_416898 of the file /boafrm/formDebugDiagnosticRun. The manipulation of the argument host leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65897 | zdh_web is a data collection, processing, monitoring, scheduling, and management platform. In zdh_web thru 5.6.17, insufficient validation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65897</link><description>zdh_web is a data collection, processing, monitoring, scheduling, and management platform. In zdh_web thru 5.6.17, insufficient validation of file upload paths in the application allows an authenticated user to write arbitrary files to the server file system, potentially overwriting existing files and leading to privilege escalation or remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66418 | urllib3 allows an unbounded number of links in the decompression chain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66418</link><description>urllib3 is a user-friendly HTTP client library for Python. Starting in version 1.24 and prior to 2.6.0, the number of links in the decompression chain was unbounded allowing a malicious server to insert a virtually unlimited number of compression steps leading to high CPU usage and massive memory allocation for the decompressed data. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64053 | A Buffer overflow vulnerability on Fanvil x210 2.12.20 devices allows attackers to cause a denial of service or potentially execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64053</link><description>A Buffer overflow vulnerability on Fanvil x210 2.12.20 devices allows attackers to cause a denial of service or potentially execute arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to the /cgi-bin/webconfig?page=upload&amp;amp;action=submit endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64054 | A reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on Fanvil x210 2.12.20 devices allows attackers to cause a denial of service or potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64054</link><description>A reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on Fanvil x210 2.12.20 devices allows attackers to cause a denial of service or potentially execute arbitrary commands via crafted POST request to the /cgi-bin/webconfig?page=upload&amp;amp;action=submit endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14089 | Himool ERP AdminActionViewSet update_account improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14089</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Himool ERP up to 2.2. Affected by this issue is the function update_account of the file /api/admin/update_account/ of the component AdminActionViewSet. Such manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14090 | AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System cardmake_down.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14090</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /manager/card/cardmake_down.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64052 | An issue was discovered in Fanvil x210 V2 2.12.20 allowing unauthenticated attackers on the local network to execute arbitrary system comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64052</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fanvil x210 V2 2.12.20 allowing unauthenticated attackers on the local network to execute arbitrary system commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64056 | File upload vulnerability in Fanvil x210 V2 2.12.20 allows unauthenticated attackers on the local network to store arbitrary files on the fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64056</link><description>File upload vulnerability in Fanvil x210 V2 2.12.20 allows unauthenticated attackers on the local network to store arbitrary files on the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65730 | Authentication Bypass via Hardcoded Credentials GoAway up to v0.62.18, fixed in 0.62.19, uses a hardcoded secret for signing JWT tokens used...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65730</link><description>Authentication Bypass via Hardcoded Credentials GoAway up to v0.62.18, fixed in 0.62.19, uses a hardcoded secret for signing JWT tokens used for authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64057 | Directory traversal vulnerability in Fanvil x210 V2 2.12.20 allows unauthenticated attackers on the local network to store files in arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64057</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in Fanvil x210 V2 2.12.20 allows unauthenticated attackers on the local network to store files in arbitrary locations and potentially modify the system configuration or other unspecified impacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14088 | ketr JEPaaS load improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14088</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ketr JEPaaS up to 7.2.8. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /je/load. This manipulation of the argument Authorization causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14085 | youlaitech youlai-mall orders improper control of dynamically-identified variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14085</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in youlaitech youlai-mall 1.0.0/2.0.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /app-api/v1/orders/. The manipulation of the argument orderId leads to improper control of dynamically-identified variables. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14086 | youlaitech youlai-mall openid access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14086</link><description>A vulnerability was found in youlaitech youlai-mall 1.0.0/2.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /app-api/v1/members/openid/. The manipulation of the argument openid results in improper access controls. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58098 | Apache HTTP Server: Server Side Includes adds query string to #exec cmd=...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58098</link><description>Apache HTTP Server 2.4.65 and earlier with Server Side Includes (SSI) enabled and mod_cgid (but not mod_cgi) passes the shell-escaped query string to #exec cmd="..." directives.

This issue affects Apache HTTP Server before 2.4.66.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.66, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6966 | Null-pointer dereference in python-apt TagSection.keys()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6966</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in TagSection.keys() in python-apt on APT-based 
Linux systems allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service 
(process crash) via a crafted deb822 file with a malformed non-UTF-8 key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13654 | CVE-2025-13654</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13654</link><description>A stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the buffer_get function of duc, a disk management tool, where a condition can evaluate to true due to underflow, allowing an out-of-bounds read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66200 | Apache HTTP Server: mod_userdir+suexec bypass via AllowOverride FileInfo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66200</link><description>mod_userdir+suexec bypass via AllowOverride FileInfo vulnerability in Apache HTTP Server. Users with access to use the RequestHeader directive in htaccess can cause some CGI scripts to run under an unexpected userid.

This issue affects Apache HTTP Server: from 2.4.7 through 2.4.65.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.66, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13620 | Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Missing Authorization in Cache REST Endpoints to Social Counter Tampering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13620</link><description>The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to missing authorization in versions up to, and including, 3.1.3. This is due to the REST routes wslu/v1/check_cache/{type}, wslu/v1/save_cache/{type}, and wslu/v1/settings/clear_counter_cache being registered with permission_callback set to __return_true and lacking capability or nonce validation in their handlers. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear or overwrite the social counter cache via crafted REST requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65082 | Apache HTTP Server: CGI environment variable override</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65082</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Escape, Meta, or Control Sequences vulnerability in Apache HTTP Server through environment variables set via the Apache configuration unexpectedly superseding variables calculated by the server for CGI programs.

This issue affects Apache HTTP Server from 2.4.0 through 2.4.65.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.66 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55753 | Apache HTTP Server: mod_md (ACME), unintended retry intervals</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55753</link><description>An integer overflow in the case of failed ACME certificate renewal leads, after a number of failures (~30 days in default configurations), to the backoff timer becoming 0. Attempts to renew the certificate then are repeated without delays until it succeeds.

This issue affects Apache HTTP Server: from 2.4.30 before 2.4.66.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.66, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59775 | Apache HTTP Server: NTLM Leakage on Windows through UNC SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59775</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability 

 in Apache HTTP Server on Windows 

with AllowEncodedSlashes On and MergeSlashes Off  allows to potentially leak NTLM 
hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests or content

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.66, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12851 | My auctions allegro &amp;lt;= 3.6.32 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion via controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12851</link><description>The My auctions allegro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.32 via the 'controller' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12876 | Projectopia – WordPress Project Management &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Attachment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12876</link><description>The Projectopia – WordPress Project Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pto_delete_file AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary attachments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12879 | User Generator and Importer &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Privilege Escalation via Arbitrary Administrator Account Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12879</link><description>The User Generator and Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to and including 1.2.2. This is due to missing nonce validation in the "Import Using CSV File" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate user privileges by creating arbitrary accounts with administrator privileges via a forged request, provided they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13614 | Cool Tag Cloud &amp;lt;= 2.29 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13614</link><description>The Cool Tag Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cool_tag_cloud' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13678 | Thai Lottery Widget &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13678</link><description>The Thai Lottery Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `thailottery` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied `width` and `height` shortcode attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13682 | Trail Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13682</link><description>The Trail Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13739 | CryptX &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13739</link><description>The CryptX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `cryptx` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12130 | WC Vendors – WooCommerce Multivendor, WooCommerce Marketplace, Product Vendors &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Vendor Product Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12130</link><description>The WC Vendors – WooCommerce Multivendor, WooCommerce Marketplace, Product Vendors plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the /vendor_dashboard/product/delete/ endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete vendor products via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13684 | ARK Related Posts &amp;lt;= 2.19 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13684</link><description>The ARK Related Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 2.19. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ark_rp_options_page function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's configuration settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12850 | My auctions allegro &amp;lt;= 3.6.32 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via auction_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12850</link><description>The My auctions allegro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘auction_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.32 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12093 | Voidek Employee Portal &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12093</link><description>The Voidek Employee Portal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform several actions like registering an account, deleting users, and modifying details within the employee portal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12186 | Weekly Planner &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12186</link><description>The Weekly Planner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12354 | Live CSS Preview &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12354</link><description>The Live CSS Preview plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_frontend_save' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's css setting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12355 | Payaza &amp;lt;= 0.3.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Order Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12355</link><description>The Payaza plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_update_order_status' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update order statuses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12373 | Torod – The smart shipping and delivery portal for e-shops and retailers &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery To Plugin&amp;#x27;s Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12373</link><description>The Torod – The smart shipping and delivery portal for e-shops and retailers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the save_settings function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12374 | Email Verification, Email OTP, Block Spam Email, Passwordless login, Hide Login, Magic Login – User Verification &amp;lt;= 2.0.39 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12374</link><description>The Email Verification, Email OTP, Block Spam Email, Passwordless login, Hide Login, Magic Login – User Verification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.39. This is due to the plugin not properly validating that an OTP was generated before comparing it to user input in the "user_verification_form_wrap_process_otpLogin" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user with a verified email address, such as an administrator, by submitting an empty OTP value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13515 | Nouri.sh Newsletter &amp;lt;= 1.0.1.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13515</link><description>The Nouri.sh Newsletter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-20023 | In CKSource CKFinder before 2.5.0.1 for ASP.NET, authenticated users could download any file from the server if the correct path to a file w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-20023</link><description>In CKSource CKFinder before 2.5.0.1 for ASP.NET, authenticated users could download any file from the server if the correct path to a file was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 06:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10055 | Time Sheets &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10055</link><description>The Time Sheets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several endpoints. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform a variety of actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12124 | FitVids for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12124</link><description>The FitVids for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12128 | Hide Categories Or Products On Shop Page &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12128</link><description>The Hide Categories Or Products On Shop Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the save_data_hcps() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12133 | EPROLO Dropshipping &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Tracking Data Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12133</link><description>The EPROLO Dropshipping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wp_ajax_eprolo_delete_tracking and wp_ajax_eprolo_save_tracking_data AJAX endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify and delete tracking data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12153 | Featured Image via URL &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary FIle Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12153</link><description>The Featured Image via URL plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation function in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12154 | Auto Thumbnailer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12154</link><description>The Auto Thumbnailer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the uploadThumb() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12163 | Omnipress &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12163</link><description>The Omnipress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12165 | Webcake – Landing Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12165</link><description>The Webcake – Landing Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'webcake_save_config' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12181 | ContentStudio &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12181</link><description>The ContentStudio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the cstu_update_post() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12189 | Bread &amp;amp; Butter: Gate content + Capture leads + Collect first-party data + Nurture with Ai agents &amp;lt;= 7.10.1321 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12189</link><description>The Bread &amp; Butter: Gate content + Capture leads + Collect first-party data + Nurture with Ai agents plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.10.1321. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the uploadImage() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files that make remote code execution possible via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12190 | Image Optimizer by wps.sk &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Bulk Image Optimization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12190</link><description>The Image Optimizer by wps.sk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the imagopby_ajax_optimize_gallery() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger bulk optimization via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12191 | PDF Catalog for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.18 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12191</link><description>The PDF Catalog for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pdfcatalog' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12368 | Sermon Manager &amp;lt;= 2.30.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12368</link><description>The Sermon Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `sermon-views` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.30.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12370 | Takeads &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Missing Authorization to Plugin Settings Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12370</link><description>The Takeads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's configuration options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13144 | ContentStudio &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13144</link><description>The ContentStudio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7. This is due to missing or insufficient nonce validation on the add_cstu_settings function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13360 | Quantic Social Image Hover &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13360</link><description>The Quantic Social Image Hover plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13512 | CoSign Single Signon &amp;lt;= 0.3.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13512</link><description>The CoSign Single Signon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13528 | Feedback Modal for Website &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Feedback Data Exfiltration via &amp;#x27;export_data&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13528</link><description>The Feedback Modal for Website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_export' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export all feedback data in CSV or JSON format via the 'export_data' parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13621 | dream gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;dreampluginsmain&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13621</link><description>The dream gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'dreampluginsmain' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13622 | Jabbernotification &amp;lt;= 0.99-RC2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via admin.php PATH_INFO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13622</link><description>The Jabbernotification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the admin.php PATH_INFO in all versions up to, and including, 0.99-RC2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13623 | Twitscription &amp;lt;= 0.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via admin.php PATH_INFO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13623</link><description>The Twitscription plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the admin.php PATH_INFO in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13625 | WP-SOS-Donate Donation Sidebar Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13625</link><description>The WP-SOS-Donate Donation Sidebar Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13860 | Easy Jump Links Menus &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13860</link><description>The Easy Jump Links Menus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `h_tags` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32900 | In the KDE Connect information-exchange protocol before 2025-04-18, a packet can be crafted to temporarily change the displayed information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32900</link><description>In the KDE Connect information-exchange protocol before 2025-04-18, a packet can be crafted to temporarily change the displayed information about a device, because broadcast UDP is used. This affects KDE Connect before 1.33.0 on Android, KDE Connect before 25.04 on desktop, KDE Connect before 0.5 on iOS, Valent before 1.0.0.alpha.47, and GSConnect before 59.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66270 | The KDE Connect protocol 8 before 2025-11-28 does not correlate device IDs across two packets. This affects KDE Connect before 25.12 on desk...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66270</link><description>The KDE Connect protocol 8 before 2025-11-28 does not correlate device IDs across two packets. This affects KDE Connect before 25.12 on desktop, KDE Connect before 0.5.4 on iOS, KDE Connect before 1.34.4 on Android, GSConnect before 68, and Valent before 1.0.0.alpha.49.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32901 | In KDE Connect before 1.33.0 on Android, malicious device IDs (sent via broadcast UDP) could cause an application crash.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32901</link><description>In KDE Connect before 1.33.0 on Android, malicious device IDs (sent via broadcast UDP) could cause an application crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 05:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32899 | In KDE Connect before 1.33.0 on Android, a packet can be crafted that causes two paired devices to unpair. Specifically, it is an invalid di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32899</link><description>In KDE Connect before 1.33.0 on Android, a packet can be crafted that causes two paired devices to unpair. Specifically, it is an invalid discovery packet sent over broadcast UDP.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12417 | SurveyFunnel – Survey Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12417</link><description>The SurveyFunnel – Survey Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'surveyfunnel_lite_survey' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13006 | SurveyFunnel – Survey Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13006</link><description>The SurveyFunnel – Survey Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 via several unprotected /wp-json/surveyfunnel/v2/ REST API endpoints. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from survey responses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13312 | CRM Memberships &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated &amp;#x27;ntzcrm_add_new_tag&amp;#x27; AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13312</link><description>The CRM Memberships plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized membership tag creation due to a missing capability check on the 'ntzcrm_add_new_tag' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary membership tags and modify CRM configuration that should be restricted to administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13313 | CRM Memberships &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation via Unauthenticated Password Reset in &amp;#x27;ntzcrm_changepassword&amp;#x27; AJAX Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13313</link><description>The CRM Memberships plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via password reset in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This is due to missing authorization and authentication checks on the `ntzcrm_changepassword` AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset arbitrary user passwords and gain unauthorized access to user accounts via the `ntzcrm_changepassword` endpoint, granted they can obtain or enumerate a target user's email address. The plugin also exposes the `ntzcrm_get_users` endpoint without authentication, allowing attackers to enumerate subscriber email addresses, facilitating the exploitation of the password reset vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13362 | Norby AI &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13362</link><description>The Norby AI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13494 | SSP Debug &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13494</link><description>The SSP Debug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to the plugin storing PHP error logs in a predictable, web-accessible location (wp-content/uploads/ssp-debug/ssp-debug.log) without any access controls. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view sensitive debugging information including full URLs, client IP addresses, User-Agent strings, WordPress user IDs, and internal filesystem paths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32898 | The KDE Connect verification-code protocol before 2025-04-18 uses only 8 characters and therefore allows brute-force attacks. This affects K...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32898</link><description>The KDE Connect verification-code protocol before 2025-04-18 uses only 8 characters and therefore allows brute-force attacks. This affects KDE Connect before 1.33.0 on Android, KDE Connect before 25.04 on desktop, KDE Connect before 0.5 on iOS, Valent before 1.0.0.alpha.47, and GSConnect before 59.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 04:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13066 | Demo Importer Plus &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via WXR Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13066</link><description>The Demo Importer Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting WXR files, allowing double extension files to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid WXR file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 03:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27389 | Application Installation Source Verification Flaw May Lead to Risk Detection Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27389</link><description>A flaw exists in the verification of application installation sources within ColorOS. Under specific conditions, this issue may cause the risk detection mechanism to fail, which could allow malicious applications to be installed without proper warning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 03:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11759 | Backup, Restore and Migrate your sites with XCloner &amp;lt;= 4.8.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery in Xcloner_Remote_Storage:save()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11759</link><description>The Backup, Restore and Migrate your sites with XCloner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the Xcloner_Remote_Storage:save() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add or modify an FTP backup configuration via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Successful exploitation allows an attacker to set an attacker-controlled FTP site for backup storage and exfiltrate potentially sensitive site data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12804 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.14.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bookingcalendar Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12804</link><description>The Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin 'bookingcalendar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 10.14.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62223 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) for Mac Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14052 | youlaitech youlai-mall members getMemberById access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14052</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in youlaitech youlai-mall 1.0.0/2.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getMemberById of the file /mall-ums/app-api/v1/members/. The manipulation of the argument memberId leads to improper access controls. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>