<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 13:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2122 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro Connection denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2122</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Connection Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27636 | Apache Camel: Camel Message Header Injection via Improper Filtering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27636</link><description>Bypass/Injection vulnerability in Apache Camel.

This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.10.0 through &lt;= 4.10.1, from 4.8.0 through &lt;= 4.8.4, from 3.10.0 through &lt;= 3.22.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.10.2 for 4.10.x LTS, 4.8.5 for 4.8.x LTS and 3.22.4 for 3.x releases.

The vulnerability arises due to a bug in the default filtering mechanism that only blocks headers starting with "Camel", "camel", or "org.apache.camel.". Attackers can bypass this filter by altering the casing of letters. This allows attackers to inject headers which can be exploited to invoke arbitrary methods from the Bean registry and also supports using Simple Expression Language (or OGNL in some cases) as part of the method parameters passed to the bean. It's important to note that only methods in the same bean declared in the bean URI could be invoked.


Mitigation: You can easily work around this in your Camel applications by removing the headers in your Camel routes. There are many ways of doing this, also globally or per route. This means you could use the removeHeaders EIP, to filter out anything like "cAmel, cAMEL" etc, or in general everything not starting with "Camel", "camel" or "org.apache.camel.".</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2121 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro File Storage access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2121</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. Affected is an unknown function of the component File Storage. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2120 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro Configuration File hostapd.conf cleartext storage in a file or on disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2120</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /tmp/hostapd.conf of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage in a file or on disk. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2119 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro Device Registration default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2119</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Device Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2118 | Quantico Tecnologia PRMV Login Endpoint login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2118</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quantico Tecnologia PRMV 6.48. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/login.php of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2117 | Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System reportCenter.do electricDocList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System 3.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function electricDocList of the file /newsedit/report/reportCenter.do. The manipulation of the argument fvID/catID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 07:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2116 | Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System File Protocol imageProxy.do server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System 3.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /newsedit/newsedit/xy/imageProxy.do of the component File Protocol Handler. The manipulation of the argument xyImgUrl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1362 | easy-broken-link-checker &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Bulk Actions via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1362</link><description>The URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce WordPress plugin through 9.0.2 does not have CSRF checks in some bulk actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins perform unwanted actions, such as deleting customers via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1363 | easy-broken-link-checker &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1363</link><description>The URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce WordPress plugin through 9.0.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1382 | Contact Us By Lord Linus &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1382</link><description>The Contact Us By Lord Linus WordPress plugin through 2.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2115 | zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System AcceptZip.ashx ProcessRequest unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2115</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System 3.1. Affected is the function ProcessRequest of the file /AcceptZip.ashx. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 05:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2114 | Shenzhen Sixun Software Sixun Shanghui Group Business Management System Reset Password Interface OperatorStop.asp improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2114</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Shenzhen Sixun Software Sixun Shanghui Group Business Management System 7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /WebPages/Adm/OperatorStop.asp of the component Reset Password Interface. The manipulation of the argument OperId leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 04:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2113 | AT Software Solutions ATSVD Esqueceu a senha sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2113</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AT Software Solutions ATSVD up to 3.4.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Esqueceu a senha. The manipulation of the argument txtCPF leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.4.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52968 | MariaDB Server 10.4 before 10.4.33, 10.5 before 10.5.24, 10.6 before 10.6.17, 10.7 through 10.11 before 10.11.7, 11.0 before 11.0.5, and 11....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52968</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.4 before 10.4.33, 10.5 before 10.5.24, 10.6 before 10.6.17, 10.7 through 10.11 before 10.11.7, 11.0 before 11.0.5, and 11.1 before 11.1.4 calls fix_fields_if_needed under mysql_derived_prepare when derived is not yet prepared, leading to a find_field_in_table crash.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52969 | MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, and 11.0 through 11.0.* can sometimes crash with an empty bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52969</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, and 11.0 through 11.0.* can sometimes crash with an empty backtrace log. This may be related to make_aggr_tables_info and optimize_stage2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52970 | MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, 11.0 through 11.0.*, and 11.1 through 11.4.* crashes in Item_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52970</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, 11.0 through 11.0.*, and 11.1 through 11.4.* crashes in Item_direct_view_ref::derived_field_transformer_for_where.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52971 | MariaDB Server 10.10 through 10.11.* and 11.0 through 11.4.* crashes in JOIN::fix_all_splittings_in_plan.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52971</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.10 through 10.11.* and 11.0 through 11.4.* crashes in JOIN::fix_all_splittings_in_plan.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2112 | user-xiangpeng yaoqishan MediaInfoService.java getMediaLisByFilter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2112</link><description>A vulnerability was found in user-xiangpeng yaoqishan up to a47fec4a31cbd13698c592dfdc938c8824dd25e4. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getMediaLisByFilter of the file cn/javaex/yaoqishan/service/media_info/MediaInfoService.java. The manipulation of the argument typeId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 21:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27840 | Espressif ESP32 chips allow 29 hidden HCI commands, such as 0xFC02 (Write memory).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27840</link><description>Espressif ESP32 chips allow 29 hidden HCI commands, such as 0xFC02 (Write memory).</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 19:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10326 | RomethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Missing Authorization in save_options and reset_widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10326</link><description>The RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_options and reset_widgets functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify plugin settings or reset plugin widgets to their default state (all enabled). NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 12:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13924 | Starter Templates by FancyWP &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13924</link><description>The Starter Templates by FancyWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 via the 'http_request_host_is_external' filter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 12:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11640 | VikRentCar Car Rental Management System &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11640</link><description>The VikRentCar Car Rental Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change plugin access privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Successful exploitation allows attackers with subscriber-level privileges and above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13649 | 140+ Widgets | Xpro Addons For Elementor – FREE &amp;lt;= 1.4.6.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13649</link><description>The 140+ Widgets | Xpro Addons For Elementor – FREE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13675 | SlingBlocks – Gutenberg Blocks by FunnelKit (Formerly WooFunnels) &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13675</link><description>The SlingBlocks – Gutenberg Blocks by FunnelKit (Formerly WooFunnels) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the "Icon List" Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1664 | Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1664</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Parallax slider in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13359 | Product Input Fields for WooCommerce  &amp;lt;= 1.12.1 - Unauthenticated Limited File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13359</link><description>The Product Input Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the add_product_input_fields_to_order_item_meta() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.1. This may make it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Please note that by default the plugin is only vulnerable to a double extension file upload attack, unless an administrators leaves the accepted file extensions field blank which can make .php file uploads possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1322 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1322</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10 via the 'feed' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1323 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1323</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'databeat' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1324 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1324</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'public-form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1325 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Exeuction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1325</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution due to a missing capability check on the 'rcl_preview_post' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1783 | Gallery Styles &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1783</link><description>The Gallery Styles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Gallery Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10321 | All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10321</link><description>The All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 in elements/advanced-tab/template/view.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13816 | Aiomatic - AI Content Writer, Editor, ChatBot &amp;amp; AI Toolkit &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Multiple Administrator Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13816</link><description>The Aiomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer &amp; Editor, GPT-3 &amp; GPT-4, ChatGPT ChatBot &amp; AI Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability checks on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update and delete posts, list and delete batches, list assistant uploaded files, delete personas, delete forms, delete templates, and clear logs. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13882 | Aiomatic - AI Content Writer, Editor, ChatBot &amp;amp; AI Toolkit &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13882</link><description>The Aiomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer &amp; Editor, GPT-3 &amp; GPT-4, ChatGPT ChatBot &amp; AI Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'aiomatic_generate_featured_image' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0177 | Javo Core &amp;lt;= 3.0.0.080 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation in ajax_signup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0177</link><description>The Javo Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0.080. This is due to the plugin allowing users who are registering new accounts to set their own role. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain elevated privileges by creating an account with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1287 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1287</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown, Syntax Highlighter, and Page Scroll widgets in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11087 | miniOrange Social Login and Register (Discord, Google, Twitter, LinkedIn) Pro Addon &amp;lt;= 200.3.9 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11087</link><description>The miniOrange Social Login and Register (Discord, Google, Twitter, LinkedIn) Pro Addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 200.3.9. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 07:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13908 | SMTP by BestWebSoft &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13908</link><description>The SMTP by BestWebSoft plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'save_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 07:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13825 | Email Keep &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13825</link><description>The Email Keep WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 06:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13826 | Email Keep &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Email Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13826</link><description>The Email Keep WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 06:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12114 | FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp;amp; Carousel &amp;lt;= 2.4.29 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Custom+) Arbitrary Post/Page Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12114</link><description>The FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp; Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.29 via the foogallery_attachment_modal_save AJAX action due to missing validation on a user controlled key (img_id). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with granted access and above, to update arbitrary post and page content. This requires the Gallery Creator Role setting to be a value lower than 'Editor' for there to be any real impact.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12119 | FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp;amp; Carousel &amp;lt;= 2.4.29 - Authenticated (Custom+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Album Title Size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12119</link><description>The FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp; Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the default_gallery_title_size parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with granted gallery and album creator roles, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13844 | Post SMTP &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via columns Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13844</link><description>The Post SMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the ‘columns’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 05:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13640 | Print Invoice &amp;amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.4.1 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13640</link><description>The Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.1 via the 'wcdn/invoice' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/wcdn/invoice directory which can contain invoice files if an email attachment setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 04:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12460 | Years Since – Timeless &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12460</link><description>The Years Since – Timeless Texts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'years-since' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13774 | Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer &amp;lt;= 3.1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Cross-Site Scriping via Wishlist Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13774</link><description>The Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_to_multiple_wishlist' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13835 | Post Meta Data Manager &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authentciated (Admin+) Multisite Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13835</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to multisite privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying the existence of a multisite installation prior to allowing user meta to be added/modified. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to gain elevated privileges on subsites that would otherwise be inaccessible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13890 | Allow PHP Execute &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13890</link><description>The Allow PHP Execute plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to allowing PHP code to be entered by all users for whom unfiltered HTML is allowed. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject PHP code into posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13895 | Code Snippets CPT &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13895</link><description>The The Code Snippets CPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1481 | Shortcode Cleaner Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1481</link><description>The Shortcode Cleaner Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the download_backup() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to export arbitrary options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1504 | Post Lockdown &amp;lt;= 4.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1504</link><description>The Post Lockdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.2 via the 'pl_autocomplete' AJAX action due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1261 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1261</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability exists due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-3307.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27839 | operations/attestation/AttestationTask.kt in the Tangem SDK before 5.18.3 for Android has a logic flow in offline wallet attestation (genuin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27839</link><description>operations/attestation/AttestationTask.kt in the Tangem SDK before 5.18.3 for Android has a logic flow in offline wallet attestation (genuineness check) that causes verification results to be disregarded during the first scan of a card. Exploitation may not have been possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2097 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setRptWizardCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2097</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1800T 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. This issue affects the function setRptWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument loginpass leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2095 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setDmzCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2095</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK EX1800T 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. This affects the function setDmzCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2096 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setRebootScheCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2096</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK EX1800T 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. This vulnerability affects the function setRebootScheCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument mode/week/minute/recHour leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27822 | An issue was discovered in the Masquerade module before 1.x-1.0.1 for Backdrop CMS. It allows people to temporarily switch to another user a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27822</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Masquerade module before 1.x-1.0.1 for Backdrop CMS. It allows people to temporarily switch to another user account. The module provides a "Masquerade as admin" permission to restrict people (who can masquerade) from switching to an account with administrative privileges. This permission is not always honored and may allow non-administrative users to masquerade as an administrator. This vulnerability is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have a role with the "Masquerade as user" permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27823 | An issue was discovered in the Mail Disguise module before 1.x-1.0.5 for Backdrop CMS. It enables a website to obfuscate email addresses, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27823</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Mail Disguise module before 1.x-1.0.5 for Backdrop CMS. It enables a website to obfuscate email addresses, and should prevent spambots from collecting them. The module doesn't sufficiently validate the data attribute value on links, potentially leading to a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This is mitigated by the fact an attacker must be able to insert link (&lt;a&gt;) HTML elements containing data attributes into the page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27824 | An XSS issue was discovered in the Link iframe formatter module before 1.x-1.1.1 for Backdrop CMS. It doesn't sufficiently sanitize input be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27824</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in the Link iframe formatter module before 1.x-1.1.1 for Backdrop CMS. It doesn't sufficiently sanitize input before displaying results to the screen. This vulnerability is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have the ability to create content containing an iFrame field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27825 | An XSS issue was discovered in the Bootstrap 5 Lite theme before 1.x-1.0.3 for Backdrop CMS. It doesn't sufficiently sanitize certain class ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27825</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in the Bootstrap 5 Lite theme before 1.x-1.0.3 for Backdrop CMS. It doesn't sufficiently sanitize certain class names.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27826 | An XSS issue was discovered in the Bootstrap Lite theme before 1.x-1.4.5 for Backdrop CMS. It doesn't sufficiently sanitize certain class na...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27826</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in the Bootstrap Lite theme before 1.x-1.4.5 for Backdrop CMS. It doesn't sufficiently sanitize certain class names.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2093 | PHPGurukul Online Library Management System change-password.php password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2093</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Library Management System 3.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /change-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email/phone number leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2094 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setWiFiExtenderConfig os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2094</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1800T 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWiFiExtenderConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument apcliKey/key leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42733 | An issue in Docmosis Tornado v.2.9.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the UNC path inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42733</link><description>An issue in Docmosis Tornado v.2.9.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the UNC path input</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2024 | Trimble SketchUp SKP File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2024</link><description>Trimble SketchUp SKP File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trimble SketchUp. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25210.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26643 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26643</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43052 | IBM Control Center external service interaction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43052</link><description>IBM Control Center 6.2.1 through 6.3.1 is vulnerable to an external service interaction attack, caused by improper validation of user-supplied input. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to induce the application to perform server-side DNS lookups or HTTP requests to arbitrary domain names. By submitting suitable payloads, an attacker can cause the application server to attack other systems that it can interact with.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35894 | IBM Control Center HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35894</link><description>IBM Control Center 6.2.1 through 6.3.1 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers. This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12975 | Silicon Labs CPC can leak information in full duplex SPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12975</link><description>A buffer overread can occur in the CPC application when operating in full duplex SPI upon receiving an invalid packet over the SPI interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0162 | IBM Aspera Shares XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0162</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.9.9 through 1.10.0 PL7 is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13086 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13086</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability has been reported to affect product. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QTS 5.2.0.2851 build 20240808 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.0.2851 build 20240808 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38638 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38638</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to modify or corrupt memory.

QTS 5.2.x/QuTS hero h5.2.x are not affected.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.9.2954 build 20241120 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48864 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48864</link><description>A files or directories accessible to external parties vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to read/write files or directories.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4741 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50390 | QHora</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50390</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QHora. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuRouter 2.4.5.032 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50394 | Helpdesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50394</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect Helpdesk. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Helpdesk 3.3.3 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50405 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50405</link><description>An improper neutralization of CRLF sequences ('CRLF Injection') vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to modify application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53692 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53692</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53693 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53693</link><description>An improper neutralization of CRLF sequences ('CRLF Injection') vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to modify application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53694 | QVPN Device Client, Qsync, Qfinder Pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53694</link><description>A time-of-check time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition vulnerability has been reported to affect several product versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local attackers who have gained user access to gain access to otherwise unauthorized resources.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QVPN Device Client for Mac 2.2.5 and later
Qsync for Mac 5.1.3 and later
Qfinder Pro Mac 7.11.1 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53695 | HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53695</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been reported to affect HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to modify memory or crash processes.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync 25.1.4.952 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53696 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53696</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been reported to affect QuLog Center. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuLog Center 1.7.0.829 ( 2024/10/01 ) and later
QuLog Center 1.8.0.888 ( 2024/10/15 ) and later
QTS 4.5.4.2957 build 20241119 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2956 build 20241119 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53697 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53697</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to modify or corrupt memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53698 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53698</link><description>A double free vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to modify memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53699 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53699</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to modify or corrupt memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.3.3006 build 20250108 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53700 | QHora</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53700</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QHora. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuRouter 2.4.6.028 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27604 | XWiki Confluence Migrator Pro&amp;#x27;s homepage is public</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27604</link><description>XWiki Confluence Migrator Pro helps admins to import confluence packages into their XWiki instance. The homepage of the application is public which enables a guest to download the package which might contain sensitive information. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27607 | Python JSON Logger has a Potential RCE via missing `msgspec-python313-pre` dependency</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27607</link><description>Python JSON Logger is a JSON Formatter for Python Logging. Between 30 December 2024 and 4 March 2025 Python JSON Logger was vulnerable to RCE through a missing dependency. This occurred because msgspec-python313-pre was deleted by the owner leaving the name open to being claimed by a third party. If the package was claimed, it would allow them RCE on any Python JSON Logger user who installed the development dependencies on Python 3.13 (e.g. pip install python-json-logger[dev]). This issue has been resolved with 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27603 | XWiki Confluence Migrator Pro allows Remote Code Execution via unescaped translations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27603</link><description>XWiki Confluence Migrator Pro helps admins to import confluence packages into their XWiki instance. A user that doesn't have programming rights can execute arbitrary code due to an unescaped translation when creating a page using the Migration Page template. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27597 | Vue I18n Prototype Pollution in `handleFlatJson`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27597</link><description>Vue I18n is the internationalization plugin for Vue.js. @intlify/message-resolver and @intlify/vue-i18n-core are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution through the entry function: handleFlatJson. An attacker can supply a payload with Object.prototype setter to introduce or modify properties within the global prototype chain, causing denial of service (DoS) a the minimum consequence. Moreover, the consequences of this vulnerability can escalate to other injection-based attacks, depending on how the library integrates within the application. For instance, if the polluted property propagates to sensitive Node.js APIs (e.g., exec, eval), it could enable an attacker to execute arbitrary commands within the application's context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25617 | Incorrect Access Control in Unifiedtransform 2.X leads to Privilege Escalation allowing teachers to create syllabus.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25617</link><description>Incorrect Access Control in Unifiedtransform 2.X leads to Privilege Escalation allowing teachers to create syllabus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27518 | Cognita CORS misconfiguration in backend API server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27518</link><description>Cognita is a RAG (Retrieval Augmented Generation) Framework for building modular, open source applications for production by TrueFoundry. An insecure CORS configuration in the Cognita backend server allows arbitrary websites to send cross site requests to the application. This vulnerability is fixed in commit 75079c3d3cf376381489b9a82ee46c69024e1a15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27519 | Cognita Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27519</link><description>Cognita is a RAG (Retrieval Augmented Generation) Framework for building modular, open source applications for production by TrueFoundry. A path traversal issue exists at /v1/internal/upload-to-local-directory which is enabled when the Local env variable is set to true, such as when Cognita is setup using Docker. Because the docker environment sets up the backend uvicorn server with auto reload enabled, when an attacker overwrites the /app/backend/__init__.py file, the file will automatically be reloaded and executed. This allows an attacker to get remote code execution in the context of the Docker container. This vulnerability is fixed in commit a78bd065e05a1b30a53a3386cc02e08c317d2243.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27152 | Possible SSRF and Credential Leakage via Absolute URL in axios Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27152</link><description>axios is a promise based HTTP client for the browser and node.js. The issue occurs when passing absolute URLs rather than protocol-relative URLs to axios. Even if ⁠baseURL is set, axios sends the request to the specified absolute URL, potentially causing SSRF and credential leakage. This issue impacts both server-side and client-side usage of axios. This issue is fixed in 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2089 | StarSea99 starsea-mall com.siro.mall.controller.mall.UserController updateInfo updateUserInfo access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2089</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in StarSea99 starsea-mall 1.0/2.X and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function updateUserInfo of the file /personal/updateInfo of the component com.siro.mall.controller.mall.UserController. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2090 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System Sub Admin add-subadmin.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2090</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-subadmin.php of the component Sub Admin Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2088 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2088</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/emailid/mobileNumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2086 | StarSea99 starsea-mall update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2086</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in StarSea99 starsea-mall 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/indexConfigs/update. The manipulation of the argument redirectUrl leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2087 | StarSea99 starsea-mall update cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2087</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in StarSea99 starsea-mall 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/goods/update. The manipulation of the argument goodsName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2084 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System Search Report Page search-report.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2084</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-report.php of the component Search Report Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2085 | StarSea99 starsea-mall save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2085</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in StarSea99 starsea-mall 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/carousels/save. The manipulation of the argument redirectUrl leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12634 | Related Posts, Inline Related Posts, Contextual Related Posts, Related Content By PickPlugins &amp;lt;= 2.0.59 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12634</link><description>The Related Posts, Inline Related Posts, Contextual Related Posts, Related Content By PickPlugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including 2.0.59. This is due to missing nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1768 | SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO &amp;lt;= 12.4.05 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via search Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1768</link><description>The SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the 'search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 12.4.05 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1886 | Pass-Back vulnerability in Sage 200 Spain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1886</link><description>Pass-Back vulnerability in versions prior to 2025.35.000 of Sage 200 Spain. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to discover stored SMTP credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1887 | SMB forced authentication vulnerability in Sage 200 Spain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1887</link><description>SMB forced authentication vulnerability in versions prior to 2025.35.000 of Sage 200 Spain. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to obtain NTLMv2-SSP Hash by changing any of the paths to a UNC path pointing to a server controlled by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13668 | WordPress Activity O Meter &amp;lt;= 1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13668</link><description>The WordPress Activity O Meter WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9458 | Reservit Hotel &amp;lt; 3.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9458</link><description>The Reservit Hotel WordPress plugin does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13552 | SupportCandy – Helpdesk &amp;amp; Customer Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13552</link><description>The SupportCandy – Helpdesk &amp; Customer Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0 via file upload due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to download attachments for support tickets that don't belong to them. If an admin enables tickets for guests, this can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13635 | VK Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.94.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13635</link><description>The VK Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.94.2.2 via the page content block. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the content of private posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13805 | Advanced File Manager &amp;lt;= 5.2.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13805</link><description>The Advanced File Manager — Ultimate WordPress File Manager and Document Library Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, and granted permissions by an Administrator, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13857 | WPGet API &amp;lt;= 2.2.10 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13857</link><description>The WPGet API – Connect to any external REST API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21835 | usb: gadget: f_midi: fix MIDI Streaming descriptor lengths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21835</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: gadget: f_midi: fix MIDI Streaming descriptor lengths

While the MIDI jacks are configured correctly, and the MIDIStreaming
endpoint descriptors are filled with the correct information,
bNumEmbMIDIJack and bLength are set incorrectly in these descriptors.

This does not matter when the numbers of in and out ports are equal, but
when they differ the host will receive broken descriptors with
uninitialized stack memory leaking into the descriptor for whichever
value is smaller.

The precise meaning of "in" and "out" in the port counts is not clearly
defined and can be confusing.  But elsewhere the driver consistently
uses this to match the USB meaning of IN and OUT viewed from the host,
so that "in" ports send data to the host and "out" ports receive data
from it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21836 | io_uring/kbuf: reallocate buf lists on upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21836</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/kbuf: reallocate buf lists on upgrade

IORING_REGISTER_PBUF_RING can reuse an old struct io_buffer_list if it
was created for legacy selected buffer and has been emptied. It violates
the requirement that most of the field should stay stable after publish.
Always reallocate it instead.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21837 | io_uring/uring_cmd: unconditionally copy SQEs at prep time</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21837</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring/uring_cmd: unconditionally copy SQEs at prep time

This isn't generally necessary, but conditions have been observed where
SQE data is accessed from the original SQE after prep has been done and
outside of the initial issue. Opcode prep handlers must ensure that any
SQE related data is stable beyond the prep phase, but uring_cmd is a bit
special in how it handles the SQE which makes it susceptible to reading
stale data. If the application has reused the SQE before the original
completes, then that can lead to data corruption.

Down the line we can relax this again once uring_cmd has been sanitized
a bit, and avoid unnecessarily copying the SQE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21838 | usb: gadget: core: flush gadget workqueue after device removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21838</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: gadget: core: flush gadget workqueue after device removal

device_del() can lead to new work being scheduled in gadget-&gt;work
workqueue. This is observed, for example, with the dwc3 driver with the
following call stack:
  device_del()
    gadget_unbind_driver()
      usb_gadget_disconnect_locked()
        dwc3_gadget_pullup()
	  dwc3_gadget_soft_disconnect()
	    usb_gadget_set_state()
	      schedule_work(&amp;amp;gadget-&gt;work)

Move flush_work() after device_del() to ensure the workqueue is cleaned
up.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21839 | KVM: x86: Load DR6 with guest value only before entering .vcpu_run() loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21839</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: x86: Load DR6 with guest value only before entering .vcpu_run() loop

Move the conditional loading of hardware DR6 with the guest's DR6 value
out of the core .vcpu_run() loop to fix a bug where KVM can load hardware
with a stale vcpu-&gt;arch.dr6.

When the guest accesses a DR and host userspace isn't debugging the guest,
KVM disables DR interception and loads the guest's values into hardware on
VM-Enter and saves them on VM-Exit.  This allows the guest to access DRs
at will, e.g. so that a sequence of DR accesses to configure a breakpoint
only generates one VM-Exit.

For DR0-DR3, the logic/behavior is identical between VMX and SVM, and also
identical between KVM_DEBUGREG_BP_ENABLED (userspace debugging the guest)
and KVM_DEBUGREG_WONT_EXIT (guest using DRs), and so KVM handles loading
DR0-DR3 in common code, _outside_ of the core kvm_x86_ops.vcpu_run() loop.

But for DR6, the guest's value doesn't need to be loaded into hardware for
KVM_DEBUGREG_BP_ENABLED, and SVM provides a dedicated VMCB field whereas
VMX requires software to manually load the guest value, and so loading the
guest's value into DR6 is handled by {svm,vmx}_vcpu_run(), i.e. is done
_inside_ the core run loop.

Unfortunately, saving the guest values on VM-Exit is initiated by common
x86, again outside of the core run loop.  If the guest modifies DR6 (in
hardware, when DR interception is disabled), and then the next VM-Exit is
a fastpath VM-Exit, KVM will reload hardware DR6 with vcpu-&gt;arch.dr6 and
clobber the guest's actual value.

The bug shows up primarily with nested VMX because KVM handles the VMX
preemption timer in the fastpath, and the window between hardware DR6
being modified (in guest context) and DR6 being read by guest software is
orders of magnitude larger in a nested setup.  E.g. in non-nested, the
VMX preemption timer would need to fire precisely between #DB injection
and the #DB handler's read of DR6, whereas with a KVM-on-KVM setup, the
window where hardware DR6 is "dirty" extends all the way from L1 writing
DR6 to VMRESUME (in L1).

    L1's view:
    ==========
    
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640961: kvm_entry: vcpu 0
 A:  L1 Writes DR6
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640963: : Set DRs, DR6 = 0xffff0ff1

 B:        CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640967: kvm_exit: vcpu 0 reason EXTERNAL_INTERRUPT intr_info 0x800000ec

 D: L1 reads DR6, arch.dr6 = 0
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640969: : Sync DRs, DR6 = 0xffff0ff0

           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640976: kvm_entry: vcpu 0
    L2 reads DR6, L1 disables DR interception
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640980: kvm_exit: vcpu 0 reason DR_ACCESS info1 0x0000000000000216
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640983: kvm_entry: vcpu 0

           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640983: : Set DRs, DR6 = 0xffff0ff0

    L2 detects failure
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640987: kvm_exit: vcpu 0 reason HLT
    L1 reads DR6 (confirms failure)
           CPU 0/KVM-7289    [023] d....  2925.640990: : Sync DRs, DR6 = 0xffff0ff0

    L0's view:
    ==========
    L2 reads DR6, arch.dr6 = 0
          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] d....  3410.005610: kvm_exit: vcpu 23 reason DR_ACCESS info1 0x0000000000000216
          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] .....  3410.005610: kvm_nested_vmexit: vcpu 23 reason DR_ACCESS info1 0x0000000000000216

    L2 =&gt; L1 nested VM-Exit
          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] .....  3410.005610: kvm_nested_vmexit_inject: reason: DR_ACCESS ext_inf1: 0x0000000000000216

          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] d....  3410.005610: kvm_entry: vcpu 23
          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] d....  3410.005611: kvm_exit: vcpu 23 reason VMREAD
          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] d....  3410.005611: kvm_entry: vcpu 23
          CPU 23/KVM-5046    [001] d....  3410.
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21840 | thermal/netlink: Prevent userspace segmentation fault by adjusting UAPI header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21840</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

thermal/netlink: Prevent userspace segmentation fault by adjusting UAPI header

The intel-lpmd tool [1], which uses the THERMAL_GENL_ATTR_CPU_CAPABILITY
attribute to receive HFI events from kernel space, encounters a
segmentation fault after commit 1773572863c4 ("thermal: netlink: Add the
commands and the events for the thresholds").

The issue arises because the THERMAL_GENL_ATTR_CPU_CAPABILITY raw value
was changed while intel_lpmd still uses the old value.

Although intel_lpmd can be updated to check the THERMAL_GENL_VERSION and
use the appropriate THERMAL_GENL_ATTR_CPU_CAPABILITY value, the commit
itself is questionable.

The commit introduced a new element in the middle of enum thermal_genl_attr,
which affects many existing attributes and introduces potential risks
and unnecessary maintenance burdens for userspace thermal netlink event
users.

Solve the issue by moving the newly introduced
THERMAL_GENL_ATTR_TZ_PREV_TEMP attribute to the end of the
enum thermal_genl_attr. This ensures that all existing thermal generic
netlink attributes remain unaffected.

[ rjw: Subject edits ]</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21841 | cpufreq/amd-pstate: Fix cpufreq_policy ref counting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21841</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cpufreq/amd-pstate: Fix cpufreq_policy ref counting

amd_pstate_update_limits() takes a cpufreq_policy reference but doesn't
decrement the refcount in one of the exit paths, fix that.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21842 | amdkfd: properly free gang_ctx_bo when failed to init user queue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21842</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

amdkfd: properly free gang_ctx_bo when failed to init user queue

The destructor of a gtt bo is declared as
void amdgpu_amdkfd_free_gtt_mem(struct amdgpu_device *adev, void **mem_obj);
Which takes void** as the second parameter.

GCC allows passing void* to the function because void* can be implicitly
casted to any other types, so it can pass compiling.

However, passing this void* parameter into the function's
execution process(which expects void** and dereferencing void**)
will result in errors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21843 | drm/panthor: avoid garbage value in panthor_ioctl_dev_query()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21843</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/panthor: avoid garbage value in panthor_ioctl_dev_query()

'priorities_info' is uninitialized, and the uninitialized value is copied
to user object when calling PANTHOR_UOBJ_SET(). Using memset to initialize
'priorities_info' to avoid this garbage value problem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10804 | Ultimate Video Player &amp;lt;= 10.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10804</link><description>The Ultimate Video Player WordPress &amp; WooCommerce Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 10.0 via the content/downloader.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12035 | CS Framework &amp;lt;= 7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12035</link><description>The CS Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the cs_widget_file_delete() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12036 | CS Framework &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12036</link><description>The CS Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 6.9 via the get_widget_settings_json() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12607 | School Management System for Wordpress &amp;lt;= 92.0.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;mj_smgt_show_event_task&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12607</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the 'mj_smgt_show_event_task' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 92.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12609 | School Management System for Wordpress &amp;lt;= 92.0.0 - Authenticated (Student+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;view-attendance&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12609</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'view-attendance' page in all versions up to, and including, 92.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query in the mj_smgt_view_student_attendance() function.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Student-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12610 | School Management System for Wordpress &amp;lt;= 93.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12610</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mj_smgt_remove_feetype' and 'mj_smgt_remove_category_new' AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 93.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12611 | School Management System for Wordpress &amp;lt;= 93.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12611</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 93.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12876 | Golo - Directory &amp;amp; Listing, Travel WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation via Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12876</link><description>The Golo - City Travel Guide WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.10. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13431 | Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13431</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the accent_color and background parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13781 | Hero Maps Premium - Customizable Google Maps Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13781</link><description>The Hero Maps Premium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13904 | Platform.ly for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Unauthenticated Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13904</link><description>The Platform.ly for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 via the 'hooks' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9658 | School Management System for Wordpress &amp;lt;= 93.0.0 - Authenticated (Student+) Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9658</link><description>The School Management System for Wordpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 93.0.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email and password through the mj_smgt_update_user() and mj_smgt_add_admission() functions, along with a local file inclusion vulnerability. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with student-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses and passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account. This was escalated four months ago after no response to our initial outreach, yet it still vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0959 | Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.9.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via reg_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0959</link><description>The Eventer - WordPress Event &amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the reg_id parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1315 | InWave Jobs &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1315</link><description>The InWave Jobs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via password reset in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26331 | Dell ThinOS 2411 and prior, contains an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26331</link><description>Dell ThinOS 2411 and prior, contains an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12837 | GPU DDK - Exploitable kernel double free on apsFenceSyncCheckpoints allocated with arbitrary size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12837</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to corrupt kernel heap memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 07:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27816 | A vulnerability was discovered in the Arctera InfoScale 7.0 through 8.0.2 where a .NET remoting endpoint can be exploited due to the insecur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27816</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the Arctera InfoScale 7.0 through 8.0.2 where a .NET remoting endpoint can be exploited due to the insecure deserialization of potentially untrusted messages. The vulnerability is present in the Windows Plugin_Host service, which runs on all the servers where InfoScale is installed. The service is used only when applications are configured for Disaster Recovery (DR) using the DR wizard. Disabling the Plugin_Host service manually will eliminate the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 07:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12576 | GPU DDK - Untrusted app can crash firmware by forcing MCU access to non-aligned address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12576</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger a crash of the FW running on the GPU freezing graphics output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13906 | Gallery by BestWebSoft – Customizable Image and Photo Galleries for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.7.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13906</link><description>The Gallery by BestWebSoft – Customizable Image and Photo Galleries for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.3 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'import_gallery_from_csv' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 07:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0863 | Flexmls® IDX &amp;lt;= 3.14.27 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0863</link><description>The Flexmls® IDX Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idx_frame' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 07:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1309 | UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.04 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1309</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the uip_save_form_as_option() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.04. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 07:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12809 | Wishlist &amp;lt;= 1.0.43 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12809</link><description>The Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wishlist_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.43 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 06:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13320 | CURCY - WooCommerce Multi Currency - Currency Switcher &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13320</link><description>The CURCY - WooCommerce Multi Currency - Currency Switcher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'wc_filter_price_meta[where]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13655 | Flex Mag - Responsive WordPress News Theme &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Option Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13655</link><description>The Flex Mag - Responsive WordPress News Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the propanel_of_ajax_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary option values on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to delete an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1475 | WPCOM Member &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Authentication Bypass via &amp;#x27;user_phone&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1475</link><description>The WPCOM Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5. This is due to insufficient verification on the 'user_phone' parameter when logging in. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if SMS login is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27795 | JXL in GraphicsMagick before 1.3.46 lacks image dimension resource limits.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27795</link><description>JXL in GraphicsMagick before 1.3.46 lacks image dimension resource limits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 05:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27796 | WPG in GraphicsMagick before 1.3.46 mishandles palette buffer allocation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27796</link><description>WPG in GraphicsMagick before 1.3.46 mishandles palette buffer allocation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 05:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2066 | projectworlds Life Insurance Management System updateAgent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2066</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /updateAgent.php. The manipulation of the argument agent_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 04:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2067 | projectworlds Life Insurance Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2067</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument key leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2064 | projectworlds Life Insurance Management System deletePayment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2064</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /deletePayment.php. The manipulation of the argument recipt_no leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 04:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2065 | projectworlds Life Insurance Management System editAgent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2065</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /editAgent.php. The manipulation of the argument agent_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 04:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2062 | projectworlds Life Insurance Management System clientStatus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2062</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /clientStatus.php. The manipulation of the argument client_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2063 | projectworlds Life Insurance Management System deleteNominee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2063</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /deleteNominee.php. The manipulation of the argument nominee_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2061 | code-projects Online Ticket Reservation System passenger.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2061</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ticket Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /passenger.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26708 | ZTELink has a configuration defect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26708</link><description>There is a configuration defect vulnerability in ZTELink 5.4.9 for iOS. This vulnerability is caused by a flaw in the WiFi parameter configuration of the ZTELink. An attacker can obtain unauthorized access to the WiFi service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2060 | PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2060</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 03:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13526 | EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.0.7.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Event Attendees Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13526</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability checks on the export_submittion_attendees function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download list of attendees for any event.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0748 | Homey &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to User Verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0748</link><description>The Homey theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.4.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'homey_verify_user_manually' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update verify an user via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0749 | Homey &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Limited Authentication Bypass due to Missing Empty Value Check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0749</link><description>The Homey theme for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.4.3. This is due to the 'verification_id' value being set to empty, and the not empty check is missing in the dashboard user profile page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in to the first verified user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2058 | PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2058</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2059 | PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal booking-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2059</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/booking-details.php. The manipulation of the argument ambulanceregnum leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2054 | code-projects Blood Bank Management System edit_state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2054</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_state.php. The manipulation of the argument state_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2057 | PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal about-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2057</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Emergency Ambulance Hiring Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/about-us.php. The manipulation of the argument pagedes leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 02:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2053 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System visitor-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2053</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /visitor-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:04:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2051 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System search-visitor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2051</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search-visitor.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2052 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2052</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument contactno leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>