<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-46976 | TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 contains a command injection via the file_name parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46976</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 contains a command injection via the file_name parameter in the UploadFirmwareFile function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46977 | TOTOLINK LR1200GB V9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46977</link><description>TOTOLINK LR1200GB V9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the function loginAuth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25045 | WordPress RSVPMarker Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25045</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in David F. Carr RSVPMaker allows SQL Injection.This issue affects RSVPMaker: from n/a through 9.9.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5116 | The Live updates from Excel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ipushpull_page' shortcode in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5116</link><description>The Live updates from Excel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ipushpull_page' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-1203 | Improper file verification vulnerability in SaAT Netizen installer ver.1.2.0.424 and earlier, and SaAT Netizen ver.1.2.0.8 (Build427) and ea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1203</link><description>Improper file verification vulnerability in SaAT Netizen installer ver.1.2.0.424 and earlier, and SaAT Netizen ver.1.2.0.8 (Build427) and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to conduct a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful exploitation may result in a malicious file being downloaded and executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 12:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38994 | An issue in Univention UCS v.5.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain privileges via the check_univention_joinstatus f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38994</link><description>An issue in Univention UCS v.5.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain privileges via the check_univention_joinstatus function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5073 | The iframe forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iframe' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5073</link><description>The iframe forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'iframe' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5099 | The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5099</link><description>The HTML filter and csv-file search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 2.7 via the 'src' attribute of the 'csvsearch' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5114 | The idbbee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idbbee' shortcode in versions up to, and incl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5114</link><description>The idbbee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'idbbee' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3007 | Unauthorized Access Vulnerability in Syska SW100 Smartwatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3007</link><description>The vulnerability exists in Syska SW100 Smartwatch due to an improper implementation and/or configuration of Nordic Device Firmware Update (DFU) which is used for performing Over-The-Air (OTA) firmware updates on the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) devices. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by setting arbitrary values to handle on the vulnerable device over Bluetooth.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform firmware update, device reboot or data manipulation on the target device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40681 | WordPress Groundhogg Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.11.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40681</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Groundhogg Inc. Groundhogg plugin &lt;= 2.7.11.10 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46622 | WordPress WPPizza Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.18.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46622</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ollybach WPPizza – A Restaurant Plugin plugin &lt;= 3.18.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46313 | WordPress Zotpress Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46313</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Katie Seaborn Zotpress plugin &lt;= 7.3.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-2968 | LINE@ for Android version 1.0.0 and LINE@ for iOS version 1.0.0 are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-2968</link><description>LINE@ for Android version 1.0.0 and LINE@ for iOS version 1.0.0 are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allows non-SSL/TLS communications. As a result, any API may be invoked from a script injected by a MITM (man-in-the-middle) attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-0897 | LINE for Android version 5.0.2 and earlier and LINE for iOS version 5.0.0 and earlier are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack sinc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-0897</link><description>LINE for Android version 5.0.2 and earlier and LINE for iOS version 5.0.0 and earlier are vulnerable to MITM (man-in-the-middle) attack since the application allows non-SSL/TLS communications. As a result, any API may be invoked from a script injected by a MITM (man-in-the-middle) attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46312 | WordPress Smart Online Order for Clover Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46312</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Zaytech Smart Online Order for Clover plugin &lt;= 1.5.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5412 | The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5412</link><description>The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5428 | The Image vertical reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5428</link><description>The Image vertical reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5429 | The Information Reel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 10.0 d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5429</link><description>The Information Reel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 10.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5430 | The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5430</link><description>The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5431 | The Left right image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5431</link><description>The Left right image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5433 | The Message ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.2 due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5433</link><description>The Message ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5434 | The Superb slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5434</link><description>The Superb slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5435 | The Up down image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5435</link><description>The Up down image slideshow gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5436 | The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5436</link><description>The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5437 | The WP fade in text news plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5437</link><description>The WP fade in text news plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5438 | The wp image slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5438</link><description>The wp image slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5439 | The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5439</link><description>The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 8.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5464 | The Jquery accordion slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5464</link><description>The Jquery accordion slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 8.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5873 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in pimcore/pimcore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5873</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository pimcore/pimcore prior to 11.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46210 | WordPress WC Captcha Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46210</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WebCource WC Captcha plugin &lt;= 1.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46451 | Best Courier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the change username field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46451</link><description>Best Courier Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the change username field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46361 | Artifex Software jbig2dec v0.20 was discovered to contain a SEGV vulnerability via jbig2_error at /jbig2dec/jbig2.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46361</link><description>Artifex Software jbig2dec v0.20 was discovered to contain a SEGV vulnerability via jbig2_error at /jbig2dec/jbig2.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45996 | SQL injection vulnerability in Senayan Library Management Systems Slims v.9 and Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45996</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Senayan Library Management Systems Slims v.9 and Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the reborrowLimit parameter in the member_type.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43139 | An issue in franfinance before v.2.0.27 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation.php, and controllers/front/val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43139</link><description>An issue in franfinance before v.2.0.27 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the validation.php, and controllers/front/validation.php components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36263 | Prestashop opartlimitquantity 1.4.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection. OpartlimitquantityAlertlimitModuleFrontController::displayAja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36263</link><description>Prestashop opartlimitquantity 1.4.5 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection. OpartlimitquantityAlertlimitModuleFrontController::displayAjaxPushAlertMessage()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47174 | Thorn SFTP gateway 3.4.x before 3.4.4 uses Pivotal Spring Framework for Java deserialization of untrusted data, which is not supported by Pi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47174</link><description>Thorn SFTP gateway 3.4.x before 3.4.4 uses Pivotal Spring Framework for Java deserialization of untrusted data, which is not supported by Pivotal, a related issue to CVE-2016-1000027. Also, within the specific context of Thorn SFTP gateway, this leads to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46356 | In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) before 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `SearchA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46356</link><description>In the module "CSV Feeds PRO" (csvfeeds) before 2.6.1 from Bl Modules for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The method `SearchApiCsv::getProducts()` has sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27846 | SQL injection vulnerability found in PrestaShop themevolty v.4.0.8 and before allow a remote attacker to gain privileges via the tvcmsblog, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27846</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability found in PrestaShop themevolty v.4.0.8 and before allow a remote attacker to gain privileges via the tvcmsblog, tvcmsvideotab, tvcmswishlist, tvcmsbrandlist, tvcmscategorychainslider, tvcmscategoryproduct, tvcmscategoryslider, tvcmspaymenticon, tvcmstestimonial components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45378 | In the module "PrestaBlog" (prestablog) version 4.4.7 and before from HDclic for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45378</link><description>In the module "PrestaBlog" (prestablog) version 4.4.7 and before from HDclic for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection. The script ajax slider_positions.php has a sensitive SQL call that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-20110 | JHipster generator-jhipster before 2.23.0 allows a timing attack against validateToken due to a string comparison that stops at the first ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-20110</link><description>JHipster generator-jhipster before 2.23.0 allows a timing attack against validateToken due to a string comparison that stops at the first character that is different. Attackers can guess tokens by brute forcing one character at a time and observing the timing. This of course drastically reduces the search space to a linear amount of guesses based on the token length times the possible characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25155 | DOMPurify before 1.0.11 allows reverse tabnabbing in demos/hooks-target-blank-demo.html because links lack a 'rel="noopener noreferrer"' att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25155</link><description>DOMPurify before 1.0.11 allows reverse tabnabbing in demos/hooks-target-blank-demo.html because links lack a 'rel="noopener noreferrer"' attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45899 | An issue in the component SuperUserSetuserModuleFrontController:init() of idnovate superuser before v2.4.2 allows attackers to bypass authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45899</link><description>An issue in the component SuperUserSetuserModuleFrontController:init() of idnovate superuser before v2.4.2 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted HTTP call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31794 | MuPDF v1.21.1 was discovered to contain an infinite recursion in the component pdf_mark_list_push. This vulnerability allows attackers to ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31794</link><description>MuPDF v1.21.1 was discovered to contain an infinite recursion in the component pdf_mark_list_push. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46040 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in GetSimpleCMS v.3.4.0a allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the a crafted payload to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46040</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in GetSimpleCMS v.3.4.0a allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the a crafted payload to the components.php function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46139 | KernelSU signature validation mismatch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46139</link><description>KernelSU is a Kernel based root solution for Android. Starting in version 0.6.1 and prior to version 0.7.0, if a KernelSU installed device is infected with a malware whose app signing block specially constructed, it can take over root privileges on the device. The vulnerable verification logic actually obtains the signature of the last block with an id of `0x7109871a`, while the verification logic during Android installation is to obtain the first one. In addition to the actual signature upgrade that has been fixed (KSU thought it was V2 but was actually V3), there is also the problem of actual signature downgrading (KSU thought it was V2 but was actually V1). Find a condition in the signature verification logic that will cause the signature not to be found error, and KernelSU does not implement the same conditions, so KSU thinks there is a V2 signature, but the APK signature verification actually uses the V1 signature. This issue is fixed in version 0.7.0. As workarounds, keep the KernelSU manager installed and avoid installing unknown apps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5861 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in microweber/microweber</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5861</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository microweber/microweber prior to 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5862 | Missing Authorization in hamza417/inure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5862</link><description>Missing Authorization in GitHub repository hamza417/inure prior to Build95.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5863 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5863</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5864 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5864</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5865 | Insufficient Session Expiration in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5865</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5866 | Sensitive Cookie in HTTPS Session Without &amp;#x27;Secure&amp;#x27; Attribute in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5866</link><description>Sensitive Cookie in HTTPS Session Without 'Secure' Attribute in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5867 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in thorsten/phpmyfaq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5867</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository thorsten/phpmyfaq prior to 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46138 | JumpServer default admin user email leak password reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46138</link><description>JumpServer is an open source bastion host and maintenance security audit system that complies with 4A specifications. Prior to version 3.8.0, the default email for initial user admin is `admin[@]mycompany[.]com`, and users reset their passwords by sending an email. Currently, the domain `mycompany.com` has not been registered. However, if it is registered in the future, it may affect the password reset functionality. This issue has been patched in version 3.8.0 by changing the default email domain to `example.com`. Those who cannot upgrade may change the default email domain to `example.com` manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:02:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46129 | xkeys Seal encryption used fixed key for all encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46129</link><description>NATS.io is a high performance open source pub-sub distributed communication technology, built for the cloud, on-premise, IoT, and edge computing. The cryptographic key handling library, nkeys, recently gained support for encryption, not just for signing/authentication. This is used in nats-server 2.10 (Sep 2023) and newer for authentication callouts. In nkeys versions 0.4.0 through 0.4.5, corresponding with NATS server versions 2.10.0 through 2.10.3, the nkeys library's `xkeys` encryption handling logic mistakenly passed an array by value into an internal function, where the function mutated that buffer to populate the encryption key to use. As a result, all encryption was actually to an all-zeros key. This affects encryption only, not signing.  
FIXME: FILL IN IMPACT ON NATS-SERVER AUTH CALLOUT SECURITY. nkeys Go library 0.4.6, corresponding with NATS Server 2.10.4, has a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available. For any application handling auth callouts in Go, if using the nkeys library, update the dependency, recompile and deploy that in lockstep.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 23:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45672 | Frigate unsafe deserialization in `load_config_with_no_duplicates` of `frigate/util/builtin.py`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45672</link><description>Frigate is an open source network video recorder. Prior to version 0.13.0 Beta 3, an unsafe deserialization vulnerability was identified in the endpoints used to save configurations for Frigate. This can lead to unauthenticated remote code execution. This can be performed through the UI at `/config` or through a direct call to `/api/config/save`. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to both know very specific information about a user's Frigate server and requires an authenticated user to be tricked into clicking a specially crafted link to their Frigate instance. This vulnerability could exploited by an attacker under the following circumstances: Frigate publicly exposed to the internet (even with authentication); attacker knows the address of a user's Frigate instance; attacker crafts a specialized page which links to the user's Frigate instance; attacker finds a way to get an authenticated user to visit their specialized page and click the button/link. Input is initially accepted through `http.py`. The user-provided input is then parsed and loaded by `load_config_with_no_duplicates`. However, `load_config_with_no_duplicates` does not sanitize this input by merit of using `yaml.loader.Loader` which can instantiate custom constructors. A provided payload will be executed directly at `frigate/util/builtin.py:110`. This issue may lead to pre-authenticated Remote Code Execution. Version 0.13.0 Beta 3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46502 | An issue in OpenCRX v.5.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46502</link><description>An issue in OpenCRX v.5.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45670 | Frigate cross-site request forgery in `config_save` and `config_set` request handlers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45670</link><description>Frigate is an open source network video recorder. Prior to version 0.13.0 Beta 3, the `config/save` and `config/set` endpoints of Frigate do not implement any CSRF protection. This makes it possible for a request sourced from another site to update the configuration of the Frigate server (e.g. via "drive-by" attack). Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to both know very specific information about a user's Frigate server and requires an authenticated user to be tricked into clicking a specially crafted link to their Frigate instance. This vulnerability could exploited by an attacker under the following circumstances: Frigate publicly exposed to the internet (even with authentication); attacker knows the address of a user's Frigate instance; attacker crafts a specialized page which links to the user's Frigate instance; attacker finds a way to get an authenticated user to visit their specialized page and click the button/link. This issue can lead to arbitrary configuration updates for the Frigate server, resulting in denial of service and possible data exfiltration. Version 0.13.0 Beta 3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45671 | Frigate reflected XSS through `/&amp;lt;camera_name&amp;gt;` API endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45671</link><description>Frigate is an open source network video recorder. Prior to version 0.13.0 Beta 3, there is a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in any API endpoints reliant on the `/&lt;camera_name&gt;` base path as values provided for the path are not sanitized. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to both know very specific information about a user's Frigate server and requires an authenticated user to be tricked into clicking a specially crafted link to their Frigate instance. This vulnerability could exploited by an attacker under the following circumstances: Frigate publicly exposed to the internet (even with authentication); attacker knows the address of a user's Frigate instance; attacker crafts a specialized page which links to the user's Frigate instance; attacker finds a way to get an authenticated user to visit their specialized page and click the button/link. As the reflected values included in the URL are not sanitized or escaped, this permits execution arbitrary Javascript payloads. Version 0.13.0 Beta 3 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43798 | BigBlueButton Blind SSRF When Uploading Presentation (mitigation bypass)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43798</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. BigBlueButton prior to versions 2.6.12 and 2.7.0-rc.1 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). This issue is a bypass of CVE-2023-33176. A patch in versions 2.6.12 and 2.7.0-rc.1 disabled follow redirect at `httpclient.execute` since the software no longer has to follow it when using `finalUrl`. There are no known workarounds. We recommend upgrading to a patched version of BigBlueButton.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44397 | CloudExplorer Lite permission bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44397</link><description>CloudExplorer Lite is an open source, lightweight cloud management platform. Prior to version 1.4.1, the gateway filter of CloudExplorer Lite uses a controller with path starting with `matching/API/`, which can cause a permission bypass. Version 1.4.1 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43797 | BigBlueButton Stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability at Guest Lobby</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43797</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. Prior to versions 2.6.11 and 2.7.0-beta.3, Guest Lobby was vulnerable to cross-site scripting when users wait to enter the meeting due to inserting unsanitized messages to the element using unsafe innerHTML. Text sanitizing was added for lobby messages starting in versions 2.6.11 and 2.7.0-beta.3. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46478 | An issue in minCal v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the customer_data parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46478</link><description>An issue in minCal v.1.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the customer_data parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 22:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42323 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DouHaocms v.3.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the adminAction.cl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42323</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DouHaocms v.3.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the adminAction.class.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-39172 | A stored XSS in the process overview (bersicht zugewiesener Vorgaenge) in mbsupport openVIVA c2 20220101 allows a remote, authenticated, low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39172</link><description>A stored XSS in the process overview (bersicht zugewiesener Vorgaenge) in mbsupport openVIVA c2 20220101 allows a remote, authenticated, low-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code in the victim's browser via name field of a process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45956 | An issue discovered in Govee LED Strip v3.00.42 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted Move and MoveWithOnoff commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45956</link><description>An issue discovered in Govee LED Strip v3.00.42 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted Move and MoveWithOnoff commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5349 | Draw while calling getdrawinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5349</link><description>A memory leak flaw was found in ruby-magick, an interface between Ruby and ImageMagick. This issue can lead to a denial of service (DOS) by memory exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43792 | baserCMS Code Injection Vulnerability in Mail Form Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43792</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. In versions 4.6.0 through 4.7.6, there is a Code Injection vulnerability in the mail form of baserCMS. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43648 | baserCMS Directory Traversal vulnerability in Form submission data management Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43648</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 4.8.0, there is a Directory Traversal Vulnerability in the form submission data management feature of baserCMS. Version 4.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43649 | baserCMS CSRF vulnerability in Content preview Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43649</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 4.8.0, there is a cross site request forgery vulnerability in the content preview feature of baserCMS. Version 4.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36767 | tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.8.0 allows shell metacharacters in titles, messages, and other input data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36767</link><description>tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.8.0 allows shell metacharacters in titles, messages, and other input data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42804 | BigBlueButton Path Traversal – Reading Certain File Extensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42804</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. BigBlueButton prior to version 2.6.0-beta.1 has a path traversal vulnerability that allows an attacker with a valid starting folder path, to traverse and read other files without authentication, assuming the files have certain extensions (txt, swf, svg, png). In version 2.6.0-beta.1, input validation was added on the parameters being passed and dangerous characters are stripped. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43647 | baserCMS Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in File upload Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43647</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Prior to version 4.8.0, there is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the file upload feature of baserCMS. Version 4.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47104 | tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.15.0 allows shell metacharacters (such as a backquote or a dollar sign) in titles, messages...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47104</link><description>tinyfiledialogs (aka tiny file dialogs) before 3.15.0 allows shell metacharacters (such as a backquote or a dollar sign) in titles, messages, and other input data. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-36767, which only considered single and double quote characters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42803 | BigBlueButton Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42803</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom. BigBlueButton prior to version 2.6.0-beta.2 is vulnerable to unrestricted file upload, where the insertDocument API call does not validate the given file extension before saving the file, and does not remove it in case of validation failures. BigBlueButton 2.6.0-beta.2 contains a patch. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41891 | FlyteAdmin SQL Injection in List Filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41891</link><description>FlyteAdmin is the control plane for Flyte responsible for managing entities and administering workflow executions. Prior to version 1.1.124, list endpoints on FlyteAdmin have a SQL vulnerability where a malicious user can send a REST request with custom SQL statements as list filters. The attacker needs to have access to the FlyteAdmin installation, typically either behind a VPN or authentication. Version 1.1.124 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47101 | The installer (aka openvpn-client-installer) in Securepoint SSL VPN Client before 2.0.40 allows local privilege escalation during installati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47101</link><description>The installer (aka openvpn-client-installer) in Securepoint SSL VPN Client before 2.0.40 allows local privilege escalation during installation or repair.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21301 | In ActivityManagerService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21301</link><description>In ActivityManagerService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21302 | In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21302</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21303 | In Content, here is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21303</link><description>In Content, here is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21304 | In Content Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21304</link><description>In Content Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21305 | In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21305</link><description>In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21367 | In Scudo, there is a possible way to exploit certain heap OOB read/write issues due to an insecure implementation/design. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21367</link><description>In Scudo, there is a possible way to exploit certain heap OOB read/write issues due to an insecure implementation/design. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21368 | In Audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21368</link><description>In Audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21369 | In Usage Access, there is a possible way to display a Settings usage access restriction toggle screen due to a permissions bypass. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21369</link><description>In Usage Access, there is a possible way to display a Settings usage access restriction toggle screen due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21370 | In the Security Element API, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21370</link><description>In the Security Element API, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21371 | In Secure Element, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21371</link><description>In Secure Element, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21372 | In libdexfile, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21372</link><description>In libdexfile, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21373 | In Telephony, there is a possible way for a guest user to change the preferred SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21373</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible way for a guest user to change the preferred SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21374 | In System UI, there is a possible factory reset protection bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21374</link><description>In System UI, there is a possible factory reset protection bypass due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21375 | In Sysproxy, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer underflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21375</link><description>In Sysproxy, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer underflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21376 | In Telephony, there is a possible way to retrieve the ICCID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21376</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible way to retrieve the ICCID due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21377 | In SELinux Policy, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21377</link><description>In SELinux Policy, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21378 | In Telecomm, there is a possible way to silence the ring for calls of secondary users due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21378</link><description>In Telecomm, there is a possible way to silence the ring for calls of secondary users due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21379 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21379</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the Bluetooth server with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21380 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21380</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21381 | In Media Resource Manager, there is a possible local arbitrary code execution due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21381</link><description>In Media Resource Manager, there is a possible local arbitrary code execution due to use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21382 | In Content Resolver, there is a possible method to access metadata about existing content providers on the device due to a missing permissio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21382</link><description>In Content Resolver, there is a possible method to access metadata about existing content providers on the device due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21383 | In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to unintentionally send extra data due to an unclear prompt. This could lead to local info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21383</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to unintentionally send extra data due to an unclear prompt. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21384 | In Package Manager, there is a possible possible permissions bypass due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21384</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible possible permissions bypass due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21385 | In Whitechapel, there is a possible out of bounds read due to memory corruption. This could lead to local information disclosure with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21385</link><description>In Whitechapel, there is a possible out of bounds read due to memory corruption. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21387 | In User Backup Manager, there is a possible way to leak a token to bypass user confirmation for backup due to log information disclosure. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21387</link><description>In User Backup Manager, there is a possible way to leak a token to bypass user confirmation for backup due to log information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21388 | In Settings, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21388</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible restriction bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21389 | In Settings, there is a possible bypass of profile owner restrictions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21389</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible bypass of profile owner restrictions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21390 | In Sim, there is a possible way to evade mobile preference restrictions due to a permission bypass. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21390</link><description>In Sim, there is a possible way to evade mobile preference restrictions due to a permission bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21391 | In Messaging, there is a possible way to disable the messaging application due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21391</link><description>In Messaging, there is a possible way to disable the messaging application due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21392 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege when conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21392</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege when connecting to a Bluetooth device with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21393 | In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to change SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21393</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way for the user to change SIM due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21394 | In Telecomm, there is a possible bypass of a multi user security boundary due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21394</link><description>In Telecomm, there is a possible bypass of a multi user security boundary due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21395 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a use after free. This could lead to remote information disclosure over Bluetoot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21395</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a use after free. This could lead to remote information disclosure over Bluetooth with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21396 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21396</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21397 | In Setup Wizard, there is a possible way to save a WiFi network due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21397</link><description>In Setup Wizard, there is a possible way to save a WiFi network due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21398 | In sdksandbox, there is a possible strandhogg style overlay attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21398</link><description>In sdksandbox, there is a possible strandhogg style overlay attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40101 | In collapse of canonicalize_md.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40101</link><description>In collapse of canonicalize_md.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45780 | In Print Service, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45780</link><description>In Print Service, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21297 | In SEPolicy, there is a possible way to access the factory MAC address due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21297</link><description>In SEPolicy, there is a possible way to access the factory MAC address due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21298 | In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed applications due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21298</link><description>In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed applications due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21299 | In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21299</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21300 | In PackageManager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21300</link><description>In PackageManager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21306 | In ContentService, there is a possible way to read installed sync content providers due to side channel information disclosure. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21306</link><description>In ContentService, there is a possible way to read installed sync content providers due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21307 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible way for a paired Bluetooth device to access a long term identifier for an Android device due to a permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21307</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible way for a paired Bluetooth device to access a long term identifier for an Android device due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21308 | In Composer, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21308</link><description>In Composer, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21309 | In libcore, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21309</link><description>In libcore, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21310 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21310</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21311 | In Settings, there is a possible way to control private DNS settings from a secondary user due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21311</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way to control private DNS settings from a secondary user due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21312 | In IntentResolver, there is a possible cross-user media read due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21312</link><description>In IntentResolver, there is a possible cross-user media read due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21313 | In Core, there is a possible way to forward calls without user knowledge due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21313</link><description>In Core, there is a possible way to forward calls without user knowledge due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21314 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21314</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21315 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21315</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21316 | In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21316</link><description>In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21317 | In ContentService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21317</link><description>In ContentService, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21318 | In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information dis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21318</link><description>In Content, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21319 | In UsageStatsService, there is a possible way to read installed 3rd party apps due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21319</link><description>In UsageStatsService, there is a possible way to read installed 3rd party apps due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21320 | In Device Policy, there is a possible way to verify if a particular admin app is registered on the device due to side channel information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21320</link><description>In Device Policy, there is a possible way to verify if a particular admin app is registered on the device due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21321 | In Package Manager, there is a possible cross-user settings disclosure due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21321</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible cross-user settings disclosure due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21323 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21323</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21324 | In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21324</link><description>In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21325 | In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21325</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21326 | In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21326</link><description>In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21327 | In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21327</link><description>In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21328 | In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to a missing permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21328</link><description>In Package Installer, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21329 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21329</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21330 | In Overlay Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21330</link><description>In Overlay Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21331 | In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21331</link><description>In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21332 | In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21332</link><description>In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21333 | In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21333</link><description>In Text Services, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21334 | In App Ops Service, there is a possible disclosure of information about installed packages due to a logic error in the code. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21334</link><description>In App Ops Service, there is a possible disclosure of information about installed packages due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21335 | In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21335</link><description>In Settings, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21336 | In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21336</link><description>In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21337 | In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21337</link><description>In InputMethod, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21338 | In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21338</link><description>In Input Method, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21339 | In Minikin, there is a possible way to trigger ANR by showing a malicious message due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to remote deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21339</link><description>In Minikin, there is a possible way to trigger ANR by showing a malicious message due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21340 | In Telecomm, there is a possible way to get the call state due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21340</link><description>In Telecomm, there is a possible way to get the call state due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21341 | In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to bypass required permissions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21341</link><description>In Permission Manager, there is a possible way to bypass required permissions due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21342 | In Speech, there is a possible way to bypass background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21342</link><description>In Speech, there is a possible way to bypass background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21343 | In ActivityStarter, there is a possible background activity launch due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21343</link><description>In ActivityStarter, there is a possible background activity launch due to an unsafe PendingIntent. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21344 | In Job Scheduler, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21344</link><description>In Job Scheduler, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21345 | In Game Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21345</link><description>In Game Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21346 | In the Device Idle Controller, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side chan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21346</link><description>In the Device Idle Controller, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21347 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21347</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21348 | In Window Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21348</link><description>In Window Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21349 | In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21349</link><description>In Package Manager, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21350 | In Media Projection, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21350</link><description>In Media Projection, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21351 | In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21351</link><description>In Activity Manager, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21352 | In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21352</link><description>In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21353 | In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21353</link><description>In NFA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21354 | In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21354</link><description>In Package Manager Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21355 | In libaudioclient, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21355</link><description>In libaudioclient, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21356 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21356</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21357 | In NFC, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21357</link><description>In NFC, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21358 | In UWB Google, there is a possible way for a malicious app to masquerade as system app com.android.uwb.resources due to improperly used cryp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21358</link><description>In UWB Google, there is a possible way for a malicious app to masquerade as system app com.android.uwb.resources due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21359 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21359</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure in the Bluetooth server with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21360 | In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21360</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21361 | In Bluetooth, there is a possibility of code-execution due to a use after free. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21361</link><description>In Bluetooth, there is a possibility of code-execution due to a use after free. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege in the privileged Bluetooth process with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21362 | In Usage, there is a possible permanent DoS due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21362</link><description>In Usage, there is a possible permanent DoS due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21364 | In ContactsProvider, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local persistent denial of service in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21364</link><description>In ContactsProvider, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local persistent denial of service in the Phone app with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21365 | In Contacts, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service in the Phone app with Use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21365</link><description>In Contacts, there is a possible crash loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service in the Phone app with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21366 | In Scudo, there is a possible way for an attacker to predict heap allocation patterns due to insecure implementation/design. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21366</link><description>In Scudo, there is a possible way for an attacker to predict heap allocation patterns due to insecure implementation/design. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36920 | Clickjacking vulnerability in SAP Enable Now</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36920</link><description>In SAP Enable Now - versions WPB_MANAGER 1.0, WPB_MANAGER_CE 10, WPB_MANAGER_HANA 10, ENABLE_NOW_CONSUMP_DEL 1704, the X-FRAME-OPTIONS response header is not implemented, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to attempt clickjacking, which could result in disclosure or modification of information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47090 | NATS nats-server before 2.9.23 and 2.10.x before 2.10.2 has an authentication bypass. An implicit $G user in an authorization block can some...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47090</link><description>NATS nats-server before 2.9.23 and 2.10.x before 2.10.2 has an authentication bypass. An implicit $G user in an authorization block can sometimes be used for unauthenticated access, even when the intention of the configuration was for each user to have an account. The earliest affected version is 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-39810 | In NFC, there is a possible way to setup a default contactless payment app without user consent due to a missing permission check. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39810</link><description>In NFC, there is a possible way to setup a default contactless payment app without user consent due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-20264 | In Usage Stats Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions due to side channel info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20264</link><description>In Usage Stats Service, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21293 | In PackageManagerNative, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21293</link><description>In PackageManagerNative, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21294 | In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed packages due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21294</link><description>In Slice, there is a possible disclosure of installed packages due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21295 | In SliceManagerService, there is a possible way to check if a content provider is installed due to a missing null check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21295</link><description>In SliceManagerService, there is a possible way to check if a content provider is installed due to a missing null check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21296 | In Permission, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21296</link><description>In Permission, there is a possible way to determine whether an app is installed, without query permissions, due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44323 | PDF Jbig2 memory-corruption Vulnerability - MSFT T5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44323</link><description>Adobe Acrobat for Edge version 118.0.2088.46 (and earlier) is affected by a Use After Free vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48189 | An SMM driver input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48189</link><description>An SMM driver input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4575 | A vulnerability due to improper write protection of UEFI variables was reported in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4575</link><description>A vulnerability due to improper write protection of UEFI variables was reported in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with physical or local access and elevated privileges the ability to bypass Secure Boot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4573 | An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the ThinkPad X1 Fold Gen 1 could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4573</link><description>An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the ThinkPad X1 Fold Gen 1 could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4574 | An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4574</link><description>An SMI handler input validation vulnerability in the BIOS of some ThinkPad models could allow an attacker with local access and elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4964 | Potential open redirect vulnerability in opentext SMAX and AMX product. </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4964</link><description>Potential open redirect vulnerability
in opentext Service Management Automation X
(SMAX)  versions 2020.05, 2020.08,
2020.11, 2021.02, 2021.05, 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11 and opentext Asset
Management X (AMX) versions 2021.08, 2021.11, 2022.05, 2022.11. The
vulnerability could allow attackers to redirect a user to
malicious websites.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5049 | The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rafflepress' and 'raffl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5049</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rafflepress' and 'rafflepress_gutenberg' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.12.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on 'giframe' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5164 | The Bellows Accordion Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5164</link><description>The Bellows Accordion Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5199 | The PHP to Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 0.3 via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5199</link><description>The PHP to Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 0.3 via the 'php-to-page' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above, to include local file and potentially execute code on the server. While subscribers may need to poison log files or otherwise get a file installed in order to achieve remote code execution, author and above users can upload files by default and achieve remote code execution easily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5250 | The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 via a shortcode attribute. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5250</link><description>The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 via a shortcode attribute. This allows subscriber-level, and above, attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files with arbitrary content can be uploaded and included. This is limited to .php files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5251 | The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5251</link><description>The Grid Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'grid_plus_save_layout_callback' and 'grid_plus_delete_callback' functions in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber privileges or above, to add, update or delete grid layout.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5252 | The FareHarbor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5252</link><description>The FareHarbor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5315 | The Google Maps made Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5315</link><description>The Google Maps made Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 0.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5335 | The Buzzsprout Podcasting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'buzzsprout' shortcode in versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5335</link><description>The Buzzsprout Podcasting plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'buzzsprout' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5362 | The Carousel, Recent Post Slider and Banner Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'spice_post_slider'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5362</link><description>The Carousel, Recent Post Slider and Banner Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'spice_post_slider' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5565 | The Shortcode Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortmenu' shortcode in versions up to, and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5565</link><description>The Shortcode Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shortmenu' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5566 | The Simple Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5566</link><description>The Simple Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5583 | The WP Simple Galleries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.34 via deserializatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5583</link><description>The WP Simple Galleries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.34 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'wpsimplegallery_gallery' post meta via 'wpsgallery' shortcode. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5666 | The Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcpaccordion' shortcode in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5666</link><description>The Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcpaccordion' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5843 | The Ads by datafeedr.com plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 via the 'dfads_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5843</link><description>The Ads by datafeedr.com plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 via the 'dfads_ajax_load_ads' function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. The parameters of the callable function are limited, they cannot be specified arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5832 | Improper Input Validation in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5832</link><description>Improper Input Validation in GitHub repository mintplex-labs/anything-llm prior to 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5833 | Improper Access Control in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5833</link><description>Improper Access Control in GitHub repository mintplex-labs/anything-llm prior to 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42431 | Potential XSS on user preferences page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42431</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BlueSpiceAvatars extension of BlueSpice allows logged in user to inject arbitrary HTML into the profile image dialog on Special:Preferences. This only applies to the genuine user context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5844 | Unverified Password Change in pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5844</link><description>Unverified Password Change in GitHub repository pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle prior to 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45798 | Yettiesoft VestCert Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45798</link><description>In Yettiesoft VestCert versions 2.36 to 2.5.29, a vulnerability exists due to improper validation of third-party modules. This allows malicious actors to load arbitrary third-party modules, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45799 | MLSoft TCO!stream Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45799</link><description>In MLSoft TCO!stream versions 8.0.22.1115 and below, a vulnerability exists due to insufficient permission validation. This allows an attacker to make the victim download and execute arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45797 | DreamSecurity MagicLine Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45797</link><description>A Buffer overflow vulnerability in DreamSecurity MagicLine4NX versions 1.0.0.1 to 1.0.0.26 allows an attacker to remotely execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45746 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script. Affected pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45746</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script. Affected products/versions are as follows: Movable Type 7 r.5405 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Advanced 7 r.5405 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Premium 1.58 and earlier, Movable Type Premium Advanced 1.58 and earlier, Movable Type Cloud Edition (Version 7) r.5405 and earlier, and Movable Type Premium Cloud Edition 1.58 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44141 | Inkdrop prior to v5.6.0 allows a local attacker to conduct a code injection attack by having a legitimate user open a specially crafted mark...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44141</link><description>Inkdrop prior to v5.6.0 allows a local attacker to conduct a code injection attack by having a legitimate user open a specially crafted markdown file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46866 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccCLUT::Interp3d in IccProfLib/IccTagLut.cpp in libSampleICC.a attempts to access ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46866</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccCLUT::Interp3d in IccProfLib/IccTagLut.cpp in libSampleICC.a attempts to access array elements at out-of-bounds indexes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46867 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccXformMatrixTRC::GetCurve in IccCmm.cpp in libSampleICC.a has a NULL pointer derefe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46867</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX 79ecb74, CIccXformMatrixTRC::GetCurve in IccCmm.cpp in libSampleICC.a has a NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-25736 | Windows kube-proxy LoadBalancer contention</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25736</link><description>Kube-proxy
 on Windows can unintentionally forward traffic to local processes 
listening on the same port (“spec.ports[*].port”) as a LoadBalancer 
Service when the LoadBalancer controller
 does not set the “status.loadBalancer.ingress[].ip” field. Clusters 
where the LoadBalancer controller sets the 
“status.loadBalancer.ingress[].ip” field are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46865 | /api/v1/company/upload-logo in CompanyController.php in crater through 6.0.6 allows a superadmin to execute arbitrary PHP code by placing th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46865</link><description>/api/v1/company/upload-logo in CompanyController.php in crater through 6.0.6 allows a superadmin to execute arbitrary PHP code by placing this code into an image/png IDAT chunk of a Company Logo image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5842 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in dolibarr/dolibarr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5842</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository dolibarr/dolibarr prior to 16.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46863 | Peppermint Ticket Management before 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/users/file/download?filepath=./../ P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46863</link><description>Peppermint Ticket Management before 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/users/file/download?filepath=./../ POST request.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46864 | Peppermint Ticket Management through 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/ticket/1/file/download?filepath=../...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46864</link><description>Peppermint Ticket Management through 0.2.4 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a /api/v1/ticket/1/file/download?filepath=../ POST request.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4393 | HTML and SMTP Injection in LiquidFiles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4393</link><description>HTML and SMTP injections on the registration page of LiquidFiles versions 3.7.13 and below, allow an attacker to perform more advanced phishing attacks against an organization.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 23:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2007-10003 | The Hackers Diet Plugin HTTP POST Request ajax_blurb.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2007-10003</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in The Hackers Diet Plugin up to 0.9.6b on WordPress. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ajax_blurb.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 0.9.7b is able to address this issue. The patch is named 7dd8acf7cd8442609840037121074425d363b694. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243803.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 17:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2005-10002 | almosteffortless secure-files Plugin secure-files.php sf_downloads path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2005-10002</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in almosteffortless secure-files Plugin up to 1.1 on WordPress. Affected is the function sf_downloads of the file secure-files.php. The manipulation of the argument downloadfile leads to path traversal. Upgrading to version 1.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is cab025e5fc2bcdad8032d833ebc38e6bd2a13c92. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243804.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33638 | Run copy with container in a malicious directory may cause container escaping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33638</link><description>When the isula cp command is used to copy files from a container to a host machine and the container is controlled by an attacker, the attacker can escape the container.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33635 | Pull malicious images may cause process to be hijacked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33635</link><description>When malicious images are pulled by isula pull, attackers can execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33636 | Load malicious images may cause process to be hijacked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33636</link><description>When the isula load command is used to load malicious images, attackers can execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33637 | Export container in a malicious directory may cause process to be hijacked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33637</link><description>When the isula export command is used to export a container to an image and the container is controlled by an attacker, the attacker can escape the container.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 08:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-33634 | Malicious image running containers may cause DoS attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33634</link><description>iSulad uses the lcr+lxc runtime (default) to run malicious images, which can cause DOS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 07:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46862 | An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel through 6.5.9. During a race with SQ thread exit, an io_uring/fdinfo.c io_uring_show_fdinfo NULL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46862</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Linux kernel through 6.5.9. During a race with SQ thread exit, an io_uring/fdinfo.c io_uring_show_fdinfo NULL pointer dereference can occur.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40685 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40685</link><description>Management Central as part of IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Navigator contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with command line access to the operating system can exploit this vulnerability to elevate privileges to gain root access to the operating system.  IBM X-Force ID:  264116.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40686 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40686</link><description>Management Central as part of IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 Navigator contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability.  A malicious actor with command line access to the operating system can exploit this vulnerability to elevate privileges to gain component access to the operating system.  IBM X-Force ID:  264114.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43041 | IBM QRadar information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43041</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to information exposure allowing a delegated Admin tenant user with a specific domain security profile assigned to see data from other domains.  This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-34352.  IBM X-Force ID:  266808.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46858 | Moodle 4.3 allows /grade/report/grader/index.php?searchvalue= reflected XSS when logged in as a teacher. NOTE: the Moodle Security FAQ link ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46858</link><description>Moodle 4.3 allows /grade/report/grader/index.php?searchvalue= reflected XSS when logged in as a teacher. NOTE: the Moodle Security FAQ link states "Some forms of rich content [are] used by teachers to enhance their courses ... admins and teachers can post XSS-capable content, but students can not."</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5838 | Insufficient Session Expiration in linkstackorg/linkstack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5838</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration in GitHub repository linkstackorg/linkstack prior to v4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5839 | Privilege Chaining in hestiacp/hestiacp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5839</link><description>Privilege Chaining in GitHub repository hestiacp/hestiacp prior to 1.8.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5840 | Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password in linkstackorg/linkstack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5840</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password in GitHub repository linkstackorg/linkstack prior to v4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 02:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>