<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:35:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-5145 | Netcore POWER13 Query String cgi-bin command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5145</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Netcore NBR1005GPEV2, B6V2, COVER5, NAP830, NAP930, NBR100V2, NBR200V2 and POWER13 up to 20250508. This affects an unknown part of the file /www/cgi-bin/ of the component Query String Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 05:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5140 | Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System ThirdMenuController.class this.oursNetService.getData server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5140</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System up to 8.1 SP2. This affects the function this.oursNetService.getData of the file com\ours\www\ehr\openPlatform1\open4ClientType\controller\ThirdMenuController.class. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 01:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5139 | Qualitor testaConexaoOffice365.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5139</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Qualitor 8.20. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /html/ad/adconexaooffice365/request/testaConexaoOffice365.php. The manipulation of the argument nmconexao leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5138 | Bitwarden PDF File cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bitwarden up to 2.25.1. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component PDF File Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 01:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5137 | DedeCMS Incomplete Fix CVE-2018-9175 sys_verifies.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5137</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7.117. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file dede/sys_verifies.php?action=getfiles of the component Incomplete Fix CVE-2018-9175. The manipulation of the argument refiles leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 01:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5136 | Tmall Demo Payment Identifier pay random values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5136</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. This affects an unknown part of the file /tmall/order/pay/ of the component Payment Identifier Handler. The manipulation leads to insufficiently random values. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 23:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5135 | Tmall Demo Product Details Page admin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5135</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tmall/admin/ of the component Product Details Page. The manipulation of the argument Product Name/Product Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 22:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5134 | Tmall Demo Buy Item Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5134</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Buy Item Page. The manipulation of the argument Detailed Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5133 | Tmall Demo Search Box cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5133</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. Affected is an unknown function of the component Search Box. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 21:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5132 | Tmall Demo logout cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5132</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file tmall/admin/account/logout. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 21:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5131 | Tmall Demo uploadCategoryImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function uploadCategoryImage of the file tmall/admin/uploadCategoryImage. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 20:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5130 | Tmall Demo uploadProductImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5130</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tmall Demo up to 20250505. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function uploadProductImage of the file tmall/admin/uploadProductImage. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 20:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5129 | Sangfor 零信任访问控制系统 aTrust MSASN1.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5129</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sangfor 零信任访问控制系统 aTrust 2.3.10.60 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library MSASN1.dll. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Local access is required to approach this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 16:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5128 | ScriptAndTools Real-Estate-website-in-PHP Admin Login Panel admin sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5128</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ScriptAndTools Real-Estate-website-in-PHP 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/ of the component Admin Login Panel. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 16:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5127 | FLIR AX8 prod.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5127</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in FLIR AX8 up to 1.46.16. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /prod.php. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5126 | FLIR AX8 settingsregional.php setDataTime command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5126</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FLIR AX8 up to 1.46.16. This vulnerability affects the function setDataTime of the file \usr\www\application\models\settingsregional.php. The manipulation of the argument year/month/day/hour/minute leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 15:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5124 | Sony SNC-M1 Administrative Interface default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5124</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Sony SNC-M1, SNC-M3, SNC-RZ25N, SNC-RZ30N, SNC-DS10, SNC-CS3N and SNC-RX570N up to 1.30. This affects an unknown part of the component Administrative Interface. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. The vendor was contacted early about this issue. They confirmed the existence but pointed out that they "have published the 'Hardening Guide' on the Web from July 2018 to January 2025 and have thoroughly informed customers of the recommendation to change their initial passwords".</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4223 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via login_url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4223</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘login_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. A valid username/password pair needs to be supplied in order to be successfully exploited and any injected scripts will only execute in the context of that authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 04:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4336 | eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via set_file()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4336</link><description>The eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the set_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This is only exploitable by unauthenticated attackers in default configurations where the the default password is left as 1:1, or where the attacker gains access to the credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4602 | eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4602</link><description>The eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Reads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 via the get_file() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information. This is only exploitable by unauthenticated attackers in default configurations where the the default password is left as 1:1, or where the attacker gains access to the credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4603 | eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4603</link><description>The eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the delete_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php). This is only exploitable by unauthenticated attackers in default configurations where the the default password is left as 1:1, or where the attacker gains access to the credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5058 | eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via set_image()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5058</link><description>The eMagicOne Store Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the set_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This is only exploitable by unauthenticated attackers in default configurations where the the default password is left as 1:1, or where the attacker gains access to the credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3869 | 4stats &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3869</link><description>The 4stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the stats/stats.php page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48751 | The process_lock crate 0.1.0 for Rust allows data races in unlock.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48751</link><description>The process_lock crate 0.1.0 for Rust allows data races in unlock.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48752 | In the process-sync crate 0.2.2 for Rust, the drop function lacks a check for whether the pthread_mutex is unlocked.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48752</link><description>In the process-sync crate 0.2.2 for Rust, the drop function lacks a check for whether the pthread_mutex is unlocked.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48753 | In the anode crate 0.1.0 for Rust, data races can occur in unlock in SpinLock.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48753</link><description>In the anode crate 0.1.0 for Rust, data races can occur in unlock in SpinLock.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48754 | In the memory_pages crate 0.1.0 for Rust, division by zero can occur.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48754</link><description>In the memory_pages crate 0.1.0 for Rust, division by zero can occur.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48755 | In the spiral-rs crate 0.2.0 for Rust, allocation can be attempted for a ZST (zero-sized type).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48755</link><description>In the spiral-rs crate 0.2.0 for Rust, allocation can be attempted for a ZST (zero-sized type).</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48756 | In group_number in the scsir crate 0.2.0 for Rust, there can be an overflow because a hardware device may expect a small number of bits (e.g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48756</link><description>In group_number in the scsir crate 0.2.0 for Rust, there can be an overflow because a hardware device may expect a small number of bits (e.g., 5 bits) for group number.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5055 | Smart Forms &amp;lt;= 2.6.98 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5055</link><description>The Smart Forms – when you need more than just a contact form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.98 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 03:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13427 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13427</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 1.9.9 and completely fixed in version 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 02:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5119 | Emlog Pro api_controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5119</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Emlog Pro 2.5.11 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /include/controller/api_controller.php. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure and confirmed the existence of the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 21:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48738 | An e-mail flooding vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, 5.4.0 before 5.4.10, and 5.5.0 before 5.5.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48738</link><description>An e-mail flooding vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, 5.4.0 before 5.4.10, and 5.5.0 before 5.5.1 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to use the password reset feature without limits. This can lead to several consequences, including mailbox storage exhaustion for targeted users, reputation damage to the SMTP server, potentially causing it to be blacklisted, and overload of the SMTP server's outbound mail queue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48739 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, 5.4.0 before 5.4.10, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48739</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, 5.4.0 before 5.4.10, and 5.5.0 before 5.5.1 allows remote authenticated attackers with admin permissions (allowing them to access specific API endpoints) to manipulate URLs to direct requests to unexpected hosts or ports. This allows the attacker to use a TheHive server as a proxy to reach internal or otherwise restricted resources. This could be exploited to access other servers on the internal network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48740 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, 5.4.0 before 5.4.10, and 5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48740</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, 5.4.0 before 5.4.10, and 5.5.0 before 5.5.1 allows a remote attacker to trigger requests on their victim's behalf, if the attacker lures a privileged user, authenticated with basic authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48741 | A Broken Access Control vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, and 5.4.0 before 5.4.10 allows remote,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48741</link><description>A Broken Access Control vulnerability in StrangeBee TheHive 5.2.0 before 5.2.16, 5.3.0 before 5.3.11, and 5.4.0 before 5.4.10 allows remote, authenticated, and unprivileged users to retrieve alerts, cases, logs, observables, or tasks, regardless of the user's permissions, through a specific API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48735 | A SQL Injection issue in the request body processing in BOS IPCs with firmware 21.45.8.2.2_220219 before 21.45.8.2.3_230220 allows remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48735</link><description>A SQL Injection issue in the request body processing in BOS IPCs with firmware 21.45.8.2.2_220219 before 21.45.8.2.3_230220 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from the database via crafted input in the request body.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44998 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /tinyfilemanager.php of TinyFileManager v2.4.7 allows attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44998</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /tinyfilemanager.php of TinyFileManager v2.4.7 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the js-theme-3 parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46176 | Hardcoded credentials in the Telnet service in D-Link DIR-605L v2.13B01 and DIR-816L v2.06B01 allow attackers to remotely execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46176</link><description>Hardcoded credentials in the Telnet service in D-Link DIR-605L v2.13B01 and DIR-816L v2.06B01 allow attackers to remotely execute arbitrary commands via firmware analysis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51102 | PHPGURUKUL Student Management System using PHP and MySQL v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at /studentreco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51102</link><description>PHPGURUKUL Student Management System using PHP and MySQL v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at /studentrecordms/login.php via the username and password parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34873 | On MOBOTIX P3 cameras before MX-V4.7.2.18 and Mx6 cameras before MX-V5.2.0.61, the tcpdump feature does not properly validate input, which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34873</link><description>On MOBOTIX P3 cameras before MX-V4.7.2.18 and Mx6 cameras before MX-V5.2.0.61, the tcpdump feature does not properly validate input, which allows authenticated users to execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24917 | Improper Access Control leads to Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24917</link><description>In Tenable Network Monitor versions prior to 6.5.1 on a Windows host, it was found that a non-administrative user could stage files in a local directory to run arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges, potentially leading to local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24916 | Improper Access Control leads to Local Priviledge Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24916</link><description>When installing Tenable Network Monitor to a non-default location on a Windows host, Tenable Network Monitor versions prior to 6.5.1 did not enforce secure permissions for sub-directories. This could allow for local privilege escalation if users had not secured the directories in the non-default installation location.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48375 | Schule Missing Rate Limiting on OTP Email Requests – Susceptible to Abuse &amp;amp; DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48375</link><description>Schule is open-source school management system software. Prior to version 1.0.1, the file forgot_password.php (or equivalent endpoint responsible for email-based OTP generation) lacks proper rate limiting controls, allowing attackers to abuse the OTP request functionality. This vulnerability can be exploited to send an excessive number of OTP emails, leading to potential denial-of-service (DoS) conditions or facilitating user harassment through email flooding. Version 1.0.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43860 | OpemRMS Vulnerable to Stored XSS Attack in the Additional Address Section of Patient Demographics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43860</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in versions prior to 7.0.3.4 allows any authenticated user with patient creation and editing privileges to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the system by entering malicious payloads in the (1) Text Box fields of Address, Address Line 2, Postal Code and City fields  and (2) Drop Down menu options of Address Use, State and Country of the Additional Addresses section of the Contact tab in Patient Demographics. The injected script can execute in two scenarios: (1) dynamically during form input, and (2) when the form data is later loaded for editing. Version 7.0.3.4 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48376 | Dnn.Platform&amp;#x27;s Site Import could use an external source with a crafted request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48376</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Prior to version 9.13.9, a malicious SuperUser (Host) could craft a request to use an external url for a site export to then be imported. Version 9.13.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48377 | Dnn.Platform vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in module actions in edit mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48377</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Prior to version 9.13.9, a specially crafted URL may be constructed which can inject an XSS payload that is triggered by using some module actions. Version 9.13.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48378 | Dnn.Platform vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) with svg files rendered inline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48378</link><description>DNN (formerly DotNetNuke) is an open-source web content management platform (CMS) in the Microsoft ecosystem. Prior to version 9.13.9, uploaded SVG files could contain scripts and if rendered inline those scripts could run allowing XSS attacks. Version 9.13.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51103 | PHPGURUKUL Student Management System using PHP and MySQL v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at /studentreco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51103</link><description>PHPGURUKUL Student Management System using PHP and MySQL v1 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at /studentrecordms/password-recovery.php via the emailid and id parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32967 | OpenEMR doesn&amp;#x27;t log password administration properly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32967</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. A logging oversight in versions prior to 7.0.3.4 allows password change events to go unrecorded on the client-side log viewer, preventing administrators from auditing critical actions. This weakens traceability and opens the system to undetectable misuse by insiders or attackers. Version 7.0.3.4 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53154 | parse_string in cJSON before 1.7.18 has a heap-based buffer over-read via {"1":1, with no trailing newline if cJSON_ParseWithLength is calle...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53154</link><description>parse_string in cJSON before 1.7.18 has a heap-based buffer over-read via {"1":1, with no trailing newline if cJSON_ParseWithLength is called.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48704 | Phpgurukul Medical Card Generation System v1.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection in admin/contactus.php via the parameter pagedes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48704</link><description>Phpgurukul Medical Card Generation System v1.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection in admin/contactus.php via the parameter pagedes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51099 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component mcgs/download-medical-cards.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51099</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component mcgs/download-medical-cards.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the searchdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32794 | OpenEMR Stored XSS via Patient Name Field in Procedure Orders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32794</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in versions prior to 7.0.3.4 allows any authenticated user with patient creation privileges to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the system by entering malicious payloads in the First and Last Name fields during patient registration. This code is later executed when viewing the patient's encounter under Orders → Procedure Orders. Version 7.0.3.4 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-31807 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions). Affected d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31807</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions). Affected devices do not properly check the integrity of firmware updates. This could allow a local attacker to upload a maliciously modified firmware onto the device. In a second scenario, a remote attacker who is able to intercept the transfer of a valid firmware from the server to the device could modify the firmware "on the fly".</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-31812 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V2.95.3.18). Affected server applications contain an out of bounds ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31812</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V2.95.3.18). Affected server applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated buffer while checking the integrity of incoming packets. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to create a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48702 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection via the searchdata parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48702</link><description>PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection via the searchdata parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51101 | PHPGURUKUL Restaurant Table Booking System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the searchda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51101</link><description>PHPGURUKUL Restaurant Table Booking System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the searchdata parameter at /rtbs/check-status.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25110 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in markedjs/marked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25110</link><description>Marked prior to version 0.3.17 is vulnerable to a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) attack due to catastrophic backtracking in several regular expressions used for parsing HTML tags and markdown links. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by providing specially crafted markdown input, such as deeply nested or repetitively structured brackets or tag attributes, which cause the parser to hang and lead to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51107 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /mcgs/admin/contactus.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51107</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /mcgs/admin/contactus.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the pagetitle, pagedes, and email parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51108 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /admin/card-bwdates-report.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Genera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51108</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the component /admin/card-bwdates-report.php of PHPGURUKUL Medical Card Generation System using PHP and MySQL v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the fromdate and todate parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51360 | An issue in Hospital Management System In PHP V4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hms/doctor/edit-profile.php fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51360</link><description>An issue in Hospital Management System In PHP V4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the hms/doctor/edit-profile.php file</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5114 | easysoft zentaopms Editor index.php edit deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5114</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in easysoft zentaopms 21.5_20250307 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function Edit of the file /index.php?m=editor&amp;amp;f=edit&amp;amp;filePath=cGhhcjovLy9ldGMvcGFzc3dk&amp;amp;action=edit of the component Committer. The manipulation of the argument filePath leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5111 | FreeFloat FTP Server TYPE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5111</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component TYPE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5112 | FreeFloat FTP Server MGET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5112</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component MGET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3580 | An access control vulnerability was discovered in Grafana OSS where an Organization administrator could permanently delete the Server admini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3580</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in Grafana OSS where an Organization administrator could permanently delete the Server administrator account. This vulnerability exists in the DELETE /api/org/users/ endpoint.

The vulnerability can be exploited when:

1. An Organization administrator exists

2. The Server administrator is either:

   - Not part of any organization, or
   - Part of the same organization as the Organization administrator
Impact:

- Organization administrators can permanently delete Server administrator accounts

- If the only Server administrator is deleted, the Grafana instance becomes unmanageable

- No super-user permissions remain in the system

- Affects all users, organizations, and teams managed in the instance

The vulnerability is particularly serious as it can lead to a complete loss of administrative control over the Grafana instance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5110 | FreeFloat FTP Server VERBOSE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5110</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component VERBOSE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5109 | FreeFloat FTP Server STATUS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5109</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component STATUS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7803 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7803</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.6 before 17.10.7, 17.11 before 17.11.3, and 18.0 before 18.0.1. A Discord webhook integration may cause DoS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9163 | User Interface (UI) Misrepresentation of Critical Information in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9163</link><description>A business logic error in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.1 prior to 17.10.7, 17.11 prior to 17.11.3 and 18.0 prior to 18.0.1 where an attacker can cause a branch name confusion in confidential MRs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31049 | WordPress Dash &amp;lt;= 1.3 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31049</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton Dash allows Object Injection. This issue affects Dash: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31053 | WordPress KBx Pro Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.9.8 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31053</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in quantumcloud KBx Pro Ultimate allows Path Traversal. This issue affects KBx Pro Ultimate: from n/a through 7.9.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31056 | WordPress WhatsCart plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31056</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Techspawn WhatsCart - Whatsapp Abandoned Cart Recovery, Order Notifications, Chat Box, OTP for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WhatsCart - Whatsapp Abandoned Cart Recovery, Order Notifications, Chat Box, OTP for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31060 | WordPress Capie &amp;lt;= 1.0.40 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31060</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Capie allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Capie: from n/a through 1.0.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31064 | WordPress Vizeon - Business Consulting &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31064</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Vizeon - Business Consulting allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Vizeon - Business Consulting: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31069 | WordPress HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31069</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme allows Object Injection. This issue affects HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31397 | WordPress Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31397</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in smartcms Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Bus Ticket Booking with Seat Reservation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31423 | WordPress Umberto &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31423</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Umberto allows Object Injection. This issue affects Umberto: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31430 | WordPress The Business &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31430</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton The Business allows Object Injection. This issue affects The Business: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31631 | WordPress Fish House &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31631</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Fish House allows Object Injection. This issue affects Fish House: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31632 | WordPress La Boom &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31632</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SpyroPress La Boom allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects La Boom: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31633 | WordPress Kiamo - Responsive Business Service WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31633</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Kiamo - Responsive Business Service WordPress Theme allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Kiamo - Responsive Business Service WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31636 | WordPress WP Post Modules for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SaurabhSharma WP Post Modules for Elementor allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Post Modules for Elementor: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31912 | WordPress Enzio - Responsive Business WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31912</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Enzio - Responsive Business WordPress Theme allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Enzio - Responsive Business WordPress Theme: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31913 | WordPress Ogami &amp;lt;= 1.53 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31913</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Ogami allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ogami: from n/a through 1.53.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31914 | WordPress Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp;amp; Autoresponder &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31914</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in kamleshyadav Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31916 | WordPress JP Students Result Management System Premium plugin 1.1.7 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31916</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in joy2012bd JP Students Result Management System Premium allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects JP Students Result Management System Premium: from 1.1.7 through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31918 | WordPress Simple Business Directory Pro &amp;lt;= 15.4.8 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31918</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in quantumcloud Simple Business Directory Pro allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Simple Business Directory Pro: from n/a through 15.4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31924 | WordPress Crafts &amp;amp; Arts &amp;lt;= 2.5 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31924</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in designthemes Crafts &amp; Arts allows Object Injection. This issue affects Crafts &amp; Arts: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31927 | WordPress Acerola &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31927</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in themeton Acerola allows Object Injection. This issue affects Acerola: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32284 | WordPress Pet World &amp;lt;= 2.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32284</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in designthemes Pet World allows Object Injection. This issue affects Pet World: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32285 | WordPress Butcher theme &amp;lt;= 2.40 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32285</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ApusTheme Butcher allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Butcher: from n/a through 2.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32286 | WordPress Butcher &amp;lt;= 2.40 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32286</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Butcher allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Butcher: from n/a through 2.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32289 | WordPress Yozi &amp;lt;= 2.0.52 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32289</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ApusTheme Yozi allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Yozi: from n/a through 2.0.52.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32292 | WordPress Jarvis – Night Club, Concert, Festival WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.8.11 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32292</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Jarvis – Night Club, Concert, Festival WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Jarvis – Night Club, Concert, Festival WordPress: from n/a through 1.8.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32293 | WordPress Finance Consultant &amp;lt;= 2.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32293</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in designthemes Finance Consultant allows Object Injection. This issue affects Finance Consultant: from n/a through 2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32294 | WordPress Oxpitan &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32294</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Oxpitan allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Oxpitan: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32302 | WordPress Winnex &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32302</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Winnex allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Winnex: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32309 | WordPress Healsoul &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32309</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeMove Healsoul allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Healsoul: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39480 | WordPress Car Dealer &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39480</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeMakers Car Dealer allows Object Injection. This issue affects Car Dealer: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39485 | WordPress GrandTour Theme &amp;lt;= 5.5.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39485</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods Grand Tour | Travel Agency WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Grand Tour | Travel Agency WordPress: from n/a through 5.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39489 | WordPress CouponXL &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39489</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in pebas CouponXL allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects CouponXL: from n/a through 4.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39490 | WordPress Backpack Traveler &amp;lt;= 2.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39490</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Backpack Traveler allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Backpack Traveler: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39494 | WordPress Wilmër theme &amp;lt; 3.4.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39494</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Wilmër allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Wilmër: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39495 | WordPress Avantage Theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39495</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Avantage allows Object Injection. This issue affects Avantage: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39499 | WordPress Medicare Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39499</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in BoldThemes Medicare allows Object Injection. This issue affects Medicare: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39500 | WordPress Goodlayers Hostel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39500</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hostel allows Object Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hostel: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39501 | WordPress Goodlayers Hostel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39501</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hostel allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hostel: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39502 | WordPress Goodlayers Hostel Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39502</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hostel allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Goodlayers Hostel: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39503 | WordPress Goodlayers Hotel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39503</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hotel allows Object Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hotel: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39504 | WordPress Goodlayers Hotel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39504</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hotel allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Goodlayers Hotel: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39505 | WordPress Goodlayers Hotel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39505</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GoodLayers Goodlayers Hotel allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Goodlayers Hotel: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39506 | WordPress Nasa Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39506</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NasaTheme Nasa Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Nasa Core: from n/a through 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39536 | WordPress JobHunt Job Alerts &amp;lt;= 3.6 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39536</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Chimpstudio JobHunt Job Alerts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects JobHunt Job Alerts: from n/a through 3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41377 | Cryptographic vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41377</link><description>Cryptographic vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700. This vulnerability allows a user to retrieve the encryption key, resulting in the loading of malicious firmware.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41378 | Injection vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41378</link><description>The SSID field is not parsed correctly and can be used to inject commands into the hostpad.conf file. This can be exploited by an attacker to extend his knowledge of the system and compromise other devices. The information is filtered by the logs function of the web panel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41379 | Injection vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41379</link><description>The Intellian C700 web panel allows you to add firewall rules. Each of these rules has an associated ID, but there is a problem when adding a new rule, the ID used to create the database entry may be different from the JSON ID. If the rule needs to be deleted later, the system will use the JSON ID and therefore fail. This can be exploited by an attacker to create rules that cannot be deleted unless the device is reset to factory defaults.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41380 | Injection vulnerability in Iridium Certus 700</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41380</link><description>Iridium Certus 700 version 1.0.1 has an embedded credentials vulnerability in the code. This vulnerability allows a local user to retrieve the SSH hash string.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46437 | WordPress Tayori Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tayoricom Tayori Form allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Tayori Form: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46440 | WordPress kStats Reloaded plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46440</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mark kStats Reloaded allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects kStats Reloaded: from n/a through 0.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46444 | WordPress Ads Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.88 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46444</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in scripteo Ads Pro Plugin allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ads Pro Plugin: from n/a through 4.88.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46446 | WordPress Libro de Reclamaciones &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46446</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ivanrojas Libro de Reclamaciones allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Libro de Reclamaciones: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46448 | WordPress Document Management System &amp;lt;= 1.24 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46448</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in reifsnyderb Document Management System allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Document Management System: from n/a through 1.24.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46454 | WordPress Meta Keywords &amp;amp; Description &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46454</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in svil4ok Meta Keywords &amp;amp; Description allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Meta Keywords &amp;amp; Description: from n/a through 0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46455 | WordPress WP HRM LITE &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46455</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in IndigoThemes WP HRM LITE allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP HRM LITE: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46456 | WordPress Theme Blvd Sliders plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46456</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason Theme Blvd Sliders allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Blvd Sliders: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46458 | WordPress occupancyplan plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3.0 - CSRF to SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46458</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in x000x occupancyplan allows SQL Injection. This issue affects occupancyplan: from n/a through 1.0.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46460 | WordPress Easy Guide &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Detheme Easy Guide allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Easy Guide: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46463 | WordPress Mailing Group Listserv &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46463</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Yamna Khawaja Mailing Group Listserv allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Mailing Group Listserv: from n/a through 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46468 | WordPress Fable Extra &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46468</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPFable Fable Extra allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Fable Extra: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46474 | WordPress SEUR Oficial &amp;lt;= 2.2.23 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46474</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SEUR OFICIAL SEUR Oficial allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects SEUR Oficial: from n/a through 2.2.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46486 | WordPress Nomupay Payment Processing Gateway &amp;lt;= 7.1.7 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46486</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in totalprocessing Nomupay Payment Processing Gateway allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Nomupay Payment Processing Gateway: from n/a through 7.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46487 | WordPress EC Authorize.net plugin &amp;lt;=  0.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46487</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sftranna EC Authorize.net allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects EC Authorize.net: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46488 | WordPress Visual Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46488</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dastan800 Visual Builder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Visual Builder: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46490 | WordPress Crossword Compiler Puzzles &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46490</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in wordwebsoftware Crossword Compiler Puzzles allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Crossword Compiler Puzzles: from n/a through 5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46493 | WordPress Crossword Compiler Puzzles &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46493</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wordwebsoftware Crossword Compiler Puzzles allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Crossword Compiler Puzzles: from n/a through 5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46515 | WordPress Category Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46515</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M A Vinoth Kumar Category Widget allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Category Widget: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46518 | WordPress IGIT Related Posts With Thumb Image After Posts &amp;lt;=  4.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46518</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in phpaddicted IGIT Related Posts With Thumb Image After Posts allows Stored XSS. This issue affects IGIT Related Posts With Thumb Image After Posts: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46526 | WordPress My Custom Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46526</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in janekniefeldt My Custom Widgets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects My Custom Widgets: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46527 | WordPress Web3Press – Decentralize Publishing with Writing NFT plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46527</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in LikeCoin Web3Press allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Web3Press: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46537 | WordPress Section Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46537</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ctltwp Section Widget allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Section Widget: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46539 | WordPress Fable Extra &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPFable Fable Extra allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Fable Extra: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47438 | WordPress WP Job Portal plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47438</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in wpjobportal WP Job Portal allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47453 | WordPress WP Smart Import &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47453</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Xylus Themes WP Smart Import allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Smart Import: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47458 | WordPress B2i Investor Tools plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47458</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in B2itech B2i Investor Tools allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects B2i Investor Tools: from n/a through 1.0.7.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47461 | WordPress Subaccounts for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47461</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in mediaticus Subaccounts for WooCommerce allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Subaccounts for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47478 | WordPress ProfileGrid  &amp;lt;= 5.9.5.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47478</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid  allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.9.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47492 | WordPress Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47492</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in add-ons.org Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47512 | WordPress Tainacan plugin &amp;lt;=  0.21.14 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47512</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in tainacan Tainacan allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Tainacan: from n/a through 0.21.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47513 | WordPress Infocob CRM Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47513</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in James Laforge Infocob CRM Forms allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Infocob CRM Forms: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47529 | WordPress Experto CTA Widget – Call To Action, Sticky CTA, Floating Button Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Settings Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47529</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UX Design Experts Experto CTA Widget &amp;#8211; Call To Action, Sticky CTA, Floating Button Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Experto CTA Widget &amp;#8211; Call To Action, Sticky CTA, Floating Button Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47530 | WordPress WPFunnels &amp;lt;= 3.5.18 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47530</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WPFunnels WPFunnels allows Object Injection. This issue affects WPFunnels: from n/a through 3.5.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47532 | WordPress CoinPayments.net Payment Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.17 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47532</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in CoinPayments CoinPayments.net Payment Gateway for WooCommerce allows Object Injection. This issue affects CoinPayments.net Payment Gateway for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47535 | WordPress Opal Woo Custom Product Variation &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47535</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wpopal Opal Woo Custom Product Variation allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Opal Woo Custom Product Variation: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47539 | WordPress Eventin &amp;lt;= 4.0.26 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47539</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Themewinter Eventin allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Eventin: from n/a through 4.0.26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47541 | WordPress Mail Mint &amp;lt;= 1.17.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47541</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in WPFunnels Mail Mint allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Mail Mint: from n/a through 1.17.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47558 | WordPress MapSVG plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.31 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47558</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47568 | WordPress ZoomSounds plugin &amp;lt;= 6.91 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47568</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ZoomIt ZoomSounds allows Object Injection. This issue affects ZoomSounds: from n/a through 6.91.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47575 | WordPress School Management plugin &amp;lt;= 92.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in mojoomla School Management allows SQL Injection. This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 92.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47599 | WordPress Facturante &amp;lt;= 1.11 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in facturante Facturante allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Facturante: from n/a through 1.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47603 | WordPress belingoGeo &amp;lt;= 1.12.0 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47603</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Belingo belingoGeo allows Path Traversal. This issue affects belingoGeo: from n/a through 1.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47611 | WordPress User Meta plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47611</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Khaled User Meta allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects User Meta: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47613 | WordPress School Management System for Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 92.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47613</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mojoomla School Management allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects School Management: from n/a through 92.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47618 | WordPress BMI Adult &amp;amp; Kid Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47618</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mortgage Calculator BMI Adult &amp; Kid Calculator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BMI Adult &amp; Kid Calculator: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47619 | WordPress 6Storage Rentals &amp;lt;= 2.19.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47619</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 6Storage 6Storage Rentals allows Path Traversal. This issue affects 6Storage Rentals: from n/a through 2.19.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47631 | WordPress Hospital Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 47.0(20-11-2023) - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47631</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in mojoomla Hospital Management System allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Hospital Management System: from 47.0(20 through 11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47637 | WordPress STAGGS &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47637</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in STAGGS STAGGS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects STAGGS: from n/a through 2.11.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47640 | WordPress Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in printcart Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47641 | WordPress Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47641</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in printcart Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Printcart Web to Print Product Designer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47642 | WordPress Ajar in5 Embed &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47642</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Ajar Productions Ajar in5 Embed allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Ajar in5 Embed: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47646 | WordPress PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Broken Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47646</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password vulnerability in Gilblas Ngunte Possi PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration allows Password Recovery Exploitation. This issue affects PSW Front-end Login &amp;amp; Registration: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47658 | WordPress ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47658</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ELEXtensions ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System: from n/a through 3.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47660 | WordPress WC Affiliate &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47660</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Codexpert, Inc WC Affiliate allows Object Injection. This issue affects WC Affiliate: from n/a through 2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47663 | WordPress Hospital Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 47.0(20-11-2023) - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47663</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in mojoomla Hospital Management System allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Hospital Management System: from 47.0(20 through 11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47670 | WordPress WordPress Social Login and Register &amp;lt;= 7.6.10 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47670</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in miniOrange WordPress Social Login and Register allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WordPress Social Login and Register: from n/a through 7.6.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47671 | WordPress Binary MLM Plan &amp;lt;= 3.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47671</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LETSCMS MLM Software Binary MLM Plan allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Binary MLM Plan: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47672 | WordPress miniOrange Discord Integration &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47672</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in miniOrange miniOrange Discord Integration allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects miniOrange Discord Integration: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47673 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.16 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tychesoftwares Arconix Shortcodes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47678 | WordPress FunnelCockpit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelCockpit FunnelCockpit allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FunnelCockpit: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47680 | WordPress xili-tidy-tags plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.06 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47680</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michel - xiligroup dev xili-tidy-tags allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects xili-tidy-tags: from n/a through 1.12.06.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47687 | WordPress StoreKeeper for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 14.4.4 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47687</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in StoreKeeper B.V. StoreKeeper for WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects StoreKeeper for WooCommerce: from n/a through 14.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47690 | WordPress Lead Form Data Collection to CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47690</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in smackcoders Lead Form Data Collection to CRM allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Lead Form Data Collection to CRM: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48241 | WordPress Verge3D plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Soft8Soft LLC Verge3D allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Verge3D: from n/a through 4.9.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48245 | WordPress Quick Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fullworks Quick Contact Form  allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Quick Contact Form : from n/a through 8.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48271 | WordPress Leadinfo &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Settings Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48271</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leadinfo Leadinfo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Leadinfo: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48273 | WordPress WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48273</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wpjobportal WP Job Portal allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48275 | WordPress Visual Header &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48275</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dastan800 Visual Header allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Visual Header: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48283 | WordPress Majestic Support &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48283</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Majestic Support Majestic Support allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Majestic Support: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48286 | WordPress ReDi Restaurant Reservation plugin &amp;lt;= 24.1209 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in catkin ReDi Restaurant Reservation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ReDi Restaurant Reservation: from n/a through 24.1209.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48287 | WordPress Pix 4x sem juros – Pagaleve &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48287</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Pagaleve Pix 4x sem juros &amp;#8211; Pagaleve allows Object Injection. This issue affects Pix 4x sem juros &amp;#8211; Pagaleve: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48289 | WordPress Kids Planet &amp;lt;= 2.2.14 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48289</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in AncoraThemes Kids Planet allows Object Injection. This issue affects Kids Planet: from n/a through 2.2.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48292 | WordPress Tourmaster plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48292</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in GoodLayers Tourmaster allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Tourmaster: from n/a through 5.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5107 | Fujian Kelixun xml_cdr_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixun 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /app/xml_cdr/xml_cdr_details.php. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5108 | zongzhige ShopXO ZIP File Payment.php Upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zongzhige ShopXO 6.5.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function Upload of the file app/admin/controller/Payment.php of the component ZIP File Handler. The manipulation of the argument params leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1123 | Solid Mail – SMTP email and logging made by SolidWP &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1123</link><description>The Solid Mail – SMTP email and logging made by SolidWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via email Name, Subject, and Body in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5105 | TOZED ZLT W51 Service Port 7777 heap inspection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5105</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOZED ZLT W51 up to 1.4.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Service Port 7777. The manipulation leads to improper clearing of heap memory before release. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5106 | Fujian Kelixun Filename fax_view.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5106</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixun 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /app/fax/fax_view.php of the component Filename Handler. The manipulation of the argument fax_file leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36527 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36527</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8511 are vulnerable to SQL injection while exporting reports.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41407 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41407</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8511 are vulnerable to SQL injection in the OU History report.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3893 | SQL Injection in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3893</link><description>While editing pages managed by MegaBIP a user with high privileges is prompted to give a reasoning for performing this action. Input provided by the the user is not sanitized, leading to SQL Injection vulnerability. 
Version 5.20 of MegaBIP fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3894 | Stored XSS in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3894</link><description>Text editor embedded into MegaBIP software does not neutralize user input allowing Stored XSS attacks on other users. In order to use the editor high privileges are required.  
Version 5.20 of MegaBIP fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3895 | Low token entropy in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3895</link><description>Token used for resetting passwords in MegaBIP software are generated using a small space of random values combined with a queryable value.
 It allows an unauthenticated attacker who know user login names to brute force these tokens and change account passwords (including these belonging to administrators). 
Version 5.20 of MegaBIP fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4379 | Reflected XSS in DobryCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4379</link><description>DobryCMS in versions 2.* and lower is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). Improper input validation in szukaj parameter allows arbitrary JavaScript to be executed on victim's browser when specially crafted URL is opened.

A hotfix for affected versions was released on 29.04.2025. It removes the vulnerability without incrementing the version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:22:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13945 | Stored Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13945</link><description>Stored Absolute Path Traversal vulnerabilities in ASPECT could expose sensitive data 
if administrator credentials become compromised.

This issue affects ASPECT-Enterprise: through 3.*; NEXUS Series: through 3.*; MATRIX Series: through 3.*.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47149 | The optional feature 'Anti-Virus &amp; Sandbox' of i-FILTER contains an issue with improper pattern file validation. If exploited, the product m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47149</link><description>The optional feature 'Anti-Virus &amp; Sandbox' of i-FILTER contains an issue with improper pattern file validation. If exploited, the product may treat an unauthorized pattern file as an authorized. If the product uses a specially crafted pattern file, information in the server where the product is running may be retrieved, and/or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5096 | TablePress &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5096</link><description>The TablePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'data-caption', 'data-s-content-padding', 'data-s-title', and 'data-footer' data-attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48695 | An issue was discovered in CyberDAVA before 1.1.20. A privilege escalation vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to escalate their priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48695</link><description>An issue was discovered in CyberDAVA before 1.1.20. A privilege escalation vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to escalate their privilege by abusing the following API due to the lack of access control: /api/v2/users/user//role/ROLE/ (admin access can be achieved).</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48708 | gs_lib_ctx_stash_sanitized_arg in base/gslibctx.c in Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.0 lacks argument sanitization for the # case.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48708</link><description>gs_lib_ctx_stash_sanitized_arg in base/gslibctx.c in Artifex Ghostscript through 10.05.0 lacks argument sanitization for the # case.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4594 | Tournamatch &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4594</link><description>The Tournamatch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'trn-ladder-registration-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 03:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48701 | openDCIM through 23.04 allows SQL injection in people_depts.php because prepared statements are not used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48701</link><description>openDCIM through 23.04 allows SQL injection in people_depts.php because prepared statements are not used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 03:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5098 | KL-001-2025-003: Mobile Dynamix PrinterShare Mobile Print Gmail Oauth Token Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5098</link><description>PrinterShare Android application allows the capture of Gmail authentication tokens that can be reused to access a user's Gmail account without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5099 | KL-001-2025-004: Mobile Dynamix PrinterShare Mobile Print Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5099</link><description>An Out of Bounds Write occurs when the native library attempts PDF rendering, which can be exploited to achieve memory corruption and potentially arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5100 | KL-001-2025-005: Mobile Dynamix PrinterShare Mobile Print Double-Free Memory Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5100</link><description>A double-free condition occurs during the cleanup of temporary image files, which can be exploited to achieve memory corruption and potentially arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2394 | Ecovacs Home Android and iOS Mobile Applications up to version 3.3.0 contained embedded access keys and secrets for Alibaba Object Storage S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2394</link><description>Ecovacs Home Android and iOS Mobile Applications up to version 3.3.0 contained embedded access keys and secrets for Alibaba Object Storage Service (OSS), leading to sensitive data disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>