<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:41:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-9918 | Zip Slip in Google SecOps SOAR allows for Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9918</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability in the archive extraction component in Google SecOps SOAR Server (versions 6.3.54.0, 6.3.53.2, and all prior versions) allows an authenticated attacker with permissions to import Use Cases to achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) via uploading a malicious ZIP archive containing path traversal sequences.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0763 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0763</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_custom_fields function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change plugin custom fields.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5801 | Digital Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via column Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5801</link><description>The Digital Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘column’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8215 | Responsive Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8215</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8316 | Certifica WP &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via evento Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8316</link><description>The Certifica WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘evento’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8318 | Jobify &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via keyword Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8318</link><description>The Jobify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘keyword’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8392 | Mitfahrgelegenheit &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via date Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8392</link><description>The Mitfahrgelegenheit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘date’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8398 | azurecurve BBCode &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8398</link><description>The azurecurve BBCode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'url' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8417 | Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp;amp; Crawler &amp;lt;= 5.1.4 - Unauthenticated PHP Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8417</link><description>The Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp; Crawler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP code injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.4. This is due to reliance on a guessable numeric token (e.g. ?key= 900001705) without proper authentication, combined with the unsafe use of eval() on user-supplied input. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server via a forged request granted they can guess or brute-force the numeric key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8422 | Propovoice &amp;lt;= 1.7.6.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8422</link><description>The Propovoice: All-in-One Client Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.6.7 via the send_email() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8423 | My WP Translate &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Option Read and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8423</link><description>The My WP Translate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the mtswpt_remove_plugin() and ajax_update_export_code() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read and delete arbitrary WordPress options which can cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8425 | My WP Translate &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8425</link><description>The My WP Translate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the ajax_import_strings() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8445 | Countdown Timer for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;countdown_label&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8445</link><description>The Countdown Timer for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'countdown_label' Parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8481 | Blog Designer For Elementor – Post Slider, Post Carousel, Post Grid &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8481</link><description>The Blog Designer For Elementor – Post Slider, Post Carousel, Post Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.1.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the bdfe_install_activate_rswpbs_only function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install the 'rs-wp-books-showcase' plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8492 | Salon Booking System &amp;lt;= 10.20 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated AJAX Actions Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8492</link><description>The Salon Booking System, Appointment Scheduling for Salons, Spas &amp; Small Businesses plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax function in all versions up to, and including, 10.20. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute AJAX actions, including limited file uploads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8570 | BeyondCart Connector &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Missing Configuration of JWT Secret to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via determine_current_user Filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8570</link><description>The BeyondCart Connector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to improper JWT secret management and authorization within the determine_current_user filter in versions 1.4.2 through 2.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to craft valid tokens and assume any user’s identity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8686 | WP Easy FAQs &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via WP_EASY_FAQ Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8686</link><description>The WP Easy FAQs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's WP_EASY_FAQ shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8689 | Elements Plus! &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8689</link><description>The Elements Plus! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Comparison, HotSpot Plus, and Google Maps widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8691 | WP Scriptcase &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8691</link><description>The WP Scriptcase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8692 | Coupon API &amp;lt;= 6.2.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;log_duration&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8692</link><description>The Coupon API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘log_duration’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8721 | Workable API &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via workable_jobs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8721</link><description>The Workable Api plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's workable_jobs shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9073 | All in one Minifier &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9073</link><description>The All in one Minifier plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9123 | CBX Map for Google Map &amp;amp; OpenStreetMap &amp;lt;= 1.1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9123</link><description>The CBX Map for Google Map &amp; OpenStreetMap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the popup heading and location address parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9128 | eID Easy &amp;lt;= 4.9.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9128</link><description>The eID Easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9451 | Smartcat Translator for WPML &amp;lt;= 3.1.69 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection via orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9451</link><description>The Smartcat Translator for WPML plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.69 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9617 | Publish approval &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9617</link><description>The Publish approval plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the publish_save_option function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9620 | Seo Monster &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9620</link><description>The Seo Monster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the check_integration() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9623 | Admin in English with Switch &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9623</link><description>The Admin in English with Switch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the enable_eng function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify administrator language settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9627 | Run Log &amp;lt;= 1.7.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9627</link><description>The Run Log plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the oirl_plugin_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings including distance units, pace display preferences, style themes, and display positions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9628 | The integration of the AMO.CRM &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9628</link><description>The The integration of the AMO.CRM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings_page function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify critical API connection settings including the AMO.CRM API URL, login credentials, and API hash key via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9631 | AutoCatSet &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9631</link><description>The AutoCatSet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the autocatset_ajax function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger automatic recategorization of posts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9632 | PhpList Subber &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9632</link><description>The PhpList Subber plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the bulk_action_handler function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger bulk synchronization of subscription forms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9633 | LH Signing &amp;lt;= 2.83 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9633</link><description>The LH Signing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.83. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the plugin_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9634 | Plugin updates blocker &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9634</link><description>The Plugin updates blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the pub_save action handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable or enable plugin updates via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9635 | Analytics Reduce Bounce Rate &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9635</link><description>The Analytics Reduce Bounce Rate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the unbounce_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify Google Analytics tracking settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9693 | User Meta – User Profile Builder and User management plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9693</link><description>The User Meta – User Profile Builder and User management plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the postInsertUserProcess function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9850 | Evenium &amp;lt;= 1.3.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9850</link><description>The Evenium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'evenium_single_event' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9855 | Enhanced BibliPlug &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Authenticated (Contirbutor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9855</link><description>The Enhanced BibliPlug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bibliplug_authors' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9860 | Mixtape &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9860</link><description>The Mixtape plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mixtape' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9861 | ThemeLoom Widgets &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9861</link><description>The ThemeLoom Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'los_showposts' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9874 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9874</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 via the 'uclwp_dashboard' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8479 | Zoho Flow &amp;lt;= 2.14.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8479</link><description>The Zoho Flow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.14.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the zoho_flow_deactivate_plugin function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify typography settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 06:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9034 | Wp Edit Password Protected &amp;lt; 1.3.5 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9034</link><description>The Wp Edit Password Protected  WordPress plugin before 1.3.5 does not validate a parameter before redirecting the user to its value, leading to an Open Redirect issue</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 06:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10247 | JEPaaS Filter doFilterInternal access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10247</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in JEPaaS 7.2.8. This vulnerability affects the function doFilterInternal of the component Filter Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9059 | Elevation of Privileges Vulnerability in IT Management Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9059</link><description>The Altiris Core Agent Updater package (AeXNSC.exe) is prone to an elevation of privileges vulnerability through DLL hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10246 | lokibhardwaj PHP-Code-For-Unlimited-File-Upload f.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10246</link><description>A weakness has been identified in lokibhardwaj PHP-Code-For-Unlimited-File-Upload up to 124fe96324915490c81eaf7db3234b0b4e4bab3c. This affects an unknown part of the file /f.php. This manipulation of the argument h causes cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9910 | Versions of the package jsondiffpatch before 0.7.2 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via HtmlFormatter::nodeBegin. An attacker ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9910</link><description>Versions of the package jsondiffpatch before 0.7.2 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via HtmlFormatter::nodeBegin. An attacker can inject malicious scripts into HTML payloads that may lead to code execution if untrusted payloads were used as source for the diff, and the result renderer using the built-in html formatter on a private website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 05:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9776 | CatFolders – Tame Your WordPress Media Library by Category &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection via CSV Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9776</link><description>The CatFolders – Tame Your WordPress Media Library by Category plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the CSV Import contents in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10236 | binary-husky gpt_academic LaTeX File latex_toolbox.py merge_tex_files_ path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10236</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in binary-husky gpt_academic up to 3.91. Impacted is the function merge_tex_files_ of the file crazy_functions/latex_fns/latex_toolbox.py of the component LaTeX File Handler. Such manipulation of the argument \input{} leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 02:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10245 | Display Painéis TGA Galeria rename path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10245</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Display Painéis TGA up to 7.1.41. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /gallery/rename of the component Galeria Page. The manipulation of the argument current_folder results in path traversal. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 02:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6088 | Improper Authorization in danny-avila/librechat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6088</link><description>In version 0.7.8 of danny-avila/librechat, improper authorization controls in the conversation sharing feature allow unauthorized access to other users' conversations if the conversation ID is known. Although UUIDv4 conversation IDs are generated server-side and are difficult to brute force, they can be obtained from less-protected sources such as server-side access logs, browser history, or screenshots. The vulnerability permits a logged-in user to gain read-only access to another user's conversations by exploiting the `/api/share/conversationID` endpoint, which lacks authorization checks. This issue is resolved in version v0.7.9-rc1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10235 | Scada-LTS Reports reports.shtm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10235</link><description>A flaw has been found in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /reports.shtm of the component Reports Module. This manipulation of the argument Colour causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10234 | Scada-LTS Data Point Edit data_point_edit.shtm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10234</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Scada-LTS up to 2.7.8.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /data_point_edit.shtm of the component Data Point Edit Module. The manipulation of the argument Text Renderer properties results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10233 | kalcaddle kodbox editor.class.php fileSave path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10233</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in kalcaddle kodbox 1.61. This affects the function fileGet/fileSave of the file app/controller/explorer/editor.class.php. The manipulation of the argument path leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10232 | 299ko FileManagerAPIController.php delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10232</link><description>A weakness has been identified in 299ko up to 2.0.0. Affected by this issue is the function getSentDir/delete of the file plugin/filemanager/controllers/FileManagerAPIController.php. Executing manipulation can lead to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10229 | Freshwork logout redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10229</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Freshwork up to 1.2.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /api/v2/logout. Such manipulation of the argument post_logout_redirect_uri leads to open redirect. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.2.3 will fix this issue. You should upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10218 | lostvip-com ruoyi-go Background Management SysRoleDao.go SelectListPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10218</link><description>A flaw has been found in lostvip-com ruoyi-go 2.1. This affects the function SelectListPage of the file modules/system/dao/SysRoleDao.go of the component Background Management Page. This manipulation of the argument sortName causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10216 | GrandNode Voucher ConfirmOrder race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10216</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in GrandNode up to 2.3.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /checkout/ConfirmOrder/ of the component Voucher Handler. The manipulation of the argument giftvouchercouponcode results in race condition. The attack may be launched remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59052 | Angular SSR: Global Platform Injector Race Condition Leads to Cross-Request Data Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59052</link><description>Angular is a development platform for building mobile and desktop web applications using TypeScript/JavaScript and other languages. Angular uses a DI container (the "platform injector") to hold request-specific state during server-side rendering. For historical reasons, the container was stored as a JavaScript module-scoped global variable. When multiple requests are processed concurrently, they could inadvertently share or overwrite the global injector state. In practical terms, this can lead to one request responding with data meant for a completely different request, leaking data or tokens included on the rendered page or in response headers. As long as an attacker had network access to send any traffic that received a rendered response, they may have been able to send a large number of requests and then inspect the responses for information leaks. The APIs `bootstrapApplication`, `getPlatform`, and `destroyPlatform` were vulnerable and required SSR-only breaking changes.
The issue has been patched in all active release lines as well as in the v21 prerelease. Patched packages include `@angular/platform-server` 21.0.0-next.3, 20.3.0, 19.2.15, and 18.2.14 and `@angular/ssr` 21.0.0-next.3, 20.3.0, 19.2.16, and 18.2.21. Several workarounds are available. Disable SSR via Server Routes or builder options, remove any asynchronous behavior from custom `bootstrap` functions, remove uses of `getPlatform()` in application code, and/or ensure that the server build defines `ngJitMode` as false.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45669 | IBM Security Verify Information Queue denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45669</link><description>IBM Security Verify Information Queue 10.0.5, 10.0.6, 10.0.7, and 10.0.8 could allow a remote user to cause a denial of service due to improper handling of special characters that could lead to uncontrolled resource consumption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45671 | IBM Security Verify Information Queue information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45671</link><description>IBM Security Verify Information Queue 10.0.5, 10.0.6, 10.0.7, and 10.0.8 

uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47120 | IBM Security Verify Information Queue code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47120</link><description>IBM Security Verify Information Queue 10.0.5, 10.0.6, 10.0.7, and 10.0.8 could allow a privileged user to escalate their privileges and attack surface on the host due to the containers running with unnecessary privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10211 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS getArticle CollectController server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10211</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS 3.3.0. The affected element is the function CollectController of the file /cms/collect/getArticle. The manipulation of the argument taskUrl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43783 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.73 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43783</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.73 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.1, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, 7.4 update 73 through update 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the /c/portal/comment/discussion/get_editor path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54376 | Hoverfly&amp;#x27;s WebSocket endpoint `/api/v2/ws/logs` reachable without authentication even when --auth is enabled.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54376</link><description>Hoverfly is an open source API simulation tool. In versions 1.11.3 and prior, Hoverfly’s admin WebSocket endpoint /api/v2/ws/logs is not protected by the same authentication middleware that guards the REST admin API. Consequently, an unauthenticated remote attacker can stream real-time application logs (information disclosure) and/or gain insight into internal file paths, request/response bodies, and other potentially sensitive data emitted in logs. Version 1.12.0 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10200 | Use after free in Serviceworker in Google Chrome on Desktop prior to 140.0.7339.127 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10200</link><description>Use after free in Serviceworker in Google Chrome on Desktop prior to 140.0.7339.127 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10201 | Inappropriate implementation in Mojo in Google Chrome on Android, Linux, ChromeOS prior to 140.0.7339.127 allowed a remote attacker to bypas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10201</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Mojo in Google Chrome on Android, Linux, ChromeOS prior to 140.0.7339.127 allowed a remote attacker to bypass site isolation via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43784 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.124, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.8, 2024.Q1.1 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43784</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.124, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.8, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows guest users to obtain object entries information via the API Builder.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10210 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS Api.js search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10210</link><description>A weakness has been identified in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.0. Impacted is the function Search of the file app/modules/api/service/Api.js. Executing manipulation of the argument key can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59049 | Mockoon has a Path Traversal and LFI in the static file serving endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59049</link><description>Mockoon provides way to design and run mock APIs. Prior to version 9.2.0, a mock API configuration for static file serving follows the same approach presented in the documentation page, where the server filename is generated via templating features from user input is vulnerable to Path Traversal and LFI, allowing an attacker to get any file in the mock server filesystem.
The issue may be particularly relevant in cloud hosted server instances. Version 9.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54123 | Hoverfly vulnerable to remote code execution at `/api/v2/hoverfly/middleware` endpoint due to insecure middleware implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54123</link><description>Hoverfly is an open source API simulation tool. In versions 1.11.3 and prior, the middleware functionality in Hoverfly is vulnerable to command injection vulnerability at `/api/v2/hoverfly/middleware` endpoint due to insufficient validation and sanitization in user input. The vulnerability exists in the middleware management API endpoint `/api/v2/hoverfly/middleware`. This issue is born due to combination of three code level flaws: Insufficient Input Validation in middleware.go line 94-96; Unsafe Command Execution in local_middleware.go line 14-19; and Immediate Execution During Testing in hoverfly_service.go line 173. This allows an attacker to gain remote code execution (RCE) on any system running the vulnerable Hoverfly service. Since the input is directly passed to system commands without proper checks, an attacker can upload a malicious payload or directly execute arbitrary commands (including reverse shells) on the host server with the privileges of the Hoverfly process. Commit 17e60a9bc78826deb4b782dca1c1abd3dbe60d40 disables the set middleware API by default, and subsequent changes to documentation make users aware of the security changes of exposing the set middleware API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9714 | Stack overflow in libxml2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9714</link><description>Uncontrolled recursion in XPath evaluation in libxml2 up to and including version 2.9.14 allows a local attacker to cause a stack overflow via crafted expressions. XPath processing functions `xmlXPathRunEval`, `xmlXPathCtxtCompile`, and `xmlXPathEvalExpr` were resetting recursion depth to zero before making potentially recursive calls. When such functions were called recursively this could allow for uncontrolled recursion and lead to a stack overflow. These functions now preserve recursion depth across recursive calls, allowing recursion depth to be controlled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10209 | Papermerge DMS Authorization Token improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10209</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Papermerge DMS up to 3.5.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Authorization Token Handler. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8696 | DoS attack against the Stork UI from an unauthenticated user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8696</link><description>If an unauthenticated user sends a large amount of data to the Stork UI, it may cause memory and disk use problems for the system running the Stork server.
This issue affects Stork versions 1.0.0 through 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50892 | The eudskacs.sys driver version 20250328 shipped with EaseUs Todo Backup 1.2.0.1 fails to properly validate privileges for I/O requests (IRP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50892</link><description>The eudskacs.sys driver version 20250328 shipped with EaseUs Todo Backup 1.2.0.1 fails to properly validate privileges for I/O requests (IRP_MJ_READ/IRP_MJ_WRITE) sent to its device object. This allows a local, low-privileged attacker to perform arbitrary raw disk reads and writes, leading to sensitive information disclosure, denial of service, or local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55976 | Intelbras IWR 3000N 1.9.8 exposes the Wi-Fi password in plaintext via the /api/wireless endpoint. Any unauthenticated user on the local netw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55976</link><description>Intelbras IWR 3000N 1.9.8 exposes the Wi-Fi password in plaintext via the /api/wireless endpoint. Any unauthenticated user on the local network can directly obtain the Wi-Fi network password by querying this endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57392 | BenimPOS Masaustu 3.0.x is affected by insecure file permissions. The application installation directory grants Everyone and BUILTIN\Users g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57392</link><description>BenimPOS Masaustu 3.0.x is affected by insecure file permissions. The application installation directory grants Everyone and BUILTIN\Users groups FILE_ALL_ACCESS, allowing local users to replace or modify .exe and .dll files. This may lead to privilege escalation or arbitrary code execution upon launch by another user or elevated context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57520 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Decap CMS thru 3.8.3. Input fields such as body, tags, title, and description are not p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57520</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Decap CMS thru 3.8.3. Input fields such as body, tags, title, and description are not properly sanitized before being rendered in the content preview pane. This enables an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript which executes whenever a user views the preview panel. The vulnerability affects multiple input vectors and does not require user interaction beyond viewing the affected content.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57642 | A Shell Upload vulnerability in Tourism Management System 2.0 allows an attacker to upload and execute arbitrary PHP shell scripts on the se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57642</link><description>A Shell Upload vulnerability in Tourism Management System 2.0 allows an attacker to upload and execute arbitrary PHP shell scripts on the server, leading to remote code execution and unauthorized access to the system. This can result in the compromise of sensitive data and system functionality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43785 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.45 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024 Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.9, 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43785</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.45 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024 Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.9, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, and 7.4 update 45 through update 92 allows remote attackers to execute an arbitrary web script or HTML in the My Workflow Tasks page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20159 | Cisco IOS XR Software Management Interface ACL Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20159</link><description>A vulnerability in the management interface access control list (ACL) processing feature in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured ACLs for the SSH, NetConf, and gRPC features.

This vulnerability exists because management interface ACLs have not been supported on Cisco IOS XR Software Packet I/O infrastructure platforms for Linux-handled features such as SSH, NetConf, or gRPC. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ingress ACL that is applied on the management interface of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20248 | Cisco IOS XR Software Image Verification Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20248</link><description>A vulnerability in the installation process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass Cisco IOS XR Software image signature verification and load unsigned software on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of files during the installation of an .iso file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying contents of the .iso image and then installing and activating it on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load an unsigned file as part of the image activation process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20340 | Cisco IOS XR Address Resolution Protocol Broadcast Storm Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20340</link><description>A vulnerability in the Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) implementation of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a broadcast storm, leading to a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to how Cisco IOS XR Software processes a high, sustained rate of ARP traffic hitting the management interface. Under certain conditions, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an excessive amount of traffic to the management interface of an affected device, overwhelming its ARP processing capabilities. A successful exploit could result in degraded device performance, loss of management connectivity, and complete unresponsiveness of the system, leading to a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43886 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) a Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability. A high privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43886</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) a Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Filesystem access for attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59045 | Stalwart vulnerable to Memory Exhaustion via CalDAV Event Expansion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59045</link><description>Stalwart is a mail and collaboration server. Starting in version 0.12.0 and prior to version 0.13.3, a memory exhaustion vulnerability exists in Stalwart's CalDAV implementation that allows authenticated attackers to cause denial-of-service by triggering unbounded memory consumption through recurring event expansion. An authenticated attacker can crash the Stalwart server by creating recurring events with large payloads and triggering their expansion through CalDAV REPORT requests. A single malicious request expanding 300 events with 1000-character descriptions can consume up to 2 GB of memory. The vulnerability exists in the `ArchivedCalendarEventData.expand` function, which processes CalDAV `REPORT` requests with event expansion. When a client requests recurring events in their expanded form using the `` element, the server stores all expanded event instances in memory without enforcing size limits. Users should upgrade to Stalwart version 0.13.3 or later to receive a fix. If immediate upgrading is not possible, implement memory limits at the container/system level; monitor server memory usage for unusual spikes; consider rate limiting CalDAV REPORT requests; and restrict CalDAV access to trusted users only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43725 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, Generic Application Agent, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, contain(s) an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43725</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, Generic Application Agent, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, contain(s) an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43887 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A low privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43887</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43938 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) a Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability. A high privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43938</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) a Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to gain unauthorized access with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57569 | Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the portList parameter in /goform/setNAT.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57569</link><description>Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the portList parameter in /goform/setNAT.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57571 | Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. via the macFilterList parameter in goform/setNAT.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57571</link><description>Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. via the macFilterList parameter in goform/setNAT.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59034 | Indico may disclose unauthorized user details access via legacy API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59034</link><description>Indico is an event management system that uses Flask-Multipass, a multi-backend authentication system for Flask. Prior to version 3.3.8, a legacy API to retrieve user details could be misused to retrieve profile details of other users without having admin permissions due to a broken access check. Users should to update to Indico 3.3.8 as soon as possible. As a workaround, it is possible to restrict access to the affected API (e.g. in the webserver config).</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59035 | Indico vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting via LaTeX math code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59035</link><description>Indico is an event management system that uses Flask-Multipass, a multi-backend authentication system for Flask. Prior to version 3.3.8, there is a Cross-Site-Scripting vulnerability when rendering LaTeX math code in contribution or abstract descriptions. Users should to update to Indico 3.3.8 as soon as possible. As a workaround, only let trustworthy users create content on Indico. Note that a conference doing a Call for Abstracts actively invites external speakers (who the organizers may not know and thus cannot fully trust) to submit content, hence the need to update to a a fixed version ASAP in particular when using such workflows.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8681 | Pega Platform versions 7.1.0 to Infinity 24.2.2 are affected by a Stored XSS issue in a user interface component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8681</link><description>Pega Platform versions 7.1.0 to Infinity 24.2.2 are affected by a Stored XSS issue in a user interface component.  Requires a high privileged user with a developer role.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43885 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43885</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43884 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43884</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, Hyper-V contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Command execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57572 | Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the onlineList parameter in goform/setParentControl.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57572</link><description>Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the onlineList parameter in goform/setParentControl.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43888 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, Hyper-V, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43888</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, Hyper-V, version(s) 19.19 and 19.20, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57570 | Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the QosList parameter in goform/setQoS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57570</link><description>Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the QosList parameter in goform/setQoS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57573 | Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the wifiTimeClose parameter in goform/setWifi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57573</link><description>Tenda F3 V12.01.01.48_multi and after is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the wifiTimeClose parameter in goform/setWifi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29592 | oasys v1.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in ProcedureController.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29592</link><description>oasys v1.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in ProcedureController.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58764 | Claude Code rg command had Command Injection that allowed bypass of user approval prompt for command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58764</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Due to an error in command parsing, versions prior to 1.0.105 were vulnerable to a bypass of the Claude Code confirmation prompt to trigger execution of an untrusted command. Reliably exploiting this requires the ability to add untrusted content into a Claude Code context window. Users on standard Claude Code auto-update will have received this fix automatically. Users performing manual updates are advised to update to version 1.0.105 or the latest version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59041 | Claude Code vulnerable to arbitrary code execution caused by maliciously configured git email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59041</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. At startup, Claude Code executed a command templated in with `git config user.email`. Prior to version 1.0.105, a maliciously configured user email in git could be used to trigger arbitrary code execution before a user accepted the workspace trust dialog. Users on standard Claude Code auto-update will have received this fix automatically. Users performing manual updates are advised to update to version 1.0.105 or the latest version.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56578 | An issue in RTSPtoWeb v.2.4.3 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and executearbitrary code via the lack of authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56578</link><description>An issue in RTSPtoWeb v.2.4.3 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and executearbitrary code via the lack of authentication mechanisms</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56466 | Hardcoded credentials in Dietly v1.25.0 for android allows attackers to gain sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56466</link><description>Hardcoded credentials in Dietly v1.25.0 for android allows attackers to gain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56413 | OS Command injection vulnerability in function OperateSSH in 1panel 2.0.8 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands via the operation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56413</link><description>OS Command injection vulnerability in function OperateSSH in 1panel 2.0.8 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands via the operation parameter to the /api/v2/hosts/ssh/operate endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56407 | A vulnerability has been found in HuangDou UTCMS V9 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function RunSql of the file a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56407</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HuangDou UTCMS V9 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function RunSql of the file app/modules/ut-data/admin/mysql.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56404 | An issue was discovered in MariaDB MCP 0.1.0 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information via the SSE service as the SSE service lacks u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56404</link><description>An issue was discovered in MariaDB MCP 0.1.0 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information via the SSE service as the SSE service lacks user validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56405 | An issue was discovered in litmusautomation litmus-mcp-server thru 0.0.1 allowing unauthorized attackers to control the target's MCP service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56405</link><description>An issue was discovered in litmusautomation litmus-mcp-server thru 0.0.1 allowing unauthorized attackers to control the target's MCP service through the SSE protocol.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56406 | An issue was discovered in mcp-neo4j 0.3.0 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information or execute arbitrary commands via the SSE servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56406</link><description>An issue was discovered in mcp-neo4j 0.3.0 allowing attackers to gain sensitive information or execute arbitrary commands via the SSE service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10231 | N-central Incorrect Default Permissions could lead to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10231</link><description>An Incorrect File Handling Permission bug exists on the N-central Windows Agent and Probe that, in the right circumstances, can allow a local low-level user to run commands with elevated permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10224 | Incorrect Evaluation of LDAP Nested Groups during Login in AxxonSoft Axxon One</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10224</link><description>Improper Authentication (CWE-287) in the LDAP authentication engine in AxxonSoft Axxon One 2.0.2 and earlier on Windows allows a remote authenticated user to be denied access or misassigned roles via incorrect evaluation of nested LDAP group memberships during login.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10225 | Incorrect Memory Allocation in OpenSSL-Based Session Module in AxxonSoft Axxon One</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10225</link><description>Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer (CWE-119) in the OpenSSL-based session module in AxxonSoft Axxon One 2.0.6 and earlier on Windows allows a remote attacker under high load conditions to cause application crashes or unpredictable behavior via triggering memory reallocation errors when handling expired session keys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10226 | PostgreSQL Upgrade from v10 to v17.4 in AxxonSoft Axxon One 2.0.8 and earlier to Address Multiple Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10226</link><description>Dependency on Vulnerable Third-Party Component (CWE-1395) in the PostgreSQL backend in AxxonSoft Axxon One 2.0.8 and earlier on Windows and Linux allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, or cause denial-of-service via exploitation of multiple known CVEs present in PostgreSQL v10.x, which are resolved in PostgreSQL 17.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10227 | Lack of Encryption in Object Archive in AxxonSoft Axxon One before 2.0.8</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10227</link><description>Missing Encryption of Sensitive Data (CWE-311) in the Object Archive component in AxxonSoft Axxon One before 2.0.8 on Windows and Linux allows a local attacker with access to exported storage or stolen physical drives to extract sensitive archive data in plaintext via lack of encryption at rest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10220 | Outdated Third-Party NuGet Packages in AxxonSoft Axxon One VMS 2.0.0 through 2.0.4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10220</link><description>Use of Unmaintained Third Party Components (CWE-1104) in the NuGet dependency components in AxxonSoft Axxon One VMS 2.0.0 through 2.0.4 on Windows allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or bypass security features via exploitation of vulnerable third-party packages such as Google.Protobuf, DynamicData, System.Runtime.CompilerServices.Unsafe, and others.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10221 | Hardcoded Password Exposure in AxxonNet ARP Agent Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10221</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File (CWE-532) in the ARP Agent component in AxxonSoft Axxon One / AxxonNet 2.0.4 and earlier on Windows platforms allows a local attacker to obtain plaintext credentials via reading TRACE log files containing serialized JSON with passwords.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10222 | Sensitive Information Disclosure in Diagnostic Dumps in AxxonSoft Axxon One VMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10222</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor (CWE-200) in the diagnostic dump component in AxxonSoft Axxon One VMS 2.0.0 through 2.0.1 on Windows allows a local attacker to obtain licensing-related information such as timestamps, license states, and registry values via reading diagnostic export files created by the built-in troubleshooting tool.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10223 | Improper Session Cleanup on Role Removal in Web Admin Panel in AxxonSoft Axxon One</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10223</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration (CWE-613) in the Web Admin Panel in AxxonSoft Axxon One prior to 2.0.3 on Windows allows a local or remote authenticated attacker to retain access with removed privileges via continued use of an unexpired session token until natural expiration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7718 | Resideo Plugin for Resideo - Real Estate WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7718</link><description>The Resideo Plugin for Resideo - Real Estate WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40725 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Azon Dominator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40725</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Azon Dominator. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending them a malicious URL using the “q” parameter in /search via GET. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10213 | DLL search path hijacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10213</link><description>DLL search path hijacking vulnerability in the UPDF.exe executable for Windows version 1.8.5.0 allows attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by placing a dxtn.dll file of their choice in the 'C:\Users\\AppData\Local\Microsoft\WindowsApps\' directory, which could lead to arbitrary code execution and persistence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10214 | DLL search path hijacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10214</link><description>DLL search path hijacking vulnerability in the UPDF.exe executable for Windows version 1.8.5.0 allows attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by placing a FREngine.dll file of their choice in the 'C:\Users\\AppData\Local\UPDF\FREngine\Bin64\' directory, which could lead to arbitrary code execution and persistence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10215 | DLL search path hijacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10215</link><description>DLL search path hijacking vulnerability in the UPDF.exe executable for Windows version 1.8.5.0 allows attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by placing a FREngine.dll file of their choice in the 'C:\Users\Public\AppData\Local\UPDF\FREngine\Bin64\' directory, which could lead to arbitrary code execution and persistence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40979 | DLL search order hijack in Wave by Grandstream Networks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40979</link><description>DLL search order hijacking vulnerability in the wave.exe executable for Windows 11, version 1.27.8. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by placing an arbitrary file in the 'C:\Users\AppData\Local\Temp' directory, which could lead to arbitrary code execution and persistence. This vulnerability is only replicable in versions of Windows 11 and does not affect earlier versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36756 | Device Takeover vulnerability in SolaX Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36756</link><description>A problem with missing authorization on SolaX Cloud platform allows taking over any SolaX solarpanel inverter of which the serial number is known.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36757 | Bypass of administrator login screen in SolaX Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36757</link><description>It is possible to bypass the administrator login screen on SolaX Cloud. An attacker could use parameter tampering to bypass the login screen and gain limited access to the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36758 | Bypass of bruteforce protection in SolaX Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36758</link><description>It is possible to bypass the clipping level of authentication attempts in SolaX Cloud through the use of the 'Forgot Password' functionality as an oracle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36759 | Sensitive Information Disclosure in SolaX Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36759</link><description>Through the provision of user names, SolaX Cloud will suggest (similar) user accounts and thereby leak sensitive information such as user email addresses and phone numbers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41714 | Path Traversal via &amp;#x27;Upload-Key&amp;#x27; in SmartEMS Upload Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41714</link><description>The upload endpoint insufficiently validates the 'Upload-Key' request header. By supplying path traversal sequences, an authenticated attacker can cause the server to create upload-related artifacts outside the intended storage location. In certain configurations this enables arbitrary file write and may be leveraged to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9943 | Unauthenticated SQL Injection Vulnerability in Shibboleth Service Provider</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9943</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in the "ID" attribute of the SAML response when the replay cache of the Shibboleth Service Provider (SP) is configured to use an SQL database as storage service. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this issue via blind SQL injection, allowing for the extraction of arbitrary data from the database, if the database connection is configured to use the ODBC plugin. The vulnerability arises from insufficient escaping of single quotes in the class SQLString (file odbc-store.cpp, lines 253-271).

This issue affects Shibboleth Service Provider through 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10001 | Import any XML, CSV or Excel File to WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.9.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Limited Unsafe File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10001</link><description>The Import any XML, CSV or Excel File to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the import functionality in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload unsafe files like .phar files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10040 | WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.27 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) FTP/SFTP Credential Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10040</link><description>The WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_ftp_details' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 7.27. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve a configured set of SFTP/FTP credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10049 | Responsive Filterable Portfolio &amp;lt;= 1.0.24 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10049</link><description>The Responsive Filterable Portfolio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation via the HdnMediaSelection_image field in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10126 | MyBrain Utilities &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10126</link><description>The MyBrain Utilities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugins's 'mbumap' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10142 | PagBank / PagSeguro Connect para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.44.3 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10142</link><description>The PagBank / PagSeguro Connect para WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'status' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.44.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6189 | Duplicate Page and Post &amp;lt;= 2.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via meta_key Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6189</link><description>The Duplicate Page and Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘meta_key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7049 | WPGYM - Wordpress Gym Management System &amp;lt;= 67.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7049</link><description>The WPGYM - Wordpress Gym Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 67.7.0 via the 'MJ_gmgt_gmgt_add_user' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change the email, password, and other details of any user, including Administrator users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7826 | Testimonial &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7826</link><description>The Testimonial plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'iNICtestimonial' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7843 | Auto Save Remote Images (Drafts) &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7843</link><description>The Auto Save Remote Images (Drafts) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 via the fetch_images() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8778 | NitroPack &amp;lt;= 1.18.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Settings Update via nitropack_set_compression_ajax Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8778</link><description>The NitroPack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the nitropack_set_compression_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.18.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the nitropack-enableCompression option and effectively change plugin compression settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9367 | Welcart e-Commerce &amp;lt;= 2.11.20 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9367</link><description>The Welcart e-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9463 | Payments Plugin and Checkout Plugin for WooCommerce: Stripe, PayPal, Square, Authorize.net &amp;lt;= 1.117.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via order_by Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9463</link><description>The Payments Plugin and Checkout Plugin for WooCommerce: Stripe, PayPal, Square, Authorize.net plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order_by’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.117.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9622 | WP Blast | SEO &amp;amp; Performance Booster &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Cache Clearing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9622</link><description>The WP Blast | SEO &amp; Performance Booster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple administrative actions in the Settings class. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger cache purging, sitemap clearing, plugin data purging, and score resetting operations via forged requests granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9857 | Heateor Login – Social Login Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9857</link><description>The Heateor Login – Social Login Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Heateor_Facebook_Login' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9888 | Maspik &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9888</link><description>The Maspik – Ultimate Spam Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the clear_log function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear all spam logs via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9979 | Maspik &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Spam Log Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9979</link><description>The Maspik plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in version 2.5.6 and prior. This is due to missing capability checks on the Maspik_spamlog_download_csv function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to export and download the spam log database containing blocked submission attempts, which may include misclassified but legitimate submissions with sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8388 | PowerPack Lite for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting Via &amp;#x27;cursor_url&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8388</link><description>The PowerPack Elementor Addons (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘cursor_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 04:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10197 | HJSoft HCM Human Resources Management System downlawbase sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10197</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HJSoft HCM Human Resources Management System up to 20250822. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /templates/attestation/../../selfservice/lawresource/downlawbase. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10195 | Seismic App com.seismic.doccenter AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10195</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Seismic App 2.4.2 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.seismic.doccenter. Such manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10172 | UTT 750W formPictureUrl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10172</link><description>A flaw has been found in UTT 750W up to 3.2.2-191225. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/formPictureUrl. Executing manipulation of the argument importpictureurl can lead to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59044 | Himmelblau vulnerable to GID collision via group name-derived mapping (privilege escalation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59044</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. Himmelblau 0.9.x derives numeric GIDs for Entra ID groups from the group display name when himmelblau.conf `id_attr_map = name` (the default configuration). Because Microsoft Entra ID allows multiple groups with the same `displayName` (including end-user–created personal/O365 groups, depending on tenant policy), distinct directory groups can collapse to the same numeric GID on Linux. This issue only applies to Himmelblau versions 0.9.0 through 0.9.22. Any resource or service on a Himmelblau-joined host that enforces authorization by numeric GID (files/dirs, etc.) can be unintentionally accessible to a user who creates or joins a different Entra/O365 group that happens to share the same `displayName` as a privileged security group. Users should upgrade to 0.9.23, or 1.0.0 or later, to receive a patch. Group to GID mapping now uses Entra ID object IDs (GUIDs) and does not collide on same-name groups. As a workaround, use tenant policy hardening to restrict arbitrary group creation until all hosts are patched.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59046 | interactive-git-checkout has Command Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59046</link><description>The npm package `interactive-git-checkout` is an interactive command-line tool that allows users to checkout a git branch while it prompts for the branch name on the command-line. It is available as an npm package and can be installed via `npm install -g interactive-git-checkout`. Versions up to and including 1.1.4 of the `interactive-git-checkout` tool are vulnerable to a command injection vulnerability because the software passes the branch name to the `git checkout` command using the Node.js child process module's `exec()` function without proper input validation or sanitization. Commit 8dd832dd302af287a61611f4f85e157cd1c6bb41 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59039 | Prebid Universal Creative on npm briefly compromised</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59039</link><description>Prebid Universal Creative (PUC) is a JavaScript API to render multiple formats. Npm users of PUC 1.17.3 or PUC latest were briefly affected by crypto-related malware. This includes the extremely popular jsdelivr hosting of this file. The maintainers of PUC unpublished version 1.17.3. Users should see Prebid.js 9 release notes for suggestions on moving off the deprecated workflow of using the PUC or pointing to a dynamic version of it. PUC users pointing to latest should transition to 1.17.2 as soon as possible to avoid similar attacks in the future.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59042 | PyInstaller has local privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59042</link><description>PyInstaller bundles a Python application and all its dependencies into a single package. Due to a special entry being appended to `sys.path` during the bootstrap process of a PyInstaller-frozen application, and due to the bootstrap script attempting to load an optional module for bytecode decryption while this entry is still present in `sys.path`, an application built with PyInstaller &lt; 6.0.0 may be tricked by an unprivileged attacker into executing arbitrary python code when **all** of the following conditions are met. First, the application is built with PyInstaller &lt; 6.0.0; both onedir and onefile mode are affected. Second, the optional bytecode encryption code feature was not enabled during the application build. Third, the attacker can create files/directories in the same directory where the executable is located. Fourth, the filesystem supports creation of files/directories that contain `?` in their name (i.e., non-Windows systems). Fifth, the attacker is able to determine the offset at which the PYZ archive is embedded in the executable. The attacker can create a directory (or a zip archive) next to the executable, with the name that matches the format used by PyInstaller's bootloader to transmit information about the location of PYZ archive to the bootstrap script. If this directory (or zip archive) contains a python module whose name matches the name used by the optional bytecode encryption feature, this module will be loaded and executed by the bootstrap script (in the absence of the real, built-in module that is available when the bytecode-encryption feature is enabled). This results in arbitrary code execution that requires no modification of the executable itself. If the executable is running with elevated privileges (for example, due to having the `setuid` bit set), the code in the injected module is also executed with the said elevated privileges, resulting in a local privilege escalation. PyInstaller 6.0.0 (f5adf291c8b832d5aff7632844f7e3ddf7ad4923) removed support for bytecode encryption; this effectively removes the described attack vector, due to the bootstrap script not attempting to load the optional module for bytecode-decryption anymore. PyInstaller 6.10.0 (cfd60b510f95f92cb81fc42735c399bb781a4739) reworked the bootstrap process to avoid (ab)using `sys.path` for transmitting location of the PYZ archive, which further eliminates the possibility of described injection procedure. If upgrading PyInstaller is not feasible, this issue can be worked around by ensuring proper permissions on directories containing security-sensitive executables (i.e., executables with `setuid` bit set) should mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58447 | rAthena has heap-based buffer overflow in login server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58447</link><description>rAthena is an open-source cross-platform massively multiplayer online role playing game (MMORPG) server. Versions prior to commit 2f5248b have a heap-based buffer overflow in the login server, remote attacker to overwrite adjacent session fields by sending a crafted `CA_SSO_LOGIN_REQ` with an oversized token length. This leads to immediate denial of service (crash) and it is possible to achieve remote code execution via heap corruption. Commit 2f5248b fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58448 | rAthena has SQL Injection in PartyBooking component via `WorldName` parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58448</link><description>rAthena is an open-source cross-platform massively multiplayer online role playing game (MMORPG) server. Versions prior to commit 0d89ae0 have a SQL Injection in the PartyBooking component via `WorldName` parameter. Commit 0d89ae0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58750 | rAthena missing bound check in chclif_parse_moveCharSlot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58750</link><description>rAthena is an open-source cross-platform massively multiplayer online role playing game (MMORPG) server. Versions prior to commit 0cc348b are missing a bound check in `chclif_parse_moveCharSlot` that can result in reading and writing out of bounds using input from the user. The problem has been fixed in commit 0cc348b.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59038 | Prebid.js NPM package briefly compromised</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59038</link><description>Prebid.js is a free and open source library for publishers to quickly implement header bidding. NPM users of prebid 10.9.2 may have been briefly compromised by a malware campaign. The malicious code attempts to redirect crypto transactions on the site to the attackers' wallet. Version 10.10.0 fixes the issue. As a workaround, it is also possible to downgrade to 10.9.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59036 | Infrahub allows authentication with deleted and expired API tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59036</link><description>Infrahub offers a central hub to manage data, templates, and playbooks. Prior to versiond 1.3.9 and 1.4.5, a bug in the authentication logic will cause API tokens that were deleted and/or expired to be considered valid. This means that any API token that is associated with an active user account can authenticate successfully. This issue is fixed in versions 1.3.9 and 1.4.5. As a workaround, users can delete or deactivate the account associated with a deleted API token to prevent that token from authenticating.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58131 | Zoom Workplace VDI Plugin macOS Universal installer for VMware Horizon - Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58131</link><description>Race condition in the Zoom Workplace VDI Plugin macOS Universal installer for VMware Horizon before version 6.4.10 (or before 6.2.15 and 6.3.12 in their respective tracks) may allow an authenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58134 | Zoom Workplace Clients for Windows - Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58134</link><description>Incorrect authorization in certain Zoom Workplace Clients for Windows may allow an authenticated user to conduct an impact to integrity via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58135 | Zoom Workplace Clients for Windows - Improper Action Enforcement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58135</link><description>Improper action enforcement in certain Zoom Workplace Clients for Windows may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49460 | Zoom Workplace Clients - Argument Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49460</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption in certain Zoom Workplace Clients may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49461 | Zoom Workplace Clients - Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49461</link><description>Cross-site scripting in certain Zoom Workplace Clients may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54258 | Substance3D - Modeler | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54258</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.22.2 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file. Scope is unchanged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54259 | Substance3D - Modeler | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54259</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.22.2 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file. Scope is unchanged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54260 | Substance3D - Modeler | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54260</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.22.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file. Scope is unchanged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10171 | UTT 1250GW formConfigApConfTemp sub_453DC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10171</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 1250GW up to 3.2.2-200710. This vulnerability affects the function sub_453DC of the file /goform/formConfigApConfTemp. Performing manipulation results in buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49458 | Zoom Workplace Clients - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49458</link><description>Buffer overflow in certain Zoom Workplace Clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49459 | Zoom Workplace for Windows on ARM  - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49459</link><description>Missing authorization in the installer for Zoom Workplace for Windows on ARM before version 6.5.0 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9997 | CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability exists that could cause com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9997</link><description>CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability exists that could cause command injection in BLMon that is executed in the operating system console when in a SSH session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54243 | Substance3D - Viewer | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54243</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54244 | Substance3D - Viewer | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54244</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54245 | Substance3D - Viewer | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54245</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58462 | OPEXUS FOIAXpress PAL SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58462</link><description>OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL) before version 11.13.1.0 allows SQL injection via SearchPopularDocs.aspx. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could read, write, or delete any content in the underlying database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9996 | CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability exists that could cause the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9996</link><description>CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability exists that could cause the execution of any shell command when executing a netstat command using BLMon Console in an SSH session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10159 | An authentication bypass vulnerability allows remote attackers to gain administrative privileges on Sophos AP6 Series Wireless Access Points...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10159</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability allows remote attackers to gain administrative privileges on Sophos AP6 Series Wireless Access Points older than firmware version 1.7.2563 (MR7).</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10169 | UTT 1200GW ConfigWirelessBase buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10169</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 1200GW up to 3.0.0-170831. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/ConfigWirelessBase. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10170 | UTT 1200GW formApLbConfig sub_4B48F8 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10170</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 1200GW up to 3.0.0-170831. This affects the function sub_4B48F8 of the file /goform/formApLbConfig. Such manipulation of the argument loadBalanceNameOld leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23342 | The NVIDIA NVDebug tool contains a vulnerability that may allow an actor to gain access to a privileged account . A successful exploit of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23342</link><description>The NVIDIA NVDebug tool contains a vulnerability that may allow an actor to gain access to a privileged account . A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23343 | The NVIDIA NVDebug tool contains a vulnerability that may allow an actor to write files to restricted components. A successful exploit of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23343</link><description>The NVIDIA NVDebug tool contains a vulnerability that may allow an actor to write files to restricted components. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure, denial of service, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23344 | The NVIDIA NVDebug tool contains a vulnerability that may allow an actor to run code on the platform host as a non-privileged user. A succes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23344</link><description>The NVIDIA NVDebug tool contains a vulnerability that may allow an actor to run code on the platform host as a non-privileged user. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7746 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability exists that could cause an unvali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7746</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability exists that could cause an unvalidated data injected by a malicious user potentially leading to modify or read data in a victim’s browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54239 | After Effects | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54239</link><description>After Effects versions 25.3, 24.6.7 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure, potentially disclosing sensitive information. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54240 | After Effects | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54240</link><description>After Effects versions 25.3, 24.6.7 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure, potentially disclosing sensitive information. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54241 | After Effects | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54241</link><description>After Effects versions 25.3, 24.6.7 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure, potentially disclosing sensitive information. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57633 | A command injection vulnerability in FTP-Flask-python through 5173b68 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary OS comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57633</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in FTP-Flask-python through 5173b68 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands. The /ftp.html endpoint's "Upload File" action constructs a shell command from the ftp_file parameter and executes it using os.system() without sanitization or escaping.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54084 | Calix Gigacenter ONT  - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54084</link><description>OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Calix GigaCenter ONT (Quantenna SoC modules) allows authenticated attackers with 'super' user credentials to execute arbitrary OS commands through improper input validation, potentially leading to full system compromise.This issue affects GigaCenter ONT: 844E, 844G, 844GE, 854GE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34178 | Netgate pfSense CE Suricata package v7.0.8_2 Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34178</link><description>In pfSense CE /suricata/suricata_app_parsers.php, the value of the policy_name parameter is not sanitized of HTML-related strings/characters before being directly displayed. This can result in stored cross-site scripting. The attacker must be authenticated with at least "WebCfg - Services: suricata package" permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43491 | Poly Lens Desktop Application – Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43491</link><description>A vulnerability in the Poly Lens Desktop application running on the Windows platform might allow modifications to the filesystem, which might lead to SYSTEM level privileges being granted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44595 | Halo v2.20.17 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /halo_host/archives/{name}.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44595</link><description>Halo v2.20.17 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /halo_host/archives/{name}.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54083 | Calix GigaCenter ONT firmware - Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54083</link><description>Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Calix GigaCenter ONT (Quantenna SoC modules) allows admin access to the web interface.This issue affects GigaCenter ONT: 844E, 844G, 844GE, 854GE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59037 | DuckDB NPM packages 1.3.3 and 1.29.2 briefly compromised with malware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59037</link><description>DuckDB is an analytical in-process SQL database management system. On 08 September 2025, the DuckDB distribution for Node.js on npm was compromised with malware (along with several other packages). An attacker published new versions of four of DuckDB's packages that included malicious code to interfere with cryptocoin transactions* According to the npm statistics, nobody has downloaded these packages before they were deprecated. The packages and versions `@duckdb/node-api@1.3.3`, `@duckdb/node-bindings@1.3.3`, `duckdb@1.3.3`, and `@duckdb/duckdb-wasm@1.29.2` were affected. DuckDB immediately deprecated the specific versions, engaged npm support to delete the affected verions, and re-released the node packages with higher version numbers (1.3.4/1.30.0). Users may upgrade to versions 1.3.4, 1.30.0, or a higher version to protect themselves. As a workaround, they may also downgrade to 1.3.2 or 1.29.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34176 | Netgate pfSense CE Suricata Package v7.0.8_2 Directory Traversal Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34176</link><description>In pfSense CE /suricata/suricata_ip_reputation.php, the value of the iplist parameter is not sanitized of directory traversal-related strings/characters. This value is directly used in a file existence check operation. While the contents of the file cannot be read, the server reveals whether the file exists, which enables an attacker to enumerate files on the target. The attacker must be authenticated with at least "WebCfg - Services: suricata package" permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34177 | Netgate pfSense CE Suricata package v7.0.8_2 Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34177</link><description>In pfSense CE /suricata/suricata_flow_stream.php, the value of the policy_name parameter is not sanitized of HTML-related strings/characters before being directly displayed. This can result in stored cross-site scripting. The attacker must be authenticated with at least "WebCfg - Services: suricata package" permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44593 | Halo prior to 2.20.13 allows bypassing file type detection and uploading malicious files such as .exe and .html files. Specifically, .html f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44593</link><description>Halo prior to 2.20.13 allows bypassing file type detection and uploading malicious files such as .exe and .html files. Specifically, .html files can trigger stored XSS vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.13</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58763 | Tautulli vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution via Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58763</link><description>Tautulli is a Python based monitoring and tracking tool for Plex Media Server. A command injection vulnerability in Tautulli v2.15.3 and prior allows attackers with administrative privileges to obtain remote code execution on the application server. This vulnerability requires the application to have been cloned from GitHub and installed manually. When Tautulli is cloned directly from GitHub and installed manually, the application manages updates and versioning through calls to the `git` command. In the code, this is performed through the `runGit` function in `versioncheck.py`. Since `shell=True` is passed to `subproces.Popen`, this call is vulnerable to subject to command injection, as shell characters within arguments will be passed to the underlying shell. A concrete location where this can be triggered is in the `checkout_git_branch` endpoint. This endpoint stores a user-supplied remote and branch name into the `GIT_REMOTE` and `GIT_BRANCH` configuration keys without sanitization. Downstream, these keys are then fetched and passed directly into `runGit` using a format string. Hence, code execution can be obtained by using `$()` interpolation in a command. Version 2.16.0 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58765 | wabac.js has XSS vulnerability in 404 error handling logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58765</link><description>wabac.js provides a full web archive replay system, or 'wayback machine', using Service Workers. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the 404 error handling logic of wabac.js v2.23.10 and below. The parameter `requestURL` (derived from the original request target) is directly embedded into an inline `</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58768 | DeepChat&amp;#x27;s Mermaid rendering has XSS leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58768</link><description>DeepChat is a smart assistant uses artificial intelligence. Prior to version 0.3.5, in the Mermaid chart rendering component, there is a risky operation of directly using `innerHTML` to set user content. Therefore, any malicious content rendered via Mermaid will directly trigger the exploit chain, leading to command execution. This vulnerability is primarily caused by a failure to fully address the existing XSS issue in the project, leading to another exploit chain. The exploit chain is consistent with the report GHSA-hqr4-4gfc-5p2j, executing arbitrary JavaScript code via XSS and arbitrary commands via exposed IPC. Version 0.3.5 contains an updated fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34174 | Netgate pfSense CE Status_Traffic_Totals Package v2.3.2_7 Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34174</link><description>In pfSense CE /usr/local/www/status_traffic_totals.php, the value of the start-day parameter is not ensured to be a numeric value or sanitized of HTML-related characters/strings before being directly displayed in the input box. This value can be saved as the default value to be displayed to all users when visiting the Status Traffic Totals page, resulting in stored cross-site scripting. The attacker must be authenticated with at least "WebCfg - Status: Traffic Totals" permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34175 | Netgate pfSense CE Suricata package v7.0.8_2 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34175</link><description>In pfSense CE /usr/local/www/suricata/suricata_filecheck.php, the value of the filehash parameter is directly displayed without sanitizing for HTML-related characters/strings. This can result in reflected cross-site scripting if the victim is authenticated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54255 | Acrobat Reader | Violation of Secure Design Principles (CWE-657)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54255</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30254, 20.005.30774, 25.001.20672 and earlier are affected by a Violation of Secure Design Principles vulnerability that could result in a security feature bypass. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54257 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54257</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30254, 20.005.30774, 25.001.20672 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file, and scope is unchanged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58762 | Tautulli vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution via write primitive and `Script` notification agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58762</link><description>Tautulli is a Python based monitoring and tracking tool for Plex Media Server. In Tautulli v2.15.3 and earlier, an attacker with administrative access can use the `pms_image_proxy` endpoint to write arbitrary python scripts into the application filesystem. This leads to remote code execution when combined with the `Script` notification agent. If an attacker with administrative access changes the URL of the PMS to a server they control, they can then abuse the `pms_image_proxy` to obtain a file write into the application filesystem. This can be done by making a `pms_image_proxy` request with a URL in the `img` parameter and the desired file name in the `img_format` parameter. Tautulli then uses a hash of the desired metadata together with the `img_format` in order to construct a file path. Since the attacker controls `img_format` which occupies the end of the file path, and `img_format` is not sanitised, the attacker can then use path traversal characters to specify filename of their choosing. If the specified file does not exist, Tautaulli will then attempt to fetch the image from the configured PMS. Since the attacker controls the PMS, they can return arbitrary content in response to this request, which will then be written into the specified file. An attacker can write an arbitrary python script into a location on the application file system. The attacker can then make use of the built-in `Script` notification agent to run the local script, obtaining remote code execution on the application server. Users should upgrade to version 2.16.0 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7635 | Calix GigaCenter ONT - Unauthenticated Telnet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7635</link><description>Unauthenticated Telnet access vulnerability in Calix GigaCenter ONT allows root access.This issue affects GigaCenter ONT: 844E, 844G, 844GE, 854GE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34173 | Netgate pfSense CE Snort package v4.1.6_25 Directory Traversal Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34173</link><description>In pfSense CE /usr/local/www/snort/snort_ip_reputation.php, the value of the iplist parameter is not sanitized of directory traversal-related characters/strings before being used to check if a file exists. While the contents of the file cannot be read, the server reveals whether a file exists, which allows an attacker to enumerate files on the target. The attacker must be authenticated with at least "WebCfg - Services: Snort package" permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44594 | halo v2.20.17 and before is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) in /apis/uc.api.storage.halo.run/v1alpha1/attachments/-/upload-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44594</link><description>halo v2.20.17 and before is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF) in /apis/uc.api.storage.halo.run/v1alpha1/attachments/-/upload-from-url.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53914 | Calix GigaCenter ONT (Broadcom SoC) - Excessive Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53914</link><description>Excessive Privileges vulnerability in Calix GigaCenter ONT (Broadcom SoC modules) allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects GigaCenter ONT: 844E, 844G, 844GE, 854GE, 812G, 813G, 818G.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58760 | Tautulli vulnerable to Unauthenticated Path Traversal in `/image` endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58760</link><description>Tautulli is a Python based monitoring and tracking tool for Plex Media Server. The `/image` API endpoint in Tautulli v2.15.3 and earlier is vulnerable to path traversal, allowing unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files from the application server's filesystem. In Tautulli, the `/image` API endpoint is used to serve static images from the application's data directory to users. This endpoint can be accessed without authentication, and its intended purpose is for server background images and icons within the user interface. Attackers can exfiltrate files from the application file system, including the `tautulli.db` SQLite database containing active JWT tokens, as well as the `config.ini` file which contains the hashed admin password, the JWT token secret, and the Plex Media Server token and connection details. If the password is cracked, or if a valid JWT token is present in the database, an unauthenticated attacker can escalate their privileges to obtain administrative control over the application. Version 2.16.0 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58761 | Tautulli vulnerable to Unauthenticated Path Traversal in `real_pms_image_proxy`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58761</link><description>Tautulli is a Python based monitoring and tracking tool for Plex Media Server. The `real_pms_image_proxy` endpoint in Tautulli v2.15.3 and prior is vulnerable to path traversal, allowing unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files from the application server's filesystem. The `real_pms_image_proxy` is used to fetch an image directly from the backing Plex Media Server. The image to be fetched is specified through an `img` URL parameter, which can either be a URL or a file path. There is some validation ensuring that `img` begins with the prefix `interfaces/default/images` in order to be served from the local filesystem. However this can be bypassed by passing an `img` parameter which begins with a valid prefix, and then adjoining path traversal characters in order to reach files outside of intended directories. An attacker can exfiltrate files on the application file system, including the `tautulli.db` SQLite database containing active JWT tokens, as well as the `config.ini` file which contains the hashed admin password, the JWT token secret, and the Plex Media Server token and connection details. If the password is cracked, or if a valid JWT token is present in the database, an unauthenticated attacker can escalate their privileges to obtain administrative control over the application. Version 2.16.0 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53913 | Calix GigaCenter ONT (Quantenna SoC) - Excessive Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53913</link><description>Excessive Privileges vulnerability in Calix GigaCenter ONT (Quantenna SoC modules) allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects GigaCenter ONT: 844E, 844G, 844GE, 854GE, 812G, 813G, 818G.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58753 | copyparty: Sharing a single file does not fully restrict access to other files in source folder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58753</link><description>Copyparty is a portable file server. In versions prior to 1.19.8, there was a missing permission-check in the shares feature (the `shr` global-option). When a share was created for just one file inside a folder, it was possible to access the other files inside that folder by guessing the filenames. It was not possible to descend into subdirectories in this manner; only the sibling files were accessible. This issue did not affect filekeys or dirkeys. Version 1.19.8 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58758 | TinyEnv: Missing .env file not required — may cause unexpected behavior</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58758</link><description>TinyEnv is an environment variable loader for PHP applications. In versions 1.0.1, 1.0.2, 1.0.9, and 1.0.10, TinyEnv did not require the `.env` file to exist when loading environment variables. This could lead to unexpected behavior where the application silently ignores missing configuration, potentially causing insecure defaults or deployment misconfigurations. The issue has been fixed in version 1.0.11. All users should upgrade to 1.0.11 or later. As a workaround, users can manually verify the existence of the `.env` file before initializing TinyEnv.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58759 | TinyEnv: Inline comments not stripped properly in .env values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58759</link><description>TinyEnv is an environment variable loader for PHP applications. In versions 1.0.9 and 1.0.10, TinyEnv did not properly strip inline comments inside .env values. This could lead to unexpected behavior or misconfiguration, where variables contain unintended characters (including # or comment text). Applications depending on strict environment values may expose logic errors, insecure defaults, or failed authentication. The issue is fixed in v1.0.11. Users should upgrade to the latest patched version. As a temporary workaround, avoid using inline comments in .env files, or sanitize loaded values manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58435 | Open OnDemand didn&amp;#x27;t rotate password for VNC batch_connect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58435</link><description>Open OnDemand is an open-source HPC portal. Prior to versions 3.1.15 and 4.0.7, noVNC interactive applications did not correctly rotate the password when TurboVNC was higher than version 3.1.2. The likelihood of exploitation is low as a user would need to share their link to an active desktop session and the other user would need to be authenticated to the portal. But obtaining the link would allow that user to perform any actions as the original user and access their data. Open OnDemand 3.1.15 and 4.0.7 have patched this vulnerability and correctly rotate passwords for any version of TurboVNC. As a workaround, downgrade TurboVNC to a version lower than 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58442 | Saleor has user enumeration vulnerability due to different error messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58442</link><description>Saleor is an e-commerce platform. Starting in version 3.21.0 and prior to version 3.21.16, requesting certain fields in the response of `accountRegister` may result in errors that could unintentionally reveal whether a user with the provided email already exists in Saleor. Version 3.21.16 fixes the issue. As a workaround, rate-limit the mutation to reduce the impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34172 | Netgate pfSense CE HAProxy Package 0.63_10 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34172</link><description>In pfSense CE /usr/local/www/haproxy/haproxy_stats.php, the value of the showsticktablecontent parameter is displayed after being read from HTTP GET requests. This can enable reflected cross-site scripting when the victim is authenticated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36011 | IBM Jazz for Service Management information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36011</link><description>IBM Jazz for Service Management 1.1.3.0 through 1.1.3.24 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58180 | OctoPrint is Vulnerable to RCE Attacks via Unsanitized Filename in File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58180</link><description>OctoPrint provides a web interface for controlling consumer 3D printers. OctoPrint versions up until and including 1.11.2 contain a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to upload a file under a specially crafted filename that will allow arbitrary command execution if said filename becomes included in a command defined in a system event handler and said event gets triggered. If no event handlers executing system commands with uploaded filenames as parameters have been configured, this vulnerability does not have an impact. The vulnerability is patched in version 1.11.3. As a workaround, OctoPrint administrators who have event handlers configured that include any kind of filename based placeholders should disable those by setting their `enabled` property to `False` or unchecking the "Enabled" checkbox in the GUI based Event Manager. Alternatively, OctoPrint administrators should set `feature.enforceReallyUniversalFilenames` to `true` in `config.yaml` and restart OctoPrint, then vet the existing uploads and make sure to delete any suspicious looking files. As always, OctoPrint administrators are advised to not expose OctoPrint on hostile networks like the public internet, and to vet who has access to their instance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58430 | listmonk Vulnerable to CSRF to XSS Chain That Can Lead to Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58430</link><description>listmonk is a standalone, self-hosted, newsletter and mailing list manager. In versions up to and including 1.1.0, every http request in addition to the session cookie `session` there included `nonce`. The value is not checked and validated by the backend, removing `nonce` allows the requests to be processed correctly. This may seem harmless, but if chained to other vulnerabilities it can become a critical vulnerability. Cross-site request forgery and cross-site scripting chained together can result in improper admin account creation. As of time of publication, no patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36125 | IBM Hardware Management Console - Power Systems cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36125</link><description>IBM Hardware Management Console - Power 10.3.1050.0 and 11.1.1110.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58063 | CoreDNS: DNS Cache Pinning via etcd Lease ID Confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58063</link><description>CoreDNS is a DNS server that chains plugins. Starting in version 1.2.0 and prior to version 1.12.4, the CoreDNS etcd plugin contains a TTL confusion vulnerability where lease IDs are incorrectly used as TTL values, enabling DNS cache pinning attacks. This effectively creates a DoS condition for DNS resolution of affected services. The `TTL()` function in `plugin/etcd/etcd.go` incorrectly casts etcd lease IDs (64-bit integers) to uint32 and uses them as TTL values. Large lease IDs become very large TTLs when cast to uint32. This enables cache pinning attacks. Version 1.12.4 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47415 | RECWAVE Filepath Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47415</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CRESTRON TOUCHSCREENS x70 allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects TOUCHSCREENS x70: from 3.000.0110.001 before 3.001.0031.001.











Confirmed Affected Hardware: TSW-760, TSW-1060 



Confirmed Affected Firmware: 3.002.1061 - (no fix released, product discontinued)



 

For x70  



The Affected Firmware:- 3.000.0110.001  and versions below 



The Fixed Firmware:- 3.001.0031.001</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43786 | Enumeration of ERC from object entry in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.1, 2024.Q2.0 throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43786</link><description>Enumeration of ERC from object entry in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.1, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, 2023.Q4.0 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allow attackers to determine existent ERC in the application by exploit the time response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55053 | CWE-328: Use of Weak Hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55053</link><description>CWE-328: Use of Weak Hash</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55054 | CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting')</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55054</link><description>CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55051 | CWE-1392: Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55051</link><description>CWE-1392: Use of Default Credentials</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55052 | CWE-200 Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55052</link><description>CWE-200 Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55050 | CWE-1242: Inclusion of Undocumented Features</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55050</link><description>CWE-1242: Inclusion of Undocumented Features</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43781 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.110 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43781</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.110 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.8, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the URL in search bar portlet</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55049 | Use of Default Cryptographic Key (CWE-1394)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55049</link><description>Use of Default Cryptographic Key (CWE-1394)</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55729 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the ConfluenceLayoutSection macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55729</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the ac:type in the ConfluenceLayoutSection macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page The classes parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution. Version 1.26.5 has a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55730 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the confluence paste code macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55730</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the title in the confluence paste code macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page. The classes parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution. Version 1.26.5 has a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57060 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the rules parameter in the dns_forward_rule_store function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57060</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the rules parameter in the dns_forward_rule_store function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55047 | CWE-798 Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55047</link><description>CWE-798 Use of Hard-coded Credentials</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55048 | Multiple CWE-78</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55048</link><description>Multiple CWE-78</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55728 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution using the panel macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55728</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the classes parameter in the panel macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page The classes parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution. Version 1.26.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10164 | lmsys sglang update_weights_from_tensor main deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10164</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in lmsys sglang 0.4.6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file /update_weights_from_tensor. The manipulation of the argument serialized_named_tensors results in deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29089 | An issue in TP-Link AX10 Ax1500 v.1.3.10 Build (20230130) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29089</link><description>An issue in TP-Link AX10 Ax1500 v.1.3.10 Build (20230130) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55727 | XWiki Remote Macros vulnerable to remote code execution from width parameter in the column macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55727</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Starting in version 1.0 and prior to version 1.26.5, missing escaping of the width parameter in the column macro allows remote code execution for any user who can edit any page or who can access the CKEditor converter. The width parameter is used without escaping in XWiki syntax, thus allowing XWiki syntax injection which enables remote code execution when the macro has been installed by a user with programming right, or it at least allows executing Velocity code as the wiki admin. Version 1.26.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54242 | Premiere Pro | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54242</link><description>Premiere Pro versions 25.3, 24.6.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file, and scope is unchanged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54256 | Dreamweaver Desktop | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) (CWE-352)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54256</link><description>Dreamweaver Desktop versions 21.5 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must click on a malicious link, and scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57278 | The LB-Link BL-CPE300M AX300 4G LTE Router firmware version BL-R8800_B10_ALK_SL_V01.01.02P42U14_06 does not implement proper session handlin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57278</link><description>The LB-Link BL-CPE300M AX300 4G LTE Router firmware version BL-R8800_B10_ALK_SL_V01.01.02P42U14_06 does not implement proper session handling. After a user authenticates from a specific IP address, the router grants access to any other client using that same IP, without requiring credentials or verifying client identity. There are no session tokens, cookies, or unique identifiers in place. This flaw allows an attacker to obtain full administrative access simply by configuring their device to use the same IP address as a previously authenticated user. This results in a complete authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43775 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.5, 2024...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43775</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.128, and Liferay DXP 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.5, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.12, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.12, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via remote app title field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57085 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the v17 parameter in the UploadCfg function. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57085</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the v17 parameter in the UploadCfg function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57086 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the String parameter in the formDeleteMeshNode function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57086</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the String parameter in the formDeleteMeshNode function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57665 | Element Plus Link component (el-link) through 2.10.6 implements insufficient input validation for the href attribute, creating a security ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57665</link><description>Element Plus Link component (el-link) through 2.10.6 implements insufficient input validation for the href attribute, creating a security abstraction gap that obscures URL-based attack vectors. The component passes user-controlled href values directly to underlying anchor elements without protocol validation, URL sanitization, or security headers. This allows attackers to inject malicious URLs using dangerous protocols (javascript:, data:, file:) or redirect users to external malicious sites. While native HTML anchor elements present similar risks, UI component libraries bear additional responsibility for implementing security safeguards and providing clear risk documentation. The vulnerability enables XSS attacks, phishing campaigns, and open redirect exploits affecting applications that use Element Plus Link components with user-controlled or untrusted URL inputs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10198 | LizardBytes Sunshine for Windows contains a DLL search-order hijacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10198</link><description>Sunshine for Windows, version v2025.122.141614, contains a DLL search-order hijacking vulnerability, allowing attackers to insert a malicious DLL in user-writeable PATH directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10199 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in LizardBytes&amp;#x27; Sunshine for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10199</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Sunshine for Windows (version v2025.122.141614 and likely prior versions) due to an unquoted service path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57078 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pppoeServerWhiteMacIndex parameter in the formModifyPppAuthWhi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57078</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pppoeServerWhiteMacIndex parameter in the formModifyPppAuthWhiteMac function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9269 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability found in embedded web server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9269</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability has been identified in the embedded web server in various Lexmark devices. This vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to force the device to send an arbitrary HTTP request to a third-party server. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to internal network access / potential data disclosure from a device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57087 | Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the countryCode parameter in the werlessAdvancedSet function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57087</link><description>Tenda W30E V16.01.0.19 (5037) was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the countryCode parameter in the werlessAdvancedSet function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47997 | Microsoft SQL Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47997</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49692 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49692</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49734 | PowerShell Direct Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49734</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53796 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53796</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53797 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53797</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53798 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53798</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53799 | Windows Imaging Component Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53799</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53800 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53800</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53801 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53801</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53802 | Windows Bluetooth Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53802</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53803 | Windows Kernel Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53803</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53804 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53804</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53805 | HTTP.sys Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53805</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53806 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53806</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53807 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53807</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53808 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53808</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53809 | Local Security Authority Subsystem Service (LSASS) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53809</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53810 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53810</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54091 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54091</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54092 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54092</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54093 | Windows TCP/IP Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54093</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54094 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54094</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54095 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54095</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54096 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54096</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54097 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54097</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54098 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54098</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54099 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54099</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54101 | Windows SMB Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54101</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54102 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54102</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54103 | Windows Management Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54103</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54104 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54104</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54105 | Microsoft Brokering File System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54105</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54106 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54106</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54107 | MapUrlToZone Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54107</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54108 | Capability Access Management Service (camsvc) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54108</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54109 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54109</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54110 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54110</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54111 | Windows UI XAML Phone DatePickerFlyout Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54111</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54112 | Microsoft Virtual Hard Disk Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54112</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54113 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54113</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54114 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service (Cdpsvc) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54114</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54115 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54115</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54116 | Windows MultiPoint Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54116</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54261 | ColdFusion | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54261</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2025.3, 2023.15, 2021.21 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution by an attacker. Scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54894 | Local Security Authority Subsystem Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54894</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54895 | SPNEGO Extended Negotiation (NEGOEX) Security Mechanism Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54895</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54896 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54896</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54897 | Microsoft SharePoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54897</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54898 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54898</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54899 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54899</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54900 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54900</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54901 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54901</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54902 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54902</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54903 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54903</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54904 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54904</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54905 | Microsoft Word Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54905</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54906 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54906</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54907 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54907</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54908 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54908</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54910 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54910</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54911 | Windows BitLocker Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54911</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54912 | Windows BitLocker Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54912</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54913 | Windows UI XAML Maps MapControlSettings Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54913</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54915 | Windows Defender Firewall Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54915</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54916 | Windows NTFS Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54916</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54917 | MapUrlToZone Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54917</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54918 | Windows NTLM Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54918</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54919 | Windows Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54919</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55223 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55224 | Windows Hyper-V Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55224</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55225 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55225</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55226 | Graphics Kernel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55226</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55227 | Microsoft SQL Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55227</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55228 | Windows Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55228</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55232 | Microsoft High Performance Compute (HPC) Pack Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55232</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55234 | Windows SMB Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55234</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55236 | Graphics Kernel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55236</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55243 | Microsoft OfficePlus Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55243</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55245 | Xbox Gaming Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55245</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55316 | Azure Arc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55316</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55317 | Microsoft AutoUpdate (MAU) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55317</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57070 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the gstUp parameter in the guestWifiRuleRefresh function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57070</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the gstUp parameter in the guestWifiRuleRefresh function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57071 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the vpnUsers parameter in the formAddVpnUsers function. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57071</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the vpnUsers parameter in the formAddVpnUsers function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57072 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the staticRouteGateway parameter in the formSetStaticRoute functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57072</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the staticRouteGateway parameter in the formSetStaticRoute function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57062 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the delDhcpIndex parameter in the formDelDhcpRule function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57062</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the delDhcpIndex parameter in the formDelDhcpRule function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57063 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the portMappingIndex parameter in the formDelPortMapping function....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57063</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the portMappingIndex parameter in the formDelPortMapping function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57069 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pPppUser parameter in the getsinglepppuser function. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57069</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the pPppUser parameter in the getsinglepppuser function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54246 | Adobe Experience Manager | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54246</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54247 | Adobe Experience Manager | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54247</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54248 | Adobe Experience Manager | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54248</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read access. Scope is changed</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54249 | Adobe Experience Manager | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) (CWE-918)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54249</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to manipulate server-side requests and bypass security controls allowing unauthorized read access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54250 | Adobe Experience Manager | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54250</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54251 | Adobe Experience Manager | XML Injection (aka Blind XPath Injection) (CWE-91)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54251</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by an XML Injection vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to manipulate XML queries and gain limited unauthorized write access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54252 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54252</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.23.0 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. This could result in bypassing security features within the application. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57061 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formIPMacBindModify function via the ruleId, ip, mac, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57061</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formIPMacBindModify function via the ruleId, ip, mac, v6 and remark parameters. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57064 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the bindDhcpIndex parameter in the modifyDhcpRule function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57064</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the bindDhcpIndex parameter in the modifyDhcpRule function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57538 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the HTTP Proxy field within the Datacenter configuration panel of Proxmox Virtual Envir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57538</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the HTTP Proxy field within the Datacenter configuration panel of Proxmox Virtual Environment (PVE) 8.4 allows an authenticated user to inject malicious input. The input is stored and executed in the context of other users' browsers when they view the affected configuration page. This can lead to arbitrary JavaScript execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57539 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the U2F Origin field of the Datacenter configuration in Proxmox Virtual Environment (PV...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57539</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the U2F Origin field of the Datacenter configuration in Proxmox Virtual Environment (PVE) 8.4 allows authenticated users to store malicious input. The payload is rendered unsafely in the Web UI and executed when viewed by other users, potentially leading to session hijacking or other attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57540 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the WebAuthn Relying Party field within the Datacenter configuration of Proxmox ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57540</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the WebAuthn Relying Party field within the Datacenter configuration of Proxmox Virtual Environment (PVE) 8.4. Authenticated users can inject JavaScript code that is later executed in the browsers of users who view the configuration page, enabling client-side attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58975 | WordPress Advanced Settings Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58975</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Helmut Wandl Advanced Settings allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Advanced Settings: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58976 | WordPress Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.31.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58976</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Equalize Digital Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital: from n/a through 1.31.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58977 | WordPress WP eBay Product Feeds Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58977</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Rhys Wynne WP eBay Product Feeds allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects WP eBay Product Feeds: from n/a through 3.4.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58978 | WordPress PDF Generator for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58978</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Swings PDF Generator for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects PDF Generator for WordPress: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58979 | WordPress BerqWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.53 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58979</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BerqWP BerqWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects BerqWP: from n/a through 2.2.53.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58980 | WordPress Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58980</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in recorp Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58981 | WordPress Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.31.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58981</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Equalize Digital Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Checker by Equalize Digital: from n/a through 1.31.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58982 | WordPress Pixeline&amp;#x27;s Email Protector Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58982</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pixeline Pixeline&amp;#039;s Email Protector allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Pixeline&amp;#039;s Email Protector: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58983 | WordPress Include Me Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58983</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stefano Lissa Include Me allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Include Me: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58984 | WordPress Welcart e-Commerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58984</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nanbu Welcart e-Commerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Welcart e-Commerce: from n/a through 2.11.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58985 | WordPress Additional Custom Product Tabs for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58985</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Additional Custom Product Tabs for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Additional Custom Product Tabs for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58987 | WordPress Football Pool Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AntoineH Football Pool allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Football Pool: from n/a through 2.12.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58988 | WordPress My Tickets Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58988</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joe Dolson My Tickets allows Stored XSS. This issue affects My Tickets: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58989 | WordPress Dynamic Text Field For Contact Form 7 Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in silverplugins217 Dynamic Text Field For Contact Form 7 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dynamic Text Field For Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58990 | WordPress ShopLentor Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58990</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HasTech ShopLentor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShopLentor: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58991 | WordPress WooCommerce Booking Bundle Hours Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58991</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cristiano Zanca WooCommerce Booking Bundle Hours allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Booking Bundle Hours: from n/a through 0.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58993 | WordPress Tutor LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58993</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themeum Tutor LMS allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Tutor LMS: from n/a through 3.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58997 | WordPress Mow Theme &amp;lt;= 4.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58997</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Frenify Mow allows Code Injection. This issue affects Mow: from n/a through 4.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5005 | Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM index_event.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5005</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM up to 8.6.5.4. This affects an unknown function of the file crm/WeiXinApp/dingtalk/index_event.php. The manipulation of the argument corpurl results in server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5500 | ZhenShi Mibro Fit App com.xiaoxun.xunoversea.mibrofit AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5500</link><description>A flaw has been found in ZhenShi Mibro Fit App 1.6.3.17499 on Android. This impacts an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.xiaoxun.xunoversea.mibrofit. This manipulation causes improper export of android application components. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30875 | WordPress WP Weixin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alexandre Froger WP Weixin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Weixin: from n/a through 1.3.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32486 | WordPress Material Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32486</link><description>Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password vulnerability in Hossein Material Dashboard. This issue affects Material Dashboard: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32688 | WordPress Target Video Easy Publish plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sovica Target Video Easy Publish. This issue affects Target Video Easy Publish: from n/a through 3.8.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32689 | WordPress Download Manager and Payment Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.13 - Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32689</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in ThemesGrove WP SmartPay. This issue affects WP SmartPay: from n/a through 2.7.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39523 | WordPress GoodBarber plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.26 - Open Redirection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39523</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in GoodBarber GoodBarber. This issue affects GoodBarber: from n/a through 1.0.26.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39541 | WordPress WP Simple Booking Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39541</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Roland Murg WP Simple Booking Calendar. This issue affects WP Simple Booking Calendar: from n/a through 2.0.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39553 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.9 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39553</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in andy_moyle Church Admin. This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 5.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47437 | WordPress LiteSpeed Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47437</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in LiteSpeed Technologies LiteSpeed Cache. This issue affects LiteSpeed Cache: from n/a through 7.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47569 | WordPress WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47569</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPSwings WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card - Create, Sell and Manage Gift Cards with Customized Email Templates. This issue affects WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card - Create, Sell and Manage Gift Cards with Customized Email Templates: from n/a through 2.8.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47570 | WordPress WooCommerce Photo Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in villatheme WooCommerce Photo Reviews. This issue affects WooCommerce Photo Reviews: from n/a through 1.3.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47571 | WordPress Super Store Finder plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47571</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in highwarden Super Store Finder. This issue affects Super Store Finder: from n/a through 6.9.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47579 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.5.2 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47579</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeGoods Photography. This issue affects Photography: from n/a through 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47694 | WordPress Blog Designer PRO plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in solwin Blog Designer PRO. This issue affects Blog Designer PRO: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47695 | WordPress Blog Designer PRO plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Authenticated Non-Arbitrary Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47695</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in solwin Blog Designer PRO. This issue affects Blog Designer PRO: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48101 | WordPress Constant Contact for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48101</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in webdevstudios Constant Contact for WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Constant Contact for WordPress: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49430 | WordPress Ultimate Video Player Plugin &amp;lt;= 10.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49430</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in FWDesign Ultimate Video Player allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Ultimate Video Player: from n/a through 10.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49860 | WordPress Majestic Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49860</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Majestic Support Majestic Support. This issue affects Majestic Support: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53291 | WordPress Spreadconnect plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53291</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in spoddev2021 Spreadconnect. This issue affects Spreadconnect: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53303 | WordPress ThemeMove Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53303</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThemeMove ThemeMove Core allows Object Injection. This issue affects ThemeMove Core: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53340 | WordPress Awesome Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53340</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in awesomesupport Awesome Support. This issue affects Awesome Support: from n/a through 6.3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53348 | WordPress Kalium Theme &amp;lt;= 3.18.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53348</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Laborator Kalium. This issue affects Kalium: from n/a through 3.18.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54709 | WordPress Sala Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54709</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in uxper Sala. This issue affects Sala: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57057 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the listStr parameter in the ipMacBindListStore function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57057</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the listStr parameter in the ipMacBindListStore function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57058 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formSetDebugCfg function via the pEnable, pLevel, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57058</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain multiple stack overflows in the formSetDebugCfg function via the pEnable, pLevel, and pModule parameters. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57059 | Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the dhcpIndex parameter in the addDhcpRule function. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57059</link><description>Tenda G3 v3.0br_V15.11.0.17 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the dhcpIndex parameter in the addDhcpRule function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58215 | WordPress Ziston Theme &amp;lt; 1.4.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58215</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Ziston allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ziston: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59005 | WordPress Categorify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59005</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in frenify Categorify allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Categorify: from n/a through 1.0.7.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59008 | WordPress ZIP Code Based Content Protection plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59008</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PressTigers ZIP Code Based Content Protection allows SQL Injection. This issue affects ZIP Code Based Content Protection: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55143 | Reflected text injection in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55143</link><description>Reflected text injection in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary text into a crafted HTTP response. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55144 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55144</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure restricted settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55141 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55141</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure authentication related settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55142 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55142</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure authentication related settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55139 | SSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Iva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55139</link><description>SSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to enumerate internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55147 | CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Iva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55147</link><description>CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute sensitive actions on behalf of the victim user. User interaction is required</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55148 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55148</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure restricted settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52915 | K7RKScan.sys 23.0.0.10, part of the K7 Security Anti-Malware suite, allows an admin-privileged user to send crafted IOCTL requests to termin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52915</link><description>K7RKScan.sys 23.0.0.10, part of the K7 Security Anti-Malware suite, allows an admin-privileged user to send crafted IOCTL requests to terminate processes that are protected through a third-party implementation. This is caused by insufficient caller validation in the driver's IOCTL handler, enabling unauthorized processes to perform those actions in kernel space. Successful exploitation can lead to denial of service by disrupting critical third-party services or applications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55145 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55145</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723  and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker to hijack existing HTML5 connections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55146 | An unchecked return value in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55146</link><description>An unchecked return value in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to trigger a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8711 | CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Iva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8711</link><description>CSRF in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 2.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute limited actions on behalf of the victim user. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52322 | An issue in Open5GS v2.7.2 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted Create Session Request message to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52322</link><description>An issue in Open5GS v2.7.2 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted Create Session Request message to the SMF (PGW-C), using the IP address of a legitimate UE in the PDN Address Allocation (PAA) field</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8712 | Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 22...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8712</link><description>Missing authorization in Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.9 or 22.8R2, Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.6, Ivanti ZTA Gateway before 22.8R2.3-723 and Ivanti Neurons for Secure Access before 22.8R1.4 (Fix deployed on 02-Aug-2025) allows a remote authenticated attacker with read-only admin privileges to configure restricted settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9712 | Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9712</link><description>Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9872 | Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9872</link><description>Insufficient filename validation in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before 2024 SU3 Security Update 1 and 2022 SU8 Security Update 2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10183 | XML External Entity Injection in TecConnect 4.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10183</link><description>A blind XML External Entity (XXE) injection in the OpenMessaging webservice in TecCom TecConnect 4.1 allows an unauthenticated attacker to exfiltrate arbitrary files to an attacker-controlled server. TecConnect 4.1 is considered end-of-life as of December 2023. Users are advised to upgrade to TecCom Connect 5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52277 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in YesWiki v.4.54 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the meta co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52277</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in YesWiki v.4.54 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the meta configuration robots field</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10107 | TRENDnet TEW-831DR formSysCmd command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10107</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TRENDnet TEW-831DR 1.0 (601.130.1.1410). Impacted is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSysCmd. The manipulation of the argument sysHost leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43776 | A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 202...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43776</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.19 and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows an remote authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript through Custom Object field label. The malicious payload is stored and executed through Process Builder's Configuration tab without proper escaping.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33045 | Legacy Serial Redirection SMRAM Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33045</link><description>APTIOV contains vulnerabilities in the BIOS where a privileged user may cause “Write-what-where Condition” and “Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor” through local access. The successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities can lead to information disclosure, arbitrary data writing, and impact Confidentiality, Integrity, and Availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47416 | ConsoleFindCommandMatchList</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47416</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the ConsoleFindCommandMatchList function in libsymproc. so imported by ctpd that may lead to unauthorized execution of an attacker-defined file that gets prioritized by the ConsoleFindCommandMatchList.



A third-party researcher discovered that the ConsoleFindCommandMatchList enumerates the /dev/shm/symproc/c directory in alphabetical order to identify console commands. Permission levels are inferred from the integer values present in each command's file name. 



Confirmed Affected Hardware: TSW-760, TSW-1060 



Confirmed Affected Firmware: 3.002.1061 



Fixed Firmware: no fixed released (product is discontinued and end of life)



 



For x70  



The Affected Firmware:- 3.000.0110.001  and versions below 



The Fixed Firmware:- 3.001.0031.001</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9951 | Remote code execution via Heap Buffer Overflow in FFmpeg JPEG2000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9951</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow write exists in jpeg2000dec FFmpeg which allows an attacker to potentially gain remote code execution or cause denial of service via the channel definition cdef atom of JPEG2000.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45325 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiDDoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45325</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiDDoS-F version 7.0.0 through 7.02 and before 6.6.3 may allow a privileged attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53609 | A Relative Path Traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0.2 through 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53609</link><description>A Relative Path Traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0.2 through 7.0.11 may allow an authenticated attacker to perform an arbitrary file read on the underlying system via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54236 | Adobe Commerce | Improper Input Validation (CWE-20)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54236</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. A successful attacker can abuse this to achieve session takeover, increasing the confidentiality and integrity impact to high. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9994 | Amp’ed RF BT-AP 111 Bluetooth access point&amp;#x27;s HTTP admin interface does not require authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9994</link><description>The Amp’ed RF BT-AP 111 Bluetooth access point's HTTP admin interface does not have an authentication feature, allowing unauthorized access to anyone with network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7350 | Rockwell Automation Stratix® IOS Cross-Site Request Forgery to Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7350</link><description>A security issue affecting multiple Cisco devices also directly impacts Stratix® 5410, 5700, and 8000 devices. This can lead to remote code execution by uploading and running malicious configurations without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7970 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Activation Manager Lack of Encryption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7970</link><description>A security issue exists within FactoryTalk Activation Manager.  An error in the implementation of cryptography within the software could allow attackers to decrypt traffic. This could result in data exposure, session hijacking, or full communication compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9065 | Rockwell Automation ThinManager® Server-Side Request Forgery Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9065</link><description>A server-side request forgery security issue exists within Rockwell Automation ThinManager® software due to the lack of input sanitization. Authenticated attackers can exploit this vulnerability by specifying external SMB paths, exposing the ThinServer® service account NTLM hash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9161 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Optix Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9161</link><description>A security issue exists within FactoryTalk Optix MQTT broker due to the lack of URI sanitization. This flaw enables the loading of remote Mosquito plugins, which can be used to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9364 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Analytics™ LogixAI® Exposed Redis DB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9364</link><description>An open database issue exists in the affected product and version. The security issue stems from an over permissive Redis instance. This could result in an attacker on the intranet accessing sensitive data and potential alteration of data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8007 | Rockwell Automation 1756-ENT2R, EN4TR, EN4TRXT Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8007</link><description>A security issue exists in the protected mode of 1756-EN4TR and 1756-EN2TR communication modules, where a Concurrent Forward Close operation can trigger a Major Non-Recoverable (MNFR) fault. This condition may lead to unexpected system crashes and loss of device availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8008 | Rockwell Automation 1756-ENT2R, EN4TR, EN4TRXT Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8008</link><description>A security issue exists in the protected mode of EN4TR devices, where sending specifically crafted messages during a Forward Close operation can cause the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9160 | Rockwell Automation CompactLogix® 5480 Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9160</link><description>A code execution security issue exists in the affected product. An attacker with physical access could abuse the maintenance menu of the controller with a crafted payload. The security issue can result in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9166 | Rockwell Automation ControlLogix® 5580 V35.013 Denial-Of-Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9166</link><description>A denial-of-service security issue exists in the affected product and version. The security issue stems from the controller repeatedly attempting to forward messages. The issue could result in a major nonrecoverable fault on the controller.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8277 | Libssh: memory exhaustion via repeated key exchange in libssh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8277</link><description>A flaw was found in libssh's handling of key exchange (KEX) processes when a client repeatedly sends incorrect KEX guesses. The library fails to free memory during these rekey operations, which can gradually exhaust system memory. This issue can lead to crashes on the client side, particularly when using libgcrypt, which impacts application stability and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10095 | SQL injection in SMPP component of SMSEagle firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10095</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in the SMPP server component of the SMSEagle firmware, specifically affecting the handling of certain parameters within the server's database interactions. The vulnerability is isolated to the SMPP server, which operates with its own dedicated database, separate from the main software's database. This isolation limits the scope of the vulnerability to the SMPP server's operations. The vulnerability arises from improper sanitization of user input in the SMPP server's scripts.

This issue has been fixed in version 6.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 10:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24404 | Apache HertzBeat (incubating): RCE by parse http sitemap xml response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24404</link><description>XML Injection RCE by parse http sitemap xml response vulnerability in Apache HertzBeat.












The attacker needs to have an authenticated account with access, and add monitor parsed by xml, returned special content can trigger the XML parsing vulnerability.

This issue affects Apache HertzBeat (incubating): before 1.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48208 | Apache HertzBeat (incubating): Jmx JNDI injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48208</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an LDAP Query ('LDAP Injection') vulnerability in Apache HertzBeat .












The attacker needs to have an authenticated account with access, and the attack can only be triggered by crafting custom commands. A successful attack would result in arbitrary script execution.

This issue affects Apache HertzBeat: through 1.7.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.7.3], which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41701 | Beckhoff: Deserialization of untrusted data by TwinCAT 3 Engineering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41701</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can trick a local user into executing arbitrary commands by opening a deliberately manipulated project file with an affected engineering tool. These arbitrary commands are executed in the user context.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59013 | Open Redirect in TYPO3 CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59013</link><description>An open‑redirect vulnerability in GeneralUtility::sanitizeLocalUrl of TYPO3 CMS 9.0.0–9.5.54, 10.0.0–10.4.53, 11.0.0–11.5.47, 12.0.0–12.4.36, and 13.0.0–13.4.17 allows an attacker to redirect users to arbitrary external sites, enabling phishing attacks by supplying a manipulated, sanitized URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59014 | Denial of Service in TYPO3 Bookmark Toolbar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59014</link><description>An uncaught exception in the Bookmark Toolbar of TYPO3 CMS versions 11.0.0–11.5.47, 12.0.0–12.4.36, and 13.0.0–13.4.17 lets administrator‑level backend users trigger a denial‑of‑service condition in the backend user interface by saving manipulated data in the bookmark toolbar.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59015 | Insufficient Entropy in Password Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59015</link><description>A deterministic three‑character prefix in the Password Generation component of TYPO3 CMS versions 12.0.0–12.4.36 and 13.0.0–13.4.17 reduces entropy, allowing attackers to carry out brute‑force attacks more quickly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59016 | Information Disclosure via File Abstraction Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59016</link><description>Error messages containing sensitive information in the File Abstraction Layer in TYPO3 CMS versions 9.0.0-9.5.54, 10.0.0-10.4.53, 11.0.0-11.5.47, 12.0.0-12.4.36, and 13.0.0-13.4.17 allow backend users to disclose full file paths via failed low-level file-system operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59017 | Broken Access Control in Backend AJAX Routes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59017</link><description>Missing authorization checks in the Backend Routing of TYPO3 CMS versions 9.0.0‑9.5.54, 10.0.0‑10.4.53, 11.0.0‑11.5.47, 12.0.0‑12.4.36, and 13.0.0‑13.4.17 allow backend users to directly invoke AJAX backend routes without having access to the corresponding backend modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59018 | Information Disclosure in Workspaces Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59018</link><description>Missing authorization checks in the Workspace Module of TYPO3 CMS versions 9.0.0‑9.5.54, 10.0.0‑10.4.53, 11.0.0‑11.5.47, 12.0.0‑12.4.36, and 13.0.0‑13.4.17 allow backend users to directly invoke the corresponding AJAX backend route to disclose sensitive information without having access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59019 | Information Disclosure via CSV Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59019</link><description>Missing authorization checks in the CSV download feature of TYPO3 CMS versions 11.0.0‑11.5.47, 12.0.0‑12.4.36, and 13.0.0‑13.4.17 allow backend users to disclose information from arbitrary database tables stored within the users' web mounts without having access to them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40594 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS G220 V6.4 (All versions &lt; V6.4 HF2), SINAMICS S200 V6.4 (All versions), SINAMICS S210 V6.4 (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40594</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS G220 V6.4 (All versions &lt; V6.4 HF2), SINAMICS S200 V6.4 (All versions), SINAMICS S210 V6.4 (All versions &lt; V6.4 HF2). The affected devices allow a factory reset to be executed without the required privileges due to improper privilege management as well as manipulation of configuration data because of leaked privileges of previous sessions. This could allow an unauthorized attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40757 | A vulnerability has been identified in APOGEE PXC Series (BACnet) (All versions), APOGEE PXC Series (P2 Ethernet) (All versions), TALON TC S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40757</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in APOGEE PXC Series (BACnet) (All versions), APOGEE PXC Series (P2 Ethernet) (All versions), TALON TC Series (BACnet) (All versions). Affected devices connected to the network allow unrestricted access to sensitive files, such as databases. This could allow an attacker to download encrypted .db file containing passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40795 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40795</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40796 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40796</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40797 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40797</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40798 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40798</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.1.3). Affected products contain a out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40802 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device may be susceptible to resource...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40802</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device may be susceptible to resource exhaustion when subjected to high volumes of query requests.
This could allow an attacker to cause a temporary denial of service, with the system recovering once the activity stops.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40803 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device exposes certain non-critical i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40803</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RST2428P (6GK6242-6PA00) (All versions). The affected device exposes certain non-critical information from the device. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker to access sensitive data, potentially leading to a breach of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40804 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Virtualization as a Service (SIVaaS) (All versions). The affected application exposes a netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40804</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Virtualization as a Service (SIVaaS) (All versions). The affected application exposes a network share without any authentication. This could allow an attacker to access or alter sensitive data without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10134 | Goza - Nonprofit Charity WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10134</link><description>The Goza - Nonprofit Charity WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the alone_import_pack_restore_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 08:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9539 | AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp;amp; custom integrations in WordPress &amp;lt;= 5.3.6 - Missing Authorization To Authenticated (Subscriber+) Remote Code Execution via Automation Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9539</link><description>The AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp; custom integrations in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the automatorwp_ajax_import_automation_from_url function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary automations, which can lead to Remote Code Execution or Privilege escalation once such automation is activated by the administrator</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9542 | AutomatorWP &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9542</link><description>The AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp; custom integrations in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple plugin's functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify integration settings or view existing automations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8889 | Compress Then Upload &amp;lt; 1.0.5 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8889</link><description>The Compress &amp; Upload WordPress plugin before 1.0.5 does not properly validate uploaded files, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9111 | WPBOT &amp;lt; 7.1.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9111</link><description>The AI ChatBot for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 7.1.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 06:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9058 | Mikado Core &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9058</link><description>The Mikado Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9061 | Wilmer Core &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9061</link><description>The Wilmer Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 2.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9489 | WP-Members Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via Profile Names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9489</link><description>The The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.2. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 04:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43777 | Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43777</link><description>Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.9, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.19 exposes "Internal Server Error" in the response body when a login attempt is made with a deleted Client Secret.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 03:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10122 | Maccms10 Database.php rep sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Maccms10 2025.1000.4050. Affected is the function rep of the file application/admin/controller/Database.php. Performing manipulation of the argument where results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 03:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10123 | D-Link DIR-823X set_static_leases sub_415028 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10123</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X up to 250416. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_415028 of the file /goform/set_static_leases. Executing manipulation of the argument Hostname can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 03:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10121 | uverif kami_list addbatch sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10121</link><description>A flaw has been found in uverif up to 3.2. This affects the function addbatch of the file /admin/kami_list. This manipulation of the argument note causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42911 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver (Service Data Download)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42911</link><description>SAP NetWeaver (Service Data Download) allows an authenticated user to call a remote-enabled function module, which could grant access to information about the SAP system and operating system. This leads to a low impact on confidentiality, with no effect on the integrity and availability of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42912 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42912</link><description>SAP HCM My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This issue has a significant impact on the application's integrity, while confidentiality and availability remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42913 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42913</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP HCM My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application allows an authenticated attacker with in-depth system knowledge to escalate privileges and perform activities that are otherwise restricted, resulting in a low impact on the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42914 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42914</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP HCM My Timesheet Fiori 2.0 application allows an authenticated attacker with in-depth system knowledge to escalate privileges and perform activities that are otherwise restricted, resulting in a low impact on the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42915 | Missing Authorization Check in Fiori app (Manage Payment Blocks)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42915</link><description>Fiori app Manage Payment Blocks does not perform the necessary authorization checks, allowing an attacker with basic user privileges to abuse functionalities that should be restricted to specific user groups.This issue could impact both the confidentiality and integrity of the application without affecting the availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42916 | Missing input validation vulnerability in SAP S/4HANA (Private Cloud or On-Premise)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42916</link><description>Due to missing input validation, an attacker with high privilege access to ABAP reports could delete the content of arbitrary database tables, if the tables are not protected by an authorization group. This leads to a high impact on integrity and availability of the database but no impact on confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42917 | Missing Authorization check in SAP HCM (Approve Timesheets Fiori 2.0 application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42917</link><description>SAP HCM Approve Timesheets Fiori 2.0 application does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This issue has a significant impact on the application's integrity, while confidentiality and availability remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42918 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP (Background Processing)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42918</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP allows authenticated users with access to background processing to gain unauthorized read access to profile parameters.  This results in a low impact on confidentiality, with no impact on integrity or availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42920 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Supplier Relationship Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42920</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SAP Supplier Relationship Management, an unauthenticated attacker could generate a malicious link and make it publicly accessible. If an authenticated victim clicks on the link, the injected input is processed during the page generation, resulting in the execution of malicious content. This execution allows the attacker to access and modify information within the victim's browser scope, impacting confidentiality and integrity, while availability remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42922 | Insecure File Operations vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Deploy Web Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42922</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java allows an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user to use a flaw in an available service to upload an arbitrary file. This file when executed can lead to a full compromise of confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42923 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SAP Fiori App (F4044 Manage Work Center Groups)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42923</link><description>Due to insufficient CSRF protection in SAP Fiori App Manage Work Center Groups, an authenticated user could be tricked by an attacker to send unintended request to the web server. This has low impact on integrity and no impact on confidentiality and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42925 | Predictable Object Identifier vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (IIOP Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42925</link><description>Due to the lack of randomness in assigning Object Identifiers in the SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA IIOP service, an authenticated attacker with low privileges could predict the identifiers by conducting a brute force search. By leveraging knowledge of several identifiers generated close to the same time, the attacker could determine a desired identifier which could enable them to access limited system information. This poses a low risk to confidentiality without impacting the integrity or availability of the service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42926 | Missing Authentication check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42926</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java does not perform an authentication check when an attacker attempts to access internal files within the web application.Upon successfully exploitation, an unauthenticated attacker could access these files to gather additional sensitive information about the system.This vulnerability has a low impact on confidentiality and does not affect the integrity or availability of the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42927 | Information Disclosure due to Outdated OpenSSL Version in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Adobe Document Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42927</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java application uses Adobe Document Service, installed with a vulnerable version of OpenSSL.Successful exploitation of known vulnerabilities in the outdated OpenSSL library would allow user with high system privileges to access and modify system information.This vulnerability has a low impact on confidentiality and integrity, with no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42929 | Missing input validation vulnerability in SAP Landscape Transformation Replication Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42929</link><description>Due to missing input validation, an attacker with high privilege access to ABAP reports could delete the content of arbitrary database tables, if the tables are not protected by an authorization group. This leads to a high impact on integrity and availability of the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42930 | Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in SAP Business Planning and Consolidation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42930</link><description>SAP Business Planning and Consolidation allows an authenticated standard user to call a function module by crafting specific parameters that causes a loop, consuming excessive resources and resulting in system unavailability. This leads to high impact on the availability of the application, there is no impact on confidentiality or integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42933 | Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information in SAP Business One (SLD)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42933</link><description>When a user logs in via SAP Business One native client, the SLD backend service fails to enforce proper encryption of certain APIs. This leads to exposure of sensitive credentials within http response body. As a result, it has a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42938 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42938</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the SAP NetWeaver ABAP Platform, an unauthenticated attacker could generate a malicious link and make it publicly accessible. If an authenticated user clicks on this link, the injected input is processed during the website�s page generation, resulting in the creation of malicious content. When executed, this content allows the attacker to access or modify information within the victim's browser scope, impacting the confidentiality and integrity�while availability remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42944 | Insecure Deserialization vulnerability in SAP Netweaver (RMI-P4)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42944</link><description>Due to a deserialization vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver, an unauthenticated attacker could exploit the system through the RMI-P4 module by submitting malicious payload to an open port. The deserialization of such untrusted Java objects could lead to arbitrary OS command execution, posing a high impact to the application's confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42958 | Missing Authentication check in SAP NetWeaver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42958</link><description>Due to a missing authentication check in the SAP NetWeaver application on IBM i-series, the application allows high privileged unauthorized users to read, modify, or delete sensitive information, as well as access administrative or privileged functionalities. This results in a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10116 | SiempreCMS file_upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10116</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SiempreCMS up to 1.3.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /docs/admin/file_upload.php. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10117 | SourceCodester Simple To-Do List System Add New Task fetch_tasks.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10117</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Simple To-Do List System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /fetch_tasks.php of the component Add New Task. Executing manipulation with the input  can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10118 | itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10118</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10120 | Tenda AC20 GetParentControlInfo strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10120</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC20 up to 16.03.08.12. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument mac results in buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43778 | A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.11, 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43778</link><description>A Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.11, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.16, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.20 allows an remote authenticated attacker to inject JavaScript through the name of a fieldset in Kaleo Forms Admin. The malicious payload is stored and executed without proper sanitization or escaping.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10114 | PHPGurukul Small CRM profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10114</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Small CRM 4.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10115 | SiempreCMS user_search_ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10115</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SiempreCMS up to 1.3.6. This affects an unknown part of the file user_search_ajax.php. This manipulation of the argument name/userName causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43774 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.17 allows a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43774</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Liferay Portal 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.17 allows a remote authenticated user to inject JavaScript code via Style Book theme name. This malicious payload is then reflected and executed within the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10113 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10113</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/room/index.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 01:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>