<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:18:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-3016 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp MDL File MDLMaterialLoader.cpp ParseTextureColorData resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3016</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This vulnerability affects the function Assimp::MDLImporter::ParseTextureColorData of the file code/AssetLib/MDL/MDLMaterialLoader.cpp of the component MDL File Handler. The manipulation of the argument mWidth/mHeight leads to resource consumption. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 6.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 5d2a7482312db2e866439a8c05a07ce1e718bed1. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54806 | Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Arbitrary command execution in cmd.cgi which allows for the execution of system comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54806</link><description>Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Arbitrary command execution in cmd.cgi which allows for the execution of system commands via the web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54807 | In Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America), the UPNP service is vulnerable to command injection in the function addmap_exec which parses the N...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54807</link><description>In Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America), the UPNP service is vulnerable to command injection in the function addmap_exec which parses the NewInternalClient parameter of the AddPortMapping SOAPAction into a system call without sanitation. An attacker can send a specially crafted SOAPAction request for AddPortMapping via the router's WANIPConn1 service to achieve arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54808 | Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SetDefaultConnectionService function due t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54808</link><description>Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SetDefaultConnectionService function due to an unconstrained use of sscanf. The vulnerability allows for control of the program counter and can be utilized to achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54809 | Netgear Inc WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the parse_st_header function due to use of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54809</link><description>Netgear Inc WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the parse_st_header function due to use of a request header parameter in a strncpy where size is determined based on the input specified. By sending a specially crafted packet, an attacker can take control of the program counter and hijack control flow of the program to execute arbitrary system commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54802 | In Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America), the UPNP service (/usr/sbin/upnp) is vulnerable to stack-based buffer overflow in the M-SEARCH Hos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54802</link><description>In Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America), the UPNP service (/usr/sbin/upnp) is vulnerable to stack-based buffer overflow in the M-SEARCH Host header.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54803 | Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Command Injection. An attacker can send a specially crafted request to post.cgi, upda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54803</link><description>Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Command Injection. An attacker can send a specially crafted request to post.cgi, updating the nvram parameter pppoe_peer_mac and forcing a reboot. This will result in command injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54804 | Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Command Injection. An attacker can send a specially crafted request to post.cgi, upda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54804</link><description>Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Command Injection. An attacker can send a specially crafted request to post.cgi, updating the nvram parameter wan_hostname and forcing a reboot. This will result in command injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54805 | Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Command Injection. An attacker can send a specially crafted request to post.cgi, upda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54805</link><description>Netgear WNR854T 1.5.2 (North America) is vulnerable to Command Injection. An attacker can send a specially crafted request to post.cgi, updating the nvram parameter get_email. After which, they can visit the send_log.cgi endpoint which uses the parameter in a system call to achieve command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24456 | An E-RAB Release Command packet containing a malformed NAS PDU will cause the Athonet MME to immediately crash, potentially due to a buffer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24456</link><description>An E-RAB Release Command packet containing a malformed NAS PDU will cause the Athonet MME to immediately crash, potentially due to a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3015 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp ASE File ASELoader.cpp BuildUniqueRepresentation out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3015</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This affects the function Assimp::ASEImporter::BuildUniqueRepresentation of the file code/AssetLib/ASE/ASELoader.cpp of the component ASE File Handler. The manipulation of the argument mIndices leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 6.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 7c705fde418d68cca4e8eff56be01b2617b0d6fe. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3010 | Khronos Group glslang Intermediate.cpp isConversionAllowed null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3010</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Khronos Group glslang 15.1.0. Affected by this issue is the function glslang::TIntermediate::isConversionAllowed of the file glslang/MachineIndependent/Intermediate.cpp. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21893 | keys: Fix UAF in key_put()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21893</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

keys: Fix UAF in key_put()

Once a key's reference count has been reduced to 0, the garbage collector
thread may destroy it at any time and so key_put() is not allowed to touch
the key after that point.  The most key_put() is normally allowed to do is
to touch key_gc_work as that's a static global variable.

However, in an effort to speed up the reclamation of quota, this is now
done in key_put() once the key's usage is reduced to 0 - but now the code
is looking at the key after the deadline, which is forbidden.

Fix this by using a flag to indicate that a key can be gc'd now rather than
looking at the key's refcount in the garbage collector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31124 | Zitadel  allows User Enumeration by loginname attribute normalization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31124</link><description>Zitadel is open-source identity infrastructure software. ZITADEL administrators can enable a setting called "Ignoring unknown usernames" which helps mitigate attacks that try to guess/enumerate usernames. If enabled, ZITADEL will show the password prompt even if the user doesn't exist and report "Username or Password invalid". While the setting was correctly respected during the login flow, the user's username was normalized leading to a disclosure of the user's existence. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.71.6, 2.70.8, 2.69.9, 2.68.9, 2.67.13, 2.66.16, 2.65.7, 2.64.6, and 2.63.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31123 | Zitadel Expired JWT Keys Usable for Authorization Grants</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31123</link><description>Zitadel is open-source identity infrastructure software. A vulnerability existed where expired keys can be used to retrieve tokens. Specifically, ZITADEL fails to properly check the expiration date of the JWT key when used for Authorization Grants. This allows an attacker with an expired key to obtain valid access tokens. This vulnerability does not affect the use of JWT Profile for OAuth 2.0 Client Authentication on the Token and Introspection endpoints, which correctly reject expired keys. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.71.6, 2.70.8, 2.69.9, 2.68.9, 2.67.13, 2.66.16, 2.65.7, 2.64.6, and 2.63.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3009 | Jinher Network OA NetDiskProperty.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3009</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Jinher Network OA C6. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /C6/JHSoft.Web.NetDisk/NetDiskProperty.aspx. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31129 | jooby-pac4j: deserialization of untrusted data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31129</link><description>Jooby is a web framework for Java and Kotlin. The pac4j io.jooby.internal.pac4j.SessionStoreImpl#get module deserializes untrusted data. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.17.0 (2.x) and 3.7.0 (3.x).</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3008 | Novastar CX40 NetFilter Utility netconfig popen command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3008</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Novastar CX40 up to 2.44.0. Affected is the function system/popen of the file /usr/nova/bin/netconfig of the component NetFilter Utility. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29908 | Netty QUIC hash collision DoS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29908</link><description>Netty QUIC codec is a QUIC codec for netty which makes use of quiche. An issue was discovered in the codec. A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash map used to manage connections) allows remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs). This vulnerability is fixed in 0.0.71.Final.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31128 | gifplayer XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31128</link><description>gifplayer is a customizable jquery plugin to play and stop animated gifs. gifplayer contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.3.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3007 | Novastar CX40 NetFilter Utility netconfig getopt stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3007</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Novastar CX40 up to 2.44.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function getopt of the file /usr/nova/bin/netconfig of the component NetFilter Utility. The manipulation of the argument cmd/netmask/pipeout/nettask leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3006 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3006</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit-category.php?id=8. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3005 | Sayski ForestBlog Friend Link cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3005</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sayski ForestBlog up to 20250321 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Friend Link Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31125 | Vite has a `server.fs.deny` bypassed for `inline` and `raw` with `?import` query</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31125</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for javascript. Vite exposes content of non-allowed files using ?inline&amp;amp;import or ?raw?import. Only apps explicitly exposing the Vite dev server to the network (using --host or server.host config option) are affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 6.2.4, 6.1.3, 6.0.13, 5.4.16, and 4.5.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31122 | scratch-coding-hut.github.io Login Links Generation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31122</link><description>scratch-coding-hut.github.io is the website for Coding Hut. In 1.0-beta3 and earlier, the login link can be used to login to any account by changing the username in the username field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3004 | Sayski ForestBlog search cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3004</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sayski ForestBlog up to 20250321 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30006 | Xorcom CompletePBX &amp;lt;= 5.2.35 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30006</link><description>Xorcom CompletePBX is vulnerable to a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) in the administrative control panel.




This issue affects CompletePBX: all versions up to and prior to 5.2.35</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31117 | OpenEMR Out-of-Band Server-Side Request Forgery (OOB SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31117</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. An Out-of-Band Server-Side Request Forgery (OOB SSRF) vulnerability was identified in OpenEMR, allowing an attacker to force the server to make unauthorized requests to external or internal resources. this attack does not return a direct response but can be exploited through DNS or HTTP interactions to exfiltrate sensitive information. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30004 | Xorcom CompletePBX &amp;lt;= 5.2.35 Task Scheduler Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30004</link><description>Xorcom CompletePBX is vulnerable to command injection in the administrator Task Scheduler functionality, allowing for attackers to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.




This issue affects CompletePBX: all versions up to and prior to 5.2.35</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30005 | Xorcom CompletePBX &amp;lt;= 5.2.35 Authenticated Path Traversal &amp;amp; File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30005</link><description>Xorcom CompletePBX is vulnerable to a path traversal via the Diagnostics reporting module, which will allow reading of arbitrary files and additionally delete any retrieved file in place of the expected report.




This issue affects CompletePBX: all versions up to and prior to 5.2.35</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31116 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) has a SSRF Vulnerability fix bypass on assetlinks_check with DNS Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31116</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is a pen-testing, malware analysis and security assessment framework capable of performing static and dynamic analysis. The mitigation for CVE-2024-29190 in valid_host() uses socket.gethostbyname(), which is vulnerable to SSRF abuse using DNS rebinding technique. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2292 | Xorcom CompletePBX &amp;lt;= 5.2.35 Authenticated File Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2292</link><description>Xorcom CompletePBX is vulnerable to an authenticated path traversal, allowing for arbitrary file reads via the Backup and Restore functionality.This issue affects CompletePBX: through 5.2.35.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30368 | Zulip allows the deletion of organization by administrators of a different organization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30368</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. The API for deleting an organization export is supposed to be restricted to organization administrators, but its handler failed to check that the field belongs to the same organization as the user. Therefore, an administrator of any organization was incorrectly allowed to delete an export of a different organization. This is fixed in Zulip Server 10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30369 | Zulip allows the deletion of Custom profile fields by administrators of a different organization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30369</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. The API for deleting an organization custom profile field is supposed to be restricted to organization administrators, but its handler failed to check that the field belongs to the same organization as the user. Therefore, an administrator of any organization was incorrectly allowed to delete custom profile fields belonging to a different organization. This is fixed in Zulip Server 10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3003 | ESAFENET CDG UserAjax sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3003</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ESAFENET CDG 3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /CDGServer3/UserAjax. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2794 | Kentico Xperience Staging Unsafe Reflection Kentico Xperience</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2794</link><description>An unsafe reflection vulnerability in Kentico Xperience allows an unauthenticated attacker to kill the current process, leading to a Denial-of-Service condition.




This issue affects Xperience: through 13.0.180.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30223 | Beego allows Reflected/Stored XSS in Beego&amp;#x27;s RenderForm() Function Due to Unescaped User Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30223</link><description>Beego is an open-source web framework for the Go programming language. Prior to 2.3.6, a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Beego's RenderForm() function due to improper HTML escaping of user-controlled data. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript code that executes in victims' browsers, potentially leading to session hijacking, credential theft, or account takeover. The vulnerability affects any application using Beego's RenderForm() function with user-provided data. Since it is a high-level function generating an entire form markup, many developers would assume it automatically escapes attributes (the way most frameworks do). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30149 | OpenEMR Reflected XSS in AJAX Script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30149</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. OpenEMR allows reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) in the AJAX Script interface\super\layout_listitems_ajax.php via the target parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30161 | OpenEMR Stored XSS in OpenEMR Bronchitis Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30161</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. A stored XSS vulnerability in the Bronchitis form component of OpenEMR allows anyone who is able to edit a bronchitis form to steal credentials from administrators. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1449 | Admin Shell Access Vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Verve Asset Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1449</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Verve Asset Manager due to insufficient variable sanitizing. A portion of the administrative web interface for Verve's Legacy Agentless Device Inventory (ADI) capability (deprecated since the 1.36 release) allows users to change a variable with inadequate sanitizing. If exploited, it could allow a threat actor with administrative access to run arbitrary commands in the context of the container running the service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29772 | OpenEMR allows Reflected XSS in CAMOS new.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29772</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. The POST parameter hidden_subcategory is output to the page without being properly processed. This leads to a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vul;nerability in CAMOS new.php. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30155 | Tuleap does not enforce read permissions on parent trackers in the REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30155</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Tuleap does not enforce read permissions on parent trackers in the REST API. This vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.5.99.1742392651 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.5-5 and 16.4-8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3002 | Digital China DCME-520 mon_merge_stat_hist.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3002</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Digital China DCME-520 up to 20250320. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /usr/local/WWW/function/audit/newstatistics/mon_merge_stat_hist.php. The manipulation of the argument type_name leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30209 | Tuleap has improper permission handling in the REST endpoints and release notes display of the FRS plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30209</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. An attacker can access release notes content or information via the FRS REST endpoints it should not have access to. This vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.5.99.1742812323 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.5-6 and 16.4-10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30203 | Tuleap allows XSS via the content of RSS feeds in the RSS widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30203</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Tuleap allows cross-site scripting (XSS) via the content of RSS feeds in the RSS widgets. A project administrator or someone with control over an used RSS feed could use this vulnerability to force victims to execute uncontrolled code. This vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.5.99.1742562878 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.5-5 and 16.4-8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29766 | Tuleap has missing CSRF protections on artifact submission &amp;amp; edition from the tracker view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29766</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Tuleap has missing CSRF protections on artifact submission &amp; edition from the tracker view. An attacker could use this vulnerability to trick victims into submitting or editing artifacts or follow-up comments. The vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.5.99.1741784483 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.5-3 and 16.4-8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29929 | Tuleap is missing CSRF protection on tracker hierarchy administration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29929</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Tuleap is missing CSRF protection on tracker hierarchy administration. An attacker could use this vulnerability to trick victims into submitting or editing artifacts or follow-up comments. This vulnerability is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.5.99.1742306712 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.5-5 and 16.4-8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27149 | Zulip exports can leak private data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27149</link><description>Zulip server provides an open-source team chat that helps teams stay productive and focused. Prior to 10.0, the data export to organization administrators feature in Zulip leaks private data. The collection of user-agent types identifying specific integrations or HTTP libraries (E.g., ZulipGitlabWebhook, okhttp, or PycURL) that have been used to access any organization on the server was incorrectly included in all three export types, regardless of if they were used to access the exported organization or not. The "public data" and "with consent" exports metadata including the titles of some topics in private channels which the administrator otherwise did not have access to, and none of the users consented to exporting and metadata for which users were in a group DM together. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3001 | PyTorch torch.lstm_cell memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PyTorch 2.6.0. This vulnerability affects the function torch.lstm_cell. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3047 | Path Traversal in AWS SAM CLI allows file copy to build container</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3047</link><description>When running the AWS Serverless Application Model Command Line Interface (SAM CLI) build process with Docker and symlinks are included in the build files, the container environment allows a user to access privileged files on the host by leveraging the elevated permissions granted to the tool. A user could leverage the elevated permissions to access restricted files via symlinks and copy them to a more permissive location on the container. 

Users should upgrade to v1.133.0 or newer and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3048 | Path Traversal in AWS SAM CLI allows file copy to local cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3048</link><description>After completing a build with AWS Serverless Application Model Command Line Interface (SAM CLI) which include symlinks, the content of those symlinks are copied to the cache of the local workspace as regular files or directories. As a result, a user who does not have access to those symlinks outside of the Docker container would now have access via the local workspace.

Users should upgrade to version 1.134.0 and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes. After upgrading, users must re-build their applications using the sam build --use-container to update the symlinks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27095 | JumpServer has a Kubernetes Token Leak Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27095</link><description>JumpServer is an open source bastion host and an operation and maintenance security audit system. Prior to 4.8.0 and 3.10.18, an attacker with a low-privileged account can access the Kubernetes session feature and manipulate the kubeconfig file to redirect API requests to an external server controlled by the attacker. This allows the attacker to intercept and capture the Kubernetes cluster token. This can potentially allow unauthorized access to the cluster and compromise its security. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.8.0 and 3.10.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3000 | PyTorch torch.jit.script memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3000</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PyTorch 2.6.0. This affects the function torch.jit.script. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33302 | A buffer copy without checking size of input ('classic buffer overflow') in Fortinet  FortiMail webmail and administrative interface version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33302</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input ('classic buffer overflow') in Fortinet  FortiMail webmail and administrative interface version 6.4.0 through 6.4.4 and before 6.2.6 and FortiNDR administrative interface version 7.2.0 and before 7.1.0 allows an authenticated attacker with regular webmail access to trigger a buffer overflow and to possibly execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22939 | A command injection vulnerability in the telnet service of Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22939</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the telnet service of Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root and execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22940 | Incorrect access control in Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 allows unauthorized attackers to arbitrarily set the admin password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22940</link><description>Incorrect access control in Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 allows unauthorized attackers to arbitrarily set the admin password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22941 | A command injection vulnerability in the web interface of Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22941</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the web interface of Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 allows attackers to escalate privileges to root and execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22937 | An issue in Adtran 411 ONT vL80.00.0011.M2 allows attackers to escalate privileges via unspecified vectors.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22937</link><description>An issue in Adtran 411 ONT vL80.00.0011.M2 allows attackers to escalate privileges via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22938 | Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 was discovered to contain weak default passwords.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22938</link><description>Adtran 411 ONT L80.00.0011.M2 was discovered to contain weak default passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2999 | PyTorch torch.nn.utils.rnn.unpack_sequence memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2999</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PyTorch 2.6.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function torch.nn.utils.rnn.unpack_sequence. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30095 | VyOS 1.3 through 1.5 or any Debian-based system using dropbear in combination with live-build has the same Dropbear private host keys across...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30095</link><description>VyOS 1.3 through 1.5 or any Debian-based system using dropbear in combination with live-build has the same Dropbear private host keys across different installations. Thus, an attacker can conduct active man-in-the-middle attacks against SSH connections if Dropbear is enabled as the SSH daemon. I n VyOS, this is not the default configuration for the system SSH daemon, but is for the console service. To mitigate this, one can run "rm -f /etc/dropbear/*key*" and/or "rm -f /etc/dropbear-initramfs/*key*" and then dropbearkey -t rsa -s 4096 -f /etc/dropbear_rsa_host_key and reload the service or reboot the system before using Dropbear as the SSH daemon (this clears out all keys mistakenly built into the release image) or update to the latest version of VyOS 1.4 or 1.5. Note that this vulnerability is not unique to VyOS and may appear in any Debian-based Linux distribution that uses Dropbear in combination with live-build, which has a safeguard against this behavior in OpenSSH but no equivalent one for Dropbear.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12021 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12021</link><description>Coverity versions prior to 2024.9.0 are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in various administrative interfaces. The impact of exploitation may result in the compromise of local accounts managed by the Coverity platform as well as other standard impacts resulting from cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2998 | PyTorch torch.nn.utils.rnn.pad_packed_sequence memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PyTorch 2.6.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function torch.nn.utils.rnn.pad_packed_sequence. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0881 | DDoS in Ubuntu package linux-bluefield</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0881</link><description>Running DDoS on tcp port 22 will trigger a kernel crash. This issue is introduced by the backport of a commit regarding nft_lookup without the subsequent fixes that were introduced after this commit. The resolution of this CVE introduces those commits to the linux-bluefield package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2997 | zhangyanbo2007 youkefu url server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhangyanbo2007 youkefu 4.2.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /res/url. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2996 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface SysToolDDNS access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2996</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408) and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SysToolDDNS of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31526 | WordPress Behance Portfolio Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31526</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in eleopard Behance Portfolio Manager allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Behance Portfolio Manager: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31527 | WordPress WP Link Preview plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31527</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Kishan WP Link Preview allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Link Preview: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31528 | WordPress StaticPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31528</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wokamoto StaticPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects StaticPress: from n/a through 0.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31529 | WordPress Slider Path for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31529</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rashid Slider Path for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Slider Path for Elementor: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31530 | WordPress Google SEO Pressor Snippet plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31530</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in smackcoders Google SEO Pressor Snippet allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Google SEO Pressor Snippet: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31532 | WordPress AtomChat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31532</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Team AtomChat AtomChat allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AtomChat: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31533 | WordPress Salesmate Add-On for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31533</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Salesmate.io Salesmate Add-On for Gravity Forms allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Salesmate Add-On for Gravity Forms: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31535 | WordPress Simple Owl Carousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31535</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Owl Carousel allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Simple Owl Carousel: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31538 | WordPress Checklist plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31538</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in checklistcom Checklist allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Checklist: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31539 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Widgets Pack plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31539</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Blocksera Cryptocurrency Widgets Pack allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Cryptocurrency Widgets Pack: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31540 | WordPress ACME Divi Modules plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31540</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in acmemediakits ACME Divi Modules allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ACME Divi Modules: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31542 | WordPress My auctions allegro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.20 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31542</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in wphocus My auctions allegro allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects My auctions allegro: from n/a through 3.6.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31543 | WordPress Twice Commerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31543</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Twice Commerce Twice Commerce allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Twice Commerce: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31544 | WordPress Swiss Toolkit For WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31544</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Messiah Swiss Toolkit For WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Swiss Toolkit For WP: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31545 | WordPress Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.20 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31545</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Messiah Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP: from n/a through 1.0.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31546 | WordPress Swiss Toolkit For WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31546</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Messiah Swiss Toolkit For WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Swiss Toolkit For WP: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31547 | WordPress Uptime Robot Plugin for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31547</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Aphotrax Uptime Robot Plugin for WordPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Uptime Robot Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31549 | WordPress Fusion plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31549</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Agency Dominion Inc. Fusion allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Fusion: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31555 | WordPress ContentMX Content Publisher plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31555</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ContentMX ContentMX Content Publisher allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ContentMX Content Publisher: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31556 | WordPress IMPress for IDX Broker plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31556</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in IDX Broker IMPress for IDX Broker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects IMPress for IDX Broker: from n/a through 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31557 | WordPress OSM – OpenStreetMap plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MiKa OSM – OpenStreetMap allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects OSM – OpenStreetMap: from n/a through 6.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31559 | WordPress Custom Database Applications by Caspio plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Caspio Bridge Custom Database Applications by Caspio allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Custom Database Applications by Caspio: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31562 | WordPress Uptime Robot Plugin for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31562</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aphotrax Uptime Robot Plugin for WordPress allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Uptime Robot Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31566 | WordPress Rio Video Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31566</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in riosisgroup Rio Video Gallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Rio Video Gallery: from n/a through 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31567 | WordPress Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31567</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesflat Themesflat Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Themesflat Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31569 | WordPress wordpress related Posts with thumbnails plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31569</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wp-buy wordpress related Posts with thumbnails allows Stored XSS. This issue affects wordpress related Posts with thumbnails: from n/a through 3.0.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31570 | WordPress Related Posts Widget with Thumbnails plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31570</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wp-buy Related Posts Widget with Thumbnails allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Related Posts Widget with Thumbnails: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31572 | WordPress Multi Days Events and Multi Events in One Day Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31572</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in v20202020 Multi Days Events and Multi Events in One Day Calendar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Multi Days Events and Multi Events in One Day Calendar: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31574 | WordPress Custom Content Scrollbar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SoftHopper Custom Content Scrollbar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Content Scrollbar: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31575 | WordPress Flag Icons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Vasilis Triantafyllou Flag Icons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Flag Icons: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31576 | WordPress PostmarkApp Email Integrator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31576</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gagan Deep Singh PostmarkApp Email Integrator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects PostmarkApp Email Integrator: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31577 | WordPress Appointify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31577</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in appointify Appointify allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Appointify: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31583 | WordPress WP Copy Media URL plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31583</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ashish Ajani WP Copy Media URL allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Copy Media URL: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31584 | WordPress Elfsight Testimonials Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31584</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in elfsight Elfsight Testimonials Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Elfsight Testimonials Slider: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31585 | WordPress Leadfox for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31585</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in leadfox Leadfox for WordPress allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Leadfox for WordPress: from n/a through 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31586 | WordPress Gallery – Photo Albums Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.170 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31586</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Gallery – Photo Albums Plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gallery – Photo Albums Plugin: from n/a through 1.3.170.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31587 | WordPress Elfsight Testimonials Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31587</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in elfsight Elfsight Testimonials Slider allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Elfsight Testimonials Slider: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31588 | WordPress Elfsight Testimonials Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31588</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in elfsight Elfsight Testimonials Slider allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Elfsight Testimonials Slider: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31589 | WordPress Ethiopian Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31589</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kibru Demeke Ethiopian Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ethiopian Calendar: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31590 | WordPress WP Date and Time Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Denra.com WP Date and Time Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Date and Time Shortcode: from n/a through 2.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31591 | WordPress Exit Popup Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31591</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in promoz73 Exit Popup Free allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Exit Popup Free: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31592 | WordPress Send E-mail plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31592</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Paolo Melchiorre Send E-mail allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Send E-mail: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31593 | WordPress OpenMenu plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OpenMenu OpenMenu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects OpenMenu: from n/a through 3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31595 | WordPress Timeline Event History plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31595</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdiscover Timeline Event History allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Timeline Event History: from n/a through 3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31596 | WordPress Chat by Chatwee plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31596</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Chatwee Chat by Chatwee allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Chat by Chatwee: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31597 | WordPress Ultimate Live Cricket WordPress Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31597</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in crazycric Ultimate Live Cricket WordPress Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultimate Live Cricket WordPress Lite: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31598 | WordPress Quantity Dynamic Pricing &amp;amp; Bulk Discounts for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Quantity Dynamic Pricing &amp; Bulk Discounts for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Quantity Dynamic Pricing &amp; Bulk Discounts for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31600 | WordPress DesignO plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31600</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in designnbuy DesignO allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects DesignO: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31601 | WordPress Appointy Appointment Scheduler plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31601</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in appointy Appointy Appointment Scheduler allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Appointy Appointment Scheduler: from n/a through 4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31602 | WordPress Apimo Connector plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31602</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in apimofficiel Apimo Connector allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Apimo Connector: from n/a through 2.6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31603 | WordPress CF7 Spreadsheets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31603</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in moshensky CF7 Spreadsheets allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CF7 Spreadsheets: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31604 | WordPress Cal.com plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31604</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Cal.com Cal.com allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Cal.com: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31605 | WordPress Welcome Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31605</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WeblineIndia Welcome Popup allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Welcome Popup: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31606 | WordPress SP Blog Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31606</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in softpulseinfotech SP Blog Designer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects SP Blog Designer: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31607 | WordPress Simple-Audioplayer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31607</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in flomei Simple-Audioplayer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple-Audioplayer: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31608 | WordPress CookieHint WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31608</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in reDim GmbH CookieHint WP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CookieHint WP: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31609 | WordPress WPCargo Track &amp;amp; Trace plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.6 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31609</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arni Cinco WPCargo Track &amp; Trace allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WPCargo Track &amp; Trace: from n/a through 7.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31610 | WordPress Notification Bar, Sticky Notification Bar, Sticky Welcome Bar for any theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31610</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gingerplugins Notification Bar, Sticky Notification Bar, Sticky Welcome Bar for any theme allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Notification Bar, Sticky Notification Bar, Sticky Welcome Bar for any theme: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31611 | WordPress Auto Post After Image Upload plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31611</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shaharia Azam Auto Post After Image Upload allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Auto Post After Image Upload: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31613 | WordPress AB Google Map Travel plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31613</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aboobacker. AB Google Map Travel  allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects AB Google Map Travel : from n/a through 4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31614 | WordPress Terms Before Download plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31614</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hiroprot Terms Before Download allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Terms Before Download: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31615 | WordPress Simple Contact Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31615</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in owenr88 Simple Contact Forms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Contact Forms: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31616 | WordPress Varnish WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31616</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AdminGeekZ Varnish WordPress allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Varnish WordPress: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31617 | WordPress PostmarkApp Email Integrator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31617</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Gagan Deep Singh PostmarkApp Email Integrator allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects PostmarkApp Email Integrator: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31618 | WordPress Connector to CiviCRM with CiviMcRestFace plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31618</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jaap Jansma Connector to CiviCRM with CiviMcRestFace allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Connector to CiviCRM with CiviMcRestFace: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31620 | WordPress CoverManager plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31620</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in carperfer CoverManager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CoverManager: from n/a through 0.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31621 | WordPress byBrick Accordion plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31621</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in davidpaulsson byBrick Accordion allows Stored XSS. This issue affects byBrick Accordion: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31623 | WordPress Rich Text Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31623</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in richtexteditor Rich Text Editor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Rich Text Editor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31624 | WordPress Processing Projects plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31624</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LABCAT Processing Projects allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Processing Projects: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31625 | WordPress Useinfluence plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31625</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ramanparashar Useinfluence allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Useinfluence: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31627 | WordPress Media Library Assistant plugin &amp;lt;= 3.24 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31627</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in David Lingren Media Library Assistant allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Media Library Assistant: from n/a through 3.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31629 | WordPress Infusionsoft Web Form JavaScript plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31629</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jacob Allred Infusionsoft Web Form JavaScript allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Infusionsoft Web Form JavaScript: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55093 | phpIPAM through 1.7.3 has a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the install scripts.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55093</link><description>phpIPAM through 1.7.3 has a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the install scripts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2995 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface SysToolChangePwd access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2995</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/SysToolChangePwd of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29266 | Unraid 7.0.0 before 7.0.1 allows remote users to access the Unraid WebGUI and web console as root without authentication if a container is r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29266</link><description>Unraid 7.0.0 before 7.0.1 allows remote users to access the Unraid WebGUI and web console as root without authentication if a container is running in Host networking mode with Use Tailscale enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2994 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface qossetting access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2994</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/qossetting of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2586 | Ols: unauthenticated metrics flooding in openshift lightspeed service leading to resource exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2586</link><description>A flaw was found in the OpenShift Lightspeed Service, which is vulnerable to unauthenticated API request flooding. Repeated queries to non-existent endpoints inflate metrics storage and processing, consuming excessive resources. This issue can lead to monitoring system degradation, increased disk usage, and potential service unavailability. Since the issue does not require authentication, an external attacker can exhaust CPU, RAM, and disk space, impacting both application and cluster stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2993 | Tenda FH1202 default.cfg access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2993</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /default.cfg. The manipulation of the argument these leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 11:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3022 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in e-management of e-solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3022</link><description>Os command injection vulnerability in e-solutions e-management. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the server via the ‘client’ parameter in the /data/apache/e-management/api/api3.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 11:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23995 | WordPress Tantyyellow theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23995</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ta2g Tantyyellow allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tantyyellow: from n/a through 1.0.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 11:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2992 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface AdvSetWrlsafeset access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2992</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/AdvSetWrlsafeset of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 11:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31419 | WordPress Churel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31419</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeix Churel allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Churel: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30963 | WordPress JetSmartFilters plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30963</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetSmartFilters allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects JetSmartFilters: from n/a through 3.6.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2991 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface AdvSetWrlmacfilter access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2991</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/AdvSetWrlmacfilter of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3026 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements vulnerability in EJBCA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3026</link><description>The vulnerability exists in the EJBCA service, version 8.0 Enterprise. Not tested in higher versions. By modifying the ‘Host’ header in an HTTP request, it is possible to manipulate the generated links and thus redirect the client to a different base URL.  In this way, an attacker could insert his own server for the client to send HTTP requests, provided he succeeds in exploiting it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3027 | Open Redirect vulnerability in EJBCA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3027</link><description>The vulnerability exists in the EJBCA service, version 8.0 Enterprise. By making a small change to the PATH of the URL associated with the service, the server fails to find the requested file and redirects to an external page. This vulnerability could allow users to be redirected to potentially malicious external sites, which can be exploited for phishing or other social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3021 | Multiple vulnerabilities in e-management of e-solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3021</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in e-solutions e-management. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to access confidential files outside the expected scope via the ‘file’ parameter in the /downloadReport.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2990 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface AdvSetWrlGstset access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2990</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/AdvSetWrlGstset of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31376 | WordPress NanoSupport plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31376</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mayeenul Islam NanoSupport allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects NanoSupport: from n/a through 0.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31386 | WordPress Simple:Press plugin &amp;lt;= 6.10.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31386</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Simplepress Simple:Press allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple:Press: from n/a through 6.10.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 09:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2989 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface AdvSetWrl access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2989</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/AdvSetWrl of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30961 | WordPress Trackserver plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30961</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tinuzz Trackserver allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Trackserver: from n/a through 5.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 09:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2985 | code-projects Payroll Management System update_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2985</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Payroll Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file update_account.php. The manipulation of the argument deduction leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 09:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2071 | OS Command Injection Vulnerability in FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2071</link><description>A critical OS Command Injection vulnerability has been identified in the FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary operating system commands via specially crafted input. This vulnerability arises due to improper handling of untrusted input, which is passed directly to system-level commands without adequate sanitization or validation. Successful exploitation could allow attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system, potentially resulting in unauthorized access, data leakage, or full system compromise. Affected WebUI parameters are "hd" and "pi".</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2072 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2072</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been discovered in FAST LTA Silent Brick WebUI, allowing attackers to inject malicious JavaScript code into web pages viewed by users. This issue arises when user-supplied input is improperly handled and reflected directly in the output of a web page without proper sanitization or encoding. Exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser, potentially leading to session hijacking, data theft, and other malicious actions. Affected WebUI parameters are "h", "hd", "p", "pi", "s", "t", "x", "y".</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2984 | code-projects Payroll Management System delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2984</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Payroll Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /delete.php. The manipulation of the argument emp_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31406 | WordPress ELEX WooCommerce Request a Quote plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31406</link><description>Subscriber Broken Access Control in ELEX WooCommerce Request a Quote &lt;= 2.3.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31410 | WordPress WP Church Donation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31410</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ashish Ajani WP Church Donation allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WP Church Donation: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2983 | Legrand SMS PowerView os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2983</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2982 | Legrand SMS PowerView file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2982</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to file inclusion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 07:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2981 | Legrand SMS PowerView cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2981</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 07:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3019 | Cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in KNIME Business Hub web pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3019</link><description>KNIME Business Hub is affected by several cross-site scripting vulnerabilities in its web pages. If a user clicks on a malicious link or opens a malicious web page, arbitrary Java Script may be executed with this user's permissions. This can lead to information loss and/or modification of existing data.
The issues are caused by a  bug https://github.com/Baroshem/nuxt-security/issues/610  in the widely used nuxt-security module.





There are no viable workarounds therefore we strongly recommend to update to one of the following versions of KNIME Business Hub:





  *  1.13.3 or later






  *  1.12.4 or later</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2980 | Legrand SMS PowerView redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2980</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Legrand SMS PowerView 1.x. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to open redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2402 | Hard-coded password for object store of KNIME Business Hub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2402</link><description>A hard-coded, non-random password for the object store (minio) of KNIME Business Hub in all versions except the ones listed below allows an unauthenticated remote attacker in possession of the password to read and manipulate swapped jobs or read and manipulate in- and output data of active jobs. It is also possible to cause a denial-of-service of most functionality of KNIME Business Hub by writing large amounts of data to the object store directly. 



There are no viable workarounds therefore we strongly recommend to update to one of the following versions of KNIME Business Hub: 



  *  1.13.2 or later 






  *  1.12.3 or later 






  *  1.11.3 or later 






  *  1.10.3 or later</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0613 | Photo Gallery &amp;lt; 1.8.34 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0613</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.34 does not sanitised and escaped comment added on images by unauthenticated users, leading to an Unauthenticated Stored-XSS attack when comments are displayed</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2979 | WCMS Registration setregister cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2979</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in WCMS 11. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?anonymous/setregister of the component Registration. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30835 | WordPress Accounting for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30835</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Bastien Ho Accounting for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Accounting for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30855 | WordPress Ads by WPQuads plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.87.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30855</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ads by WPQuads Ads by WPQuads allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ads by WPQuads: from n/a through 2.0.87.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30987 | WordPress JetBlocks For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetBlocks For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects JetBlocks For Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31016 | WordPress JetWooBuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.18 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31016</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound JetWooBuilder allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects JetWooBuilder: from n/a through 2.1.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31043 | WordPress JetSearch plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31043</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetSearch allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects JetSearch: from n/a through 3.5.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31387 | WordPress InstaWP Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.82 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31387</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in InstaWP InstaWP Connect allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects InstaWP Connect: from n/a through 0.1.0.82.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31412 | WordPress JetProductGallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.22 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31412</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound JetProductGallery allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects JetProductGallery: from n/a through 2.1.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31414 | WordPress Cost Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.65 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31414</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stylemix Cost Calculator Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Cost Calculator Builder: from n/a through 3.2.65.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31417 | WordPress WP Docs plugin &amp;lt; 2.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31417</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood WP Docs allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Docs: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 06:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2978 | WCMS Article Publishing Page CKEditor unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2978</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WCMS 11. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php?articleadmin/upload/?&amp;amp;CKEditor=container&amp;amp;CKEditorFuncNum=1 of the component Article Publishing Page. The manipulation of the argument Upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2977 | GFI KerioConnect PDF File cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2977</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GFI KerioConnect 10.0.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component PDF File Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 05:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24517 | Use of client-side authentication issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24517</link><description>Use of client-side authentication issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain the product login password without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24852 | Storing passwords in a recoverable format issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24852</link><description>Storing passwords in a recoverable format issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, an attacker who can access the microSD card used on the product may obtain the product login password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25211 | Weak password requirements issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a brute-force attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25211</link><description>Weak password requirements issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If this issue is exploited, a brute-force attack may allow an attacker unauthorized access and login.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26689 | Direct request ('Forced Browsing') issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If a remote attacker sends a specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26689</link><description>Direct request ('Forced Browsing') issue exists in CHOCO TEI WATCHER mini (IB-MCT001) all versions. If a remote attacker sends a specially crafted HTTP request to the product, the product data may be obtained or deleted, and/or the product settings may be altered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31103 | Untrusted data deserialization vulnerability exists in a-blog cms. Processing a specially crafted request may store arbitrary files on the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31103</link><description>Untrusted data deserialization vulnerability exists in a-blog cms. Processing a specially crafted request may store arbitrary files on the server where the product is running. This can be leveraged to execute an arbitrary script on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2976 | GFI KerioConnect File Upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2976</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GFI KerioConnect 10.0.6. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component File Upload. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2975 | GFI KerioConnect Signature EditHtmlSource cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2975</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GFI KerioConnect 10.0.6 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file Settings/Email/Signature/EditHtmlSource of the component Signature Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 04:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3014 | Insecure direct object references (IDOR) in NightWolf Penetration Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3014</link><description>Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in access control in Tracking 2.1.4 on NightWolf Penetration Testing allows an attacker to access via manipulating request parameters or object references.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2974 | CodeCanyon Perfex CRM Contracts contract cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2974</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeCanyon Perfex CRM up to 3.2.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /contract of the component Contracts. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3011 | PiExtract SOOP-CLM - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3011</link><description>SOOP-CLM from PiExtract has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3013 | Insecure direct object references (IDOR) in NightWolf Penetration Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3013</link><description>Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in access control in Customer Portal before 2.1.4 on NightWolf Penetration Testing allows an attacker to access via manipulating request parameters or object references.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2973 | code-projects College Management System student.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2973</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/student.php. The manipulation of the argument profile_image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 03:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2972 | ConcreteCMS Page Attribute Display Block cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2972</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Page Attribute Display Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2970 | ConcreteCMS Switch Language Block cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected is an unknown function of the component Switch Language Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Label leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2971 | ConcreteCMS List Block cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2971</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component List Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name/Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1268 | Out-of-bounds vulnerability in EMF Recode processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1268</link><description>Out-of-bounds vulnerability in EMF Recode processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2969 | ConcreteCMS Feature Link Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2969</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function Save of the component Feature Link Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title/Body Source/Button Text leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2968 | ConcreteCMS Feature Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function Save of the component Feature Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Paragraph Source leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2967 | ConcreteCMS HTML Block save HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function Save of the component HTML Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument content leads to HTML injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2966 | ConcreteCMS Content Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function Save of the component Content Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Source leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2965 | ConcreteCMS Accordion Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Save of the component Accordion Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title/Body Source leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2964 | ConcreteCMS FAQ Block save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. Affected is the function Save of the component FAQ Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Navigation/Title Text/Description Source leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 22:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2963 | ConcreteCMS Legacy Form Block addEditQuestion cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ConcreteCMS up to 9.3.9. This issue affects the function addEditQuestion of the component Legacy Form Block Handler. The manipulation of the argument Question leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 22:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2961 | opensolon org.noear.solon.core.handle.RenderManager aa render_mav path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2961</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in opensolon up to 3.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function render_mav of the file /aa of the component org.noear.solon.core.handle.RenderManager. The manipulation of the argument template with the input ../org/example/HelloApp.class leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13804 | Vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise HPE Insight Cluster Management Utility (CMU).This issue affects HPE Insight Cluster Management U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13804</link><description>Vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise HPE Insight Cluster Management Utility (CMU).This issue affects HPE Insight Cluster Management Utility (CMU): 8.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2960 | TRENDnet TEW-637AP/TEW-638APB HTTP Request goahead sub_41DED0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2960</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in TRENDnet TEW-637AP and TEW-638APB 1.2.7/1.3.0.106. This affects the function sub_41DED0 of the file /bin/goahead of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2959 | TRENDnet TEW-410APB HTTP Request httpd sub_4019A0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-410APB 1.3.06b. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4019A0 of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2958 | TRENDnet TEW-818DRU HTTP Request httpd denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-818DRU 1.0.14.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2957 | TRENDnet TEW-411BRP+ HTTP Request httpd sub_401DB0 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2957</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-411BRP+ 2.07. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function sub_401DB0 of the file /usr/sbin/httpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 19:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2956 | TRENDnet TI-G102i HTTP Request lighttpd plugins_call_handle_uri_raw null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2956</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TI-G102i 1.0.7.S0_ /1.0.8.S0_ and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function plugins_call_handle_uri_raw of the file /usr/sbin/lighttpd of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2955 | TOTOLINK A3000RU IBMS Configuration File ExportIbmsConfig.sh access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2955</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3000RU up to 5.9c.5185 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cgi-bin/ExportIbmsConfig.sh of the component IBMS Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 17:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2954 | mannaandpoem OpenManus File file_saver.py execute access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2954</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in mannaandpoem OpenManus up to 2025.3.13. This affects the function execute of the file app/tool/file_saver.py of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2953 | PyTorch torch.mkldnn_max_pool2d denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2953</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PyTorch 2.6.0+cu124. Affected by this issue is the function torch.mkldnn_max_pool2d. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2952 | Bluestar Micro Mall api.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2952</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Bluestar Micro Mall 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/api.php?mod=upload&amp;amp;type=1. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2951 | Bluestar Micro Mall data.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2951</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Bluestar Micro Mall 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/data.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1861 | Stream HTTP wrapper truncates redirect location to 1024 bytes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1861</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when parsing HTTP redirect in the response to an HTTP request, there is currently limit on the location value size caused by limited size of the location buffer to 1024. However as per RFC9110, the limit is recommended to be 8000. This may lead to incorrect URL truncation and redirecting to a wrong location.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 06:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1736 | Stream HTTP wrapper header check might omit basic auth header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1736</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when user-supplied headers are sent, the insufficient validation of the end-of-line characters may prevent certain headers from being sent or lead to certain headers be misinterpreted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1734 | Streams HTTP wrapper does not fail for headers with invalid name and no colon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1734</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when receiving headers from HTTP server, the headers missing a colon (:) are treated as valid headers even though they are not. This may confuse applications into accepting invalid headers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1219 | libxml streams use wrong content-type header when requesting a redirected resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1219</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when requesting a HTTP resource using the DOM or SimpleXML extensions, the wrong content-type header is used to determine the charset when the requested resource performs a redirect. This may cause the resulting document to be parsed incorrectly or bypass validations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 05:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55895 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55895</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 12:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11180 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11180</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Timer Widget ekit_countdown_timer_title parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13557 | Shortcodes by United Themes  &amp;lt;= 5.1.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13557</link><description>The Shortcodes by United Themes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2006 | Inline Image Upload for BBPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.19 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2006</link><description>The Inline Image Upload for BBPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the file uploading functionality in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This may be exploitable by unauthenticated attackers when the "Allow guest users without accounts to create topics and replies" setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2249 | SoJ Soundslides &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2249</link><description>The SoJ SoundSlides plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the soj_soundslides_options_subpanel() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2266 | Checkout Mestres do WP for WooCommerce 8.6.5 - 8.7.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2266</link><description>The Checkout Mestres do WP for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the cwmpUpdateOptions() function in versions 8.6.5 to 8.7.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2803 | So-Called Air Quotes &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2803</link><description>The So-Called Air Quotes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2840 | DAP to Autoresponders Email Syncing &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2840</link><description>The DAP to Autoresponders Email Syncing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 through the publicly accessible phpinfo.php script. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1217 | Header parser of http stream wrapper does not handle folded headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1217</link><description>In PHP from 8.1.* before 8.1.32, from 8.2.* before 8.2.28, from 8.3.* before 8.3.19, from 8.4.* before 8.4.5, when http request module parses HTTP response obtained from a server, folded headers are parsed incorrectly, which may lead to misinterpreting the response and using incorrect headers, MIME types, etc.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 05:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>