<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:39:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-54558 | OpenAI Codex CLI before 0.9.0 auto-approves ripgrep (aka rg) execution even with the --pre or --hostname-bin or --search-zip or -z flag.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54558</link><description>OpenAI Codex CLI before 0.9.0 auto-approves ripgrep (aka rg) execution even with the --pre or --hostname-bin or --search-zip or -z flag.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8125 | deerwms deer-wms-2 allocatedList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8125</link><description>A vulnerability was found in deerwms deer-wms-2 up to 3.3. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/role/authUser/allocatedList. The manipulation of the argument params[dataScope] leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0251 | HCL IEM is affected by a concurrent login vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0251</link><description>HCL IEM is affected by a concurrent login vulnerability.  The application allows multiple concurrent sessions using the same user credentials, which may introduce security risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0252 | HCL IEM is affected by a password in cleartext vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0252</link><description>HCL IEM is affected by a password in cleartext vulnerability.  Sensitive information is transmitted without adequate protection, potentially exposing it to unauthorized access during transit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0253 | HCL IEM is affected by a cookie attribute not set vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0253</link><description>HCL IEM is affected by a cookie attribute not set vulnerability due to inconsistency of certain security-related configurations which could increase exposure to potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8124 | deerwms deer-wms-2 unallocatedList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8124</link><description>A vulnerability was found in deerwms deer-wms-2 up to 3.3. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/role/authUser/unallocatedList. The manipulation of the argument params[dataScope] leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0249 | HCL IEM is affected by an improper invalidation of access or JWT token vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0249</link><description>HCL IEM is affected by an improper invalidation of access or JWT token vulnerability.  A token was not invalidated which may allow attackers to access sensitive data without authorization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0250 | HCL IEM is affected by an authorization token sent in cookie vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0250</link><description>HCL IEM is affected by an authorization token sent in cookie vulnerability.  A token used for authentication and authorization is being handled in a manner that may increase its exposure to security risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7742 | Authentication Bypass in LG Innotek Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7742</link><description>An authentication vulnerability exists in the LG Innotek camera model LNV5110R firmware that allows a malicious actor to upload an HTTP POST request to the devices non-volatile storage. This action may result in remote code execution that allows an attacker to run arbitrary commands on the target device at the administrator privilege level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22165 | This Medium severity ACE (Arbitrary Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 4.2.8 of Sourcetree for Mac.

This ACE (Arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22165</link><description>This Medium severity ACE (Arbitrary Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 4.2.8 of Sourcetree for Mac.

This ACE (Arbitrary Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 5.9, allows a locally authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Sourcetree for Mac users upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://www.sourcetreeapp.com/download-archives .

You can download the latest version of Sourcetree for Mac from the download center https://www.sourcetreeapp.com/download-archives .

This vulnerability was found through the Atlassian Bug Bounty Program by Karol Mazurek (AFINE).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32429 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to SQL injection through getdeleteddocuments.vm template sort parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32429</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions 9.4-rc-1 through 16.10.5 and 17.0.0-rc-1 through 17.2.2, it's possible for anyone to inject SQL using the parameter sort of the getdeleteddocuments.vm. It's injected as is as an ORDER BY value. This is fixed in versions 16.10.6 and 17.3.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3614 | ElementsKit Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3614</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attribute of a custom widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53940 | Quiet uses insecure, inconsistent verification on local backend token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53940</link><description>Quiet is an alternative to team chat apps like Slack, Discord, and Element that does not require trusting a central server or running one's own. In versions 6.1.0-alpha.4 and below, Quiet's API for backend/frontend communication was using an insecure, not constant-time comparison function for token verification. This allowed for a potential timing attack where an attacker would try different token values and observe tiny differences in the response time (wrong characters fail faster) to guess the whole token one character at a time. This is fixed in version 6.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54379 | eKuiper API endpoints handling SQL queries with user-controlled table names.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54379</link><description>LF Edge eKuiper is a lightweight IoT data analytics and stream processing engine running on resource-constraint edge devices. In versions before 2.2.1, there is a critical SQL Injection vulnerability in the getLast API functionality of the eKuiper project. This flaw allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements on the underlying SQLite database by manipulating the table name input in an API request. Exploitation can lead to data theft, corruption, or deletion, and full database compromise. This is fixed in version 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31952 | HCL iAutomate is affected by an insufficient session expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31952</link><description>HCL iAutomate is affected by an insufficient session expiration.  This allows tokens to remain valid indefinitely unless manually revoked, increasing the risk of unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31955 | HCL iAutomate is affected by a sensitive data exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31955</link><description>HCL iAutomate is affected by a sensitive data exposure vulnerability.  This issue may allow unauthorized access to sensitive information within the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8123 | deerwms deer-wms-2 edit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8123</link><description>A vulnerability was found in deerwms deer-wms-2 up to 3.3. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/dept/edit. The manipulation of the argument ancestors leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6260 | Network Thermostat X-Series WiFi Thermostats Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6260</link><description>The embedded web server on the thermostat listed version ranges contain a vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers, either on the local area network or from the Internet via a router with port forwarding set up, to gain direct access to the thermostat's embedded web server and reset user credentials by manipulating specific elements of the embedded web interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7404 | Calibre Web 0.6.24 &amp;amp; Autocaliweb 0.7.0 - Blind C</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7404</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Calibre Web, Autocaliweb allows Blind OS Command Injection.This issue affects Calibre Web: 0.6.24 (Nicolette); Autocaliweb: from 0.7.0 before 0.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:57:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31953 | HCL iAutomate is affected by hardcoded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31953</link><description>HCL iAutomate includes hardcoded credentials which may result in potential exposure of confidential data if intercepted or accessed by unauthorized parties.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6998 | Calibre Web 0.6.24 &amp;amp; Autocaliweb 0.7.0 - ReDoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6998</link><description>ReDoS in strip_whitespaces() function in cps/string_helper.py in janeczku Calibre Web 0.6.24 (Nicolette) allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause denial of service via specially crafted username parameter that triggers catastrophic backtracking during login.


ReDoS in strip_whitespaces() function in cps/string_helper.py in gelbphoenix Autocaliweb 0.7.0 on allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause denial of service via specially crafted username parameter that triggers catastrophic backtracking during login.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8115 | PHPGurukul Taxi Stand Management System new-autoortaxi-entry-form.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8115</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Taxi Stand Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/new-autoortaxi-entry-form.php. The manipulation of the argument registrationnumber/licensenumber leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5039 | Privilege Ecalation due to Untrusted Search Path Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5039</link><description>A maliciously crafted binary file, when present while loading files in certain Autodesk applications, could lead to execution of arbitrary code in the context of the current process due to an untrusted search path being utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45702 | SoftPerfect Pty Ltd Connection Quality Monitor v1.1 was discovered to store all credentials in plaintext.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45702</link><description>SoftPerfect Pty Ltd Connection Quality Monitor v1.1 was discovered to store all credentials in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46993 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46993</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.22 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46996 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46996</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.22 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47061 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47061</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.22 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25214 | A race condition vulnerability exists in the aVideoEncoder.json.php unzip functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25214</link><description>A race condition vulnerability exists in the aVideoEncoder.json.php unzip functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A series of specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36548 | A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the LoginWordPress loginForm cancelUri parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36548</link><description>A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the LoginWordPress loginForm cancelUri parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary Javascript execution. An attacker can get a user to visit a webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41420 | A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the userLogin cancelUri parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41420</link><description>A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the userLogin cancelUri parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary Javascript execution. An attacker can get a user to visit a webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46410 | A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the managerPlaylists PlaylistOwnerUsersId parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46410</link><description>A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the managerPlaylists PlaylistOwnerUsersId parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary Javascript execution. An attacker can get a user to visit a webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48732 | An incomplete blacklist exists in the .htaccess sample of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48732</link><description>An incomplete blacklist exists in the .htaccess sample of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to a arbitrary code execution. An attacker can request a .phar file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50128 | A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the videoNotFound 404ErrorMsg parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev maste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50128</link><description>A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the videoNotFound 404ErrorMsg parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary Javascript execution. An attacker can get a user to visit a webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53084 | A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the videosList page parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53084</link><description>A cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the videosList page parameter functionality of WWBN AVideo 14.4 and dev master commit 8a8954ff. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary Javascript execution. An attacker can get a user to visit a webpage to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33109 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33109</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 is vulnerable to a privilege escalation caused by an invalid database authority check.  A bad actor could execute a database procedure or function without having all required permissions, in addition to causing denial of service for some database actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51088 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/WifiGuestSet. The manipulation of the argument `shareSpeed` le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51088</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/WifiGuestSet. The manipulation of the argument `shareSpeed` leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51089 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain heap overflow at /goform/GetParentControlInfo.The manipulation of the argument `mac` lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51089</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain heap overflow at /goform/GetParentControlInfo.The manipulation of the argument `mac` leads to heap-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33013 | IBM MQ Operator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33013</link><description>IBM MQ Operator LTS 2.0.0 through 2.0.29, MQ Operator CD 3.0.0, 3.0.1, 3.1.0 through 3.1.3, 3.3.0, 3.4.0, 3.4.1, 3.5.0, 3.5.1, 3.6.0, and MQ Operator SC2 3.2.0 through 3.2.13 Container could disclose sensitive information to a local user due to improper clearing of heap memory before release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36005 | IBM MQ Operator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36005</link><description>IBM MQ Operator LTS 2.0.0 through 2.0.29, MQ Operator CD 3.0.0, 3.0.1, 3.1.0 through 3.1.3, 3.3.0, 3.4.0, 3.4.1, 3.5.0, 3.5.1, 3.6.0, and MQ Operator SC2 3.2.0 through 3.2.13 Internet Pass-Thru could allow a malicious user to obtain sensitive information from another TLS session connection by the proxy to the same hostname and port due to improper certificate validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51087 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/saveParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument time l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51087</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/saveParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51082 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. The manipulation of the argument `timeZ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51082</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. The manipulation of the argument `timeZone` leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51085 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument `timeZone` and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51085</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06` was discovered to contain stack overflow at /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument `timeZone` and `timeType` leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8114 | : null pointer dereference in libssh kex session id calculation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8114</link><description>A flaw was found in libssh, a library that implements the SSH protocol. When calculating the session ID during the key exchange (KEX) process, an allocation failure in cryptographic functions may lead to a NULL pointer dereference. This issue can cause the client or server to crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45731 | A group deletion race condition in 2FAuth v5.5.0 causes data inconsistencies and orphaned accounts when a group is deleted while other opera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45731</link><description>A group deletion race condition in 2FAuth v5.5.0 causes data inconsistencies and orphaned accounts when a group is deleted while other operations are pending.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4784 | SQLi in Moderec&amp;#x27;s Tourtella</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4784</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Moderec Tourtella allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Tourtella: before 26.05.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4822 | SQLi in Bayraktar Solar Energies&amp;#x27; ScadaWatt Otopilot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4822</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Bayraktar Solar Energies ScadaWatt Otopilot allows SQL Injection.This issue affects ScadaWatt Otopilot: before 27.05.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5243 | Arbitrary File Upload in SMG Software&amp;#x27;s Information Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5243</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type, Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in SMG Software Information Portal allows Code Injection, Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server, Code Inclusion.This issue affects Information Portal: before 13.06.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40680 | Encryption of sensitive data in CapillaryScope missing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40680</link><description>Lack of sensitive data encryption in CapillaryScope v2.5.0 of Capillary io, which stores both the proxy credentials and the JWT session token in plain text within different registry keys on the Windows operating system. Any authenticated local user with read access to the registry can extract these sensitive values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3669 | Supreme Addons for Beaver Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via auto_qrcodesabb Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3669</link><description>The Supreme Addons for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's auto_qrcodesabb shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4608 | Structured Content &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sc_fs_local_business Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4608</link><description>The Structured Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's sc_fs_local_business shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5084 | Post Grid Master &amp;lt;= 3.4.13 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via argsArray[&amp;#x27;read_more_text&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5084</link><description>The Post Grid Master plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘argsArray['read_more_text']’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6262 | muse.ai video embedding &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via muse-ai Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6262</link><description>The muse.ai video embedding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's muse-ai shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6380 | ONLYOFFICE Docs 1.1.0 - 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via callback Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6380</link><description>The ONLYOFFICE Docs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to missing authorization within its oo.callback REST endpoint in versions 1.1.0 to 2.2.0. The plugin’s permission callback only verifies that the supplied, encrypted attachment ID maps to an existing attachment post, but does not verify the requester’s identity or capabilities. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as an arbitrary user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6382 | Taeggie Feed &amp;lt;= 0.1.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via name Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6382</link><description>The Taeggie Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's taeggie-feed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.10. The plugin’s render() method takes the user-supplied name attribute and injects it directly into a</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6385 | WP Applink &amp;lt;= 0.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6385</link><description>The WP Applink plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6387 | WP Get The Table &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6387</link><description>The WP Get The Table plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6441 | Webinar Solution: Create live/evergreen/automated/instant webinars, stream &amp;amp; Zoom Meetings | WebinarIgnition &amp;lt;= 4.03.31 - Unauthenticated Login Token Generation to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6441</link><description>The Webinar Solution: Create live/evergreen/automated/instant webinars, stream &amp; Zoom Meetings | WebinarIgnition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated login token generation due to a missing capability check on the `webinarignition_sign_in_support_staff` and `webinarignition_register_support` functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.03.31. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate login tokens for arbitrary WordPress users under certain circumstances, issuing authorization cookies which can lead to authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6539 | Voltax Video Player &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6539</link><description>The Voltax Video Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6588 | FunnelCockpit &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via `error` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6588</link><description>The FunnelCockpit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘error’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick an administrative user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7640 | hiWeb Export Posts &amp;lt;= 0.9.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7640</link><description>The hiWeb Export Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the tool-dashboard-history.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php), via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7690 | Affiliate Plus &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7690</link><description>The Affiliate Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'affiplus_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform an unauthorized action granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7695 | Dataverse Integration 2.77 - 2.81 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via reset_password_link REST Route</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7695</link><description>The Dataverse Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to missing authorization checks within its reset_password_link REST endpoint in versions 2.77 through 2.81. The endpoint’s handler accepts a client-supplied id, email, or login, looks up that user, and calls get_password_reset_key() unconditionally. Because it only checks that the caller is authenticated, and not that they own or may edit the target account, any authenticated attacker, with Subscriber-level access and above, can obtain a password reset link for an administrator and hijack that account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7780 | Ai Engine &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Missing URL Scheme Validation to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read via simpleTranscribeAudio and get_audio Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7780</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.4. The simpleTranscribeAudio endpoint fails to restrict URL schemes before calling get_audio(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read any file on the web server and exfiltrate it via the plugin’s OpenAI API integration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7822 | WP Wallcreeper &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Susbcriber+) Cache Enable/Disable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7822</link><description>The WP Wallcreeper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_notices hook in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enable and disable caching.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7835 | iThoughts Advanced Code Editor &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7835</link><description>The iThoughts Advanced Code Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ithoughts_ace_update_options' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7959 | Station Pro &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via width and height Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7959</link><description>The Station Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘width' and 'height’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7966 | Get Youtube Subs &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via subscribe_link_att Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7966</link><description>The Get Youtube Subs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘channel', 'layout', and 'subs_count’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8071 | Mine CloudVod &amp;lt;= 2.1.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via audio Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8071</link><description>Mine CloudVod plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘audio’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26397 | SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted Deserialization of Untrusted Data Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26397</link><description>SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted is susceptible to Deserialization of Untrusted Data Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can escalate privileges to run malicious files copied to a permission-protected folder. This vulnerability requires authentication from a low-level account and local access to the host server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8009 | Security Ninja – Secure Firewall &amp;amp; Secure Malware Scanner - 5.201 - 5.242 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8009</link><description>The Security Ninja – WordPress Security Plugin &amp; Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 5.242 via the 'get_file_source' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to extract sensitive data, including the contents of any file on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7745 | Modbus TCP buffer overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7745</link><description>: Buffer Over-read vulnerability in ABB AC500 V2.This issue affects AC500 V2: through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8107 | In OceanBase's Oracle tenant mode, a malicious user with specific privileges can achieve privilege escalation to SYS-level access by executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8107</link><description>In OceanBase's Oracle tenant mode, a malicious user with specific privileges can achieve privilege escalation to SYS-level access by executing carefully crafted commands.




This vulnerability only affects OceanBase tenants in Oracle mode. Tenants in MySQL mode are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0765 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0765</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.9 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that could have allowed an unauthorized user to access custom service desk email addresses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1299 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1299</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 before 18.0.5, all versions starting from 18.1 before 18.1.3, all versions starting from 18.2 before 18.2.1 that, under circumstances, could have allowed an unauthorized user to read deployment job logs by sending a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41240 | Mounted Kubernetes Secrets under a predictable path located within the web server document root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41240</link><description>Three Bitnami Helm charts mount Kubernetes Secrets under a predictable path (/opt/bitnami/*/secrets) that is located within the web server document root.
In affected versions, this can lead to unauthenticated access to sensitive credentials via HTTP/S. A remote attacker could retrieve these secrets by accessing specific URLs if the application is exposed externally. The issue affects deployments using the default value of usePasswordFiles=true, which mounts secrets as files into the container filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4976 | Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4976</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.0 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that, under certain circumstances, could have allowed an attacker to access internal notes in GitLab Duo responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7001 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7001</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.0 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that could have allowed priviledged users to access certain resource_group information through the API which should have been unavailable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7437 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8012 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7437</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ebook_store_save_form function in all versions up to, and including, 5.8012. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7852 | WPBookit &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via image_upload_handle Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7852</link><description>The WPBookit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the image_upload_handle() function hooked via the 'add_new_customer' route in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. The plugin’s image‐upload handler calls move_uploaded_file() on client‐supplied files without restricting allowed extensions or MIME types, nor sanitizing the filename. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4393 | Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4393</link><description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor has an internal service that deserializes data, which allows a local attacker to interact with the service by crafting a binary payload to crash the service or elevate privileges. 

This issue affects MyCareLink Patient Monitor models 24950 and 24952: before June 25, 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4394 | Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor Unencrypted Filesystem Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4394</link><description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor uses an unencrypted filesystem on internal storage, which allows an attacker with physical access to read and modify files. 

This issue affects MyCareLink Patient Monitor models 24950 and 24952: before June 25, 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4395 | Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor Empty Password Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4395</link><description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor has a built-in user account with an empty password, which allows an attacker with physical access to log in with no password and access modify system functionality. 

This issue affects MyCareLink Patient Monitor models 24950 and 24952: before June 25, 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4968 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Page Builder Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4968</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple Page Builder elements (Copyright Element,  Hover Box, Separator With Text, FAQ, Single Image, Custom Header, Button, Call To Action, Progress Bar, Pie Chart, Round Chart, and Line Chart) in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54365 | fastapi-guard patch contains bypassable RegEx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54365</link><description>fastapi-guard is a security library for FastAPI that provides middleware to control IPs, log requests, detect penetration attempts and more. In version 3.0.1, the regular expression patched to mitigate the ReDoS vulnerability by limiting the length of string fails to catch inputs that exceed this limit. This type of patch fails to detect cases in which the string representing the attributes of a</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15044 | Kaltura &amp;lt; 11.1.0-2 PHP Object Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15044</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Kaltura versions prior to 11.1.0-2 due to unsafe deserialization of user-controlled data within the keditorservices module. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this issue by sending a specially crafted serialized PHP object in the kdata GET parameter to the redirectWidgetCmd endpoint. Successful exploitation leads to execution of arbitrary PHP code in the context of the web server process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32019 | Harbor&amp;#x27;s repository description page allows for XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32019</link><description>Harbor is an open source trusted cloud native registry project that stores, signs, and scans content. Versions 2.11.2 and below, as well as versions 2.12.0-rc1 and 2.13.0-rc1, contain a vulnerability where the markdown field in the info tab page can be exploited to inject XSS code. This is fixed in versions 2.11.3 and 2.12.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47281 | Kyverno&amp;#x27;s Improper JMESPath Variable Evaluation Leads to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47281</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for cloud native platform engineering teams. In versions 1.14.1 and below, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability exists due to improper handling of JMESPath variable substitutions. Attackers with permissions to create or update Kyverno policies can craft expressions using the {{@}} variable combined with a pipe and an invalid JMESPath function (e.g., {{@ | non_existent_function }}). This leads to a nil value being substituted into the policy structure. Subsequent processing by internal functions, specifically getValueAsStringMap, which expect string values, results in a panic due to a type assertion failure (interface {} is nil, not string). This crashes Kyverno worker threads in the admission controller and causes continuous crashes of the reports controller pod. This is fixed in version 1.14.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53537 | LibHTP&amp;#x27;s memory leak with lzma can lead to resource starvation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53537</link><description>LibHTP is a security-aware parser for the HTTP protocol and its related bits and pieces. In versions 0.5.50 and below, there is a traffic-induced memory leak that can starve the process of memory, leading to loss of visibility. To workaround this issue, set `suricata.yaml app-layer.protocols.http.libhtp.default-config.lzma-enabled` to false. This issue is fixed in version 0.5.51.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53942 | authentik has an insufficient check for account active status during OAuth/SAML authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53942</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider that emphasizes flexibility and versatility, with support for a wide set of protocols. In versions 2025.4.4 and earlier, as well as versions 2025.6.0-rc1 through 2025.6.3, deactivated users who registered through OAuth/SAML or linked their accounts to OAuth/SAML providers can still retain partial access to the system despite their accounts being deactivated. They end up in a half-authenticated state where they cannot access the API but crucially they can authorize applications if they know the URL of the application. To workaround this issue, developers can add an expression policy to the user login stage on the respective authentication flow with the expression of return request.context["pending_user"].is_active. This modification ensures that the return statement only activates the user login stage when the user is active. This issue is fixed in versions authentik 2025.4.4 and 2025.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54377 | Roo Code Lacks Line Break Validation in its Command Execution Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54377</link><description>Roo Code is an AI-powered autonomous coding agent that lives in users' editors. In versions 3.23.18 and below, RooCode does not validate line breaks (\n) in its command input, allowing potential bypass of the allow-list mechanism. The project appears to lack parsing or validation logic to prevent multi-line command injection. When commands are evaluated for execution, only the first line or token may be considered, enabling attackers to smuggle additional commands in subsequent lines. This is fixed in version 3.23.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8058 | The regcomp function in the GNU C library version from 2.4 to 2.41 is 
subject to a double free if some previous allocation fails. It can be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8058</link><description>The regcomp function in the GNU C library version from 2.4 to 2.41 is 
subject to a double free if some previous allocation fails. It can be 
accomplished either by a malloc failure or by using an interposed malloc
 that injects random malloc failures. The double free can allow buffer 
manipulation depending of how the regex is constructed. This issue 
affects all architectures and ABIs supported by the GNU C library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44109 | A URL redirection in Pinokio v3.6.23 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44109</link><description>A URL redirection in Pinokio v3.6.23 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50477 | A URL redirection in lbry-desktop v0.53.9 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50477</link><description>A URL redirection in lbry-desktop v0.53.9 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46686 | Redis through 7.4.3 allows memory consumption via a multi-bulk command composed of many bulks, sent by an authenticated user. This occurs be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46686</link><description>Redis through 7.4.3 allows memory consumption via a multi-bulk command composed of many bulks, sent by an authenticated user. This occurs because the server allocates memory for the command arguments of every bulk, even when the command is skipped because of insufficient permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47187 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47187</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform a file upload attack due to missing authentication mechanisms. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to upload arbitrary WAV files, which may potentially exhaust the phone's storage without affecting the phone's availability or operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4439 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4439</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.10 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to perform cross-site scripting attacks when the instance is served through certain content delivery networks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4700 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4700</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.10 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that, under specific circumstances, could have potentially allowed a successful attacker to trigger unintended content rendering leading to XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50481 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /blog/blogpost/add of Mezzanine CMS v6.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50481</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /blog/blogpost/add of Mezzanine CMS v6.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into a blog post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2633 | Out of Bounds Read Vulnerability in NI LabVIEW when loading fonts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2633</link><description>Out of bounds read vulnerability due to improper bounds checking in NI LabVIEW in lvre!UDecStrToNum that may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2634 | Out of Bounds Read Vulnerability in NI LabVIEW when building font map</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2634</link><description>Out of bounds read vulnerability due to improper bounds checking in NI LabVIEW in fontmgr may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8069 | Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in AWS Client VPN Windows Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8069</link><description>During the AWS Client VPN client installation on Windows devices, the install process references the C:\usr\local\windows-x86_64-openssl-localbuild\ssl directory location to fetch the OpenSSL configuration file. As a result, a non-admin user could place arbitrary code in the configuration file. If an admin user starts the AWS Client VPN client installation process, that code could be executed with root-level privileges. This issue does not affect Linux or Mac devices. 

We recommend users discontinue any new installations of AWS Client VPN on Windows prior to version 5.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46171 | vBulletin 3.8.7 is vulnerable to a denial-of-service condition via the misc.php?do=buddylist endpoint. If an authenticated user has a suffic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46171</link><description>vBulletin 3.8.7 is vulnerable to a denial-of-service condition via the misc.php?do=buddylist endpoint. If an authenticated user has a sufficiently large buddy list, processing the list can consume excessive memory, exhausting system resources and crashing the forum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6018 | Pam-config: lpe from unprivileged to allow_active in pam</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6018</link><description>A Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerability has been discovered in pam-config within Linux Pluggable Authentication Modules (PAM). This flaw allows an unprivileged local attacker (for example, a user logged in via SSH) to obtain the elevated privileges normally reserved for a physically present, "allow_active" user. The highest risk is that the attacker can then perform all allow_active yes Polkit actions, which are typically restricted to console users, potentially gaining unauthorized control over system configurations, services, or other sensitive operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33020 | IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33020</link><description>IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody 9.0.2, 10.0, and 10.0.1 transmits sensitive information without encryption that could allow an attacker to obtain highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33076 | IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33076</link><description>IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody 9.0.2, 10.0, and 10.0.1 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A local user could overflow the buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33077 | IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33077</link><description>IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody 9.0.2, 10.0, and 10.0.1 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A local user could overflow the buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40597 | A Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40597</link><description>A Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS) or potentially results in code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40598 | A Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SMA100 series web interface, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40598</link><description>A Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SMA100 series web interface, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40596 | A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40596</link><description>A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS) or potentially results in code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36116 | IBM Db2 Mirror for i cross-site websocket hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36116</link><description>IBM Db2 Mirror for i 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 GUI is affected by cross-site WebSocket hijacking vulnerability.  By sending a specially crafted request, an unauthenticated malicious actor could exploit this vulnerability to sniff an existing WebSocket connection to then remotely perform operations that the user is not allowed to perform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36117 | IBM Db2 Mirror for i session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36117</link><description>IBM Db2 Mirror for i 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 does not disallow the session id after use which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10012 | httpdASM 0.92 Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10012</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in httpdasm version 0.92, a lightweight Windows HTTP server, that allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the host system. By sending a specially crafted GET request containing a sequence of URL-encoded backslashes and directory traversal patterns, an attacker can escape the web root and access sensitive files outside of the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10141 | Xdebug Remote Debugger Unauthenticated OS Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10141</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists within Xdebug versions 2.5.5 and earlier, a PHP debugging extension developed by Derick Rethans. When remote debugging is enabled, Xdebug listens on port 9000 and accepts debugger protocol commands without authentication. An attacker can send a crafted eval command over this interface to execute arbitrary PHP code, which may invoke system-level functions such as system() or passthru(). This results in full compromise of the host under the privileges of the web server user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15045 | Deepin lastore-daemon Privilege Escalation via Unsigned .deb Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15045</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in lastore-daemon, the system package manager daemon used in Deepin Linux (developed by Wuhan Deepin Technology Co., Ltd.). In versions 0.9.53-1 (Deepin 15.5) and 0.9.66-1 (Deepin 15.7), the D-Bus configuration permits any user in the sudo group to invoke the InstallPackage method without password authentication. By default, the first user created on Deepin is in the sudo group. An attacker with shell access can craft a .deb package containing a malicious post-install script and use dbus-send to install it via lastore-daemon, resulting in arbitrary code execution as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20198 | DC/OS Marathon UI &amp;lt; 1.9.0 Unauthenticated RCE via Docker Mount Abuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20198</link><description>The Marathon UI in DC/OS &lt; 1.9.0 allows unauthenticated users to deploy arbitrary Docker containers. Due to improper restriction of volume mount configurations, attackers can deploy a container that mounts the host's root filesystem (/) with read/write privileges. When using a malicious Docker image, the attacker can write to /etc/cron.d/ on the host, achieving arbitrary code execution with root privileges. This impacts any system where the Docker daemon honors Marathon container configurations without policy enforcement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25113 | Dicoogle PACS Web Server 2.5.0 Unauthenticated Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25113</link><description>An unauthenticated path traversal vulnerability exists in Dicoogle PACS Web Server version 2.5.0 and possibly earlier. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files on the underlying system by sending a crafted request to the /exportFile endpoint using the UID parameter. Successful exploitation can reveal sensitive files accessible by the web server user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25114 | osCommerce 2.3.4.1 Installer Unauthenticated Configuration File Injection PHP Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25114</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists within osCommerce Online Merchant version 2.3.4.1 due to insecure default configuration and missing authentication in the installer workflow. By default, the /install/ directory remains accessible after installation. An unauthenticated attacker can invoke install_4.php, submit crafted POST data, and inject arbitrary PHP code into the configure.php file. When the application later includes this file, the injected payload is executed, resulting in full server-side compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4978 | Steppschuh Remote Control Server 3.1.1.12 Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4978</link><description>Remote Control Server, maintained by Steppschuh, 3.1.1.12 allows unauthenticated remote code execution when authentication is disabled, which is the default configuration. The server exposes a custom UDP-based control protocol that accepts remote keyboard input events without verification. An attacker on the same network can issue a sequence of keystroke commands to launch a system shell and execute arbitrary commands, resulting in full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46099 | In Pluck CMS 4.7.20-dev, an authenticated attacker can upload or create a crafted PHP file under the albums module directory and access it v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46099</link><description>In Pluck CMS 4.7.20-dev, an authenticated attacker can upload or create a crafted PHP file under the albums module directory and access it via the module routing logic in albums.site.php, resulting in arbitrary command execution through a GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40599 | An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in the SMA 100 series web management interface. A remote attacker with administr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40599</link><description>An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in the SMA 100 series web management interface. A remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this flaw to upload arbitrary files to the system, potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54090 | Apache HTTP Server: &amp;#x27;RewriteCond expr&amp;#x27; always evaluates to true in 2.4.64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54090</link><description>A bug in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.64 results in all "RewriteCond expr ..." tests evaluating as "true".



Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.65, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4411 | XSS in Dataprom Informatics&amp;#x27; PACS-ACSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4411</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dataprom Informatics PACS-ACSS allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects PACS-ACSS: before 16.05.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12310 | Bypass of Login Screen on Shared Kiosk Workstations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12310</link><description>A vulnerability in Imprivata Enterprise Access Management (formerly Imprivata OneSign) allows bypassing the login screen of the shared kiosk workstation and allows unauthorized access to the underlying Windows system through the already logged-in autologon account due to insufficient handling of keyboard shortcuts.
This issue affects Imprivata Enterprise Access Management versions 5.3 through 24.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4296 | Open Redirect in HotelRunner&amp;#x27;s B2B</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4296</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in HotelRunner B2B allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects B2B: before 04.06.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40682 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40682</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to improper validation of specified type of input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40686 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40686</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers. This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41750 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41750</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 could allow a local, authenticated attacker to bypass client-side enforcement of security to manipulate data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41751 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41751</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 could allow a local, authenticated attacker to bypass client-side enforcement of security to manipulate data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50127 | Extension - dj-extensions.com - SQLi vulnerability in DJ-Flyer component 1.0-3.2 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50127</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability in DJ-Flyer component 1.0-3.2 for Joomla was discovered. The issue allows privileged users to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54294 | Extension - stackideas.com - SQLi vulnerability in Komento component 4.0.0-4.0.7 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54294</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability in Komento component 4.0.0-4.0.7for Joomla was discovered. The issue allows unprivileged users to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54295 | Extension - dj-extensions.com - Reflected XSS vulnerability in DJ-Reviews component 1.0-1.3.6 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54295</link><description>A Reflected XSS vulnerability in DJ-Reviews component 1.0-1.3.6 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54296 | Extension - mooj.org - Stored XSS vulnerability in ProFiles component 1.0-1.5.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54296</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in ProFiles component 1.0-1.5.0 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54297 | Extension - compojoom.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in CComment component 5.0.0-6.1.14 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54297</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in CComment component 5.0.0-6.1.14 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27930 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27930</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 176600 and prior are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting in the File/Directory monitor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53882 | python-mailmans logrotate configuration allows potential escalation from mailman to root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53882</link><description>A Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision vulnerability in the logrotate configuration for openSUSEs mailman3 package allows potential escalation from mailman to root. This issue affects openSUSE Tumbleweed: from ? before 3.3.10-2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41683 | Weidmueller: Root Command Injection via Unsanitized Input in event_mail_test Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41683</link><description>An authenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on affected devices due to lack of improper sanitizing of user input in the Main Web Interface (endpoint event_mail_test).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41684 | Weidmueller: Root Command Injection via Unsanitized Input in tls_iotgen_setting Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41684</link><description>An authenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on affected devices due to lack of improper sanitizing of user input in the Main Web Interface (endpoint tls_iotgen_setting).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41687 | Weidmueller: Unauthenticated Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in u-link Management API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41687</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a stack based buffer overflow in the u-link Management API to gain full access on the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8070 | Windows service registered with an unquoted ImagePath vulnerability in the system registry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8070</link><description>The Windows service configuration of ABP and AES contains an unquoted ImagePath registry value vulnerability. This allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code by placing a malicious executable in a predictable location such as C:\Program.exe. If the service runs with elevated privileges, exploitation results in privilege escalation to SYSTEM level. This vulnerability arises from an unquoted service path affecting systems where the executable resides in a path containing spaces.
Affected products and versions include: ABP 2.0.7.6130 and earlier as well as AES 1.0.6.6133 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31700 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31700</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted malicious packets, potentially causing service disruption (e.g., crashes) or remote code execution (RCE). Some devices may have deployed protection mechanisms such as Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR), which reduces the likelihood of successful RCE exploitation. However, denial-of-service (DoS) attacks remain a concern.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31701 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31701</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted malicious packets, potentially causing service disruption (e.g., crashes) or remote code execution (RCE). Some devices may have deployed protection mechanisms such as Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR), which reduces the likelihood of successful RCE exploitation. However, denial-of-service (DoS) attacks remain a concern.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6174 | WordPress Qwizcards &amp;lt;= 3.9.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6174</link><description>The Qwizcards | online quizzes and flashcards WordPress plugin through 3.9.4 does not sanitise and escape the "_stylesheet" parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or any other user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54438 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54438</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54439 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54439</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54440 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54440</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54441 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54441</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54442 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54442</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54443 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54443</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54444 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54444</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54445 | Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Server Side Request For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54445</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54446 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54446</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54447 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54447</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54448 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54448</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54451 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54451</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54452 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54452</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54453 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54453</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54449 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54449</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54450 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54450</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54454 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54454</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54455 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54455</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8020 | All versions of the package private-ip are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide an IP or hostname ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8020</link><description>All versions of the package private-ip are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide an IP or hostname that resolves to a multicast IP address (224.0.0.0/4) which is not included as part of the private IP ranges in the package's source code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8021 | All versions of the package files-bucket-server are vulnerable to Directory Traversal where an attacker can traverse the file system and acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8021</link><description>All versions of the package files-bucket-server are vulnerable to Directory Traversal where an attacker can traverse the file system and access files outside of the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8022 | Versions of the package bun after 0.0.12 are vulnerable to Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command In...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8022</link><description>Versions of the package bun after 0.0.12 are vulnerable to Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') in the $ shell API due to improper neutralization of user input. An attacker can exploit this by providing specially crafted input that includes command-line arguments or shell metacharacters, leading to unintended command execution.&#13;&#13;**Note:** This issue relates to the widely known and actively developed 'Bun' JavaScript runtime. The bun package on NPM at versions 0.0.12 and below belongs to a different and older project that happened to claim the 'bun' name in the past.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43881 | Improper validation of specified quantity in input issue exists in Real-time Bus Tracking System versions prior to 1.1. If exploited, a deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43881</link><description>Improper validation of specified quantity in input issue exists in Real-time Bus Tracking System versions prior to 1.1. If exploited, a denial of service (DoS) condition may be caused by an attacker who can log in to the administrative page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53286 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in DDNS Record functionality in Syn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53286</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in DDNS Record functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-11 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53287 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VPN Setting functionality in Synology ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53287</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VPN Setting functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-11 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53288 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NTP Region functionality in Synology R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53288</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NTP Region functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-11 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42947 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP FICA ODN framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42947</link><description>SAP FICA ODN framework allows a high privileged user to inject value inside the local variable which can then be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behaviour of the application causing high impact on integrity, low impact on availability and no impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5753 | Valuation Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via link Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5753</link><description>The Valuation Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5818 | Featured Image Plus – Quick &amp;amp; Bulk Edit with Unsplash &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5818</link><description>The Featured Image Plus – Quick &amp; Bulk Edit with Unsplash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 via the fip_get_image_options() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6054 | YANewsflash &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6054</link><description>The YANewsflash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'yanewsflash/yanewsflash.php' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6190 | Realty Portal – Agent &amp;lt;= 0.3.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via rp_user_profile() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6190</link><description>The Realty Portal – Agent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to missing authorization within the rp_user_profile() AJAX handler in versions 0.1.0 through 0.3.9. The handler reads the client-supplied meta key and value pairs from $_POST and passes them directly to update_user_meta() without restricting to a safe whitelist. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the wp_capabilities meta and grant themselves the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6214 | Omnishop &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary User Deletion via /users/delete REST Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6214</link><description>The Omnishop plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery on its /users/delete REST route in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. The route’s permission_callback only verifies that the requester is logged in, but fails to require any nonce or other proof of intent. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user accounts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6215 | Omnishop &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Registration Restriction to Unauthenticated Account Creation via /users/register REST Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6215</link><description>The Omnishop plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Registration Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. Its /users/register endpoint is exposed to the public (permission_callback always returns true) and invokes wp_create_user() unconditionally,  ignoring the site’s users_can_register option and any nonce or CAPTCHA checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary user accounts (customer) on sites where registrations should be closed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6261 | Fleetwire Fleet Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via fleetwire_list Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6261</link><description>The Fleetwire Fleet Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's fleetwire_list shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7722 | Social Streams &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7722</link><description>The Social Streams plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their user meta information in the update_user_meta() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change their user type to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8060 | Tenda AC23 httpd setMacFilterCfg sub_46C940 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8060</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_46C940 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54120 | PCL Community Edition exposes login credentials in logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54120</link><description>PCL (Plain Craft Launcher) Community Edition is a Minecraft launcher. In PCL CE versions 2.12.0-beta.5 to 2.12.0-beta.9, the login credentials used during the third-party login process are accidentally recorded in the local log file. Although the log file is not automatically uploaded or shared, if the user manually sends the log file, there is a risk of leakage. This is fixed in version 2.12.0-beta.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>