<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-14018 | Unquoted Service Path in NetBT Consultancy&amp;#x27;s e-Fatura</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14018</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in NetBT Consulting Services Inc. E-Fatura allows Leveraging/Manipulating Configuration File Search Paths, Redirect Access to Libraries.This issue affects e-Fatura: before 1.2.15.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14273 | Mattermost Jira plugin user spoofing enables Jira request forgery.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14273</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.0, 11.0.x &lt;= 11.0.5, 10.12.x &lt;= 10.12.3, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.7 with the Jira plugin enabled and Mattermost Jira plugin versions &lt;=4.4.0 fail to enforce authentication and issue-key path restrictions in the Jira plugin, which allows an unauthenticated attacker who knows a valid user ID to issue authenticated GET and POST requests to the Jira server via crafted plugin payloads that spoof the user ID and inject arbitrary issue key paths. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00555</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54890 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the Hostgroups configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54890</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Hostgroup configuration page) allows Stored 

XSS by users with elevated privileges.This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.15, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.19, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.29.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12514 | A user with elevated privileges is able to introduce a SQL Injection using the Open-tickets Notification rules configuration parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12514</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring - Open-tickets (Notification rules configuration parameters, Open tickets modules) allows 

SQL Injection to user with elevated privileges.This issue affects Infra Monitoring - Open-tickets: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.5, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.5, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8460 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the Notification rules configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8460</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Notification rules, Open tickets module) 

allows Stored 

XSS by users with elevated privileges.This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.5, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.5, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61739 | Johnson Controls IQ Panels2, 2+, IQHub, IQPanel 4, PowerG reusing a nonce, key pair in encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61739</link><description>Due to Nonce reuse, attackers can perform reply attack or decrypt captured packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61738 | Johnson Controls PowerG and IQPanel cleartext transmission of sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61738</link><description>Under certain circumstances, attacker can capture the network key, read or write encrypted packets on the PowerG network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62094 | WordPress Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62094</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Voidthemes Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder.This issue affects Void Elementor WHMCS Elements For Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 2.0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62107 | WordPress Feather Login Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62107</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PluginOps Feather Login Page allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Feather Login Page: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62880 | WordPress Custom 404 Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62880</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kunal Nagar Custom 404 Pro allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Custom 404 Pro: from n/a through 3.12.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8305 | Information Disclosure in Identity Agent Debug Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8305</link><description>An authenticated local user can obtain information that allows claiming security policy rules of another user due to sensitive information being printed in plaintext in Identity Agent for Terminal Services debug files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8304 | Information Disclosure in Identity Agent Registry Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8304</link><description>An authenticated local user can obtain information that allows claiming security policy rules of another user due to sensitive information being accessible in the Windows Registry keys for Check Point Identity Agent running on a Terminal Server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11544 | Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11544</link><description>Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauthorized firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11545 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11545</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may improperly access the HTTP server and execute arbitrary actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11540 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may access and read any files within the projector.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11540</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may access and read any files within the projector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11541 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and program...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11541</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and programs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11542 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and program...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11542</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may execute arbitrary commands and programs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11543 | Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11543</link><description>Improper Validation of Integrity Check Value vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions projectors allows a attacker may create and run unauthorized firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12049 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions Media Player MP-01 All Verisons allows a attacker may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12049</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Sharp Display Solutions Media Player MP-01 All Verisons allows a attacker may access to the web interface of the affected product without authentication and change settings or perform other operations, and deliver content from the authoring software to the affected product without authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15014 | loganhong php loganSite Article article_detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15014</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in loganhong php loganSite up to c035fb5c3edd0b2a5e32fd4051cbbc9e61a31426. This affects an unknown function of the file /includes/article_detail.php of the component Article Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15013 | floooh sokol sokol_gfx.h _sg_validate_pipeline_desc stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15013</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in floooh sokol up to 5d11344150973f15e16d3ec4ee7550a73fb995e0. The impacted element is the function _sg_validate_pipeline_desc in the library sokol_gfx.h. Such manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The name of the patch is b95c5245ba357967220c9a860c7578a7487937b0. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15012 | code-projects Refugee Food Management System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15012</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Refugee Food Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /home/home.php. This manipulation of the argument a causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15011 | code-projects Simple Stock System logout.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15011</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /logout.php. The manipulation of the argument uname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15015 | Ragic｜Enterprise Cloud Database - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15015</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database developed by Ragic has a Arbitrary File Read vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15016 | Ragic｜Enterprise Cloud Database - Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15016</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database developed by Ragic has a Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit the fixed key to generate verification information and log into the system as any user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15010 | Tenda WH450 SafeUrlFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15010</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/SafeUrlFilter. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59301 | Modbus/TCP Dos Vulnerability in DVP15MC11T</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59301</link><description>Delta Electronics DVP15MC11T lacks proper validation of the modbus/tcp packets and can lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15008 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request L7Port stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15008</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/L7Port of the component HTTP Request Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument page results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15009 | liweiyi ChestnutCMS Filename upload FilenameUtils.getExtension unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15009</link><description>A flaw has been found in liweiyi ChestnutCMS up to 1.5.8. This vulnerability affects the function FilenameUtils.getExtension of the file /dev-api/common/upload of the component Filename Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15007 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request L7Im stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15007</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/L7Im of the component HTTP Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15006 | Tenda WH450 HTTP Request CheckTools stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15006</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/CheckTools of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument ipaddress causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15005 | CouchCMS reCAPTCHA config.example.php hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15005</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in CouchCMS up to 2.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file couch/config.example.php of the component reCAPTCHA Handler. The manipulation of the argument K_RECAPTCHA_SITE_KEY/K_RECAPTCHA_SECRET_KEY results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15004 | DedeCMS freelist_main.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15004</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in DedeCMS up to 5.7.118. This impacts an unknown function of the file /freelist_main.php. The manipulation of the argument orderby leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15003 | SeaCMS admin_video.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15003</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SeaCMS up to 13.3. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file admin_video.php. Performing manipulation of the argument e_id results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15002 | SeaCMS mysqli.class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15002</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SeaCMS up to 13.3. The affected element is an unknown function of the file js/player/dmplayer/dmku/class/mysqli.class.php. Such manipulation of the argument page/limit leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62901 | WordPress WP Microdata plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62901</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tormorten WP Microdata allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Microdata: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62926 | WordPress TempTool plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HappyDevs TempTool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TempTool: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62955 | WordPress TempTool plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62955</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in HappyDevs TempTool allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects TempTool: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14995 | Tenda FH1201 SetIpBind sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14995</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH1201 1.2.0.14(408). Affected is the function sprintf of the file /goform/SetIpBind. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 08:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14800 | Redirection for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Copy via move_file_to_upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14800</link><description>The Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'move_file_to_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to copy arbitrary files on the affected site's server. If 'allow_url_fopen' is set to 'On', it is possible to upload a remote file to the server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14855 | SureForms &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14855</link><description>The SureForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form field parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14994 | Tenda FH1201/FH1206 HTTP Request webtypelibrary strcat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14994</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda FH1201 and FH1206 1.2.0.14(408)/1.2.0.8(8155). This impacts the function strcat of the file /goform/webtypelibrary of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument webSiteId causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14993 | Tenda AC18 HTTP Request SetDlnaCfg sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14993</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. This affects the function sprintf of the file /goform/SetDlnaCfg of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument scanList results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14992 | Tenda AC18 HTTP Request GetParentControlInfo strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14992</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12398 | Product Table for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12398</link><description>The Product Table for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12654 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 0.9.120 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary Directory Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12654</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary directory creation in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.120. This is due to the check_filesystem_permissions() function not properly restricting the directories that can be created, or in what location. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to create arbitrary directories.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13220 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13220</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13361 | Web to SugarCRM Lead &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom Field Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13361</link><description>The Web to SugarCRM Lead plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the custom field deletion functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete custom fields via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13693 | Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid &amp;lt;= 3.6.8 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Custom Scripts&amp;#x27; Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13693</link><description>The Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Custom scripts' setting in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14991 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System bwdates-reports-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14991</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. Executing manipulation of the argument fromdate can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9343 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9343</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ticket subjects in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14990 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14990</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. Performing manipulation of the argument viewid results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68644 | Yealink RPS before 2025-06-27 allows unauthorized access to information, including AutoP URL addresses. This was fixed by deploying an enhan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68644</link><description>Yealink RPS before 2025-06-27 allows unauthorized access to information, including AutoP URL addresses. This was fixed by deploying an enhanced authentication mechanism through a security update to all cloud instances.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11496 | Five Star Restaurant Reservations – WordPress Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11496</link><description>The Five Star Restaurant Reservations – WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rtb-name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12980 | Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks for News, Magazines, Blog Websites – PostX &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12980</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks for News, Magazines, Blog Websites – PostX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the '/ultp/v2/get_dynamic_content/' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive user metadata, including password hashes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13838 | WishSuite &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;button_text&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13838</link><description>The WishSuite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button_text' parameter of the 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14043 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Metadata Section Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14043</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized metadata section creation due to missing authorization checks in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the `create_item_permissions_check()` function unconditionally returning true, which bypasses authentication and authorization validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary metadata sections for any collection via the public REST API granted they can access the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14054 | WC Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;heading_color&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14054</link><description>The WC Builder – WooCommerce Page Builder for WPBakery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'heading_color' parameter (and multiple other styling parameters) of the `wpbforwpbakery_product_additional_information` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14071 | Live Composer – Free WordPress Website Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection via dslc_module_posts_output Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14071</link><description>The Live Composer – Free WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via deserialization of untrusted input in the dslc_module_posts_output shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14080 | Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14080</link><description>The Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This is due to missing authorization checks on the post update functionality in the fpsml_form_process AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary posts by providing a post_id parameter via the guest posting form, allowing them to change post titles, content, excerpts, and remove post authors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25445 | WordPress HappyFiles Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25445</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HappyFiles HappyFiles Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HappyFiles Pro: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25446 | WordPress HappyFiles Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25446</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HappyFiles HappyFiles Pro happyfiles-pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HappyFiles Pro: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47232 | WordPress WP Affiliate Disclosure plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47232</link><description>Vulnerability in mojofywp WP Affiliate Disclosure wp-affiliate-disclosure.This issue affects WP Affiliate Disclosure: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25068 | WordPress Magazine Edge theme &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Authenticated Arbitrary Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25068</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mapro Collins Magazine Edge allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Magazine Edge: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14989 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System search-invoices.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14989</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-invoices.php. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 23:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34290 | Versa SASE Client for Windows &amp;lt; 7.9.5 Arbitrary Folder Deletion Leading to Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34290</link><description>Versa SASE Client for Windows versions released between 7.8.7 and 7.9.4 contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability in the audit log export functionality. The client communicates user-controlled file paths to a privileged service, which performs file system operations without impersonating the requesting user. Due to improper privilege handling and a time-of-check time-of-use race condition combined with symbolic link and mount point manipulation, a local authenticated attacker can coerce the service into deleting arbitrary directories with SYSTEM privileges. This can be exploited to delete protected system folders such as C:\\Config.msi and subsequently achieve execution as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM via MSI rollback techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 20:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7733 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Authenticated (Candidate+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7733</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress, used by the JobCareer theme, is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 7.7 via the 'cs_update_application_status_callback' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Candidate-level access and above, to send a site-generated email with injected HTML to any user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7782 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Candidate+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;status&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7782</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress, used by the JobCareer theme, is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'cs_update_application_status_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 7.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Candidate-level access and above, to inject cross-site scripting into the 'status' parameter of applied jobs for any user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12492 | Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp;amp; Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12492</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.0 via the ajax_get_members function. This is due to the use of a predictable low-entropy token (5 hex characters derived from md5 of post ID) to identify member directories and insufficient authorization checks on the unauthenticated AJAX endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including usernames, display names, user roles (including administrator accounts), profile URLs, and user IDs by enumerating predictable directory_id values or brute-forcing the small 16^5 token space.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 08:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14298 | FiboSearch – Ajax Search for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.32.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via thegem_te_search Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14298</link><description>The FiboSearch – Ajax Search for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `thegem_te_search` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.32.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This vulnerability requires TheGem theme (premium) to be installed with Header Builder mode enabled, and the FiboSearch "Replace search bars" option enabled for TheGem integration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 08:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13619 | Flex Store Users &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13619</link><description>The Flex Store Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to the 'fsUserHandle::signup' and the 'fsSellerRole::add_role_seller' functions not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site. Note: The vulnerability can be exploited with the 'fs_type' parameter if the Flex Store Seller plugin is also activated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12820 | Pure WC Variation Swatches &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12820</link><description>The Pure WC Variation Swatches WordPress plugin through 1.1.7 does not have an authorization check when updating its settings, which could allow any authenticated users to update them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 06:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12581 | Attachments Handler &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12581</link><description>The Attachments Handler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12898 | Pretty Google Calendar &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Google API Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12898</link><description>The Pretty Google Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the pgcal_ajax_handler() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the Google API key set in the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13329 | File Uploader for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via add-image-data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13329</link><description>The File Uploader for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the callback function for the 'add-image-data' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files to the Uploadcare service and subsequently download them on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13365 | WP Hallo Welt &amp;lt;= 1.4. - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13365</link><description>The WP Hallo Welt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'hallo_welt_seite' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Due to the insufficient input sanitization and output escaping, this can lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13624 | Overstock Affiliate Links &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13624</link><description>The Overstock Affiliate Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14164 | Quran Gateway &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14164</link><description>The Quran Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing nonce validation in the quran_gateway_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's display settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14168 | WP DB Booster &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Database Cleanup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14168</link><description>The WP DB Booster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the cleanup_all AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete database records including post drafts, revisions, comments, and metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14591 | PII Leak Due to Change in EOR Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14591</link><description>After a recent bug fix to correctly handle CR+LF (Windows and DOS) End-of-Record (EOR) characters in delimited files, an issue was identified: using an incorrect EOR configuration can cause inaccurate parsing and leave personally identifiable information (PII) unmasked.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14633 | F70 Lead Document Download &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Media File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14633</link><description>The F70 Lead Document Download plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'file_download' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download any file from the WordPress media library by guessing or enumerating WordPress attachment IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14721 | Responsive and Swipe slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14721</link><description>The Responsive and Swipe slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's rsSlider shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14734 | Amazon affiliate lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14734</link><description>The Amazon affiliate lite Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ADAL_settings_page' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14735 | Amazon affiliate lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14735</link><description>The "Amazon affiliate lite Plugin" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14299 | Improper Content-Length Validation in HTTPS Requests on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14299</link><description>The HTTPS server on Tapo C200 V3 does not properly validate the Content-Length header, which can lead to an integer overflow. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can send crafted HTTPS requests to trigger excessive memory allocation, causing the device to crash and resulting in denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14300 | Unauthenticated Access to connectAP API Endpoint on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14300</link><description>The HTTPS service on Tapo C200 V3 exposes a connectAP interface without proper authentication. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can exploit this to modify the device’s Wi-Fi configuration, resulting in loss of connectivity and denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8065 | Buffer Overflow in ONVIF XML Parser on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8065</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ONVIF XML parser of Tapo C200 V3. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can send specially crafted SOAP XML requests, causing memory overflow and device crash, resulting in denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>