<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 13:02:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-22143 | WordPress WP Spell Check Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.17 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22143</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Spell Check.This issue affects WP Spell Check: from n/a through 9.17.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 13:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7043 | Unquoted path privilege vulnerability in ESET products for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7043</link><description>Unquoted service path in ESET products allows to 

drop a prepared program to a specific location and run on boot with the 

NT AUTHORITY\NetworkService permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22285 | WordPress Frontpage Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22285</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Elise Bosse Frontpage Manager.This issue affects Frontpage Manager: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22291 | WordPress Browser Theme Color Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22291</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marco Milesi Browser Theme Color.This issue affects Browser Theme Color: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1085 | Use-after-free in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s netfilter: nf_tables component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1085</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability in the Linux kernel's netfilter: nf_tables component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

The nft_setelem_catchall_deactivate() function checks whether the catch-all set element is active in the current generation instead of the next generation before freeing it, but only flags it inactive in the next generation, making it possible to free the element multiple times, leading to a double free vulnerability.

We recommend upgrading past commit b1db244ffd041a49ecc9618e8feb6b5c1afcdaa7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1086 | Use-after-free in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s netfilter: nf_tables component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1086</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability in the Linux kernel's netfilter: nf_tables component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

The nft_verdict_init() function allows positive values as drop error within the hook verdict, and hence the nf_hook_slow() function can cause a double free vulnerability when NF_DROP is issued with a drop error which resembles NF_ACCEPT.

We recommend upgrading past commit f342de4e2f33e0e39165d8639387aa6c19dff660.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22304 | WordPress FreshMail For WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22304</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Borbis Media FreshMail For WordPress.This issue affects FreshMail For WordPress: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22287 | WordPress Better Anchor Links Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22287</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Luděk Melichar Better Anchor Links allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Better Anchor Links: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22290 | WordPress Custom Dashboard Widgets Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22290</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AboZain,O7abeeb,UnitOne Custom Dashboard Widgets allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Custom Dashboard Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23507 | WordPress InstaWP Connect Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.9 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23507</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in InstaWP Team InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp; Migration.This issue affects InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp; Migration: from n/a through 0.1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22305 | WordPress Contact Form builder with drag &amp;amp; drop - Kali Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.36 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22305</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ali Forms Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress – Kali Forms.This issue affects Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress – Kali Forms: from n/a through 2.3.36.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1098 | Rebuild proxy-download QiniuCloud.getStorageFile information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1098</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function QiniuCloud.getStorageFile of the file /filex/proxy-download. The manipulation of the argument url leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252455.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1099 | Rebuild read-raw getFileOfData cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1099</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function getFileOfData of the file /filex/read-raw. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252456.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50357 | Cross site scripting vulnerability in AREAL SAS Webserv1 ASP Web Site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50357</link><description>A cross site scripting vulnerability in the AREAL SAS Websrv1 ASP website allows a remote low-privileged attacker to gain escalated privileges of other non-admin users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 10:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50356 | Improper Certificate Validation in AREAL Topkapi Vision (Server)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50356</link><description>SSL connections to NOVELL and Synology LDAP server are vulnerable to a man-in-the-middle attack due to improper certificate validation in AREAL Topkapi Vision (Server). This allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to gather sensitive information and prevent valid users from login.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 10:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44312 | Apache ServiceComb Service-Center: attacker can query all environment variables of the service-center server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44312</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Apache ServiceComb Service-Center.This issue affects 

Apache ServiceComb Service-Center

 before 2.1.0 (include).

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.2.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 08:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44313 | Apache ServiceComb Service-Center: attacker can perform SSRF through the frontend API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44313</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache ServiceComb Service-Center. Attackers can obtain sensitive server information through specially crafted requests.This issue affects Apache ServiceComb before 2.1.0(include).

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.2.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 08:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0836 | The WordPress Review &amp; Structure Data Schema Plugin – Review Schema plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0836</link><description>The WordPress Review &amp; Structure Data Schema Plugin – Review Schema plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the rtrs_review_edit() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify arbitrary reviews.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23775 | Integer Overflow vulnerability in Mbed TLS 2.x before 2.28.7 and 3.x before 3.5.2, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23775</link><description>Integer Overflow vulnerability in Mbed TLS 2.x before 2.28.7 and 3.x before 3.5.2, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via mbedtls_x509_set_extension().</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1012 | Wanhu ezOFFICE wf_printnum.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1012</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Wanhu ezOFFICE 11.1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file defaultroot/platform/bpm/work_flow/operate/wf_printnum.jsp. The manipulation of the argument recordId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252281 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23170 | An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 2.x before 2.28.7 and 3.x before 3.5.2. There was a timing side channel in RSA private operations. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23170</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 2.x before 2.28.7 and 3.x before 3.5.2. There was a timing side channel in RSA private operations. This side channel could be sufficient for a local attacker to recover the plaintext. It requires the attacker to send a large number of messages for decryption, as described in "Everlasting ROBOT: the Marvin Attack" by Hubert Kario.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22236 | In Spring Cloud Contract, versions 4.1.x prior to 4.1.1, versions 4.0.x prior to 4.0.5, and versions 3.1.x prior to 3.1.10, test execution i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22236</link><description>In Spring Cloud Contract, versions 4.1.x prior to 4.1.1, versions 4.0.x prior to 4.0.5, and versions 3.1.x prior to 3.1.10, test execution is vulnerable to local information disclosure via temporary directory created with unsafe permissions through the shaded com.google.guava:guava dependency in the org.springframework.cloud:spring-cloud-contract-shade dependency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0914 | Opencryptoki: timing side-channel in handling of rsa pkcs#1 v1.5 padded ciphertexts (marvin)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0914</link><description>A timing side-channel vulnerability has been discovered in the opencryptoki package while processing RSA PKCS#1 v1.5 padded ciphertexts. This flaw could potentially enable unauthorized RSA ciphertext decryption or signing, even without access to the corresponding private key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31505 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Schlix CMS v2.2.8-1, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31505</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Schlix CMS v2.2.8-1, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via a crafted .phtml file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2439 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'userpro' shortcode in versions up to, and including, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2439</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'userpro' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 5.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 02:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1069 | The Contact Form Entries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'view_page'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1069</link><description>The Contact Form Entries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'view_page' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 02:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22569 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in POSCMS v4.6.2, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to /index...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22569</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in POSCMS v4.6.2, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to /index.php?c=install&amp;m=index&amp;step=2&amp;is_install_db=0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 02:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23745 | In Notion Web Clipper 1.0.3(7), a .nib file is susceptible to the Dirty NIB attack. NIB files can be manipulated to execute arbitrary comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23745</link><description>In Notion Web Clipper 1.0.3(7), a .nib file is susceptible to the Dirty NIB attack. NIB files can be manipulated to execute arbitrary commands. Additionally, even if a NIB file is modified within an application, Gatekeeper may still permit the execution of the application, enabling the execution of arbitrary commands within the application's context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 02:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51204 | Insecure deserialization in ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51204</link><description>Insecure deserialization in ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51197 | An issue discovered in shell command execution in ROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Foxy Fitzroy, with ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51197</link><description>An issue discovered in shell command execution in ROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Foxy Fitzroy, with ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows an attacker to run arbitrary commands and cause other impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51202 | OS command injection vulnerability in command processing or system call componentsROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Foxy Fitzroy, with ROS_VER...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51202</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability in command processing or system call componentsROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Foxy Fitzroy, with ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51198 | An issue in the permission and access control components within ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51198</link><description>An issue in the permission and access control components within ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to gain escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23834 | Discourse improperly sanitized user input leads to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23834</link><description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Improperly sanitized user input could lead to an XSS vulnerability in some situations. This vulnerability only affects Discourse instances which have disabled the default Content Security Policy. The vulnerability is patched in 3.1.5 and 3.2.0.beta5.  As a workaround, ensure Content Security Policy is enabled and does not include `unsafe-inline`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1059 | Use after free in Peer Connection in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.139 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit stack corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1059</link><description>Use after free in Peer Connection in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.139 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit stack corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1060 | Use after free in Canvas in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.139 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1060</link><description>Use after free in Canvas in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.139 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1077 | Use after free in Network in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.139 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1077</link><description>Use after free in Network in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.139 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24567 | raw_call `value=` kwargs not disabled for static and delegate calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24567</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the ethereum virtual machine. Vyper compiler allows passing a value in builtin raw_call even if the call is a delegatecall or a staticcall. But in the context of delegatecall and staticcall the handling of value is not possible due to the semantics of the respective opcodes, and vyper will silently ignore the value= argument. If the semantics of the EVM are unknown to the developer, he could suspect that by specifying the `value` kwarg, exactly the given amount will be sent along to the target. This vulnerability affects 0.3.10 and earlier versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 20:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5389 | An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to modify files on Honeywell Experion VirtualUOC and UOC . ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5389</link><description>An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to modify files on Honeywell Experion VirtualUOC and UOC . This exploit could be used to write a file that may result in unexpected behavior based on configuration changes or updating of files that could result in subsequent execution of a malicious application if triggered. Honeywell recommends updating to the most recent version of the product. See Honeywell Security Notification for recommendations on upgrading and versioning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 20:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24558 | react-query-streamed-hydration xss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24558</link><description>TanStack Query supplies asynchronous state management, server-state utilities and data fetching for the web.  The `@tanstack/react-query-next-experimental` NPM package is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting vulnerability. To exploit this, an attacker would need to either inject malicious input or arrange to have malicious input be returned from an endpoint. To fix this issue, please update to version 5.18.0 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 19:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1036 | openBI Icon Screen.php uploadIcon unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1036</link><description>A vulnerability was found in openBI up to 1.0.8 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function uploadIcon of the file /application/index/controller/Screen.php of the component Icon Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252311.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21388 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21388</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24556 | XSS in @urql/next</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24556</link><description>urql is a GraphQL client that exposes a set of helpers for several frameworks.  The `@urql/next` package is vulnerable to XSS. To exploit this an attacker would need to ensure that the response returns `html` tags and that the web-application is using streamed responses (non-RSC). This vulnerability is due to improper escaping of html-like characters in the response-stream. To fix this vulnerability upgrade to version 1.1.1</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23841 | XSS in @apollo/experimental-nextjs-app-support</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23841</link><description>apollo-client-nextjs is the Apollo Client support for the Next.js App Router. The @apollo/experimental-apollo-client-nextjs NPM package is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting vulnerability. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to either inject malicious input (e.g. by redirecting a user to a specifically-crafted link) or arrange to have malicious input be returned by a GraphQL server (e.g. by persisting it in a database). To fix this issue, please update to version 0.7.0 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46230 | Sensitive Information Disclosure to Internal Log Files in Splunk Add-on Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46230</link><description>In Splunk Add-on Builder versions below 4.1.4, the app writes sensitive information to internal log files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46231 | Session Token Disclosure to Internal Log Files in Splunk Add-on Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46231</link><description>In Splunk Add-on Builder versions below 4.1.4, the application writes user session tokens to its internal log files when you visit the Splunk Add-on Builder or when you build or edit a custom app or add-on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:14:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6258 | Pkcs11-provider: side-channel proofing pkcs#1 1.5 paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6258</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in the pkcs11-provider, which is associated with Public-Key Cryptography Standards (PKCS#11). If exploited successfully, this vulnerability could result in a Bleichenbacher-like security flaw, potentially enabling a side-channel attack on PKCS#1 1.5 decryption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24565 | CrateDB database has an arbitrary file read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24565</link><description>CrateDB is a distributed SQL database that makes it simple to store and analyze massive amounts of data in real-time. There is a COPY FROM function in the CrateDB database that is used to import file data into database tables. This function has a flaw, and authenticated attackers can use the COPY FROM function to import arbitrary file content into database tables, resulting in information leakage. This vulnerability is patched in 5.3.9, 5.4.8, 5.5.4, and 5.6.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23840 | `goreleaser release --debug` shows secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23840</link><description>GoReleaser builds Go binaries for several platforms, creates a GitHub release and then pushes a Homebrew formula to a tap repository. `goreleaser release --debug` log shows secret values used in the in the custom publisher. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.24.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23825 | TablePress SSRF vulnerability due to insufficient filtering of cloud provider hosts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23825</link><description>TablePress is a table plugin for Wordpress. For importing tables, TablePress makes external HTTP requests based on a URL that is provided by the user. That user input is filtered insufficiently, which makes it is possible to send requests to unintended network locations and receive responses. On sites in a cloud environment like AWS, an attacker can potentially make GET requests to the instance's metadata REST API. If the instance's configuration is insecure, this can lead to the exposure of internal data, including credentials. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23838 | TrueLayer.Client SSRF when fetching payment or payment provider</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23838</link><description>TrueLayer.NET is the .Net client for TrueLayer.  The vulnerability could potentially allow a malicious actor to gain control over the destination URL of the HttpClient used in the API classes. For applications using the SDK, requests to unexpected resources on local networks or to the internet could be made which could lead to information disclosure. The issue can be mitigated by having strict egress rules limiting the destinations to which requests can be made, and applying strict validation to any user input passed to the `truelayer-dotnet` library. Versions of TrueLayer.Client `v1.6.0` and later are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23647 | PKCE downgrade attack in Authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23647</link><description>Authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. There is a bug in our implementation of PKCE that allows an attacker to circumvent the protection that PKCE offers. PKCE adds the code_challenge parameter to the authorization request and adds the code_verifier parameter to the token request. Prior to 2023.8.7 and 2023.10.7, a downgrade scenario is possible: if the attacker removes the code_challenge parameter from the authorization request, authentik will not do the PKCE check. Because of this bug, an attacker can circumvent the protection PKCE offers, such as CSRF attacks and code injection attacks.  Versions 2023.8.7 and 2023.10.7 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1019 | WAF bypass of the ModSecurity v3 release line</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1019</link><description>ModSecurity / libModSecurity 3.0.0 to 3.0.11 is affected by a WAF bypass for path-based payloads submitted via specially crafted request URLs. ModSecurity v3 decodes percent-encoded characters present in request URLs before it separates the URL path component from the optional query string component. This results in an impedance mismatch versus RFC compliant back-end applications. The vulnerability hides an attack payload in the path component of the URL from WAF rules inspecting it. A back-end may be vulnerable if it uses the path component of request URLs to construct queries. Integrators and users are advised to upgrade to 3.0.12. The ModSecurity v2 release line is not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1035 | openBI Icon.php uploadIcon unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1035</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in openBI up to 1.0.8 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function uploadIcon of the file /application/index/controller/Icon.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22200 | vantage6-UI docker image leaks software version information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22200</link><description>vantage6-UI is the User Interface for vantage6. The docker image used to run the UI leaks the nginx version. To mitigate the vulnerability, users can run the UI as an angular application.  This vulnerability was patched in 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 16:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22193 | vantage6 unencrypted task can be created in encrypted collaboration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22193</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC). There are no checks on whether the input is encrypted if a task is created in an encrypted collaboration. Therefore, a user may accidentally create a task with sensitive input data that will then be stored unencrypted in a database.  Users should ensure they set the encryption setting correctly.  This vulnerability is patched in 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21653 | vantage6 insecure SSH configuration for node and server containers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21653</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC).  Nodes and servers get a ssh config by default that permits root login with password authentication. In a proper deployment, the SSH service is not exposed so there is no risk, but not all deployments are ideal. The default should therefore be less permissive.  The vulnerability can be mitigated by removing the ssh part from the docker file and rebuilding the docker image.  Version 4.2.0 patches the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21671 | vantage6 username timing attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21671</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC).  It is possible to find out usernames from the response time of login requests. This could aid attackers in credential attacks.  Version 4.2.0 patches this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37518 | A code injection vulnerability affects HCL BigFix ServiceNow Data Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37518</link><description>HCL BigFix ServiceNow is vulnerable to arbitrary code injection.  A malicious authorized attacker could inject arbitrary code and execute within the context of the running user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21649 | Remote code execution </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21649</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC). Prior to 4.2.0, authenticated users could inject code into algorithm environment variables, resulting in remote code execution.  This vulnerability is patched in 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0564 | Kernel: max page sharing of kernel samepage merging (ksm) may cause memory deduplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0564</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's memory deduplication mechanism. The max page sharing of Kernel Samepage Merging (KSM), added in Linux kernel version 4.4.0-96.119, can create a side channel. When the attacker and the victim share the same host and the default setting of KSM is "max page sharing=256", it is possible for the attacker to time the unmap to merge with the victim's page. The unmapping time depends on whether it merges with the victim's page and additional physical pages are created beyond the KSM's "max page share". Through these operations, the attacker can leak the victim's page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24324 | TOTOLINK A8000RU v7.1cu.643_B20200521 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password for root stored in /etc/shadow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24324</link><description>TOTOLINK A8000RU v7.1cu.643_B20200521 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password for root stored in /etc/shadow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24325 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setParen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24325</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setParentalRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24326 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the arpEnable parameter in the setSt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24326</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the arpEnable parameter in the setStaticDhcpRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24327 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pppoePass parameter in the setIp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24327</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pppoePass parameter in the setIpv6Cfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24328 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setMacFi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24328</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setMacFilterRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24329 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setPortF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24329</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setPortForwardRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24330 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the port or enable parameter in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24330</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the port or enable parameter in the setRemoteCfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24331 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setWiFiS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24331</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the enable parameter in the setWiFiScheduleCfg function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24332 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the url parameter in the setUrlFilte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24332</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the url parameter in the setUrlFilterRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24333 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the desc parameter in the setWiFiAcl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24333</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the desc parameter in the setWiFiAclRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1034 | openBI File.php uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1034</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in openBI up to 1.0.8. This affects the function uploadFile of the file /application/index/controller/File.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252309 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1033 | openBI Datament.php agent information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1033</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in openBI up to 1.0.8. Affected by this issue is the function agent of the file /application/index/controller/Datament.php. The manipulation of the argument api leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252308.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 14:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1032 | openBI Test Connection Databasesource.php testConnection deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1032</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in openBI up to 1.0.8. Affected by this vulnerability is the function testConnection of the file /application/index/controller/Databasesource.php of the component Test Connection Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252307.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1031 | CodeAstro Expense Management System Add Expenses Page 5-Add-Expenses.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1031</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Expense Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file templates/5-Add-Expenses.php of the component Add Expenses Page. The manipulation of the argument item leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252304.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 13:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0676 | Weak password requirement vulnerability in Lamassu Bitcoin ATM Douro machines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0676</link><description>Weak password requirement vulnerability 

in Lamassu Bitcoin ATM Douro machines, in its 7.1 version

, which allows a local user to interact with the machine where the application is installed, retrieve stored hashes from the machine and crack long 4-character passwords using a dictionary attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 12:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0674 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in Lamassu Bitcoin ATM Douro machines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0674</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in Lamassu Bitcoin ATM Douro machines, in its 7.1 version, which could allow a local user to acquire root permissions by modifying the updatescript.js, inserting special code inside the script and creating the done.txt file. This would cause the watchdog process to run as root and execute the payload stored in the updatescript.js.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 12:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0675 | Improper checking for unusual or exceptional conditions vulnerability in Lamassu Bitcoin ATM Douro machines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0675</link><description>Vulnerability of improper checking for unusual or exceptional conditions

in Lamassu Bitcoin ATM Douro machines, in its 7.1 version,

 the exploitation of which could allow an attacker with physical access to the ATM to escape kiosk mode, access the underlying Xwindow interface and execute arbitrary commands as an unprivileged user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 12:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1030 | Cogites eReserv tenancyDetail.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1030</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Cogites eReserv 7.7.58. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /front/admin/tenancyDetail.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252303.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22894 | An issue in AIT-Deutschland Alpha Innotec Heatpumps wp2reg-V.3.88.0-9015 and Novelan Heatpumps wp2reg-V.3.88.0-9015, allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22894</link><description>An issue in AIT-Deutschland Alpha Innotec Heatpumps wp2reg-V.3.88.0-9015 and Novelan Heatpumps wp2reg-V.3.88.0-9015, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the password component in the shadow file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1063 | Appwrite &lt;= v1.4.13 is affected by a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the '/v1/avatars/favicon' endpoint due to an incomplete fix of C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1063</link><description>Appwrite &lt;= v1.4.13 is affected by a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the '/v1/avatars/favicon' endpoint due to an incomplete fix of CVE-2023-27159.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6942 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation EZSocket versions 3.0 and later, FR Configurat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6942</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation EZSocket versions 3.0 and later, FR Configurator2 all versions, GT Designer3 Version1(GOT1000) all versions, GT Designer3 Version1(GOT2000) all versions, GX Works2 versions 1.11M and later, GX Works3 all versions, MELSOFT Navigator versions 1.04E and later, MT Works2 all versions, MX Component versions 4.00A and later and MX OPC Server DA/UA all versions allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication by sending specially crafted packets and connect to the products illegally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6943 | Use of Externally-Controlled Input to Select Classes or Code ('Unsafe Reflection') vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation EZSocket...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6943</link><description>Use of Externally-Controlled Input to Select Classes or Code ('Unsafe Reflection') vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation EZSocket versions 3.0 and later, FR Configurator2 all versions, GT Designer3 Version1(GOT1000) all versions, GT Designer3 Version1(GOT2000) all versions, GX Works2 versions 1.11M and later, GX Works3 all versions, MELSOFT Navigator versions 1.04E and later, MT Works2 all versions, MX Component versions 4.00A and later and MX OPC Server DA/UA all versions allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by RPC with a path to a malicious library while connected to the products.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6374 | Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC WS Series WS0-GETH00200 all serial numbers a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6374</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC WS Series WS0-GETH00200 all serial numbers allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication by capture-replay attack and illegally login to the affected module. As a result, the remote attacker who has logged in illegally may be able to disclose or tamper with the programs and parameters in the modules.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22523 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Qiyu iFair version 23.8_ad0 and before, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via upl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22523</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Qiyu iFair version 23.8_ad0 and before, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via uploadimage component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1061 | The 'HTML5 Video Player' WordPress Plugin, version &lt; 2.5.25 is affected by an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'id' parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1061</link><description>The 'HTML5 Video Player' WordPress Plugin, version &lt; 2.5.25 is affected by an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'id' parameter in the  'get_view' function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 08:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36259 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Craft CMS Audit Plugin before version 3.0.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code during us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36259</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Craft CMS Audit Plugin before version 3.0.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code during user creation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 08:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36260 | An issue discovered in Craft CMS version 4.6.1. allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via crafted string to Feed-Me Nam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36260</link><description>An issue discovered in Craft CMS version 4.6.1. allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via crafted string to Feed-Me Name and Feed-Me URL fields due to saving a feed using an Asset element type with no volume selected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 08:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7225 | The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the width and height parameters in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7225</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the width and height parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.88.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21803 | Possible UAF in bt_accept_poll in Linux kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21803</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Linux Linux kernel kernel on Linux, x86, ARM (bluetooth modules) allows Local Execution of Code. This vulnerability is associated with program files https://gitee.Com/anolis/cloud-kernel/blob/devel-5.10/net/bluetooth/af_bluetooth.C.

This issue affects Linux kernel: from v2.6.12-rc2 before v6.8-rc1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22643 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SEO Panel version 4.10.0 allows remote attackers to perform unauthorized user password ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22643</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SEO Panel version 4.10.0 allows remote attackers to perform unauthorized user password resets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22648 | A Blind SSRF vulnerability exists in the "Crawl Meta Data" functionality of SEO Panel version 4.10.0. This makes it possible for remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22648</link><description>A Blind SSRF vulnerability exists in the "Crawl Meta Data" functionality of SEO Panel version 4.10.0. This makes it possible for remote attackers to scan ports in the local environment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22647 | An user enumeration vulnerability was found in SEO Panel 4.10.0. This issue occurs during user authentication, where a difference in error m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22647</link><description>An user enumeration vulnerability was found in SEO Panel 4.10.0. This issue occurs during user authentication, where a difference in error messages could allow an attacker to determine if a username is valid or not, enabling a brute-force attack with valid usernames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22646 | An email address enumeration vulnerability exists in the password reset function of SEO Panel version 4.10.0. This allows an attacker to gue...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22646</link><description>An email address enumeration vulnerability exists in the password reset function of SEO Panel version 4.10.0. This allows an attacker to guess which emails exist on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 07:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52071 | tiny-curl-8_4_0 , curl-8_4_0 and curl-8_5_0 were discovered to contain an off-by-one out-of-bounds array index via the component tool_cb_wrt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52071</link><description>tiny-curl-8_4_0 , curl-8_4_0 and curl-8_5_0 were discovered to contain an off-by-one out-of-bounds array index via the component tool_cb_wrt.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 06:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1029 | Cogites eReserv tenancyDetail.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1029</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Cogites eReserv 7.7.58 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /front/admin/tenancyDetail.php. The manipulation of the argument Nom with the input Dreux"&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert('XSS')&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252302 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 05:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21488 | Versions of the package network before 0.7.0 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Command Injection due to use of the child_process exec function wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21488</link><description>Versions of the package network before 0.7.0 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Command Injection due to use of the child_process exec function without input sanitization. If (attacker-controlled) user input is given to the mac_address_for function of the package, it is possible for an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the operating system that this package is being run on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 05:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1028 | SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like Post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1028</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Post Handler. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input &lt;marquee&gt;HACKED&lt;/marquee&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252301 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 04:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1027 | SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like Post unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1027</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Post Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252300.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 03:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21840 | Directory and File Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Storage Plug-in for VMware vCenter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21840</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Storage Plug-in for VMware vCenter allows local users to read and write specific files.

This issue affects Hitachi Storage Plug-in for VMware vCenter: from 04.0.0 through 04.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 02:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51813 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Free Open-Source Inventory Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51813</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Free Open-Source Inventory Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the staff_list parameter in the index.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51837 | Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16 is vulnerable to Missing SSL Certificate Validation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51837</link><description>Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16 is vulnerable to Missing SSL Certificate Validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5372 | The post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions through V5.21(AAZF.15)C0 and NAS542 firmware versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5372</link><description>The post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions through V5.21(AAZF.15)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions through V5.21(ABAG.12)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted query parameter attached to the URL of an affected device’s web management interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1026 | Cogites eReserv config.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1026</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Cogites eReserv 7.7.58 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file front/admin/config.php. The manipulation of the argument id with the input %22%3E%3Cscript%3Ealert(%27XSS%27)%3C/script%3E leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-252293 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22682 | DuckDB &lt;=0.9.2 and DuckDB extension-template &lt;=0.9.2 are vulnerable to malicious extension injection via the custom extension feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22682</link><description>DuckDB &lt;=0.9.2 and DuckDB extension-template &lt;=0.9.2 are vulnerable to malicious extension injection via the custom extension feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22938 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in BossCMS v.1.3.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via the init...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22938</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in BossCMS v.1.3.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via the init function in admin.class.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37571 | Softing TH SCOPE through 3.70 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37571</link><description>Softing TH SCOPE through 3.70 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51843 | react-dashboard 1.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) as httpOnly is not set.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51843</link><description>react-dashboard 1.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) as httpOnly is not set.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51982 | CrateDB 5.5.1 is contains an authentication bypass vulnerability in the Admin UI component. After configuring password authentication and_ L...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51982</link><description>CrateDB 5.5.1 is contains an authentication bypass vulnerability in the Admin UI component. After configuring password authentication and_ Local_ In the case of an address, identity authentication can be bypassed by setting the X-Real IP request header to a specific value and accessing the Admin UI directly using the default user identity.(https://github.com/crate/crate/issues/15231)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1024 | SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like New Account cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1024</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component New Account Handler. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252292.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1022 | CodeAstro Simple Student Result Management System Add Class Page add_classes.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1022</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CodeAstro Simple Student Result Management System 5.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /add_classes.php of the component Add Class Page. The manipulation of the argument Class Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252291.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 23:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23334 | aiohttp.web.static(follow_symlinks=True) is vulnerable to directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23334</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. When using aiohttp as a web server and configuring static routes, it is necessary to specify the root path for static files. Additionally, the option 'follow_symlinks' can be used to determine whether to follow symbolic links outside the static root directory. When 'follow_symlinks' is set to True, there is no validation to check if reading a file is within the root directory. This can lead to directory traversal vulnerabilities, resulting in unauthorized access to arbitrary files on the system, even when symlinks are not present.  Disabling follow_symlinks and using a reverse proxy are encouraged mitigations.  Version 3.9.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23829 |  aiohttp&amp;#x27;s HTTP parser (the python one, not llhttp) still overly lenient about separators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23829</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Security-sensitive parts of the Python HTTP parser retained minor differences in allowable character sets, that must trigger error handling to robustly match frame boundaries of proxies in order to protect against injection of additional requests. Additionally, validation could trigger exceptions that were not handled consistently with processing of other malformed input.  Being more lenient than internet standards require could, depending on deployment environment, assist in request smuggling. The unhandled exception could cause excessive resource consumption on the application server and/or its logging facilities. This vulnerability exists due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-47627. Version 3.9.2 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1021 | Rebuild HTTP Request readRawText server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1021</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. Affected by this issue is the function readRawText of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252290 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1020 | Rebuild proxy-download getStorageFile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1020</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getStorageFile of the file /filex/proxy-download. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252289 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4551 | Command Injection via Task Scheduler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4551</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in OpenText AppBuilder on Windows, Linux allows OS Command Injection.

The AppBuilder's Scheduler functionality that facilitates creation of scheduled tasks is vulnerable to command injection. This allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary operating system commands into the executing process.


This issue affects AppBuilder: from 21.2 before 23.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4552 | Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) URL Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4552</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in OpenText AppBuilder on Windows, Linux allows Probe System Files.

An authenticated AppBuilder user with the ability to create or manage existing databases can leverage them to exploit the AppBuilder server - including access to its local file system.


This issue affects AppBuilder: from 21.2 before 23.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4553 | Unauthenticated Access to AppBuilder Configuration Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4553</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in OpenText AppBuilder on Windows, Linux allows Probe System Files.


AppBuilder configuration files are viewable by unauthenticated users.


This issue affects AppBuilder: from 21.2 before 23.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4554 | XML External Entity (XXE) Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4554</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in OpenText AppBuilder on Windows, Linux allows Server Side Request Forgery, Probe System Files.

AppBuilder's XML processor is vulnerable to XML External Entity Processing (XXE), allowing an authenticated user to upload specially crafted XML files to induce server-side request forgery, disclose files local to the server that processes them.


This issue affects AppBuilder: from 21.2 before 23.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4550 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4550</link><description>Improper Input Validation, Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in OpenText AppBuilder on Windows, Linux allows Probe System Files.

An unauthenticated or authenticated user can abuse a page of AppBuilder to read arbitrary files on the server on which it is hosted. 


This issue affects AppBuilder: from 21.2 before 23.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49038 | Command injection in the ping utility on Buffalo LS210D 1.78-0.03 allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject arbitrary commands onto t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49038</link><description>Command injection in the ping utility on Buffalo LS210D 1.78-0.03 allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject arbitrary commands onto the NAS as root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 20:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1018 | PbootCMS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1018</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PbootCMS 3.2.5-20230421. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin.php?p=/Area/index#tab=t2. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252288.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 20:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51842 | An algorithm-downgrade issue was discovered in Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51842</link><description>An algorithm-downgrade issue was discovered in Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51840 | DoraCMS 2.1.8 is vulnerable to Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51840</link><description>DoraCMS 2.1.8 is vulnerable to Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24141 | Sourcecodester School Task Manager App 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'task' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24141</link><description>Sourcecodester School Task Manager App 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'task' parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22570 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /install.php?m=install&amp;c=index&amp;a=step3 of GreenCMS v2.3 allows attackers to execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22570</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /install.php?m=install&amp;c=index&amp;a=step3 of GreenCMS v2.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24139 | Sourcecodester Login System with Email Verification 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'user' parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24139</link><description>Sourcecodester Login System with Email Verification 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the 'user' parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24140 | Sourcecodester Daily Habit Tracker App 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the parameter 'tracker.'</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24140</link><description>Sourcecodester Daily Habit Tracker App 1.0 allows SQL Injection via the parameter 'tracker.'</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51839 | DeviceFarmer stf v3.6.6 suffers from Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51839</link><description>DeviceFarmer stf v3.6.6 suffers from Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24136 | The 'Your Name' field in the Submit Score section of Sourcecodester Math Game with Leaderboard v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (X...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24136</link><description>The 'Your Name' field in the Submit Score section of Sourcecodester Math Game with Leaderboard v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24134 | Sourcecodester Online Food Menu 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the 'Menu Name' and 'Description' fields in the Update M...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24134</link><description>Sourcecodester Online Food Menu 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the 'Menu Name' and 'Description' fields in the Update Menu section.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22836 | In cases where a multi-tenant stack user is operating Foundry’s Linter service, and the user changes the linter name from the default value, the renamed value may be visible to the rest of the stack’s tenants.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22836</link><description>In cases where a multi-tenant stack user is operating Foundry’s Linter service, and the user changes a group name from the default value, the renamed value may be visible to the rest of the stack’s tenants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24135 | Product Name and Product Code in the 'Add Product' section of Sourcecodester Product Inventory with Export to Excel 1.0 are vulnerable to XS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24135</link><description>Product Name and Product Code in the 'Add Product' section of Sourcecodester Product Inventory with Export to Excel 1.0 are vulnerable to XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1017 | Gabriels FTP Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1017</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Gabriels FTP Server 1.2. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument USERNAME leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252287.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30970 | Gotham table and Forward App Path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30970</link><description>Gotham Table service and Forward App were found to be vulnerable to a Path traversal issue allowing an authenticated user to read arbitrary files on the file system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23940 | Trend Micro uiAirSupport, included in the Trend Micro Security 2023 family of consumer products, version 6.0.2092 and below is vulnerable to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23940</link><description>Trend Micro uiAirSupport, included in the Trend Micro Security 2023 family of consumer products, version 6.0.2092 and below is vulnerable to a DLL hijacking/proxying vulnerability, which if exploited could allow an attacker to impersonate and modify a library to execute code on the system and ultimately escalate privileges on an affected system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 18:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1016 | Solar FTP Server PASV Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1016</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Solar FTP Server 2.1.1/2.1.2. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PASV Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-252286 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1011 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Leave delete-leave.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1011</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file delete-leave.php of the component Leave Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252280.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40551 | Shim: out of bounds read when parsing mz binaries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40551</link><description>A flaw was found in the MZ binary format in Shim. An out-of-bounds read may occur, leading to a crash or possible exposure of sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23828 | Nginx-UI authenticated RCE through injecting into the application config via CRLF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23828</link><description>Nginx-UI is a web interface to manage Nginx configurations. It is vulnerable to an authenticated arbitrary command execution via CRLF attack when changing the value of test_config_cmd or start_cmd. This vulnerability exists due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-22197 and CVE-2024-22198. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.0.0.beta.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1705 | Missing Authorization vulnerability in Forcepoint F|One SmartEdge Agent on Windows (bgAutoinstaller service modules) allows Privilege Escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1705</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Forcepoint F|One SmartEdge Agent on Windows (bgAutoinstaller service modules) allows Privilege Escalation, Functionality Bypass.This issue affects F|One SmartEdge Agent: before 1.7.0.230330-554.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40546 | Shim: out-of-bounds read printing error messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40546</link><description>A flaw was found in Shim when an error happened while creating a new ESL variable. If Shim fails to create the new variable, it tries to print an error message to the user; however, the number of parameters used by the logging function doesn't match the format string used by it, leading to a crash under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40549 | Shim: out-of-bounds read in verify_buffer_authenticode() malformed pe file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40549</link><description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim due to the lack of proper boundary verification during the load of a PE binary. This flaw allows an attacker to load a crafted PE binary, triggering the issue and crashing Shim, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40550 | Shim: out-of-bound read in verify_buffer_sbat()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40550</link><description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim when it tried to validate the SBAT information. This issue may expose sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1009 | SourceCodester Employee Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1009</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument txtusername leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252278 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1010 | SourceCodester Employee Management System edit-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1010</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file edit-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/phone/date of birth/address/date of appointment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252279.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0788 | SUPERAntiSpyware Pro X v10.0.1260 - Kernel-level API parameters manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0788</link><description>SUPERAntiSpyware Pro X v10.0.1260 is vulnerable to kernel-level API parameters manipulation and Denial of Service vulnerabilities by triggering the 0x9C402140 IOCTL code of the saskutil64.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23441 | Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 - Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23441</link><description>Vba32 Antivirus v3.36.0 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x2220A7 IOCTL code of the Vba32m64.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23827 | Nginx-UI arbitrary file write through the Import Certificate feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23827</link><description>Nginx-UI is a web interface to manage Nginx configurations. The Import Certificate feature allows arbitrary write into the system. The feature does not check if the provided user input is a certification/key and allows to write into arbitrary paths in the system. It's possible to leverage the vulnerability into a remote code execution overwriting the config file app.ini. Version 2.0.0.beta.12 fixed the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1007 | SourceCodester Employee Management System edit_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1007</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file edit_profile.php. The manipulation of the argument txtfullname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252276.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1008 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Profile Page edit-photo.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1008</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file edit-photo.php of the component Profile Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252277 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23826 | Uploading an image with a specific filename causes a server-side DoS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23826</link><description>spbu_se_site is the website of the Department of System Programming of St. Petersburg State University. Before 2024.01.29, when uploading an avatar image, an authenticated user may intentionally use a large Unicode filename which would lead to a server-side denial of service under Windows. This is due to no limitation of the length of the filename and the costly use of the Unicode normalization with the form NFKD on Windows OS.  This vulnerability was fixed in the 2024.01.29 release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23822 | Thruk Incorrect limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory (Path Traversal) (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23822</link><description>Thruk is a multibackend monitoring webinterface.  Prior to 3.12, the Thruk web monitoring application presents a vulnerability in a file upload form that allows a threat actor to arbitrarily upload files to the server to any path they desire and have permissions for. This vulnerability is known as Path Traversal or Directory Traversal. Version 3.12 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1006 | Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP Cookie common.php improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1006</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP up to 6.0.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file application/index/common.php of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument Nod_User_Id/Nod_User_Token leads to improper authentication. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252275. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1004 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi loginAuth stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1004</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. This affects the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252273 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1005 | Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP log file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1005</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Shanxi Diankeyun Technology NODERP up to 6.0.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /runtime/log. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40548 | Shim: interger overflow leads to heap buffer overflow in verify_sbat_section on 32-bits systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40548</link><description>A buffer overflow was found in Shim in the 32-bit system. The overflow happens due to an addition operation involving a user-controlled value parsed from the PE binary being used by Shim. This value is further used for memory allocation operations, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. This flaw causes memory corruption and can lead to a crash or data integrity issues during the boot phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5124 | PageLayer &amp;lt; 1.8.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5124</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer WordPress plugin before 1.8.0 doesn't prevent attackers with administrator privileges from inserting malicious JavaScript inside a post's header or footer code, even when unfiltered_html is disallowed, such as in multi-site WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5943 | Wp-Adv-Quiz &amp;lt; 1.0.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5943</link><description>The Wp-Adv-Quiz WordPress plugin before 1.0.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5956 | Wp-Adv-Quiz &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Quiz Overview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5956</link><description>The Wp-Adv-Quiz WordPress plugin through 1.0.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6165 | Restrict Usernames Emails Characters Plugin &amp;lt; 3.1.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6165</link><description>The Restrict Usernames Emails Characters WordPress plugin before 3.1.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6278 | Biteship for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 2.2.25 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6278</link><description>The Biteship: Plugin Ongkos Kirim Kurir Instant, Reguler, Kargo WordPress plugin before 2.2.25 does not sanitise and escape the biteship_error and biteship_message parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6279 | Woostify Sites Library &amp;lt; 1.4.8 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Options Update to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6279</link><description>The Woostify Sites Library WordPress plugin before 1.4.8 does not have authorisation in an AJAX action, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to update arbitrary blog options and set them to 'activated' which could lead to DoS when using a specific option name</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6389 | WordPress Toolbar &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6389</link><description>The WordPress Toolbar WordPress plugin through 2.2.6 redirects to any URL via the "wptbto" parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6390 | WordPress Users &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6390</link><description>The WordPress Users WordPress plugin through 1.4 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6391 | Custom User CSS &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6391</link><description>The Custom User CSS WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6503 | WP Plugin Lister &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Settings Update to Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6503</link><description>The WP Plugin Lister WordPress plugin through 2.1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6530 | TJ Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6530</link><description>The TJ Shortcodes WordPress plugin through 0.1.3 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6633 | Site Notes &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Admin Note Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6633</link><description>The Site Notes WordPress plugin through 2.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some of its functionalities, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions, such as deleting administration notes, via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6946 | Autotitle for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Settings Update to Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6946</link><description>The Autotitle for WordPress plugin through 1.0.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7074 | WP Social Bookmark Menu &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7074</link><description>The WP SOCIAL BOOKMARK MENU WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7089 | Easy SVG Allow &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7089</link><description>The Easy SVG Allow WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitize uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7199 | Relevanssi (Free &amp;lt; 4.22.0, Premium &amp;lt; 2.25.0) - Unauthenticated Private/Draft Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7199</link><description>The Relevanssi WordPress plugin before 4.22.0, Relevanssi Premium WordPress plugin before 2.25.0 allows any unauthenticated user to read draft and private posts via a crafted request</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7200 | EventON &amp;lt; 4.4.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7200</link><description>The EventON WordPress plugin before 4.4.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7204 | WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin &amp;lt; 3.2.0 - Unauthorized Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7204</link><description>The WP STAGING WordPress Backup plugin before 3.2.0 allows access to cache files during the cloning process which provides</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1003 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setLanguageCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1003</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this issue is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252272. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22559 | LightCMS v2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Content Management - Articles field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22559</link><description>LightCMS v2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Content Management - Articles field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23747 | The Moderna Sistemas ModernaNet Hospital Management System 2024 is susceptible to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23747</link><description>The Moderna Sistemas ModernaNet Hospital Management System 2024 is susceptible to an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. This vulnerability resides in the system's handling of user data access through a /Modernanet/LAUDO/LAU0000100/Laudo?id= URI. By manipulating this id parameter, an attacker can gain access to sensitive medical information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1002 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setIpPortFilterRules stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1002</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setIpPortFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ePort leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1014 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1014</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3 affecting versions 03.07.03 and higher. An attacker could interrupt the availability of the administration panel by sending multiple ICMP packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1015 | Remote command execution vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1015</link><description>Remote command execution vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3 affecting versions 03.07.03 and higher. An attacker could send different commands from the operating system to the system via the web configuration functionality of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1000 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252269 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1001 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0998 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252267. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0999 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0999</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument eTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252268. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0997 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument pppoeUser leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29055 | Apache Kylin: Insufficiently protected credentials in config file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29055</link><description>In Apache Kylin version 2.0.0 to 4.0.3, there is a Server Config web interface that displays the content of file 'kylin.properties', that may contain serverside credentials. When the kylin service runs over HTTP (or other plain text protocol), it is possible for network sniffers to hijack the HTTP payload and get access to the content of kylin.properties and potentially the containing credentials.

To avoid this threat, users are recommended to 

  *  Always turn on HTTPS so that network payload is encrypted.

  *  Avoid putting credentials in kylin.properties, or at least not in plain text.
  *  Use network firewalls to protect the serverside such that it is not accessible to external attackers.

  *  Upgrade to version Apache Kylin 4.0.4, which filters out the sensitive content that goes to the Server Config web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5378 | Stored XSS in SmodBIP and MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5378</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in  MegaBIP and already unsupported SmodBIP software allows for Stored XSS.This issue affects SmodBIP in all versions and MegaBIP in versions up to 4.36.2 (newer versions were not tested; the vendor has not confirmed fixing the vulnerability).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 11:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46838 | Linux: netback processing of zero-length transmit fragment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46838</link><description>Transmit requests in Xen's virtual network protocol can consist of
multiple parts.  While not really useful, except for the initial part
any of them may be of zero length, i.e. carry no data at all.  Besides a
certain initial portion of the to be transferred data, these parts are
directly translated into what Linux calls SKB fragments.  Such converted
request parts can, when for a particular SKB they are all of length
zero, lead to a de-reference of NULL in core networking code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23790 | Missing file type check in avatar picture upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23790</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in the upload functionality for user avatars allows functionality misuse due to missing check of filetypes.
This issue affects OTRS:  from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023 through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23791 | Unnecessary data is written to log if issues during indexing occurs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23791</link><description>Insertion of debug information into log file during building the elastic search index allows reading of sensitive information from articles.This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023.X through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0212 | Cloudflare WordPress plugin enables information disclosure of Cloudflare API (for low privileged users)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0212</link><description>The Cloudflare Wordpress plugin was found to be vulnerable to improper authentication. The vulnerability enables attackers with a lower privileged account to access data from the Cloudflare API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23792 | Insufficient access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23792</link><description>When adding attachments to ticket comments, 
another user can add attachments as well impersonating the orginal user. The attack requires a 
logged-in other user to know the UUID. While the legitimate user 
completes the comment, the malicious user can add more files to the 
comment.

This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023.X through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24736 | The POP3 service in YahooPOPs (aka YPOPs!) 1.6 allows a remote denial of service (reboot) via a long string to TCP port 110, a related issue...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24736</link><description>The POP3 service in YahooPOPs (aka YPOPs!) 1.6 allows a remote denial of service (reboot) via a long string to TCP port 110, a related issue to CVE-2004-1558.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 03:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0996 | Tenda i9 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0996</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda i9 1.0.0.9(4122). This affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0995 | Tenda W6 httpd wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0995</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0993 | Tenda i6 httpd WifiMacFilterGet formWifiMacFilterGet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0993</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formWifiMacFilterGet of the file /goform/WifiMacFilterGet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0994 | Tenda W6 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0994</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0991 | Tenda i6 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0991</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0992 | Tenda i6 httpd wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0992</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0989 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP Service.php del_sn_db path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0989</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected by this issue is the function del_sn_db of the file /application/index/controller/Service.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0990 | Tenda i6 httpd setAutoPing formSetAutoPing stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0990</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857). This affects the function formSetAutoPing of the file /goform/setAutoPing of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ping1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0987 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP log neutralization for logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0987</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file /runtime/log. The manipulation leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252252. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0988 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP common.php checklogin improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0988</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function checklogin of the file /application/index/common.php. The manipulation of the argument App_User_id/App_user_Token leads to improper authentication. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252253 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>