<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-47273 | setuptools has a path traversal vulnerability in PackageIndex.download that leads to Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47273</link><description>setuptools is a package that allows users to download, build, install, upgrade, and uninstall Python packages. A path traversal vulnerability in `PackageIndex` is present in setuptools prior to version 78.1.1. An attacker would be allowed to write files to arbitrary locations on the filesystem with the permissions of the process running the Python code, which could escalate to remote code execution depending on the context. Version 78.1.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4830 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSysCmd buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4830</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formSysCmd of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4829 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formStats sub_40BE30 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4829</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_40BE30 of the file /boafrm/formStats of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4827 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4827</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSaveConfig of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48187 | RAGFlow through 0.18.1 allows account takeover because it is possible to conduct successful brute-force attacks against email verification c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48187</link><description>RAGFlow through 0.18.1 allows account takeover because it is possible to conduct successful brute-force attacks against email verification codes to perform arbitrary account registration, login, and password reset. Codes are six digits and there is no rate limiting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4101 | MultiVendorX – WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solutions &amp;lt;= 4.2.22 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4101</link><description>The MultiVendorX – WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solutions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'delete_fpm_product' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.22. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts, pages, attachments, and products. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.2.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13613 | Wise Chat &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13613</link><description>The Wise Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.3 via the 'uploads' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads directory which can contain file attachments included in chat messages. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4669 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.11.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpbc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4669</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpbc shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 10.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3527 | EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3527</link><description>The EventON Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check in the 'assets/lib/settings/settings.js' file in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3888 | Jupiterx Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Inline SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3888</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the page with the included SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4826 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWirelessTbl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4826</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWirelessTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4825 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formDMZ buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4825</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formDMZ of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4824 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWsc buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4824</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formWsc of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4823 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formReflashClientTbl submit-url buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4823</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function submit-url of the file /boafrm/formReflashClientTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4610 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpmem_user_memberships Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4610</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpmem_user_memberships shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4190 | CSV Mass Importer &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4190</link><description>The CSV Mass Importer WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not properly validate uploaded files, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4819 | y_project RuoYi Offline Logout batchForceLogout improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4819</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in y_project RuoYi 4.8.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /monitor/online/batchForceLogout of the component Offline Logout. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3812 | WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot &amp;lt;= 13.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3812</link><description>The WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the qcld_openai_delete_training_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 13.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4389 | Crawlomatic Multipage Scraper Post Generator &amp;lt;= 2.6.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4389</link><description>The Crawlomatic Multipage Scraper Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the crawlomatic_generate_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4391 | Echo RSS Feed Post Generator &amp;lt;= 5.4.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4391</link><description>The Echo RSS Feed Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the echo_generate_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4818 | SourceCodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter delete-doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4818</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete-doctor.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4817 | Sourcecodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter delete-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4817</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sourcecodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/delete-appointment.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 04:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4189 | Audio Comments Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4189</link><description>The Audio Comments Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'audio-comments/audior-settings.php' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4194 | AlT Monitoring &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4194</link><description>The AlT Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ALT_Monitoring_edit' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4816 | SourceCodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4816</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/appointment.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4815 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System supplier_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4815</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /pages/supplier_update.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4814 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System supplier_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4814</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/supplier_add.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47893 | GPU DDK - OOB read and write of the shared KMD/FW memory heap (VZ/TEE setups)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47893</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to read and/or write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1706 | GPU DDK - Improper locking when accessing the pvr_exp_fence  object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1706</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger use-after-free kernel exceptions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4812 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4812</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4813 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System edit-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4813</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4811 | CodeAstro Pharmacy Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48188 | libpspp-core.a in GNU PSPP through 2.0.1 has an incorrect call from fill_buffer (in data/encrypted-file.c) to the Gnulib rijndaelDecrypt fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48188</link><description>libpspp-core.a in GNU PSPP through 2.0.1 has an incorrect call from fill_buffer (in data/encrypted-file.c) to the Gnulib rijndaelDecrypt function, leading to a heap-based buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4363 | Wholesale Market &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4363</link><description>The Wholesale Market WordPress plugin before 2.2.2, Wholesale Market for WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 2.0.1 have a flawed CSRF check when updating their settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin update them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4810 | Tenda AC7 SetRebootTimer formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetRebootTimer. The manipulation of the argument reboot_time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32407 | Samsung Internet for Galaxy Watch version 5.0.9, available up until Samsung Galaxy Watch 3, does not properly validate TLS certificates, all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32407</link><description>Samsung Internet for Galaxy Watch version 5.0.9, available up until Samsung Galaxy Watch 3, does not properly validate TLS certificates, allowing for an attacker to impersonate any and all websites visited by the user. This is a critical misconfiguration in the way the browser validates the identity of the server. It negates the use of HTTPS as a secure channel, allowing for Man-in-the-Middle attacks, stealing sensitive information or modifying incoming and outgoing traffic. NOTE: This vulnerability is in an end-of-life product that is no longer maintained by the vendor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4804 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Hotpot Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4804</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS via the spamBlocker module. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4805 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Acces Portal Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4805</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4808 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System add-normal-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add-normal-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument noadult leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4809 | Tenda AC7 setMacFilterCfg fromSafeSetMacFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromSafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4802 | Untrusted LD_LIBRARY_PATH environment variable vulnerability in the GNU C Library version 2.27 to 2.38 allows attacker controlled loading of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4802</link><description>Untrusted LD_LIBRARY_PATH environment variable vulnerability in the GNU C Library version 2.27 to 2.38 allows attacker controlled loading of dynamically shared library in statically compiled setuid binaries that call dlopen (including internal dlopen calls after setlocale or calls to NSS functions such as getaddrinfo).</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4807 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4807</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22233 | Spring Framework DataBinder Case Sensitive Match Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22233</link><description>CVE-2024-38820 ensured Locale-independent, lowercase conversion for both the configured disallowedFields patterns and for request parameter names. However, there are still cases where it is possible to bypass the disallowedFields checks.

Affected Spring Products and Versions

Spring Framework:
  *  6.2.0 - 6.2.6

  *  6.1.0 - 6.1.19

  *  6.0.0 - 6.0.27

  *  5.3.0 - 5.3.42
  *  Older, unsupported versions are also affected



Mitigation

Users of affected versions should upgrade to the corresponding fixed version.

Affected version(s)Fix Version Availability 6.2.x
 6.2.7
OSS6.1.x
 6.1.20
OSS6.0.x
 6.0.28
 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ 5.3.x
 5.3.43
 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ 
No further mitigation steps are necessary.


Generally, we recommend using a dedicated model object with properties only for data binding, or using constructor binding since constructor arguments explicitly declare what to bind together with turning off setter binding through the declarativeBinding flag. See the Model Design section in the reference documentation.

For setting binding, prefer the use of allowedFields (an explicit list) over disallowedFields.

Credit

This issue was responsibly reported by the TERASOLUNA Framework Development Team from NTT DATA Group Corporation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4806 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_bo sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4806</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/?page=back_order/view_bo. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4795 | gongfuxiang schoolcms index.php SaveInfo sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4795</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in gongfuxiang schoolcms 2.3.1. This affects the function SaveInfo of the file /index.php?m=Admin&amp;amp;c=article&amp;amp;a=SaveInfo. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4793 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration edit-student-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4793</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit-student-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument cgpa leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4794 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration news.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /news.php. The manipulation of the argument newstitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4476 | Libsoup: null pointer dereference in libsoup may lead to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4476</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability has been identified in the libsoup HTTP client library. This flaw can be triggered when a libsoup client receives a 401 (Unauthorized) HTTP response containing a specifically crafted domain parameter within the WWW-Authenticate header. Processing this malformed header can lead to a crash of the client application using libsoup. An attacker could exploit this by setting up a malicious HTTP server. If a user's application using the vulnerable libsoup library connects to this malicious server, it could result in a denial-of-service. Successful exploitation requires tricking a user's client application into connecting to the attacker's malicious server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4792 | FreeFloat FTP Server MDELETE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4792</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component MDELETE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4790 | FreeFloat FTP Server GLOB Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4790</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component GLOB Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4791 | FreeFloat FTP Server HASH Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4791</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component HASH Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4788 | FreeFloat FTP Server DELETE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4788</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component DELETE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4789 | FreeFloat FTP Server LCD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4789</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component LCD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4787 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_sale sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4787</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=sales/view_sale. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31062 | WordPress Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31062</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in redqteam Wishlist allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31063 | WordPress Wishlist &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31063</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in redqteam Wishlist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31065 | WordPress Rozario &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31065</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton Rozario allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Rozario: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31066 | WordPress Acerola &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31066</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton Acerola allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Acerola: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31068 | WordPress Seven Stars &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31068</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in themeton Seven Stars allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Seven Stars: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31071 | WordPress HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31071</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects HotStar – Multi-Purpose Business Theme: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31630 | WordPress The Business &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31630</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in themeton The Business allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects The Business: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31637 | WordPress SHOUT &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31637</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup SHOUT allows SQL Injection. This issue affects SHOUT: from n/a through 3.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31639 | WordPress Spare &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31639</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in themeton Spare allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Spare: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31640 | WordPress Magic Responsive Slider and Carousel WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Magic Responsive Slider and Carousel WordPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Magic Responsive Slider and Carousel WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31641 | WordPress UberSlider &amp;lt;= 2.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup UberSlider allows SQL Injection. This issue affects UberSlider: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31915 | WordPress Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp;amp; Autoresponder &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31915</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kamleshyadav Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Pixel WordPress Form BuilderPlugin &amp; Autoresponder: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31921 | WordPress WP Ultimate Tours Builder &amp;lt;= 1.055 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31921</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in loopus WP Ultimate Tours Builder allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Ultimate Tours Builder: from n/a through 1.055.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31922 | WordPress CSS3 Accordions for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31922</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Accordions for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CSS3 Accordions for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31923 | WordPress CSS3 Accordions for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31923</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Accordions for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CSS3 Accordions for WordPress: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31926 | WordPress Sticky Radio Player &amp;lt;= 3.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Sticky Radio Player allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Sticky Radio Player: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31928 | WordPress Multimedia Responsive Carousel with Image Video Audio Support &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Multimedia Responsive Carousel with Image Video Audio Support allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Multimedia Responsive Carousel with Image Video Audio Support: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32180 | WordPress CSS3 Tooltips for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32180</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Tooltips for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CSS3 Tooltips for WordPress: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32245 | WordPress Apollo &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Apollo allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Apollo: from n/a through 3.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32287 | WordPress Responsive HTML5 Audio Player PRO With Playlist &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32287</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Responsive HTML5 Audio Player PRO With Playlist allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Responsive HTML5 Audio Player PRO With Playlist: from n/a through 3.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32290 | WordPress Sticky HTML5 Music Player &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32290</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Sticky HTML5 Music Player allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Sticky HTML5 Music Player: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32295 | WordPress Salon Booking Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 10.10.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32295</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wordpresschef Salon Booking Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Salon Booking Pro: from n/a through 10.10.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32296 | WordPress Simple Link Directory Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 14.7.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32296</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in quantumcloud Simple Link Directory Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Simple Link Directory Pro: from n/a through 14.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32299 | WordPress QuickCal &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32299</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Themovation QuickCal allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects QuickCal: from n/a through 1.0.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32301 | WordPress CountDown Pro WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32301</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup CountDown Pro WP Plugin allows SQL Injection. This issue affects CountDown Pro WP Plugin: from n/a through 2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32306 | WordPress Radio Player Shoutcast &amp;amp; Icecast WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Radio Player Shoutcast &amp; Icecast WordPress Plugin allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Radio Player Shoutcast &amp; Icecast WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 4.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32307 | WordPress Chameleon HTML5 Audio Player With/Without Playlist &amp;lt;= 3.5.6 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Chameleon HTML5 Audio Player With/Without Playlist allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Chameleon HTML5 Audio Player With/Without Playlist: from n/a through 3.5.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32310 | WordPress QuickCal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32310</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeMove QuickCal allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects QuickCal: from n/a through 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32643 | WordPress WPGYM Plugin &amp;lt;= 65.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in mojoomla WPGYM allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WPGYM: from n/a through 65.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39481 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39481</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in imithemes Eventer allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through 3.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39482 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39482</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in imithemes Eventer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through 3.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39491 | WordPress WHMpress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2-revision-9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39491</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in WHMPress WHMpress allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WHMpress: from 6.2 through revision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39492 | WordPress WHMpress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2-revision-9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39492</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in WHMPress WHMpress allows Relative Path Traversal. This issue affects WHMpress: from 6.2 through revision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39493 | WordPress Rankie &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39493</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ValvePress Rankie allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Rankie: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39507 | WordPress Nasa Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39507</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NasaTheme Nasa Core allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Nasa Core: from n/a through 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39509 | WordPress TNC FlipBook  plugin  &amp;lt;= 12.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39509</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeNcode TNC FlipBook allows Stored XSS. This issue affects TNC FlipBook: from n/a through 12.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39511 | WordPress Pinterest Automatic Pin &amp;lt;= 4.18.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39511</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ValvePress Pinterest Automatic Pin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Pinterest Automatic Pin: from n/a through 4.18.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39537 | WordPress WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39537</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Chimpstudio WP JobHunt allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP JobHunt: from n/a through 7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46464 | WordPress Ads Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.88 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46464</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in scripteo Ads Pro Plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ads Pro Plugin: from n/a through 4.88.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47534 | WordPress Wordpress Auto Spinner &amp;lt;= 3.25.0 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47534</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ValvePress Wordpress Auto Spinner allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Wordpress Auto Spinner: from n/a through 3.25.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47556 | WordPress CSS3 Compare Pricing Tables for WordPress &amp;lt;= 11.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47556</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QuanticaLabs CSS3 Compare Pricing Tables for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CSS3 Compare Pricing Tables for WordPress: from n/a through 11.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47557 | WordPress MapSVG plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47560 | WordPress MapSVG plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.32 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47560</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.32.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47562 | WordPress MapSVG &amp;lt;= 8.5.34 - Content Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47562</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG allows Code Injection. This issue affects MapSVG: from n/a through 8.5.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47563 | WordPress CURCY plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.7 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47563</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in villatheme CURCY allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects CURCY: from n/a through 2.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47564 | WordPress EventON plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47564</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ashanjay EventON allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects EventON: from n/a through 4.9.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47567 | WordPress Video Player &amp;amp; FullScreen Video Background plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47567</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LambertGroup Video Player &amp; FullScreen Video Background allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Video Player &amp; FullScreen Video Background: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47693 | WordPress Fat Services Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47693</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in roninwp FAT Services Booking allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects FAT Services Booking: from n/a through 5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48079 | WordPress ProfileGrid  &amp;lt;= 5.9.5.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid  allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.9.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48080 | WordPress Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash &amp;lt;= 3.7.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48080</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash: from n/a through 3.7.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48112 | WordPress Dot html,php,xml etc pages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48112</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in karimmughal Dot html,php,xml etc pages allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Dot html,php,xml etc pages: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48113 | WordPress Broadstreet &amp;lt;= 1.51.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48113</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Broadstreet Broadstreet allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Broadstreet: from n/a through 1.51.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48114 | WordPress ShayanWeb Admin FontChanger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48114</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shayan Farhang Pazhooh ShayanWeb Admin FontChanger allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShayanWeb Admin FontChanger: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48115 | WordPress ValidateCertify &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48115</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Javier Revilla ValidateCertify allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects ValidateCertify: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48116 | WordPress EventON &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48116</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ashan Perera EventON allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects EventON: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48117 | WordPress WooCommerce POS &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48117</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in kilbot WooCommerce POS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WooCommerce POS: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48119 | WordPress RS WP Book Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 6.7.41 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48119</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in RS WP THEMES RS WP Book Showcase allows Code Injection. This issue affects RS WP Book Showcase: from n/a through 6.7.41.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48120 | WordPress MapSVG Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 8.6.4 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48120</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in RomanCode MapSVG Lite allows Code Injection. This issue affects MapSVG Lite: from n/a through 8.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48121 | WordPress WP Notes Widget &amp;lt;= 1.0.6  - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Steve Puddick WP Notes Widget allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WP Notes Widget: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48127 | WordPress Push notification for Mobile and Web app &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48127</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in App Cheap Push notification for Mobile and Web app allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Push notification for Mobile and Web app: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48128 | WordPress Sharespine Woocommerce Connector &amp;lt;= 4.7.55 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48128</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sharespine Sharespine Woocommerce Connector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Sharespine Woocommerce Connector: from n/a through 4.7.55.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48131 | WordPress UltraAddons Elementor Lite &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48131</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saiful Islam UltraAddons Elementor Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48132 | WordPress X Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pencilwp X Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects X Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48134 | WordPress WP Tabs &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48134</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ShapedPlugin LLC WP Tabs allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Tabs: from n/a through 2.2.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48135 | WordPress Aptivada for WP &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in aptivadadev Aptivada for WP allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Aptivada for WP: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48136 | WordPress Mortgage Calculator Estatik &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48136</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Estatik Mortgage Calculator Estatik allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Mortgage Calculator Estatik: from n/a through 2.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48137 | WordPress Interview &amp;lt;= 1.01 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in proxymis Interview allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Interview: from n/a through 1.01.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48138 | WordPress BERTHA AI &amp;lt;= 1.12.11 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48138</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in berthaai BERTHA AI allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects BERTHA AI: from n/a through 1.12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48144 | WordPress Import Export For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48144</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in sidngr Import Export For WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Import Export For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48146 | WordPress SEO Flow by LupsOnline plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48146</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Lups SEO Flow by LupsOnline allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SEO Flow by LupsOnline: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4786 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_return sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/?page=return/view_return. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40906 | BSON::XS versions 0.8.4 and earlier for Perl includes a bundled libbson 1.1.7, which has several vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40906</link><description>BSON::XS versions 0.8.4 and earlier for Perl includes a bundled libbson 1.1.7, which has several vulnerabilities.

Those include CVE-2017-14227, CVE-2018-16790, CVE-2023-0437, CVE-2024-6381, CVE-2024-6383, and CVE-2025-0755. 

BSON-XS was the official Perl XS implementation of MongoDB's BSON serialization, but this distribution has reached its end of life as of August 13, 2020 and is no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4785 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System user-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4785</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47916 | Invision Community 5.0.0 before 5.0.7 allows remote code execution via crafted template strings to themeeditor.php. The issue lies within th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47916</link><description>Invision Community 5.0.0 before 5.0.7 allows remote code execution via crafted template strings to themeeditor.php. The issue lies within the themeeditor controller (file: /applications/core/modules/front/system/themeeditor.php), where a protected method named customCss can be invoked by unauthenticated users. This method passes the value of the content parameter to the Theme::makeProcessFunction() method; hence it is evaluated by the template engine. Accordingly, this can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary PHP code by providing crafted template strings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47793 | Nextcloud Server and Groupfolders app vulnerable to bypass of group folder quota limit using attachment in text file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47793</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system, and the Nextcloud Groupfolders app provides admin-configured folders shared by everyone in a group or team. In Nextcloud Server prior to 30.0.2, 29.0.9, and 28.0.1, Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 30.0.2 and 29.0.9, and Nextcloud Groupfolders app prior to 18.0.3, 17.0.5, and 16.0.11, the absence of quota checking on attachments allowed logged-in users to upload files exceeding the group folder quota. Nextcloud Server versions 30.0.2 and 29.0.9, Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 30.0.2, 29.0.9, or 28.0.12, and Nextcloud Groupfolders app 18.0.3, 17.0.5, and 16.0.11 fix the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47794 | Nextcloud Server vulnerable to insecure temporary file creation, race with write access and permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47794</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server prior to 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 26.0.13.13, 27.1.11.13, 28.0.14.4, 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1, an attacker on a multi-user system may read temporary files from Nextcloud running with a different user account, or run a symlink attack. Nextcloud Server versions 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 26.0.13.13, 27.1.11.13, 28.0.14.4, 29.0.13, 30.0.7, and 31.0.1 fix the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4781 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4781</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email/contactno leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4782 | SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System view_receiving sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4782</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester/oretnom23 Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /sms/admin/?page=receiving/view_receiving&amp;amp;id=1. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4478 | Gnome-remote-desktop: unauthenticated rdp packet causes segfault in gnome-remote-desktop leading to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4478</link><description>A flaw was found in the gnome-remote-desktop used by Anaconda's remote install feature, where a crafted RDP packet could trigger a segmentation fault. This issue causes the service to crash and remain defunct, resulting in a denial of service. It occurs pre-boot and is likely due to a NULL pointer dereference. Rebooting is required to recover the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47791 | Nextcloud Server&amp;#x27;s test remote endpoint is not rate limited</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47791</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. In Nextcloud Server prior to 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3, a currently unused endpoint to verify a share recipient was not protected correctly, allowing to proxy requests to another server. The endpoint was removed in Nextcloud Server 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 28.0.13, 29.0.10, and 30.0.3. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47792 | Nextcloud Desktop 3rdparty applications can create share links via socket API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47792</link><description>Nextcloud Desktop is the desktop sync client for Nextcloud. In versions of Nextcloud Desktop prior to 3.15, 3rdparty applications already installed on a user machine can create link shares for almost all data via the socket API. These shares can then be easily sent off to an external service. Nextcloud Desktop fixes the issue in version 3.15. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47790 | Nextcloud Server doesn&amp;#x27;t request second factor after session timeout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47790</link><description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Nextcloud Server prior to 29.0.15, 30.0.9, and 31.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to 26.0.13.15, 27.1.11.15, 28.0.14.6, 29.0.15, 30.0.9, and 31.0.3 have a bug with session handling. The bug caused skipping the second factor confirmation after a successful login with the username and password when the server was configured with `remember_login_cookie_lifetime` set to `0`, once the session expired on the page to select the second factor and the page is reloaded. Nextcloud Server 29.0.15, 30.0.9, and 31.0.3 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13.15, 27.1.11.15, 28.0.14.6, 29.0.15, 30.0.9 and 31.0.3 contain a patch. As a workaround, set the `remember_login_cookie_lifetime` in config.php to a value other than `0`, e.g. `900`. Beware that this is only a workaround for new sessions created after the configuration change. System administration can delete affected sessions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4780 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System foreigner-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4780</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /foreigner-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32962 | Flask-AppBuilder open redirect vulnerability using HTTP host injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32962</link><description>Flask-AppBuilder is an application development framework built on top of Flask. Versions prior to 4.6.2 would allow for a malicious unauthenticated actor to perform an open redirect by manipulating the Host header in HTTP requests. Flask-AppBuilder 4.6.2 introduced the `FAB_SAFE_REDIRECT_HOSTS` configuration variable, which allows administrators to explicitly define which domains are considered safe for redirection. As a workaround, use a reverse proxy to enforce trusted host headers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4600 | HTTP Request Smuggling in Google Cloud Classic Application Load Balancer due to Improper Chunked Encoding Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4600</link><description>A request smuggling vulnerability existed in the Google Cloud Classic Application Load Balancer due to improper handling of chunked-encoded HTTP requests. This allowed attackers to craft requests that could be misinterpreted by backend servers. The issue was fixed by disallowing stray data after a chunk, and is no longer exploitable. No action is required as Classic Application Load Balancer service after 2025-04-26 is not vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4211 | Improper Link Resolution Before File Access in QFileSystemEngine on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4211</link><description>Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in QFileSystemEngine in the Qt corelib module on Windows which potentially allows Symlink Attacks and the use of Malicious Files. Issue originates from CVE-2024-38081. The vulnerability arises from the use of the GetTempPath API, which can be exploited by attackers to manipulate temporary file paths, potentially leading to unauthorized access and privilege escalation. The affected public API in the Qt Framework is QDir::tempPath() and anything that uses it, such as QStandardPaths with TempLocation, QTemporaryDir, and QTemporaryFile.This issue affects all version of Qt up to and including 5.15.18, from 6.0.0 through 6.5.8, from 6.6.0 through 6.8.1. It is fixed in Qt 5.15.19, Qt 6.5.9, Qt 6.8.2, 6.9.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4778 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System normal-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4778</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /normal-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37890 | net_sched: hfsc: Fix a UAF vulnerability in class with netem as child qdisc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37890</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net_sched: hfsc: Fix a UAF vulnerability in class with netem as child qdisc

As described in Gerrard's report [1], we have a UAF case when an hfsc class
has a netem child qdisc. The crux of the issue is that hfsc is assuming
that checking for cl-&gt;qdisc-&gt;q.qlen == 0 guarantees that it hasn't inserted
the class in the vttree or eltree (which is not true for the netem
duplicate case).

This patch checks the n_active class variable to make sure that the code
won't insert the class in the vttree or eltree twice, catering for the
reentrant case.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/netdev/CAHcdcOm+03OD2j6R0=YHKqmy=VgJ8xEOKuP6c7mSgnp-TEJJbw@mail.gmail.com/</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40907 | FCGI versions 0.44 through 0.82, for Perl, include a vulnerable version of the FastCGI fcgi2 (aka fcgi) library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40907</link><description>FCGI versions 0.44 through 0.82, for Perl, include a vulnerable version of the FastCGI fcgi2 (aka fcgi) library.

The included FastCGI library is affected by  CVE-2025-23016, causing an integer overflow (and resultant heap-based buffer overflow) via crafted nameLen or valueLen values in data to the IPC socket. This occurs in ReadParams in fcgiapp.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4777 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System view-foreigner-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4777</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /view-foreigner-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40629 | Path Traversal vulnerability in PNETLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40629</link><description>PNETLab 4.2.10 does not properly sanitize user inputs in its file access mechanisms. This allows attackers to perform directory traversal by manipulating file paths in HTTP requests. Specifically, the application is vulnerable to requests that access sensitive files outside the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4773 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration level.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4773</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/level.php. The manipulation of the argument level leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40120 | seaweedfs v3.68 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /abstract_sql/abstract_sql_store.go.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40120</link><description>seaweedfs v3.68 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /abstract_sql/abstract_sql_store.go.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:03:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2305 | Local file inclusion vulnerability in LIVE CONTRACT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2305</link><description>A Path traversal vulnerability in the file
download functionality was identified. This vulnerability allows
unauthenticated users to download arbitrary files, in the context of the
application server, from the Linux server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2306 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in LIVE CONTRACT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2306</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability was
identified in the file download functionality. This vulnerability allows users
to download sensitive documents without authentication, if the URL is known.



The attack
requires the attacker to know the documents UUIDv4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4772 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration department.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4772</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/department.php. The manipulation of the argument department leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4771 | PHPGurukul Online Course Registration course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4771</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration 3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/course.php. The manipulation of the argument coursecode leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40630 | Open redirection vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40630</link><description>Open redirection vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server affecting version 11.4.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to redirect a user to any domain by sending a malicious URL to the victim, for example “ https://icewarp.domain.com///%2e%2e” https://icewarp.domain.com///%2e%2e” . This vulnerability has been tested in Firefox.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40631 | HTTP host header injection vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40631</link><description>HTTP host header injection vulnerability in Icewarp Mail Server affecting version 11.4.0. By modifying the Host header and adding a payload, arbitrary JavaScript code can be executed on page load. The user must interact with a malicious link to be redirected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40632 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in IceWarp Mail Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40632</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) in Icewarp Mail Server affecting version 11.4.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to modify the “lastLogin” cookie with malicious JavaScript code that will be executed when the page is rendered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4770 | PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System view-normal-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4770</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Park Ticketing Management System 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view-normal-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:10:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4769 | CBEWIN Anytxt Searcher ATService.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4769</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CBEWIN Anytxt Searcher 1.3.1128.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ATService.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4768 | feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp/production_ssm PictureServiceImpl.java uploadPicture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4768</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in feng_ha_ha/megagao ssm-erp and production_ssm 1.0. This affects the function uploadPicture of the file PictureServiceImpl.java. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is distributed under two entirely different names.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4767 | defog-ai introspect Test Endpoint integration_routes.py test_custom_tool code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4767</link><description>A vulnerability was found in defog-ai introspect up to 0.1.4. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function test_custom_tool of the file introspect/backend/integration_routes.py of the component Test Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument input_model leads to code injection. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4766 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4766</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1975 | Improper Validation of Array Index in ollama/ollama</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1975</link><description>A vulnerability in the Ollama server version 0.5.11 allows a malicious user to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack by customizing the manifest content and spoofing a service. This is due to improper validation of array index access when downloading a model via the /api/pull endpoint, which can lead to a server crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4679 | A vulnerability in Synology Active Backup for Microsoft 365 allows remote authenticated attackers to obtain sensitive information via unspec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4679</link><description>A vulnerability in Synology Active Backup for Microsoft 365 allows remote authenticated attackers to obtain sensitive information via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4765 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4765</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnum leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4758 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System contact.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4758</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /contact.php. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4761 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4761</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4756 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 restart.asp denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4756</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /H5/restart.asp. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4757 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4757</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53827 | Ericsson Packet Core Controller (PCC) - Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53827</link><description>Ericsson Packet Core Controller (PCC) contains a
vulnerability where an attacker sending a large volume of specially
crafted messages may cause service degradation</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4755 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 netconfig.asp sub_497DE4 improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4755</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sub_497DE4 of the file /H5/netconfig.asp. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3624 | Missing Authorization Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3624</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer (Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer detail view component).This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8201 | Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8201</link><description>Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer (RAID Agent component).This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.8.0-00 before 11.0.4-00; Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.9.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4753 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 login.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4753</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125) and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1531 | Authentication credentials leakage vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint OVF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1531</link><description>Authentication credentials leakage  vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1245 | Bypass Connection Restriction Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1245</link><description>Bypass Connection Restriction vulnerability in Hitachi Infrastructure Analytics Advisor (Data Center Analytics component), Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer  (Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer detail view component).This issue affects Hitachi Infrastructure Analytics Advisor:; Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3201 | Kali Forms &amp;lt; 2.4.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3201</link><description>The Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 2.4.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributors to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3516 | Simple Lightbox &amp;lt; 2.9.4 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3516</link><description>The Simple Lightbox WordPress plugin before 2.9.4 does not validate and escape some of its attributes before outputting them back in a page/post, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4751 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 index.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4751</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4752 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 install_base.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4752</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125) and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /install_base.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4750 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 Configuration get_version.data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4750</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /H5/get_version.data of the component Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48174 | In libavif before 1.3.0, makeRoom in stream.c has an integer overflow and resultant buffer overflow in stream-&gt;offset+size.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48174</link><description>In libavif before 1.3.0, makeRoom in stream.c has an integer overflow and resultant buffer overflow in stream-&gt;offset+size.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4747 | Bohua NetDragon Firewall ip_status.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4747</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bohua NetDragon Firewall 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /systemstatus/ip_status.php. The manipulation of the argument subnet leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4749 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 Factory Reset backup.asp sub_4983B0 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4749</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). This vulnerability affects the function sub_4983B0 of the file /H5/backup.asp?opt=reset of the component Factory Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4759 | Versions of the package lockfile-lint-api before 5.9.2 are vulnerable to Incorrect Behavior Order: Early Validation via the resolved attribu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4759</link><description>Versions of the package lockfile-lint-api before 5.9.2 are vulnerable to Incorrect Behavior Order: Early Validation via the resolved attribute of the package URL validation which can be bypassed by extending the package name allowing an attacker to install other npm packages than the intended one.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48175 | In libavif before 1.3.0, avifImageRGBToYUV in reformat.c has integer overflows in multiplications involving rgbRowBytes, yRowBytes, uRowByte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48175</link><description>In libavif before 1.3.0, avifImageRGBToYUV in reformat.c has integer overflows in multiplications involving rgbRowBytes, yRowBytes, uRowBytes, and vRowBytes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4746 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System purchase_delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4746</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pages/purchase_delete.php. The manipulation of the argument pr_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4744 | code-projects Employee Record System edit_employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4744</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Employee Record System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file dashboard\edit_employee.php. The manipulation of the argument employeed_id/first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4745 | code-projects Employee Record System current_employees.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4745</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Employee Record System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file current_employees.php. The manipulation of the argument employeed_id/first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4743 | code-projects Employee Record System getData.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4743</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Employee Record System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/getData.php. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4741 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System purchase_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4741</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/purchase_add.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4742 | XU-YIJIE grpo-flat grpo_vanilla.py main deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4742</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in XU-YIJIE grpo-flat up to 9024b43f091e2eb9bac65802b120c0b35f9ba856. Affected is the function main of the file grpo_vanilla.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. Local access is required to approach this attack. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4169 | Posts per Cat [Unmaintained] &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4169</link><description>The Posts per Cat [Unmaintained plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ppc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4740 | BeamCtrl Airiana coef deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4740</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BeamCtrl Airiana up to 11.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file coef. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4739 | projectworlds Hospital Database Management System medicines_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4739</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Hospital Database Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /medicines_info.php. The manipulation of the argument Med_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4735 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4735</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/product.php. The manipulation of the argument Picture leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4736 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker 1.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51475 | IBM Content Navigator HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51475</link><description>IBM Content Navigator 3.0.11, 3.0.15, and 3.1.0 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4734 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System ci_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4734</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/ci_update.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47809 | Wibu CodeMeter before 8.30a sometimes allows privilege escalation immediately after installation (before a logoff or reboot). For exploitati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47809</link><description>Wibu CodeMeter before 8.30a sometimes allows privilege escalation immediately after installation (before a logoff or reboot). For exploitation, there must have been an unprivileged installation with UAC, and the CodeMeter Control Center component must be installed, and the CodeMeter Control Center component must not have been restarted. In this scenario, the local user can navigate from Import License to a privileged instance of Windows Explorer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4732 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4732</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4733 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formIpQoS buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4733</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formIpQoS of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4730 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formMapDel buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4730</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formMapDel of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument devicemac1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4731 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4731</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4729 | TOTOLINK A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formMapDelDevice command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4729</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formMapDelDevice of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument macstr leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47930 | Zulip Server has access control bypass for restrictions on creation of specific channel types</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47930</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team chat application. Starting in version 10.0 and prior to version 10.3, the "Who can create public channels" access control mechanism can be circumvented by creating a private or web-public channel, and then changing the channel privacy to public. A similar technique works for creating private channels without permission, though such a process requires either the API or modifying the HTML, as we do mark the "private" radio button as disabled in such cases. Version 10.3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4727 | Meteor livedata_server.js Object.assign redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4727</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Meteor up to 3.2.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function Object.assign of the file packages/ddp-server/livedata_server.js. The manipulation of the argument forwardedFor leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.2.2 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is f7ea6817b90952baaea9baace2a3b4366fee6a63. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4728 | SourceCodester Best Online News Portal search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4728</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Online News Portal 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchtitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0921 | Information Tampering Vulnerability in Multi-agent Notification Feature of GENESIS64 and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0921</link><description>Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability in the Pager agent of multi-agent notification feature in ICONICS GENESIS64 prior to 10.97.3, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local authenticated attacker to make an unauthorized write to arbitrary files, by creating a symbolic link from a file used as a write destination by the services of the affected products to a target file. This could allow the attacker to destroy the file on a PC with the affected products installed, resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the PC if the destroyed file is necessary for the operation of the PC.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4726 | itsourcecode Placement Management System view_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4726</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view_student.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4724 | itsourcecode Placement Management System student_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4724</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /student_profile.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4725 | itsourcecode Placement Management System view_drive.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4725</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /view_drive.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4722 | itsourcecode Placement Management System edit_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4722</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit_profile.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4723 | itsourcecode Placement Management System all_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4723</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /all_student.php. The manipulation of the argument delete leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47275 | Forgeable Encrypted Session Cookie in Apps Using Auth0-PHP SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47275</link><description>Auth0-PHP provides the PHP SDK for Auth0 Authentication and Management APIs. Starting in version 8.0.0-BETA1 and prior to version 8.14.0, session cookies of applications using the Auth0-PHP SDK configured with CookieStore have authentication tags that can be brute forced, which may result in unauthorized access. Certain pre-conditions are required to be vulnerable to this issue: Applications using the Auth0-PHP SDK, or the Auth0/symfony, Auth0/laravel-auth0, and Auth0/wordpress SDKs that rely on the Auth0-PHP SDK; and session storage configured with CookieStore. Upgrade Auth0/Auth0-PHP to v8.14.0 to receive a patch. As an additional precautionary measure, rotating cookie encryption keys is recommended. Note that once updated, any previous session cookies will be rejected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47287 | Tornado vulnerable to excessive logging caused by malformed multipart form data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47287</link><description>Tornado is a Python web framework and asynchronous networking library. When Tornado's ``multipart/form-data`` parser encounters certain errors, it logs a warning but continues trying to parse the remainder of the data. This allows remote attackers to generate an extremely high volume of logs, constituting a DoS attack. This DoS is compounded by the fact that the logging subsystem is synchronous. All versions of Tornado prior to 6.5.0 are affected. The vulnerable parser is enabled by default. Upgrade to Tornado version 6.50 to receive a patch. As a workaround, risk can be mitigated by blocking `Content-Type: multipart/form-data` in a proxy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4720 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System drop_student.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4720</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file academic/core/drop_student.php. The manipulation of the argument img leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4721 | itsourcecode Placement Management System drive.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4721</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /drive.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4718 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System customer_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4718</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/customer_add.php. The manipulation of the argument last leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4719 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System cash_transaction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4719</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /pages/cash_transaction.php. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1138 | IBM Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1138</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could disclose sensitive information to an authenticated user that could aid in further attacks against the system through a directory listing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47929 | DumbDrop vulnerable to DOM XSS via file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47929</link><description>DumbDrop, a file upload application that provides an interface for dragging and dropping files, has a DOM cross-site scripting vulnerability in the upload functionality prior to commit db27b25372eb9071e63583d8faed2111a2b79f1b. A user could be tricked into uploading a file with a malicious payload. Commit db27b25372eb9071e63583d8faed2111a2b79f1b fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2334 | Easy Digital Downloads Google Sheet Connector &amp;lt; 1.6.6 - Access Code Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2334</link><description>The edd-google-sheet-connector-pro WordPress plugin before 1.4, Easy Digital Downloads Google Sheet Connector WordPress plugin before 1.6.6 does not have CSRF check when updating its Access Code, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin change the access code to an arbitrary one via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5529 | Advanced Page Visit Counter &amp;lt;= 8.0.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5529</link><description>The Advanced Page Visit Counter  WordPress plugin before 8.0.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5932 | Travelpayouts &amp;lt; 1.1.14 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5932</link><description>The Travelpayouts: All Travel Brands in One Place WordPress plugin before 1.1.14 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5934 | Travelpayouts &amp;lt; 1.1.13 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5934</link><description>The Travelpayouts: All Travel Brands in One Place WordPress plugin before 1.1.13 does not have CSRF check in place when importing settings from the v1, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin update some settings via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6030 | LogDash Activity Log &amp;lt; 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6030</link><description>The LogDash Activity Log WordPress plugin before 1.1.4 hooks the wp_login_failed function (from src/Hooks/Users.php) in order to log failed login attempts to the database but it doesn't escape the username when it perform some SQL request leading to a SQL injection vulnerability which can be exploited using time-based technique by unauthenticated attacker</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6541 | Allow SVG &amp;lt; 1.2.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6541</link><description>The Allow SVG WordPress plugin before 1.2.0 does not sanitize uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6783 | WolfNet IDX for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.19.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6783</link><description>The WolfNet IDX for WordPress plugin through 1.19.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6786 | Payment Gateway for Telcell &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6786</link><description>The Payment Gateway for Telcell WordPress plugin through 2.0.1 does not validate the api_url parameter before redirecting the user to its value, leading to an Open Redirect issue</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7086 | SVG Uploads Support  &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7086</link><description>The SVG Uploads Support WordPress plugin through 2.1.1 does not sanitize uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7088 | Add SVG Support for Media Uploader | inventivo &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7088</link><description>The Add SVG Support for Media Uploader | inventivo WordPress plugin through 1.0.5 does not sanitize uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7168 | Better Follow Button for Jetpack &amp;lt;= 8.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7168</link><description>The Better Follow Button for Jetpack WordPress plugin through 8.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7174 | aBitGone CommentSafe &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Settings Update to Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7174</link><description>The aBitGone CommentSafe WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7195 | WP-Reply Notify &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7195</link><description>The WP-Reply Notify WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not have a CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged-in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7196 | Ultimate Noindex Nofollow Tool &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7196</link><description>The Ultimate Noindex Nofollow Tool WordPress plugin through 1.1.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7197 | Marketing Twitter Bot &amp;lt;= 1.11 - Settings Update to Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7197</link><description>The Marketing Twitter Bot WordPress plugin through 1.11 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7228 | illi Link Party! &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7228</link><description>The illi Link Party! WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow unauthenticated vistors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7229 | illi Link Party! &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7229</link><description>The illi Link Party! WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7230 | illi Link Party! &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7230</link><description>The illi Link Party! WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitize and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7231 | illi Link Party! &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Link Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7231</link><description>The illi Link Party! WordPress plugin through 1.0 lacks proper access controls, allowing unauthenticated visitors to delete links.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7239 | wp-dashboard-notes &amp;lt; 1.0.11 - Contributor+ Arbitrary Private Notes Update via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7239</link><description>The WP Dashboard Notes WordPress plugin before 1.0.11 does not validate that the user has access to the post_id parameter in its wpdn_update_note AJAX action. This allows users with a role of contributor and above to update notes created by other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7297 | TwitterPosts  &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7297</link><description>The TwitterPosts WordPress plugin through 1.0.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0249 | Advanced Schedule Posts &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0249</link><description>The Advanced Schedule Posts WordPress plugin through 2.1.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0852 | coreActivity &amp;lt; 1.8.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0852</link><description>The coreActivity: Activity Logging for WordPress plugin before 1.8.1 does not escape some request data when outputting it back in the admin dashboard, allowing unauthenticated users to perform Stored XSS attack against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0970 | User Activity Tracking and Log &amp;lt; 4.1.4 - IP Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0970</link><description>This User Activity Tracking and Log WordPress plugin before 4.1.4 retrieves client IP addresses from potentially untrusted headers, allowing an attacker to manipulate its value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10009 | Website File Changes  &amp;lt; 2.1.0 - Admin+ Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10009</link><description>The Melapress File Monitor WordPress plugin before 2.1.0 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10054 | Happyforms &amp;lt; 1.26.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10054</link><description>The Happyforms  WordPress plugin before 1.26.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10075 | Jetpack &amp;lt; 13.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Block &amp;amp; Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10075</link><description>The Jetpack  WordPress plugin before 13.8 does not ensure that the post created by the Contact Form is only accessible to authorised users, which could allow unauthenticated users to run arbitrary shortcodes and block.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10076 | Jetpack &amp;lt; 13.8, Boost &amp;lt; 3.4.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10076</link><description>The Jetpack  WordPress plugin before 13.8, Jetpack Boost  WordPress plugin before 3.4.8 use regexes in the Site Accelerator features when switching image URLs to their CDN counterpart. Unfortunately, some of them may match patterns it shouldn’t, ultimately making it possible for contributor and above users to perform Stored XSS attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10098 | ApplyOnline – Application Form Builder and Manager &amp;lt; 2.6.3 - Unauthenticated Application File Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10098</link><description>The ApplyOnline  WordPress plugin before 2.6.3 does not protect uploaded files during the application process, allowing unauthenticated users to access them and any private information they contain</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10107 | Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress &amp;lt; 1.12.17 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10107</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress  WordPress plugin before 1.12.17 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10143 | MB Custom Post Types &amp;amp; Custom Taxonomies &amp;lt; 2.7.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10143</link><description>The MB Custom Post Types &amp; Custom Taxonomies WordPress plugin before 2.7.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10144 | Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery &amp;lt; 3.2.22 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10144</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery WordPress plugin before 3.2.22 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10145 | Hubbub Lite &amp;lt; 1.34.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10145</link><description>The Hubbub Lite  WordPress plugin before 1.34.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10149 | Social Slider Feed &amp;lt; 2.2.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10149</link><description>The Social Slider Feed WordPress plugin before 2.2.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10362 | Social Media Share Buttons &amp;lt; 2.9.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10362</link><description>The Social Media Share Buttons &amp; Social Sharing Icons WordPress plugin before 2.9.1 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10475 | Lead Form Builder &amp;lt; 1.9.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10475</link><description>The Responsive Contact Form Builder &amp; Lead Generation Plugin WordPress plugin before 1.9.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10504 | ARForms Builder &amp;lt; 1.7.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10504</link><description>The Contact Form, Survey, Quiz &amp; Popup Form Builder  WordPress plugin before 1.7.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputting them in the page, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10631 | Countdown Timer &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10631</link><description>The Countdown Timer for WordPress Block Editor WordPress plugin through 1.0.5 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10632 | Nokaut Offers Box &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10632</link><description>The Nokaut Offers Box WordPress plugin through 1.4.0 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10634 | Nokaut Offers Box &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Plugin Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10634</link><description>The Nokaut Offers Box WordPress plugin through 1.4.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin reset the Nokaut Offers Box WordPress plugin through 1.4.0 via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10639 | Auto Prune Posts &amp;lt; 3.0.0- Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10639</link><description>The Auto Prune Posts WordPress plugin before 3.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10677 | BTEV &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10677</link><description>The BTEV WordPress plugin through 2.0.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10818 | JSFiddle Shortcode &amp;lt; 1.1.3 - Contributor+ XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10818</link><description>The JSFiddle Shortcode WordPress plugin before 1.1.3 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11109 | WP Google Review Slider &amp;lt; 15.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11109</link><description>The WP Google Review Slider WordPress plugin before 15.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11140 | Real WP Shop Lite Ajax eCommerce Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11140</link><description>The Real WP Shop Lite Ajax eCommerce Shopping Cart WordPress plugin through 2.0.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11141 | Sailthru Triggermail &amp;lt; 1.1 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11141</link><description>The Sailthru Triggermail WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings and is missing CSRF protection which could allow subscribers to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11189 | Social Share And Social Locker – ARSocial &amp;lt; 1.4.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11189</link><description>The Social Share And Social Locker  WordPress plugin before 1.4.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11190 | jwp-a11y &amp;lt;= 4.1.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11190</link><description>The jwp-a11y WordPress plugin through 4.1.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11221 | Full Screen (Page) Background Image Slideshow &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11221</link><description>The Full Screen (Page) Background Image Slideshow WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11266 | Geocache Stat Bar Widget &amp;lt;= 0.911 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11266</link><description>The Geocache Stat Bar Widget WordPress plugin through 0.911 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11267 | JSP Store Locator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Contributor+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11267</link><description>The JSP Store Locator WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing user with Contributor to perform SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11269 | AHAthat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11269</link><description>The AHAthat Plugin WordPress plugin through 1.6 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing Admin to perform SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11372 | Connexion Logs &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11372</link><description>The Connexion Logs WordPress plugin through 3.0.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11373 | Connexion Logs &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Log Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11373</link><description>The Connexion Logs WordPress plugin through 3.0.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11502 | Planning Center Online Giving &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Contributor+ XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11502</link><description>The Planning Center Online Giving WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11718 | tarteaucitron.js for WordPress &amp;lt; 0.3.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11718</link><description>The tarteaucitron-wp WordPress plugin before 0.3.0 allows author level and above users to add HTML into a post/page, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11719 | tarteaucitron.js for WordPress &amp;lt; 0.3.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11719</link><description>The tarteaucitron-wp WordPress plugin before 0.3.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11843 | Panorama – WordPress Project Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11843</link><description>The Panorama  WordPress plugin through 1.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12282 | WordPress连接微博 &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12282</link><description>The WordPress连接微博 WordPress plugin through 2.5.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12301 | JSP Store Locator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Deletion via Missing CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12301</link><description>The JSP Store Locator WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12679 | Prisna GWT &amp;lt; 1.4.14 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12679</link><description>The Prisna GWT  WordPress plugin before 1.4.14 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12680 | Prisna GWT &amp;lt; 1.4.14 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12680</link><description>The Prisna GWT  WordPress plugin before 1.4.14 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12716 | Simple Basic Contact Form &amp;lt; 20250114 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12716</link><description>The Simple Basic Contact Form WordPress plugin before 20250114 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12722 | Twitter Bootstrap Collapse aka Accordian Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12722</link><description>The Twitter Bootstrap Collapse aka Accordian Shortcode WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12724 | WP DeskLite &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12724</link><description>The WP DeskLite  WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12725 | Clasify Classified Listing &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12725</link><description>The Clasify Classified Listing WordPress plugin through 1.0.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12726 | ClipArt &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12726</link><description>The ClipArt WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12732 | AffiliateImporterEb &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12732</link><description>The AffiliateImporterEb WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12733 | AffiliateImporterEb &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Reflected XSS via Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12733</link><description>The AffiliateImporterEb WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12734 | Advance Post Prefix &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12734</link><description>The Advance Post Prefix WordPress plugin through 1.1.1, Advance Post Prefix WordPress plugin through 1.1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12735 | Advance Post Prefix &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12735</link><description>The Advance Post Prefix WordPress plugin through 1.1.1 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins and above to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12739 | Mobile Contact Bar &amp;lt; 3.0.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12739</link><description>The Mobile Contact Bar WordPress plugin before 3.0.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12743 | MailPoet &amp;lt; 5.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12743</link><description>The MailPoet  WordPress plugin before 5.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12750 | Competition Form &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Competition Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12750</link><description>The Competition Form WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12767 | BuddyBoss platform &amp;lt; 2.7.60 - Private Comment Exposure via IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12767</link><description>The buddyboss-platform WordPress plugin before 2.7.60 lacks proper access controls and allows a logged-in user to view comments on private posts</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12770 | WP ULike &amp;lt; 4.7.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12770</link><description>The WP ULike  WordPress plugin before 4.7.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12800 | IP Based Login &amp;lt; 2.4.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12800</link><description>The IP Based Login WordPress plugin before 2.4.1 does not sanitise values when importing, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12808 | WP ERP | Complete HR solution with recruitment &amp;lt; 1.13.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12808</link><description>The WP ERP | Complete HR solution with recruitment &amp; job listings | WooCommerce CRM &amp; Accounting WordPress plugin before 1.13.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12812 | WP ERP &amp;lt; 1.13.4 - Custom+ Unauthorized Access to Terminated Employee Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12812</link><description>The WP ERP | Complete HR solution with recruitment &amp; job listings | WooCommerce CRM &amp; Accounting WordPress plugin before 1.13.4 has an issue where employees can manipulate parameters to access the data of terminated employees.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12873 | Custom Field Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12873</link><description>The Custom Field Manager WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12874 | Top Comments &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12874</link><description>The Top Comments WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13053 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.33 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Theme Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13053</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.33 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13127 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt; 4.2.7.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13127</link><description>The LearnPress  WordPress plugin before 4.2.7.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13128 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt; 4.2.7.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13128</link><description>The LearnPress  WordPress plugin before 4.2.7.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13313 | AWeber &amp;lt;= 7.3.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13313</link><description>The AWeber  WordPress plugin through 7.3.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13357 | Ditty – Responsive News Tickers, Sliders, and Lists &amp;lt; 3.1.52 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13357</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.52 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as author to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13382 | Calculated Fields Form &amp;lt; 5.2.64 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13382</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form WordPress plugin before 5.2.64 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13383 | HD Quiz &amp;lt; 2.0.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13383</link><description>The HD Quiz WordPress plugin before 2.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13384 | Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery &amp;lt; 3.2.24 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13384</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery WordPress plugin before 3.2.24 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13482 | Icegram Engage &amp;lt; 3.1.32 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13482</link><description>The Icegram Engage  WordPress plugin before 3.1.32 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13486 | Icegram Engage &amp;lt; 3.1.32 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13486</link><description>The Icegram Engage  WordPress plugin before 3.1.32 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13616 | VikBooking &amp;lt; 1.7.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13616</link><description>The VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS WordPress plugin before 1.7.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13619 | LifterLMS – WP LMS for eLearning, Online Courses, &amp;amp; Quizzes &amp;lt; 8.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13619</link><description>The LifterLMS  WordPress plugin before 8.0.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13621 | The GDPR Framework By Data443 &amp;lt; 2.2.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13621</link><description>The GDPR Framework By Data443 WordPress plugin before 2.2.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13727 | MemberSpace – Membership Plugin and Paid Subscriptions &amp;lt; 2.1.14 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13727</link><description>The MemberSpace  WordPress plugin before 2.1.14 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against only unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13729 | Podlove Podcast Publisher &amp;lt; 4.1.24 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13729</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher WordPress plugin before 4.1.24 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13730 | Podlove Podcast Publisher &amp;lt; 4.2.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13730</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher WordPress plugin before 4.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13823 | 360 Product Rotation &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13823</link><description>The 360 Product Rotation WordPress plugin through 1.5.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against only unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13828 | Badgearoo &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13828</link><description>The Badgearoo WordPress plugin through 1.0.14 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13865 | drm-protected-video-streaming &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13865</link><description>The S3Player  WordPress plugin through 4.2.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against only unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1663 | Ultimate Noindex Nofollow Tool II &amp;lt; 1.3.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1663</link><description>The Ultimate Noindex Nofollow Tool II WordPress plugin before 1.3.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2643 | My Sticky Bar &amp;lt; 2.6.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2643</link><description>The Floating Notification Bar, Sticky Menu on Scroll, Announcement Banner, and Sticky Header for Any   WordPress plugin before 2.6.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2869 | Easy Property Listings &amp;lt;= 3.5.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2869</link><description>The Easy Property Listings WordPress plugin before 3.5.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3062 | Save as PDF by Pdfcrowd &amp;lt; 3.2.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3062</link><description>The Save as Image Plugin by Pdfcrowd WordPress plugin before 3.2.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3901 | Genesis Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3901</link><description>The Genesis Blocks WordPress plugin through 3.1.3 does not properly escape attributes provided to some of its custom blocks, making it possible for users allowed to write posts (like those with the contributor role) to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3996 | Post Grid, Post Carousel, &amp;amp; List Category Posts &amp;lt; 2.4.28 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3996</link><description>The Smart Post Show  WordPress plugin before 2.4.28 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4002 | Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel &amp;lt; 2.6.9 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4002</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel  WordPress plugin before 2.6.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4004 | Advanced Cron Manager &amp;lt; 2.5.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4004</link><description>The Advanced Cron Manager  WordPress plugin before 2.5.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4091 | Responsive Gallery Grid &amp;lt; 2.3.15 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4091</link><description>The Responsive Gallery Grid WordPress plugin before 2.3.15 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4665 | EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt; 3.5.0 -  Subscriber+ Arbitrary booking settings update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4665</link><description>The EventPrime  WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not properly validate permissions when updating bookings, allowing users to change/cancel bookings for other users. Additionally, the feature is lacking a nonce.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5026 | CM Tooltip Glossary &amp;lt; 4.3.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5026</link><description>The CM Tooltip Glossary WordPress plugin before 4.3.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5440 | If-So Dynamic Content Personalization &amp;lt; 1.8.0.3 - Contributor+ Shortcode Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5440</link><description>The If-So Dynamic Content Personalization WordPress plugin before 1.8.0.3 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6159 | Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress &amp;lt;=1.93 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6159</link><description>The Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress WordPress plugin before 1.9.4 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6335 | Tracking Code Manager &amp;lt; 2.3.0- Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6335</link><description>The Tracking Code Manager WordPress plugin before 2.3.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6462 | DL Yandex Metrika &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6462</link><description>The DL Yandex Metrika WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6478 | CTT Expresso para WooCommerce &amp;lt; 3.2.13 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6478</link><description>The CTT Expresso para WooCommerce WordPress plugin before 3.2.13 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6486 | ImageMagick Engine &amp;lt; 1.7.11 - Administrator+ OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6486</link><description>The ImageMagick Engine ImageMagick Engine WordPress plugin before 1.7.11 for WordPress is vulnerable to OS Command Injection via the "cli_path" parameter. This allows authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permission to execute arbitrary OS commands on the server leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6584 | Jetpack Boost &amp;lt; 3.4.7 - Admin+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6584</link><description>The 'wp_ajax_boost_proxy_ig' action allows administrators to make GET requests to arbitrary URLs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6665 | kbucket &amp;lt; 4.1.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6665</link><description>The KBucket: Your Curated Content in WordPress plugin before 4.1.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6667 | kbucket &amp;lt; 4.1.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6667</link><description>The KBucket: Your Curated Content in WordPress plugin before 4.1.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6668 | profilepro &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Subscriber+ Stored Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6668</link><description>The ProfilePro WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not sanitise and escape some parameters and lacks proper access controls, which could allow users with a role as low as subscriber to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6690 | WP Content Copy Protection &amp;amp; No Right Click (premium) &amp;lt; 15.3 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6690</link><description>The wccp-pro WordPress plugin before 15.3 contains an open-redirect flaw via the referrer parameter, allowing redirection of users to external sites</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6693 | WP Content Copy Protection &amp;amp; No Right Click (premium) &amp;lt;= 15.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6693</link><description>The wccp-pro WordPress plugin before 15.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6708 | Profile Builder &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Admin+ Stored Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6708</link><description>The User Profile Builder  WordPress plugin before 3.12.2 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting its content on the admin area, which allows Admin+ users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6711 | Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner &amp;lt; 2.3.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6711</link><description>The Event Tickets with Ticket Scanner WordPress plugin before 2.3.8 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6712 | MapFig Studio &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6712</link><description>The MapFig Studio WordPress plugin through 0.2.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6713 | PVN Auth Popup &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6713</link><description>The PVN Auth Popup WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6718 | PVN Auth Popup &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Contributor+ XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6718</link><description>The PVN Auth Popup WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6719 | Offload Videos – Bunny.net, AWS S3 &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 Subscriber+ CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6719</link><description>The Offload Videos  WordPress plugin before 1.0.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow low privilege users to update them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6797 | DL Robots.txt &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6797</link><description>The DL Robots.txt WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6798 | DL Verification &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6798</link><description>The DL Verification WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6809 | Simple Video Directory &amp;lt; 1.4.3 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6809</link><description>The Simple Video Directory WordPress plugin before 1.4.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7556 | Wordpress Simple Share Plugin &amp;lt;=0.5.3 - Admin+ XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7556</link><description>The Simple Share WordPress plugin through 0.5.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7758 | Stylish Price List  &amp;lt; 7.1.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7758</link><description>The Stylish Price List  WordPress plugin before 7.1.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users of contributor and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7759 | PWA For WP &amp;amp; AMP &amp;lt; 1.7.72 Administrator+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7759</link><description>The PWA for WP  WordPress plugin before 1.7.72 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7761 | Simple Job Board  &amp;lt; 2.12.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7761</link><description>In the process of testing the Simple Job Board WordPress plugin before 2.12.2, a vulnerability was found that allows you to implement Stored XSS on behalf of the editor by embedding malicious script, which entails account takeover backdoor</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7762 | Simple Job Board &amp;lt; 2.12.6 - Unauthenticated Resumes Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7762</link><description>The Simple Job Board WordPress plugin before 2.12.6 does not prevent uploaded files from being listed, allowing unauthenticated users to access and download uploaded resumes</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7769 | Wordpress Clicksold IDX Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.90 - Admin+ XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7769</link><description>The ClickSold IDX WordPress plugin through 1.90 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7984 | Joy Of Text Lite – SMS messaging for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7984</link><description>The Joy Of Text Lite  WordPress plugin through 2.3.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8009 | Sensei LMS &amp;lt; 4.20.0 - Teacher+ Users Email Address Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8009</link><description>The Sensei LMS  WordPress plugin before 4.20.0 disclose all users of the blog including their email address to teachers on the students page</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8031 | Secure Downloads &amp;lt; 1.2.3 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8031</link><description>The Secure Downloads WordPress plugin before 1.2.3 is vulnerable does not properly restrict which files can be downloaded. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with admin-level access and above, to download arbitrary files that may contain sensitive information like wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8032 | Smooth Gallery Replacement &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8032</link><description>The Smooth Gallery Replacement WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8050 | Custom Author Base &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8050</link><description>The Custom Author Base WordPress plugin through 1.1.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8082 | Widgets Reset &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8082</link><description>The Widgets Reset WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8085 | PeoplePond &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - CSRF to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8085</link><description>The PeoplePond WordPress plugin through 1.1.9 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8090 | JavaScript Logic &amp;lt;= 0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8090</link><description>The JavaScript Logic WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8094 | Ntz Antispam &amp;lt;= 2.0e - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8094</link><description>The Ntz Antispam WordPress plugin through 2.0e does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8095 | BabelZ – Google Translate Widget &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8095</link><description>The BabelZ  WordPress plugin through 1.1.5 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8187 | Smart Post Show &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8187</link><description>The Smart Post Show  WordPress plugin before 3.0.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8245 | GamiPress - Reset User &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - GamiPress User Data Removal via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8245</link><description>The GamiPress  WordPress plugin before 1.0.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8284 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.2.98 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8284</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.2.99 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8286 | GDPR Cookie Consent &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Bulk Delete via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8286</link><description>The webtoffee-gdpr-cookie-consent WordPress plugin before 2.6.1 does not have CSRF checks in some bulk actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins perform unwanted actions, such as deleting visit logs via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8397 | GDPR Cookie Consent &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8397</link><description>The webtoffee-gdpr-cookie-consent WordPress plugin before 2.6.1 does not properly sanitize and escape the IP headers when logging them, allowing visitors to conduct Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks. The payload gets triggered when an admin visits the 'Consent report' page and the malicious script is executed in the admin context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8398 | Simple Nav Archives &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8398</link><description>The Simple Nav Archives WordPress plugin through 2.1.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8426 | Pagelayer &amp;lt; 1.8.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8426</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer  WordPress plugin before 1.8.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8492 | Hustle &amp;lt; 7.8.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8492</link><description>The Hustle  WordPress plugin through 7.8.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8493 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 6.6.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8493</link><description>The Events Calendar WordPress plugin before 6.6.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8542 | Everest Forms &amp;lt; 3.0.3.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8542</link><description>The Everest Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.0.3.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8617 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 6.5.9.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8617</link><description>The Quiz Maker WordPress plugin before 6.5.9.9 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8618 | Page Builder: Pagelayer &amp;lt; 1.9.0- Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8618</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer  WordPress plugin before 1.9.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8619 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt;= 4.12.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8619</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite  WordPress plugin before 4.12.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8620 | MapPress Maps for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.93 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Map Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8620</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin before 2.93 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8670 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.8.29 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8670</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.29 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8673 | Z-Downloads &amp;lt; 1.11.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8673</link><description>The Z-Downloads WordPress plugin before 1.11.7 does not properly validate uploaded files allowing for the uploading of SVGs containing malicious JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8699 | Z-Downloads &amp;lt; 1.11.5 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8699</link><description>The Z-Downloads WordPress plugin before 1.11.5 does not properly validate files uploaded, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8700 | Event Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Calendar Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8700</link><description>The Event Calendar WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not check for authorization on delete actions, allowing unauthenticated users to delete arbitrary calendars.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8701 | Event Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8701</link><description>The events-calendar WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8702 | Backup Database &amp;lt;= 4.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8702</link><description>The Backup Database WordPress plugin through 4.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8703 | Z-Downloads &amp;lt; 1.11.6 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8703</link><description>The Z-Downloads WordPress plugin before 1.11.6 does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputting them in the page, which could allow unauthenticated visitors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks when accessing share URLs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8759 | Nested Pages &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8759</link><description>The Nested Pages WordPress plugin before 3.2.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8851 | Polls CP &amp;lt;= 1.0.75 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8851</link><description>The Polls CP WordPress plugin before 1.0.77 does not sanitise and escape some of its poll settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multi site setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8854 | Polls CP &amp;lt;= 1.0.75 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Custom Styles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8854</link><description>The Polls CP WordPress plugin before 1.0.77 does not sanitise and escape some of its poll settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multi site setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9182 | Maspik - Advanced Spam protection &amp;lt; 2.1.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9182</link><description>The Maspik  WordPress plugin before 2.1.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9227 | PowerPress Podcasting &amp;lt; 11.9.18 - Author+ XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9227</link><description>The PowerPress Podcasting plugin by Blubrry WordPress plugin before 11.9.18 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings when adding a podcast, which could allow admin users to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9233 | GS Logo Slider &amp;lt; 3.7.1 - Settings Update via Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9233</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 3.7.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9236 | Team Members Showcase &amp;lt; 4.4.2 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9236</link><description>The Team  WordPress plugin before 4.4.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9238 | AVIF &amp;amp; SVG Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG Uplaod</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9238</link><description>The AVIF Uploader WordPress plugin before 1.1.1 does not sanitise uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9390 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt; 6.0.2.1 - Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9390</link><description>The RegistrationMagic  WordPress plugin before 6.0.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9450 | Free Booking Plugin for Hotels, Restaurants and Car Rentals – eaSYNC Booking &amp;lt; 1.3.15 - Subscriber+ PayPal Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9450</link><description>The Free Booking Plugin for Hotels, Restaurants and Car Rentals  WordPress plugin before 1.3.15 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in subscriber change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9599 | Popup Box &amp;lt; 4.7.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9599</link><description>The Popup Box  WordPress plugin before 4.7.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9645 | Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt; 2.2.93 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9645</link><description>The Post Grid, Posts Slider, Posts Carousel, Post Filter, Post Masonry WordPress plugin before 2.2.93 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9662 | CYAN Backup &amp;lt; 2.5.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS via General Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9662</link><description>The CYAN Backup WordPress plugin before 2.5.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9663 | CYAN Backup &amp;lt; 2.5.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Remote Storage Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9663</link><description>The CYAN Backup WordPress plugin before 2.5.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9709 | EKC Tournament Manager &amp;lt; 2.2.2 - Create Tournaments/Teams via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9709</link><description>The EKC Tournament Manager WordPress plugin before 2.2.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9711 | EKC Tournament Manager &amp;lt; 2.2.2 - Delete Tournaments via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9711</link><description>The EKC Tournament Manager WordPress plugin before 2.2.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9765 | EKC Tournament Manager  &amp;lt; 2.2.2 - Local File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9765</link><description>The EKC Tournament Manager WordPress plugin before 2.2.2 allows a logged in admin to download system files outside of the WordPress directory</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9831 | Taskbuilder &amp;lt; 3.0.9 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9831</link><description>The Taskbuilder  WordPress plugin before 3.0.9 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9838 | Auto Affiliate Links &amp;lt; 6.4.7 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9838</link><description>The Auto Affiliate Links WordPress plugin before 6.4.7 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9879 | Website File Changes  &amp;lt; 2.1.1 - Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9879</link><description>The Melapress File Monitor WordPress plugin before 2.1.1 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9882 | Salon Booking System &amp;lt; 10.9.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9882</link><description>The Salon Booking System, Appointment Scheduling for Salons, Spas &amp; Small Businesses WordPress plugin before 1.9.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0329 | AI ChatBot for WordPress – WPBot &amp;lt; 6.2.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0329</link><description>The AI ChatBot for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 6.2.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0687 | Spiritual Gifts Survey &amp;lt;= 0.9.10 - Unauthenticated CSRF to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0687</link><description>The Spiritual Gifts Survey (and optional S.H.A.P.E survey) WordPress plugin through 0.9.10 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against only unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0688 | Spiritual Gifts Survey &amp;lt;= 0.9.10 - Unauthenticated CSRF to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0688</link><description>The Spiritual Gifts Survey (and optional S.H.A.P.E survey) WordPress plugin through 0.9.10 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against only unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1033 | Badgearoo &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1033</link><description>The Badgearoo WordPress plugin through 1.0.14 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1286 | Download HTML TinyMCE Button &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1286</link><description>The Download HTML TinyMCE Button WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1288 | wooexim &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - CSRF to Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1288</link><description>The WOOEXIM  WordPress plugin through 5.0.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make an unauthenticated user vulnerable to reflected XSS via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1289 | Plugin Oficial – Getnet para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1289</link><description>The Plugin Oficial  WordPress plugin through 1.7.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1303 | Plugin Oficial – Getnet para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Unauthenticated Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1303</link><description>The Plugin Oficial  WordPress plugin through 1.7.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against only unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1454 | Ninja Pages &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1454</link><description>The Ninja Pages WordPress plugin through 1.4.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2203 | WooCommerce Checkout &amp;amp; Funnel Builder by FunnelKit &amp;lt; 3.10.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2203</link><description>The FunnelKit  WordPress plugin before 3.10.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2247 | WP-PManager &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Category Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2247</link><description>The WP-PManager WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2248 | WP-PManager &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2248</link><description>The WP-PManager WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47928 | Spotipy repo vulnerable to secrets exfiltration via `pull_request_target`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47928</link><description>Spotipy is a Python library for the Spotify Web API. As of commit 4f5759dbfb4506c7b6280572a4db1aabc1ac778d, using `pull_request_target` on `.github/workflows/integration_tests.yml` followed by the checking out the head.sha of a forked PR can be exploited by attackers, since untrusted code can be executed having full access to secrets (from the base repo). By exploiting the vulnerability is possible to exfiltrate `GITHUB_TOKEN` and secrets `SPOTIPY_CLIENT_ID`,  `SPOTIPY_CLIENT_SECRET`. In particular `GITHUB_TOKEN` which can be used to completely overtake the repo since the token has content write privileges. The `pull_request_target` in GitHub Actions is a major security concern—especially in public repositories—because it executes untrusted code from a PR, but with the context of the base repository, including access to its secrets. Commit 9dfb7177b8d7bb98a5a6014f8e6436812a47576f reverted the change that caused the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4717 | PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System visitors-form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4717</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Company Visitor Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /visitors-form.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47789 | Horilla Open Redirect Vulnerability in Login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47789</link><description>Horilla is a free and open source Human Resource Management System (HRMS). In versions up to and including 1.3, an attacker can craft a Horilla URL that refers to an external domain. Upon clicking and logging in, the user is redirected to an external domain. This allows the redirection to any arbitrary site, including phishing or malicious domains, which can be used to impersonate Horilla and trick users. Commit 1c72404df6888bb23af73c767fdaee5e6679ebd6 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46834 | Alchemy&amp;#x27;s Modular Account can use executeUserOp to bypass allowlist prevalidation hook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46834</link><description>Alchemy's Modular Account is a smart contract account that is compatible with ERC-4337 and ERC-6900. In versions on the 2.x branch prior to commit 5e6f540d249afcaeaf76ab95517d0359fde883b0, owners of Modular Accounts can grant session keys (scoped external keys) to external parties and would use the allowlist module to restrict which external contracts can be accessed by the session key. There is a bug in the allowlist module in that we don't check for the `executeUserOp` -&gt; `execute` or `executeBatch` path, effectively allowing any session key to bypass any access control restrictions set on the session key. Session keys are able to access ERC20 and ERC721 token contracts amongst others, transferring all tokens from the account out andonfigure the permissions on external modules on session keys. They would be able to remove all restrictions set on themselves this way, or rotate the keys of other keys with higher privileges into keys that they control. Commit 5e6f540d249afcaeaf76ab95517d0359fde883b0 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47788 | Missing Path Validation Enables Path Traversal in Controller.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47788</link><description>Atheos is a self-hosted browser-based cloud IDE. Prior to v602, similar to GHSA-rgjm-6p59-537v/CVE-2025-22152, the `$target` parameter in `/controller.php` was not properly validated, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary files on the server via path traversal. v602 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47786 | Emlog vulnerable to Stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47786</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. Version 2.5.13 has a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows any registered user to construct malicious JavaScript, inducing all website users to click. In `/admin/comment.php`, the parameter `perpage_num` is not validated and is directly stored in the `admin_commend_perpage_num` field of the `emlog_options` table in the database. Moreover, the output is not filtered, resulting in the direct output of malicious code. As of time of publication, it is unclear if a patch exists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4715 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System view_application.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4715</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/view_application.php. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4716 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System credit_transaction_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4716</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /pages/credit_transaction_add.php. The manipulation of the argument prod_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47785 | EMLOG SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47785</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. In versions up to and including 2.5.9, SQL injection occurs because the $origContent parameter in admin/article_save.php is not strictly filtered. Since admin/article_save.php can be accessed by ordinary registered users, this will cause SQL injection to occur when the registered site is enabled, resulting in the injection of the admin account and password, which is then exploited by the backend remote code execution. As of time of publication, it is unknown whether a fix exists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47787 | Emlog Pro Contains a File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47787</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. Emlog Pro prior to version 2.5.10 contains a file upload vulnerability. The store.php component contains a critical security flaw where it fails to properly validate the contents of remotely downloaded ZIP plugin files. This insufficient validation allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on the vulnerable system. Version 2.5.10 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47161 | Microsoft Defender for Endpoint Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47161</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47784 | Emlog vulnerable to Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47784</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. Versions 2.5.13 and prior have a deserialization vulnerability. A user who creates a carefully crafted nickname can cause `str_replace` to replace the value of `name_orig` with empty, causing deserialization to fail and return `false`. Commit 9643250802188b791419e3c2188577073256a8a2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26481 | Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions 9.4.0.0 through 9.9.0.0, contains an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. A remote unprivileged ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26481</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions 9.4.0.0 through 9.9.0.0, contains an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. A remote unprivileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4714 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System reprint.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4714</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/reprint.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30476 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, version 5.2, contains an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30476</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, version 5.2, contains an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30475 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.2, contains an improper privilege management vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30475</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.2, contains an improper privilege management vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4712 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System account_summary.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4712</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pages/account_summary.php. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4713 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4713</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/print.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51666 | WordPress Tours plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51666</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Tours.This issue affects Tours: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56006 | WordPress Jetpack Debug Tools plugin &amp;lt; 2.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56006</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Jetpack Debug Tools.This issue affects Jetpack Debug Tools: from n/a before 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32922 | WordPress WP2LEADS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32922</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tobias WP2LEADS allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP2LEADS: from n/a through 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4711 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System stockin_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4711</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/stockin_add.php. The manipulation of the argument prod_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44110 | FluxBB 1.5.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in via the Forum Description Field in admin_forums.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44110</link><description>FluxBB 1.5.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in via the Forum Description Field in admin_forums.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47774 | Vyper&amp;#x27;s `slice()` may elide side-effects when output length is 0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47774</link><description>Vyper is the Pythonic Programming Language for the Ethereum Virtual Machine. In versions up to and including 0.4.2rc1, the `slice()` builtin can elide side effects when the output length is 0, and the source bytestring is a builtin (`msg.data` or `&lt;address&gt;.code`). The reason is that for these source locations, the check that `length &gt;= 1` is skipped. The result is that a 0-length bytestring constructed with slice can be passed to `make_byte_array_copier`, which elides evaluation of its source argument when the max length is 0. The impact is that side effects in the `start` argument may be elided when the `length` argument is 0, e.g. `slice(msg.data, self.do_side_effect(), 0)`. The fix in pull request 4645 disallows any invocation of `slice()` with length 0, including for the ad hoc locations discussed in this advisory. The fix is expected to be part of version 0.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4709 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System transaction_del.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4709</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/transaction_del.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4710 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System transaction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4710</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /pages/transaction.php. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47285 | Vyper&amp;#x27;s `concat()` builtin may elide side-effects for zero-length arguments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47285</link><description>Vyper is the Pythonic Programming Language for the Ethereum Virtual Machine. In versions up to and including 0.4.2rc1, `concat()` may skip evaluation of side effects when the length of an argument is zero. This is due to a fastpath in the implementation which skips evaluation of argument expressions when their length is zero. In practice, it would be very unusual in user code to construct zero-length bytestrings using an expression with side-effects, since zero-length bytestrings are typically constructed with the empty literal `b""`; the only way to construct an empty bytestring which has side effects would be with the ternary operator introduced in v0.3.8, e.g. `b"" if self.do_some_side_effect() else b""`. The fix is available in pull request 4644 and expected to be part of the 0.4.2 release. As a workaround, don't have side effects in expressions which construct zero-length bytestrings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43853 | iwasm vulnerable to filesystem sandbox escape with symlink when using uvwasi feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43853</link><description>The WebAssembly Micro Runtime's (WAMR) iwasm package is the executable binary built with WAMR VMcore which supports WebAssembly System Interface (WASI) and command line interface. Anyone running WAMR up to and including version 2.2.0 or WAMR built with libc-uvwasi on Windows is affected by a symlink following vulnerability. On WAMR running in Windows, creating a symlink pointing outside of the preopened directory and subsequently opening it with create flag will create a file on host outside of the sandbox. If the symlink points to an existing host file, it's also possible to open it and read its content. Version 2.3.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47279 | undici Denial of Service attack via bad certificate data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47279</link><description>Undici is an HTTP/1.1 client for Node.js. Prior to versions 5.29.0, 6.21.2, and 7.5.0, applications that use undici to implement a webhook-like system are vulnerable. If the attacker set up a server with an invalid certificate, and they can force the application to call the webhook repeatedly, then they can cause a memory leak. This has been patched in versions 5.29.0, 6.21.2, and 7.5.0. As a workaound, avoid calling a webhook repeatedly if the webhook fails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47580 | WordPress Front End Users plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.32 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47580</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rustaurius Front End Users allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Front End Users: from n/a through 3.2.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4707 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System transaction_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/transaction_add.php. The manipulation of the argument prod_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4708 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System sales_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4708</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/sales_add.php. The manipulation of the argument discount leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1647 | XSS in Bootstrap title attribute for Tooltip and Popover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bootstrap allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Bootstrap: from 3.4.1 before 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30418 | Out of Bounds Write in CheckPins() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30418</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability due to an out of bounds write in CheckPins() when using the SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.0 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30419 | Out of Bounds Read in GetSymbolBorderRectSize() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30419</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability due to an out of bounds read in GetSymbolBorderRectSize() when using the SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.0 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30420 | Out of Bounds Read in Bitmap::InternalDraw() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30420</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability due to an out of bounds read in Bitmap::InternalDraw() when using the SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.0 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30421 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in DrObjectStorage::XML_Serialize() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30421</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability due to a stack-based buffer overflow in DrObjectStorage::XML_Serialize() when using the SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.0 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4706 | projectworlds Online Examination System Procedure3b_yearwiseVisit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Examination System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Procedure3b_yearwiseVisit.php. The manipulation of the argument Visit_year leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30417 | Out of Bounds Write in Library!DecodeBase64() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30417</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability in due to an out of bounds write in Library!DecodeBase64() when using the SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.0 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48050 | In DOMPurify through 3.2.5 before 6bc6d60, scripts/server.js does not ensure that a pathname is located under the current working directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48050</link><description>In DOMPurify through 3.2.5 before 6bc6d60, scripts/server.js does not ensure that a pathname is located under the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48051 | powertip.ts in Lila (for Lichess) before ab0beaf allows XSS in some applications because of an innerHTML usage pattern in which text is extr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48051</link><description>powertip.ts in Lila (for Lichess) before ab0beaf allows XSS in some applications because of an innerHTML usage pattern in which text is extracted from a DOM node and interpreted as HTML.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4705 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System view-incomingvehicle-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System 1.13. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-incomingvehicle-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52880 | An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52880</link><description>An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before version 05.46.50, kernel 5.5 before version 05.54.50, kernel 5.6 before version 05.61.50, and kernel 5.7 before version 05.70.50. In VariableRuntimeDxe driver, SecureBootHandler uses DataSize and VariableNameSize when determining if the data or name are in the buffer, but these are supplied by the caller and therefore cannot be trusted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52877 | An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52877</link><description>An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before version 05.46.50, kernel 5.5 before version 05.54.50, kernel 5.6 before version 05.61.50, and kernel 5.7 before version 05.70.50. In VariableRuntimeDxe driver, callback function SmmCreateVariableLockList () calls CreateVariableLockListInSmm (). In CreateVariableLockListInSmm (), it uses StrSize () to get variable name size and it could lead to a buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52879 | An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52879</link><description>An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before version 05.46.50, kernel 5.5 before version 05.54.50, kernel 5.6 before version 05.61.50, and kernel 5.7 before version 05.70.50. In VariableRuntimeDxe driver, SmmUpdateVariablePropertySmi () is a SMM callback function and it uses StrCmp () to compare variable names. This action may cause a buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3440 | IBM Security Guardium cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3440</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 11.5 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52878 | An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52878</link><description>An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O kernel 5.2 before version 05.29.50, kernel 5.3 before version 05.38.50, kernel 5.4 before version 05.46.50, kernel 5.5 before version 05.54.50, kernel 5.6 before version 05.61.50, and kernel 5.7 before version 05.70.50. In VariableRuntimeDxe driver, VariableServicesSetVariable () can be called by gRT_&gt;SetVariable () or the SmmSetSensitiveVariable () or SmmInternalSetVariable () from SMM. In VariableServicesSetVariable (), it uses StrSize () to get variable name size, uses StrLen () to get variable name length and uses StrCmp () to compare strings. These actions may cause a buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2527 | Improper access control to group information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2527</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.11 failed to properly verify a user's permissions when accessing groups, which allows an attacker to view group information via an API request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2570 | System Admin Cannot Access Environment settings in System Console While System Manager Can</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2570</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.11 fail to check `RestrictSystemAdmin` setting if user doesn't have access to `ExperimentalSettings` which allows a System Manager to access `ExperimentSettings` when `RestrictSystemAdmin` is true via System Console.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4703 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4703</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System 1.13 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4704 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System 1.13 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-category.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4702 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System add-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4702</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Parking Management System 1.13. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-category.php. The manipulation of the argument catename leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4701 | VITA-MLLM Freeze-Omni utils.py torch.load deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4701</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in VITA-MLLM Freeze-Omni up to 20250421. This issue affects the function torch.load of the file models/utils.py. The manipulation of the argument path leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44185 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in /admin/change_pass.php via the pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44185</link><description>SourceCodester Best Employee Management System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in /admin/change_pass.php via the password parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46053 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in WebERP v4.15.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands and extract sensitive data by injecting a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46053</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in WebERP v4.15.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands and extract sensitive data by injecting a crafted payload into the ReportID and ReplaceReportID parameters within a POST request to /reportwriter/admin/ReportCreator.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46052 | An error-based SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability in WebERP v4.15.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL command and extract sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46052</link><description>An error-based SQL Injection (SQLi) vulnerability in WebERP v4.15.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL command and extract sensitive data by injecting a crafted payload into the DEL form field in a POST request to /StockCounts.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4698 | PHPGurukul Directory Management System forget-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4698</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/forget-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4699 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System visitors-form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4699</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/visitors-form.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44180 | Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit-brand.php?bid={brandId}.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44180</link><description>Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /edit-brand.php?bid={brandId}.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44183 | Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/profile.php via the name, email, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44183</link><description>Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/profile.php via the name, email, and mobile parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44181 | Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/add-brand.php via the brandname param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44181</link><description>Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /admin/add-brand.php via the brandname parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44182 | Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the vehiclename, modelnumber, regnumber, ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44182</link><description>Phpgurukul Vehicle Record Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the vehiclename, modelnumber, regnumber, vehiclesubtype, chasisnum, enginenumber' in the /admin/edit-vehicle.php component. This allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4516 | Use-after-free in &amp;quot;unicode_escape&amp;quot; decoder with error handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4516</link><description>There is an issue in CPython when using `bytes.decode("unicode_escape", error="ignore|replace")`. If you are not using the "unicode_escape" encoding or an error handler your usage is not affected. To work-around this issue you may stop using the error= handler and instead wrap the bytes.decode() call in a try-except catching the DecodeError.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4696 | PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4696</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4697 | PHPGurukul Directory Management System edit-directory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4697</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-directory.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4695 | PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System add-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4695</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Cyber Cafe Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add-users.php. The manipulation of the argument uadd leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4762 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in eSignaViewer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4762</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the eSignaViewer component in eSigna product versions 1.0 to 1.5 on all platforms allow an unauthenticated attacker to access arbitrary files in the document system via manipulation of file paths and object identifiers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 11:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4564 | TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.18 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4564</link><description>The TicketBAI Facturas para WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation via the 'delpdf' action in all versions up to, and including, 3.18. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 11:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31947 | Repeated LDAP login failures can lock an LDAP account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31947</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.6.x &lt;= 10.6.1, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.2, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.4, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.11 fail to lockout LDAP users following repeated login failures, which allows attackers to lock external LDAP accounts through repeated login failures through Mattermost.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3446 | Members Without Guest Invite Permissions Can Add Guests to Teams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3446</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.6.x &lt;= 10.6.1, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.2, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.4, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.11 fail to check the correct permissions which allows authenticated users who only have permission to invite non-guest users to a team to add guest users to that team via the API to add a single user to a team.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32002 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in I-O DATA network attached hard di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32002</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in I-O DATA network attached hard disk 'HDL-T Series' firmware Ver.1.21 and earlier when 'Remote Link3 function' is enabled. If exploited, a remote unauthenticated attacker may execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32738 | Missing authentication for critical function issue exists in I-O DATA network attached hard disk 'HDL-T Series' firmware Ver.1.21 and earlie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32738</link><description>Missing authentication for critical function issue exists in I-O DATA network attached hard disk 'HDL-T Series' firmware Ver.1.21 and earlier. If exploited, a remote unauthenticated attacker may change the product settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4737 | Insufficient encryption vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.aivoiceassistant) may lead to the risk of sensitive informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4737</link><description>Insufficient encryption vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.aivoiceassistant) may lead to the risk of sensitive information leakage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27525 | Information Exposure vulnerability in JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27525</link><description>Information Exposure vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager on Windows.This issue affects JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager: from 12-00 before 12-00-08, from 11-10 through 11-10-08, from 11-00 through 11-00-05, from 10-50 through 10-50-06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27523 | XXE vulnerability in JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27523</link><description>XXE vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager on Windows.This issue affects JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager: from 12-00 before 12-00-08, from 11-10 through 11-10-08, from 11-00 through 11-00-05, from 10-50 through 10-50-06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27524 | Weak encryption vulnerability in JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27524</link><description>Weak encryption vulnerability in Hitachi JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager on Windows.This issue affects JP1/IT Desktop Management 2 - Smart Device Manager: from 12-00 before 12-00-08, from 11-10 through 11-10-08, from 11-00 through 11-00-05, from 10-50 through 10-50-06.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3742 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt; 2.5.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3742</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery WordPress plugin before 2.5.1 does not validate and escape some of its attributes before outputting them back in a page/post, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13914 | File Manager Advanced Shortcode &amp;lt;= Multiple Versions - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local JavaScript File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13914</link><description>The File Manager Advanced Shortcode WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 (file-manager-advanced-shortcode) and 2.5.6 (advanced-file-manager-pro-premium), via the 'file_manager_advanced' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary JavaScript files on the server. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. Sites currently using 2.5.4 (file-manager-advanced-shortcode) should be updated to 2.6.0 (advanced-file-manager-pro-premium).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48027 | The HttpAuth plugin in pGina.Fork through 3.9.9.12 allows authentication bypass when an adversary controls DNS resolution for pginaloginserv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48027</link><description>The HttpAuth plugin in pGina.Fork through 3.9.9.12 allows authentication bypass when an adversary controls DNS resolution for pginaloginserver.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3053 | UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.07 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3053</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.07 via the uip_process_form_input() function. This is due to the function taking user supplied inputs to execute arbitrary functions with arbitrary data, and does not have any sort of capability check. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48024 | In BlueWave Checkmate before 2.1, an authenticated regular user can access sensitive application secrets via the /api/v1/settings endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48024</link><description>In BlueWave Checkmate before 2.1, an authenticated regular user can access sensitive application secrets via the /api/v1/settings endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3917 | 百度站长SEO合集(支持百度/神马/Bing/头条推送) &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3917</link><description>The 百度站长SEO合集(支持百度/神马/Bing/头条推送) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the download_remote_image_to_media_library function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4126 | EG-Series &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4126</link><description>The EG-Series plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [series] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes in the shortcode_title function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers - with contributor-level access and above, on sites with the Classic Editor plugin activated - to inject arbitrary JavaScript code in the titletag attribute that will execute whenever a user access an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4589 | Bon Toolkit &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4589</link><description>The Bon Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bt-map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4591 | Weluka Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4591</link><description>The Weluka Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'weluka-map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4579 | WP Content Security Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via CSP-Report Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4579</link><description>The WP Content Security Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blocked-uri and effective-directive  parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>