<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-46773 | Permission management vulnerability in the PMS module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46773</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the PMS module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49247 | Permission verification vulnerability in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49247</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in distributed scenarios. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49248 | Vulnerability of unauthorized file access in the Settings app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49248</link><description>Vulnerability of unauthorized file access in the Settings app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6514 | The Bluetooth module of some Huawei Smart Screen products has an identity authentication bypass vulnerability. Successful exploitation of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6514</link><description>The Bluetooth module of some Huawei Smart Screen products has an identity authentication bypass vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow attackers to access restricted functions. 

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may allow attackers to access restricted functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6458 | Client side path traversal due to lack of route parameters validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6458</link><description>Mattermost webapp fails to validate route parameters in/&lt;TEAM_NAME&gt;/channels/&lt;CHANNEL_NAME&gt; allowing an attacker to perform a client-side path traversal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6459 | Public endpoint /metrics of Calls plugin reveals channel IDs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6459</link><description>Mattermost is grouping calls in the /metrics endpoint by id and reports that id in the response. Since this id is the channelID, the public /metrics endpoint is revealing channelIDs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48849 | Ruijie EG Series Routers version EG_3.0(1)B11P216 and before allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely execute arbitrary code due to inco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48849</link><description>Ruijie EG Series Routers version EG_3.0(1)B11P216 and before allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely execute arbitrary code due to incorrect filtering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49897 | An OS command injection vulnerability exists in AE1021PE firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier and AE1021 firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier. I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49897</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in AE1021PE firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier and AE1021 firmware version 2.0.9 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by an attacker who can log in to the product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2861 | Qemu: 9pfs: improper access control on special files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2861</link><description>A flaw was found in the 9p passthrough filesystem (9pfs) implementation in QEMU. The 9pfs server did not prohibit opening special files on the host side, potentially allowing a malicious client to escape from the exported 9p tree by creating and opening a device file in the shared folder.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22522 | This Template Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker, including one with anonymous access, to inject unsafe user input int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22522</link><description>This Template Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker, including one with anonymous access, to inject unsafe user input into a Confluence page. Using this approach, an attacker is able to achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) on an affected instance. Publicly accessible Confluence Data Center and Server versions as listed below are at risk and require immediate attention. See the advisory for additional details

Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22523 | This vulnerability, if exploited, allows an attacker to perform privileged RCE (Remote Code Execution) on machines with the Assets Discovery...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22523</link><description>This vulnerability, if exploited, allows an attacker to perform privileged RCE (Remote Code Execution) on machines with the Assets Discovery agent installed. The vulnerability exists between the Assets Discovery application (formerly known as Insight Discovery) and the Assets Discovery agent.

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22524 | Certain versions of the Atlassian Companion App for MacOS were affected by a remote code execution vulnerability. An attacker could utilize ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22524</link><description>Certain versions of the Atlassian Companion App for MacOS were affected by a remote code execution vulnerability. An attacker could utilize WebSockets to bypass Atlassian Companion’s blocklist and MacOS Gatekeeper to allow execution of code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26154 | Versions of the package pubnub before 7.4.0; all versions of the package com.pubnub:pubnub; versions of the package pubnub before 6.19.0; al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26154</link><description>Versions of the package pubnub before 7.4.0; all versions of the package com.pubnub:pubnub; versions of the package pubnub before 6.19.0; all versions of the package github.com/pubnub/go; versions of the package github.com/pubnub/go/v7 before 7.2.0; versions of the package pubnub before 7.3.0; versions of the package pubnub/pubnub before 6.1.0; versions of the package pubnub before 5.3.0; versions of the package pubnub before 0.4.0; versions of the package pubnub/c-core before 4.5.0; versions of the package com.pubnub:pubnub-kotlin before 7.7.0; versions of the package pubnub/swift before 6.2.0; versions of the package pubnub before 5.2.0; versions of the package pubnub before 4.3.0 are vulnerable to Insufficient Entropy via the getKey function, due to inefficient implementation of the AES-256-CBC cryptographic algorithm. The provided encrypt function is less secure when hex encoding and trimming are applied, leaving half of the bits in the key always the same for every encoded message or file.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs to invest resources in preparing the attack and brute-force the encryption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6527 | The Email Subscription Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP_REFERER header in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6527</link><description>The Email Subscription Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP_REFERER header in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41268 | Possible stack overflow due to insufficient input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41268</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Escargot allows stack overflow and segmentation fault. This issue affects Escargot: from 3.0.0 through 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40053 | HTML injection Vulnerability in Serv-U 15.4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40053</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Serv-U 15.4 that allows an authenticated actor to insert content on the file share function feature of Serv-U, which could be used maliciously.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-27795 | License forgery in Brocade Fabric OS (FOS) hardware platforms running any version of Brocade Fabric OS software, </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-27795</link><description>Brocade Fabric OS (FOS) hardware 
platforms running any version of Brocade Fabric OS software, which 
supports the license string format; contain cryptographic 
issues that could allow for the installation of forged or fraudulent 
license keys. This would allow attackers or a malicious party to forge a
 counterfeit license key that the Brocade Fabric OS platform would 
authenticate and activate as if it were a legitimate license key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48940 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /admin.php of DaiCuo v2.5.15 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48940</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /admin.php of DaiCuo v2.5.15 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6508 | Use after free in Media Stream in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6508</link><description>Use after free in Media Stream in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6509 | Use after free in Side Panel Search in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6509</link><description>Use after free in Side Panel Search in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI interaction to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI interaction. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6510 | Use after free in Media Capture in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6510</link><description>Use after free in Media Capture in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI interaction to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI interaction. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6511 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Autofill restrictions v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6511</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Autofill restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6512 | Inappropriate implementation in Web Browser UI in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially spoof the co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6512</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Web Browser UI in Google Chrome prior to 120.0.6099.62 allowed a remote attacker to potentially spoof the contents of an iframe dialog context menu via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28875 | A Stored XSS issue in shared files download terms in Filerun Update 20220202 allows attackers to inject JavaScript code that is executed whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28875</link><description>A Stored XSS issue in shared files download terms in Filerun Update 20220202 allows attackers to inject JavaScript code that is executed when a user follows the crafted share link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28876 | A Broken Access Control issue in comments to uploaded files in Filerun through Update 20220202 allows attackers to delete comments on files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28876</link><description>A Broken Access Control issue in comments to uploaded files in Filerun through Update 20220202 allows attackers to delete comments on files uploaded by other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48930 | xinhu xinhuoa 2.2.1 contains a File upload vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48930</link><description>xinhu xinhuoa 2.2.1 contains a File upload vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24547 | On Arista MOS configuration of a BGP password will cause the password to be logged in clear text.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24547</link><description>On affected platforms running Arista MOS, the configuration of a BGP password will cause the password to be logged in clear text that can be revealed in local logs or remote logging servers by authenticated users, as well as appear in clear text in the device’s running config.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49282 | Test code in published microsoft-graph package exposes phpinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49282</link><description>msgraph-sdk-php is the Microsoft Graph Library for PHP. The Microsoft Graph PHP SDK published packages which contained test code that enabled the use of the phpInfo() function from any application that could access and execute the file at vendor/microsoft/microsoft-graph/tests/GetPhpInfo.php.  The phpInfo function exposes system information. The vulnerability affects the GetPhpInfo.php script of the PHP SDK which contains a call to the phpinfo() function. This vulnerability requires a misconfiguration of the server to be present so it can be exploited. For example, making the PHP application’s /vendor directory web accessible. The combination of the vulnerability and the server misconfiguration would allow an attacker to craft an HTTP request that executes the phpinfo() method. The attacker would then be able to get access to system information like configuration, modules, and environment variables and later on use the compromised secrets to access additional data. This problem has been patched in versions 1.109.1 and 2.0.0-RC5. If an immediate deployment with the updated vendor package is not available, you can perform the following temporary workarounds: delete the `vendor/microsoft/microsoft-graph/tests/GetPhpInfo.php` file, remove access to the `/vendor` directory, or disable the phpinfo function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49283 | Test code in published microsoft-graph-core package exposes phpinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49283</link><description>microsoft-graph-core the Microsoft Graph Library for PHP. The Microsoft Graph Beta PHP SDK published packages which contained test code that enabled the use of the phpInfo() function from any application that could access and execute the file at `vendor/microsoft/microsoft-graph-core/tests/GetPhpInfo.php`. The phpInfo function exposes system information. The vulnerability affects the GetPhpInfo.php script of the PHP SDK which contains a call to the phpinfo() function. This vulnerability requires a misconfiguration of the server to be present so it can be exploited. For example, making the PHP application’s /vendor directory web accessible. The combination of the vulnerability and the server misconfiguration would allow an attacker to craft an HTTP request that executes the phpinfo() method. The attacker would then be able to get access to system information like configuration, modules, and environment variables and later on use the compromised secrets to access additional data. This problem has been patched in version 2.0.2. If an immediate deployment with the updated vendor package is not available, you can perform the following temporary workarounds: delete the `vendor/microsoft/microsoft-graph-core/tests/GetPhpInfo.php` file, remove access to the /vendor directory, or disable the phpinfo function</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46736 | Server-Side Request Forgery in espocrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46736</link><description>EspoCRM is an Open Source CRM (Customer Relationship Management) software. In affected versions there is Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability via the upload image from url api. Users who have access to `the /Attachment/fromImageUrl` endpoint can specify URL to point to an internal host. Even though there is check for content type, it can be bypassed by redirects in some cases. This SSRF can be leveraged to disclose internal information (in some cases), target internal hosts and bypass firewalls. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `c536cee63` which is included in release version 8.0.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49297 | Unsafe YAML deserialization in PyDrive2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49297</link><description>PyDrive2 is a wrapper library of google-api-python-client that simplifies many common Google Drive API V2 tasks. Unsafe YAML deserilization will result in arbitrary code execution. A maliciously crafted YAML file can cause arbitrary code execution if PyDrive2 is run in the same directory as it, or if it is loaded in via `LoadSettingsFile`. This is a deserilization attack that will affect any user who initializes GoogleAuth from this package while a malicious yaml file is present in the same directory. This vulnerability does not require the file to be directly loaded through the code, only present. This issue has been addressed in commit `c57355dc` which is included in release version `1.16.2`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5970 | Improper authentication in the SMA100 SSL-VPN virtual office portal allows a remote authenticated attacker to create an identical external d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5970</link><description>Improper authentication in the SMA100 SSL-VPN virtual office portal allows a remote authenticated attacker to create an identical external domain user using accent characters, resulting in an MFA bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44221 | Improper neutralization of special elements in the SMA100 SSL-VPN management interface allows a remote authenticated attacker with administr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44221</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements in the SMA100 SSL-VPN management interface allows a remote authenticated attacker with administrative privilege to inject arbitrary commands as a 'nobody' user, potentially leading to OS Command Injection Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6448 | Unitronics Vision Series PLCs and HMIs use default passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6448</link><description>Unitronics Vision Series PLCs and HMIs use default administrative passwords. An unauthenticated attacker with network access to a PLC or HMI can take administrative control of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46674 | Elasticsearch-hadoop Unsafe Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46674</link><description>An issue was identified that allowed the unsafe deserialization of java objects from hadoop or spark configuration properties that could have been modified by authenticated users. Elastic would like to thank Yakov Shafranovich, with Amazon Web Services for reporting this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45083 | HyperCloud: &amp;quot;admin&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;serveradmin&amp;quot; users can be deleted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45083</link><description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists in HyperCloud that will impact the ability for a user to authenticate against the management plane.

An authenticated admin-level user may be able to delete the "admin" or "serveradmin" users, which prevents authentication from subsequently succeeding.

This issue affects HyperCloud versions 1.0 to any release before 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45084 | Media caddy removal and reinsertion without reboot may cause data loss</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45084</link><description>An issue exists in SoftIron HyperCloud where drive caddy removal and reinsertion without a reboot may erroneously cause the system to recognize the caddy as new media and wipe all data on the drives due to a missing synchronization flaw, which impacts data availability and integrity.

This issue only impacts SoftIron HyperCloud "density" storage nodes running HyperCloud software versions 1.0 to before 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45085 | When compute hosts are disabled and reenabled, they immediately transition to &amp;quot;ON&amp;quot;, not &amp;quot;INIT&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45085</link><description>An issue exists in SoftIron HyperCloud where compute nodes may come online immediately without following the correct initialization process.  In this instance, workloads may be scheduled on these nodes and deploy to a failed or erroneous state, which impacts the availability of these workloads that may be deployed during this time window.

This issue impacts HyperCloud versions from 2.0.0 to before 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45287 | Before Go 1.20, the RSA based key exchange methods in crypto/tls may exhibit a timing side channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45287</link><description>Before Go 1.20, the RSA based TLS key exchanges used the math/big library, which is not constant time. RSA blinding was applied to prevent timing attacks, but analysis shows this may not have been fully effective. In particular it appears as if the removal of PKCS#1 padding may leak timing information, which in turn could be used to recover session key bits. In Go 1.20, the crypto/tls library switched to a fully constant time RSA implementation, which we do not believe exhibits any timing side channels.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44298 | Dell PowerEdge platforms 16G Intel E5 BIOS and Dell Precision BIOS, version 1.4.4, contain active debug code security vulnerability. An unau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44298</link><description>Dell PowerEdge platforms 16G Intel E5 BIOS and Dell Precision BIOS, version 1.4.4, contain active debug code security vulnerability. An unauthenticated physical attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information tampering, code execution, denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44297 | Dell PowerEdge platforms 16G Intel E5 BIOS and Dell Precision BIOS, version 1.4.4, contain active debug code security vulnerability. An unau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44297</link><description>Dell PowerEdge platforms 16G Intel E5 BIOS and Dell Precision BIOS, version 1.4.4, contain active debug code security vulnerability. An unauthenticated physical attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure, information tampering, code execution, denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6180 | Resource exhaustion via memory leak in tokio-boring</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6180</link><description>The tokio-boring library in version 4.0.0 is affected by a memory leak issue that can lead to excessive resource consumption and potential DoS by resource exhaustion. The set_ex_data function used by the library did not deallocate memory used by pre-existing data in memory each time after completing a TLS connection causing the program to consume more resources with each new connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49446 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/nav/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49446</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/nav/save.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49447 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/nav/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49447</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/nav/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49448 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via admin/nav/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49448</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via admin/nav/delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49396 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49396</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/save.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49397 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/updateStatus.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49397</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/updateStatus.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49398 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49398</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49395 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49395</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/category/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49380 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/friend_link/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49380</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/friend_link/delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49381 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/div/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49381</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/div/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49382 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/div/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49382</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/div/delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49383 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/tag/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49383</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/tag/save.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49375 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/friend_link/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49375</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/friend_link/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49377 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/tag/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49377</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/tag/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49378 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/form/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49378</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/form/save.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49379 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /admin/friend_link/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49379</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the component /admin/friend_link/save.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49372 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/slide/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49372</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/slide/save.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49373 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/slide/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49373</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via /admin/slide/delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49374 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/slide/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49374</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/slide/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49376 | JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/tag/delete.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49376</link><description>JFinalCMS v5.0.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/tag/delete.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6357 | OS Command Injection in multiple CODESYS products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6357</link><description>A low-privileged remote attacker could exploit the vulnerability and inject additional system commands via file system libraries which could give the attacker full control of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-24403 | De-anonymization attack in TETRA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24403</link><description>The TETRA TA61 identity encryption function internally uses a 64-bit value derived exclusively from the SCK (Class 2 networks) or CCK (Class 3 networks). The structure of TA61 allows for efficient recovery of this 64-bit value, allowing an adversary to encrypt or decrypt arbitrary identities given only three known encrypted/unencrypted identity pairs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43628 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the NTRIP Stream Parsing functionality of GPSd 3.25.1~dev. A specially crafted network packet ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43628</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the NTRIP Stream Parsing functionality of GPSd 3.25.1~dev. A specially crafted network packet can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43608 | A data integrity vulnerability exists in the BR_NO_CHECK_HASH_FOR functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and dev commit 622698d7847. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43608</link><description>A data integrity vulnerability exists in the BR_NO_CHECK_HASH_FOR functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and dev commit 622698d7847. A specially crafted man-in-the-middle attack can lead to arbitrary command execution in the builder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45838 | Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45838</link><description>Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622698d7847. A specially crafted man-in-the-middle attack can lead to arbitrary command execution in the builder.This vulnerability is related to the `aufs` package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45839 | Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45839</link><description>Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622698d7847. A specially crafted man-in-the-middle attack can lead to arbitrary command execution in the builder.This vulnerability is related to the `aufs-util` package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45840 | Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45840</link><description>Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622698d7847. A specially crafted man-in-the-middle attack can lead to arbitrary command execution in the builder.This vulnerability is related to the `riscv64-elf-toolchain` package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45841 | Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45841</link><description>Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622698d7847. A specially crafted man-in-the-middle attack can lead to arbitrary command execution in the builder.This vulnerability is related to the `versal-firmware` package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45842 | Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45842</link><description>Multiple data integrity vulnerabilities exist in the package hash checking functionality of Buildroot 2023.08.1 and Buildroot dev commit 622698d7847. A specially crafted man-in-the-middle attack can lead to arbitrary command execution in the builder.This vulnerability is related to the `mxsldr` package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41835 | Apache Struts: excessive disk usage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41835</link><description>When a Multipart request is performed but some of the fields exceed the maxStringLength  limit, the upload files will remain in struts.multipart.saveDir  even if the request has been denied.
Users are recommended to upgrade to versions Struts 2.5.32 or 6.1.2.2 or Struts 6.3.0.1 or greater, which fixe this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49070 | Pre-auth RCE in Apache Ofbiz 18.12.09 due to XML-RPC still present</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49070</link><description>Pre-auth RCE in Apache Ofbiz 18.12.09.

It's due to XML-RPC no longer maintained still present.
This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.10. 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.10</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6269 | Argument injection vulnerability in Atos Unify OpenScape Session Border Controller, Atos Unify OpenScape Branch and Atos Unify OpenScape BCF </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6269</link><description>An argument injection vulnerability has been identified in the 
administrative web interface of the Atos Unify OpenScape products "Session Border Controller" (SBC) and "Branch", before version V10 R3.4.0, and OpenScape "BCF" before versions V10R10.12.00 and V10R11.05.02. This allows an 
unauthenticated attacker to gain root access to the appliance via SSH (scope change) and also bypass authentication for the administrative interface and gain
 access as an arbitrary (administrative) user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5188 | WAGO Improper Input Validation in IEC61850 Server / Telecontrol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5188</link><description>The MMS Interpreter of WagoAppRTU in versions below 1.4.6.0 which is used by the WAGO Telecontrol Configurator is vulnerable to malformed packets. An remote unauthenticated attacker could send specifically crafted packets that lead to a denial-of-service condition until restart of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 07:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43472 | An issue in MLFlow versions 2.8.1 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to REST API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43472</link><description>An issue in MLFlow versions 2.8.1 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to REST API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37572 | Softing OPC Suite version 5.25 and before has Incorrect Access Control, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via weak permission...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37572</link><description>Softing OPC Suite version 5.25 and before has Incorrect Access Control, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via weak permissions in OSF_discovery service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39248 | Dell OS10 Networking Switches running 10.5.2.x and above contain an Uncontrolled Resource Consumption (Denial of Service) vulnerability, whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39248</link><description>Dell OS10 Networking Switches running 10.5.2.x and above contain an Uncontrolled Resource Consumption (Denial of Service) vulnerability, when switches are configured with VLT and VRRP. A remote unauthenticated user can cause the network to be flooded leading to Denial of Service for actual network users. This is a high severity vulnerability as it allows an attacker to cause an outage of network. Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44295 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.6.0.x contains an improper control of a resource through its lifetime vulnerability. A low ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44295</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.6.0.x contains an improper control of a resource through its lifetime vulnerability. A low privilege attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to loss of information, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 05:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47531 | An issue was discovered in Ericsson Evolved Packet Gateway (EPG) versions 3.x before 3.25 and 2.x before 2.16, allows authenticated users to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47531</link><description>An issue was discovered in Ericsson Evolved Packet Gateway (EPG) versions 3.x before 3.25 and 2.x before 2.16, allows authenticated users to bypass system CLI and execute commands they are authorized to execute directly in the UNIX shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44288 | Dell PowerScale OneFS, 8.2.2.x through 9.6.0.x, contains an improper control of a resource through its lifetime vulnerability. An unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44288</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS, 8.2.2.x through 9.6.0.x, contains an improper control of a resource through its lifetime vulnerability. An unauthenticated network attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47304 | An issue was discovered in Vonage Box Telephone Adapter VDV23 version VDV21-3.2.11-0.5.1, allows local attackers to bypass UART authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47304</link><description>An issue was discovered in Vonage Box Telephone Adapter VDV23 version VDV21-3.2.11-0.5.1, allows local attackers to bypass UART authentication controls and read/write arbitrary values to the memory of the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21634 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in Radio Interface Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21634</link><description>Memory Corruption in Radio Interface Layer while sending an SMS or writing an SMS to SIM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22383 | Use After Free in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22383</link><description>Memory Corruption in camera while installing a fd for a particular DMA buffer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22668 | Use After Free in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22668</link><description>Memory Corruption in Audio while invoking IOCTLs calls from the user-space.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28546 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in SPS Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28546</link><description>Memory Corruption in SPS Application while exporting public key in sorter TA.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28550 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in MPP Performance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28550</link><description>Memory corruption in MPP performance while accessing DSM watermark using external memory address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28551 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in UTILS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28551</link><description>Memory corruption in UTILS when modem processes memory specific Diag commands having arbitrary address values as input arguments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28579 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28579</link><description>Memory Corruption in WLAN Host while deserializing the input PMK bytes without checking the input PMK length.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28580 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28580</link><description>Memory corruption in WLAN Host while setting the PMK length in PMK length in internal cache.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28585 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28585</link><description>Memory corruption while loading an ELF segment in TEE Kernel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28586 | Improper Restriction of Operation within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28586</link><description>Information disclosure when the trusted application metadata symbol addresses are accessed while loading an ELF in TEE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28587 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in BT Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28587</link><description>Memory corruption in BT controller while parsing debug commands with specific sub-opcodes at HCI interface level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28588 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Bluetooth Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28588</link><description>Transient DOS in Bluetooth Host while rfc slot allocation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33017 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Boot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33017</link><description>Memory corruption in Boot while running a ListVars test in UEFI Menu during boot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33018 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in User Identity Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33018</link><description>Memory corruption while using the UIM diag command to get the operators name.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33022 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33022</link><description>Memory corruption in HLOS while invoking IOCTL calls from user-space.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33024 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Radio Interface Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33024</link><description>Memory corruption while sending SMS from AP firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33041 | Reachable assertion in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33041</link><description>Under certain scenarios the WLAN Firmware will reach an assertion due to state confusion while looking up peer ids.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33042 | Improper Input Validation in Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33042</link><description>Transient DOS in Modem after RRC Setup message is received.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33043 | Reachable Assertion in Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33043</link><description>Transient DOS in Modem when a Beam switch request is made with a non-configured BWP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33044 | Reachable Assertion in Data Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33044</link><description>Transient DOS in Data modem while handling TLB control messages from the Network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33053 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33053</link><description>Memory corruption in Kernel while parsing metadata.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33054 | Improper Authentication in GPS HLOS Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33054</link><description>Cryptographic issue in GPS HLOS Driver while downloading Qualcomm GNSS assistance data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33063 | Use After Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33063</link><description>Memory corruption in DSP Services during a remote call from HLOS to DSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33070 | Improper Authentication in Automotive OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33070</link><description>Transient DOS in Automotive OS due to improper authentication to the secure IO calls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33071 | Improper Access Control in Automotive OS Platform Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33071</link><description>Memory corruption in Automotive OS whenever untrusted apps try to access HAb for graphics functionalities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33079 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33079</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio while running invalid audio recording from ADSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33080 | Buffer over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33080</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing a vender specific IE (Information Element) of reassociation response management frame.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33081 | Buffer over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33081</link><description>Transient DOS while converting TWT (Target Wake Time) frame parameters in the OTA broadcast.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33082 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33082</link><description>Memory corruption while sending an Assoc Request having BTM Query or BTM Response containing MBO IE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33083 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33083</link><description>Memory corruption in WLAN Host while processing RRM beacon on the AP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33087 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33087</link><description>Memory corruption in Core while processing RX intent request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33088 | NULL pointer dereference in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33088</link><description>Memory corruption when processing cmd parameters while parsing vdev.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33089 | NULL Pointer Dereference in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33089</link><description>Transient DOS when processing a NULL buffer while parsing WLAN vdev.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33092 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Bluetooth HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33092</link><description>Memory corruption while processing pin reply in Bluetooth, when pin code received from APP layer is greater than expected size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33097 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33097</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware while processing a FTMR frame.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33098 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33098</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing WPA IES, when it is passed with length more than expected size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33106 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33106</link><description>Memory corruption while submitting a large list of sync points in an AUX command to the IOCTL_KGSL_GPU_AUX_COMMAND.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33107 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33107</link><description>Memory corruption in Graphics Linux while assigning shared virtual memory region during IOCTL call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42563 | Integer overflow vulnerability in landmarkCopyImageToNative of libFacePreProcessingjni.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42563</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in landmarkCopyImageToNative of libFacePreProcessingjni.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to trigger heap overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42556 | Improper usage of implicit intent in Contacts prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to get sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42556</link><description>Improper usage of implicit intent in Contacts prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42557 | Out-of-bound write vulnerability in libIfaaCa prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local system attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42557</link><description>Out-of-bound write vulnerability in libIfaaCa prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local system attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42558 | Out of bounds write vulnerability in HDCP in HAL prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to perform code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42558</link><description>Out of bounds write vulnerability in HDCP in HAL prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to perform code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42559 | Improper exception management vulnerability in Knox Guard prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows Knox Guard lock bypass via changing system ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42559</link><description>Improper exception management vulnerability in Knox Guard prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows Knox Guard lock bypass via changing system time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42560 | Heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability in dec_mono_audb of libsavsac.so prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows an attacker to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42560</link><description>Heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability in dec_mono_audb of libsavsac.so prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42561 | Heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42561</link><description>Heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability in bootloader prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42562 | Integer overflow vulnerability in detectionFindFaceSupportMultiInstance of libFacePreProcessingjni.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Dec-2023 R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42562</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in detectionFindFaceSupportMultiInstance of libFacePreProcessingjni.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to trigger heap overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42564 | Improper access control in knoxcustom service prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to send broadcast with system privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42564</link><description>Improper access control in knoxcustom service prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to send broadcast with system privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42565 | Improper input validation vulnerability in Smart Clip prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers with shell privilege to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42565</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in Smart Clip prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers with shell privilege to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42566 | Out-of-bound write vulnerability in libsavsvc prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42566</link><description>Out-of-bound write vulnerability in libsavsvc prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42567 | Improper size check vulnerability in softsimd prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows stack-based buffer overflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42567</link><description>Improper size check vulnerability in softsimd prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42568 | Improper access control vulnerability in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access arbitrary files wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42568</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SmartManagerCN prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to access arbitrary files with SystemUI privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42569 | Improper authorization verification vulnerability in AR Emoji prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to read sandbox data of AR Em...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42569</link><description>Improper authorization verification vulnerability in AR Emoji prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to read sandbox data of AR Emoji.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42570 | Improper access control vulnerability in KnoxCustomManagerService prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to access device SIM PIN.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42570</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in KnoxCustomManagerService prior to SMR Dec-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to access device SIM PIN.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42571 | Abuse of remote unlock in Find My Mobile prior to version 7.3.13.4 allows physical attacker to unlock the device remotely by resetting the S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42571</link><description>Abuse of remote unlock in Find My Mobile prior to version 7.3.13.4 allows physical attacker to unlock the device remotely by resetting the Samsung Account password with SMS verification when user lost the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42572 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Samsung Account Web SDK prior to version 1.5.24 allows attacker to get sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42572</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Samsung Account Web SDK prior to version 1.5.24 allows attacker to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42573 | PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in Search Widget prior to version 3.4 in China models allows local attackers to access data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42573</link><description>PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in Search Widget prior to version 3.4 in China models allows local attackers to access data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42574 | Improper access control vulnerablility in GameHomeCN prior to version 4.2.60.2 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity in GameHo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42574</link><description>Improper access control vulnerablility in GameHomeCN prior to version 4.2.60.2 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity in GameHomeCN.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42575 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Pass prior to version 4.3.00.17 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication due to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42575</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Pass prior to version 4.3.00.17 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication due to invalid flag setting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42576 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Pass prior to version 4.3.00.17 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication due to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42576</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Pass prior to version 4.3.00.17 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication due to invalid exception handler.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42577 | Improper Access Control in Samsung Voice Recorder prior to versions 21.4.15.01 in Android 12 and Android 13, 21.4.50.17 in Android 14 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42577</link><description>Improper Access Control in Samsung Voice Recorder prior to versions 21.4.15.01 in Android 12 and Android 13, 21.4.50.17 in Android 14 allows physical attackers to access Voice Recorder information on the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42578 | Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges vulnerability in Samsung Data Store prior to version 5.2.00.7 allows remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42578</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permissions or privileges vulnerability in Samsung Data Store prior to version 5.2.00.7 allows remote attackers to access location information without permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42579 | Improper usage of insecure protocol (i.e. HTTP) in SogouSDK of Chinese Samsung Keyboard prior to versions 5.3.70.1 in Android 11, 5.4.60.49,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42579</link><description>Improper usage of insecure protocol (i.e. HTTP) in SogouSDK of Chinese Samsung Keyboard prior to versions 5.3.70.1 in Android 11, 5.4.60.49, 5.4.85.5, 5.5.00.58 in Android 12, and 5.6.00.52, 5.6.10.42, 5.7.00.45 in Android 13 allows adjacent attackers to access keystroke data using Man-in-the-Middle attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42580 | Improper URL validation from MCSLaunch deeplink in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.64.4 allows attackers to execute JavaScript API to inst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42580</link><description>Improper URL validation from MCSLaunch deeplink in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.64.4 allows attackers to execute JavaScript API to install APK from Galaxy Store.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42581 | Improper URL validation from InstantPlay deeplink in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.64.4 allows attackers to execute JavaScript API to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42581</link><description>Improper URL validation from InstantPlay deeplink in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.64.4 allows attackers to execute JavaScript API to access data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48694 | Azure RTOS USBX Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48694</link><description>Azure RTOS USBX is a USB host, device, and on-the-go (OTG) embedded stack, that is fully integrated with Azure RTOS ThreadX. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to expired pointer dereference and type confusion vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS USBX. The affected components include functions/processes in host stack and host class, related to device linked classes, ASIX, Prolific, SWAR, audio, CDC ECM in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in USBX release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48695 | Azure RTOS USBX Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48695</link><description>Azure RTOS USBX is a USB host, device, and on-the-go (OTG) embedded stack, that is fully integrated with Azure RTOS ThreadX. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to out of bounds write vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS USBX. The affected components include functions/processes in host and device classes, related to CDC ECM and RNDIS in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in USBX release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48696 | Azure RTOS USBX Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48696</link><description>Azure RTOS USBX is a USB host, device, and on-the-go (OTG) embedded stack, that is fully integrated with Azure RTOS ThreadX. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to expired pointer dereference vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS USBX. The affected components include components in host class, related to CDC ACM in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in USBX release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48697 | Azure RTOS USBX Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48697</link><description>Azure RTOS USBX is a USB host, device, and on-the-go (OTG) embedded stack, that is fully integrated with Azure RTOS ThreadX. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to memory buffer and pointer vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS USBX. The affected components include functions/processes in pictbridge and host class, related to PIMA, storage, CDC ACM, ECM, audio, hub in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in USBX release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48698 | Azure RTOS USBX Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48698</link><description>Azure RTOS USBX is a USB host, device, and on-the-go (OTG) embedded stack, that is fully integrated with Azure RTOS ThreadX. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to expired pointer dereference vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS USBX. The affected components include functions/processes in host stack and host classes, related to device linked classes, GSER and HID in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in USBX release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48315 | Azure RTOS NetX Duo Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48315</link><description>Azure RTOS NetX Duo is a TCP/IP network stack designed specifically for deeply embedded real-time and IoT applications. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to memory overflow vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS NETX Duo. The affected components include processes/functions related to ftp and sntp in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in NetX Duo release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48316 | Azure RTOS NetX Duo Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48316</link><description>Azure RTOS NetX Duo is a TCP/IP network stack designed specifically for deeply embedded real-time and IoT applications. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to memory overflow vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS NETX Duo. The affected components include processes/functions related to snmp, smtp, ftp and dtls in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in NetX Duo release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48691 | Azure RTOS NetX Duo Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48691</link><description>Azure RTOS NetX Duo is a TCP/IP network stack designed specifically for deeply embedded real-time and IoT applications. An attacker can cause an out-of-bounds write in Azure RTOS NETX Duo, that could lead to remote code execution. The affected components include process related to IGMP protocol in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fix has been included in NetX Duo release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48692 | Azure RTOS NetX Duo Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48692</link><description>Azure RTOS NetX Duo is a TCP/IP network stack designed specifically for deeply embedded real-time and IoT applications. An attacker can cause remote code execution due to memory overflow vulnerabilities in Azure RTOS NETX Duo. The affected components include processes/functions related to icmp, tcp, snmp, dhcp, nat and ftp in RTOS v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in NetX Duo release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48693 | Azure RTOS ThreadX Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48693</link><description>Azure RTOS ThreadX is an advanced real-time operating system (RTOS) designed specifically for deeply embedded applications. An attacker can cause arbitrary read and write due to vulnerability in parameter checking mechanism in Azure RTOS ThreadX, which may lead to privilege escalation. The affected components include RTOS ThreadX v6.2.1 and below. The fixes have been included in ThreadX release 6.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49289 | Cross-site Scripting in Ajax.NET Professional</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49289</link><description>Ajax.NET Professional (AjaxPro) is an AJAX framework for Microsoft ASP.NET which will create proxy JavaScript classes that are used on client-side to invoke methods on the web server. Affected versions of this package are vulnerable cross site scripting attacks. Releases before version 21.12.22.1 are affected. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5808 | Information disclosure in HNAS back</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5808</link><description>Information disclosure in SMU in Hitachi Vantara HNAS 14.8.7825.01 on Windows allows authenticated users to download sensitive files via Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR).</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49284 | Command substitution output can trigger shell expansion in fish shell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49284</link><description>fish is a smart and user-friendly command line shell for macOS, Linux, and the rest of the family. fish shell uses certain Unicode non-characters internally for marking wildcards and expansions. It will incorrectly allow these markers to be read on command substitution output, rather than transforming them into a safe internal representation. While this may cause unexpected behavior with direct input (for example, echo \UFDD2HOME has the same output as echo $HOME), this may become a minor security problem if the output is being fed from an external program into a command substitution where this output may not be expected. This design flaw was introduced in very early versions of fish, predating the version control system, and is thought to be present in every version of fish released in the last 15 years or more, although with different characters. Code execution does not appear to be possible, but denial of service (through large brace expansion) or information disclosure (such as variable expansion) is potentially possible under certain circumstances. fish shell 3.6.2 has been released to correct this issue. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49290 | Malicious parameters can cause a denial of service in lestrrat-go/jwx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49290</link><description>lestrrat-go/jwx is a Go module implementing various JWx (JWA/JWE/JWK/JWS/JWT, otherwise known as JOSE) technologies. A p2c parameter set too high in JWE's algorithm PBES2-* could lead to a denial of service. The JWE key management algorithms based on PBKDF2 require a JOSE Header Parameter called p2c (PBES2 Count). This parameter dictates the number of PBKDF2 iterations needed to derive a CEK wrapping key. Its primary purpose is to intentionally slow down the key derivation function, making password brute-force and dictionary attacks more resource- intensive. Therefore, if an attacker sets the p2c parameter in JWE to a very large number, it can cause a lot of computational consumption, resulting in a denial of service. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `64f2a229b` which has been included in release version 1.2.27 and 2.0.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26942 | Weak encryption mechanisms in RFID Tags in Yale IA-210 Alarm v1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via physical proximity to the orig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26942</link><description>Weak encryption mechanisms in RFID Tags in Yale IA-210 Alarm v1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via physical proximity to the original.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26943 | Weak encryption mechanisms in RFID Tags in Yale Keyless Lock v1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via physical proximity to the orig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26943</link><description>Weak encryption mechanisms in RFID Tags in Yale Keyless Lock v1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via physical proximity to the original.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26941 | Weak encryption mechanisms in RFID Tags in Yale Conexis L1 v1.1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via physical proximity to the orig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26941</link><description>Weak encryption mechanisms in RFID Tags in Yale Conexis L1 v1.1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via physical proximity to the original.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49291 | Improper Sanitization of Branch Name Leads to Arbitrary Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49291</link><description>tj-actions/branch-names is a Github action to retrieve branch or tag names with support for all events. The `tj-actions/branch-names` GitHub Actions improperly references the `github.event.pull_request.head.ref` and `github.head_ref` context variables within a GitHub Actions `run` step. The head ref variable is the branch name and can be used to execute arbitrary code using a specially crafted branch name. As a result an attacker can use this vulnerability to steal secrets from or abuse `GITHUB_TOKEN` permissions. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 7.0.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46480 | Incorrect Session Management and Credential Re-use in the Bluetooth LE stack of the Ultraloq UL3 2nd Gen Smart Lock Firmware 02.27.0012 allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46480</link><description>Incorrect Session Management and Credential Re-use in the Bluetooth LE stack of the Ultraloq UL3 2nd Gen Smart Lock Firmware 02.27.0012 allows an attacker to sniff the unlock code and unlock the device whilst within Bluetooth range.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49292 | Possible private key restoration in go package github.com/ecies/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49292</link><description>ecies is an Elliptic Curve Integrated Encryption Scheme for secp256k1 in Golang. If funcations Encapsulate(), Decapsulate() and ECDH() could be called by an attacker, they could recover any private key that interacts with it. This vulnerability was patched in 2.0.8. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24051 | A client side rate limit issue discovered in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via brute fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24051</link><description>A client side rate limit issue discovered in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via brute force style attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24052 | An issue discovered in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain control of the device via the change password functiona...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24052</link><description>An issue discovered in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain control of the device via the change password functionality as it does not prompt for the current password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49293 | Cross-site Scripting in `server.transformIndexHtml` via URL payload in vite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49293</link><description>Vite is a website frontend framework. When Vite's HTML transformation is invoked manually via `server.transformIndexHtml`, the original request URL is passed in unmodified, and the `html` being transformed contains inline module scripts (`&lt;script type="module"&gt;...&lt;/script&gt;`), it is possible to inject arbitrary HTML into the transformed output by supplying a malicious URL query string to `server.transformIndexHtml`. Only apps using `appType: 'custom'` and using the default Vite HTML middleware are affected. The HTML entry must also contain an inline script. The attack requires a user to click on a malicious URL while running the dev server. Restricted files aren't exposed to the attacker. This issue has been addressed in vite@5.0.5, vite@4.5.1, and vite@4.4.12. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5944 | Delta Electronics DOPSoft Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5944</link><description>Delta Electronics DOPSoft is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, which may allow for arbitrary code execution if an attacker can lead a legitimate user to execute a specially crafted file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40463 | Use of Hard-Coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40463</link><description>When configured in
debugging mode by an authenticated user with



administrative
privileges, ALEOS 4.16 and earlier store the SHA512



hash of the common
root password for that version in a directory



accessible to a user
with root privileges or equivalent access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40464 | Use of hardcoded certificate and private key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40464</link><description>Several versions of
ALEOS, including ALEOS 4.16.0, use a hardcoded



SSL certificate and
private key. An attacker with access to these items



could potentially
perform a man in the middle attack between the



ACEManager client
and ACEManager server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40465 | Improper input leads to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40465</link><description>Several versions of
ALEOS, including ALEOS 4.16.0, include an opensource



third-party
component which can be exploited from the local



area network,
resulting in a Denial of Service condition for the captive portal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49285 | Denial of Service in HTTP Message Processing in Squid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49285</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to a Buffer Overread bug Squid is vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against Squid HTTP Message processing. This bug is fixed by Squid version 6.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24049 | An issue was discovered on Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges on the device via poor credent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24049</link><description>An issue was discovered on Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges on the device via poor credential management.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24050 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24050</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted string when setting the Wi-Fi password in the admin panel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40461 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in ACEManager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40461</link><description>The ACEManager
component of ALEOS 4.16 and earlier allows an



authenticated user
with Administrator privileges to access a file



upload field which
does not fully validate the file name, creating a



Stored Cross-Site
Scripting condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40462 | Improper input leads to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40462</link><description>The ACEManager
component of ALEOS 4.16 and earlier does not



perform input
sanitization during authentication, which could



potentially result
in a Denial of Service (DoS) condition for



ACEManager without
impairing other router functions. ACEManager



recovers from the
DoS condition by restarting within ten seconds of



becoming
unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49286 | Denial of Service in Helper Process management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49286</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to an Incorrect Check of Function Return Value bug Squid is vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against its Helper process management. This bug is fixed by Squid version 6.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40459 | Improper input leads to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40459</link><description>The
ACEManager component of ALEOS 4.16 and earlier does not adequately perform
input sanitization during authentication, which could potentially result in a
Denial of Service (DoS) condition for ACEManager without impairing other router
functions. ACEManager recovers from the DoS condition by restarting within ten
seconds of becoming unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40460 | Improper input leads to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40460</link><description>The ACEManager
component of ALEOS 4.16 and earlier does not



validate uploaded
file names and types, which could potentially allow



an authenticated
user to perform client-side script execution within



ACEManager, altering
the device functionality until the device is



restarted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49288 | Denial of Service in HTTP Collapsed Forwarding in Squid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49288</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Affected versions of squid are subject to a a Use-After-Free bug which can lead to a Denial of Service attack via collapsed forwarding. All versions of Squid from 3.5 up to and including 5.9 configured with "collapsed_forwarding on" are vulnerable. Configurations with "collapsed_forwarding off" or without a "collapsed_forwarding" directive are not vulnerable. This bug is fixed by Squid version 6.0.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should remove all collapsed_forwarding lines from their squid.conf.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21162 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21162</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21163 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21163</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21164 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21164</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21166 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21166</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21215 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21215</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21216 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21216</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21217 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21217</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21218 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21218</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21227 | There is information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21227</link><description>There is information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21228 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21228</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21263 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21263</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21401 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21401</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21402 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21402</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21403 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21403</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24048 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain control of the device via c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24048</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain control of the device via crafted GET request to /man_password.htm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35668 | In visitUris of Notification.java, there is a possible way to display images from another user due to a confused deputy. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35668</link><description>In visitUris of Notification.java, there is a possible way to display images from another user due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35690 | There is elevation of privilege.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35690</link><description>There is elevation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40073 | In visitUris of Notification.java, there is a possible cross-user media read due to Confused Deputy. This could lead to local information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40073</link><description>In visitUris of Notification.java, there is a possible cross-user media read due to Confused Deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40074 | In saveToXml of PersistableBundle.java, invalid data could lead to local persistent denial of service with no additional execution privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40074</link><description>In saveToXml of PersistableBundle.java, invalid data could lead to local persistent denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40075 | In forceReplaceShortcutInner of ShortcutPackage.java, there is a possible way to register unlimited packages due to a missing bounds check. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40075</link><description>In forceReplaceShortcutInner of ShortcutPackage.java, there is a possible way to register unlimited packages due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service which results in a boot loop with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40076 | In createPendingIntent of CredentialManagerUi.java, there is a possible way to access credentials from other users due to a permissions bypa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40076</link><description>In createPendingIntent of CredentialManagerUi.java, there is a possible way to access credentials from other users due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40077 | In multiple functions of MetaDataBase.cpp, there is a possible UAF write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40077</link><description>In multiple functions of MetaDataBase.cpp, there is a possible UAF write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40078 | In a2dp_vendor_opus_decoder_decode_packet of a2dp_vendor_opus_decoder.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40078</link><description>In a2dp_vendor_opus_decoder_decode_packet of a2dp_vendor_opus_decoder.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40079 | In injectSendIntentSender of ShortcutService.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a permissions bypass. This could le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40079</link><description>In injectSendIntentSender of ShortcutService.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40080 | In multiple functions of btm_ble_gap.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40080</link><description>In multiple functions of btm_ble_gap.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40081 | In loadMediaDataInBgForResumption of MediaDataManager.kt, there is a possible way to view another user's images  due to a confused deputy. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40081</link><description>In loadMediaDataInBgForResumption of MediaDataManager.kt, there is a possible way to view another user's images  due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40082 | In modify_for_next_stage of fdt.rs, there is a possible way to render KASLR ineffective due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40082</link><description>In modify_for_next_stage of fdt.rs, there is a possible way to render KASLR ineffective due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40083 | In parse_gap_data of utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40083</link><description>In parse_gap_data of utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40084 | In run of MDnsSdListener.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40084</link><description>In run of MDnsSdListener.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40087 | In transcodeQ*ToFloat of btif_avrcp_audio_track.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40087</link><description>In transcodeQ*ToFloat of btif_avrcp_audio_track.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to paired device escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40088 | In callback_thread_event of com_android_bluetooth_btservice_AdapterService.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after fre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40088</link><description>In callback_thread_event of com_android_bluetooth_btservice_AdapterService.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40089 | In getCredentialManagerPolicy of DevicePolicyManagerService.java, there is a possible method for users to select credential managers without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40089</link><description>In getCredentialManagerPolicy of DevicePolicyManagerService.java, there is a possible method for users to select credential managers without permission due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40090 | In BTM_BleVerifySignature of btm_ble.cc, there is a possible way to bypass signature validation due to side channel information disclosure. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40090</link><description>In BTM_BleVerifySignature of btm_ble.cc, there is a possible way to bypass signature validation due to side channel information disclosure. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40091 | In onTransact of IncidentService.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40091</link><description>In onTransact of IncidentService.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40092 | In verifyShortcutInfoPackage of ShortcutService.java, there is a possible way to see another user's image due to a confused deputy. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40092</link><description>In verifyShortcutInfoPackage of ShortcutService.java, there is a possible way to see another user's image due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40094 | In keyguardGoingAway of ActivityTaskManagerService.java, there is a possible lock screen bypass due to a missing permission check. This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40094</link><description>In keyguardGoingAway of ActivityTaskManagerService.java, there is a possible lock screen bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40095 | In createDontSendToRestrictedAppsBundle of PendingIntentUtils.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a missing check. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40095</link><description>In createDontSendToRestrictedAppsBundle of PendingIntentUtils.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a missing check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40096 | In OpRecordAudioMonitor::onFirstRef of AudioRecordClient.cpp, there is a possible way to record audio from the background due to a missing f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40096</link><description>In OpRecordAudioMonitor::onFirstRef of AudioRecordClient.cpp, there is a possible way to record audio from the background due to a missing flag. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40097 | In hasPermissionForActivity of PackageManagerHelper.java, there is a possible URI grant due to improper input validation. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40097</link><description>In hasPermissionForActivity of PackageManagerHelper.java, there is a possible URI grant due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40098 | In mOnDone of NotificationConversationInfo.java, there is a possible way to access app notification data of another user due to a logic erro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40098</link><description>In mOnDone of NotificationConversationInfo.java, there is a possible way to access app notification data of another user due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40103 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a double free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40103</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to corrupt memory due to a double free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45773 | In multiple functions of btm_ble_gap.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45773</link><description>In multiple functions of btm_ble_gap.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45774 | In fixUpIncomingShortcutInfo of ShortcutService.java, there is a possible way to view another user's image due to a confused deputy. This co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45774</link><description>In fixUpIncomingShortcutInfo of ShortcutService.java, there is a possible way to view another user's image due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45775 | In CreateAudioBroadcast of broadcaster.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45775</link><description>In CreateAudioBroadcast of broadcaster.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45776 | In CreateAudioBroadcast of broadcaster.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45776</link><description>In CreateAudioBroadcast of broadcaster.cc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45777 | In checkKeyIntentParceledCorrectly of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities using system privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45777</link><description>In checkKeyIntentParceledCorrectly of AccountManagerService.java, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activities using system privileges due to Parcel Mismatch. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45779 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible malicious update to platform components due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45779</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible malicious update to platform components due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45781 | In parse_gap_data of utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45781</link><description>In parse_gap_data of utils.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24047 | An Insecure Credential Management issue discovered in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24047</link><description>An Insecure Credential Management issue discovered in Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via use of weak hashing algorithm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49280 | Data leak of password hash through xwiki change request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49280</link><description>XWiki Change Request is an XWiki application allowing to request changes on a wiki without publishing directly the changes. Change request allows to edit any page by default, and the changes are then exported in an XML file that anyone can download. So it's possible for an attacker to obtain password hash of users by performing an edit on the user profiles and then downloading the XML file that has been created. This is also true for any document that might contain password field and that a user can view.
This vulnerability impacts all version of Change Request, but the impact depends on the rights that has been set on the wiki since it requires for the user to have the Change request right (allowed by default) and view rights on the page to target. This issue cannot be easily exploited in an automated way. The patch consists in denying to users the right of editing pages that contains a password field with change request. It means that already existing change request for those pages won't be removed by the patch, administrators needs to take care of it. The patch is provided in Change Request 1.10, administrators should upgrade immediately. It's possible to workaround the vulnerability by denying manually the Change request right on some spaces, such as XWiki space which will include any user profile by default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24046 | An issue was discovered on Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via use of a crafted string in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24046</link><description>An issue was discovered on Connectize AC21000 G6 641.139.1.1256 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via use of a crafted string in the ping utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4460 | Uploading SVG, WEBP and ICO files &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4460</link><description>The Uploading SVG, WEBP and ICO files WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 does not sanitise uploaded SVG files, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to upload a malicious SVG containing XSS payloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5105 | Frontend File Manager &amp;lt; 22.6 - Editor+ Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5105</link><description>The Frontend File Manager Plugin WordPress plugin before 22.6 has a vulnerability that allows an Editor+ user to bypass the file download logic and download files such as `wp-config.php`</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5108 | Easy Newsletter Signups &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5108</link><description>The Easy Newsletter Signups WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5137 | Simply Excerpts &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5137</link><description>The Simply Excerpts WordPress plugin through 1.4 does not sanitize and escape some fields in the plugin settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as an administrator to inject arbitrary web scripts even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in a multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5141 | BSK Contact Form 7 Blacklist &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5141</link><description>The BSK Contact Form 7 Blacklist WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not sanitise and escape the inserted_count parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5210 | AMP+ Plus &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5210</link><description>The AMP+ Plus WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5762 | Filr – Secure document library &amp;lt; 1.2.3.6 - Author+ RCE via file upload with phar ext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5762</link><description>The Filr WordPress plugin before 1.2.3.6 is vulnerable from an RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, which allows the operating system to execute commands and fully compromise the server on behalf of a user with Author-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5809 | Popup box &amp;lt; 3.8.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Categories</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5809</link><description>The Popup box WordPress plugin before 3.8.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5874 | Popup box &amp;lt; 3.8.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Popup Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5874</link><description>The Popup box WordPress plugin before 3.8.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5884 | Word Balloon &amp;lt; 4.20.3 - Avatar Removal via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5884</link><description>The Word Balloon WordPress plugin before 4.20.3 does not protect some of its actions against CSRF attacks, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to trick a logged in user to delete arbitrary avatars by clicking a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5951 | Welcart e-Commerce &amp;lt; 2.9.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5951</link><description>The Welcart e-Commerce WordPress plugin before 2.9.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5952 | Welcart e-Commerce &amp;lt; 2.9.5 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5952</link><description>The Welcart e-Commerce WordPress plugin before 2.9.5 unserializes user input from cookies, which could allow unautehtniacted users to perform PHP Object Injection when a suitable gadget is present on the blog</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5953 | Welcart e-Commerce &amp;lt; 2.9.5 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5953</link><description>The Welcart e-Commerce WordPress plugin before 2.9.5 does not validate files to be uploaded, as well as does not have authorisation and CSRF in an AJAX action handling such upload. As a result, any authenticated users, such as subscriber could upload arbitrary files, such as PHP on the server</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5990 | Funnelforms Free &amp;lt; 3.4.2 - Form Deletion/Duplication via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5990</link><description>The Interactive Contact Form and Multi Step Form Builder with Drag &amp; Drop Editor WordPress plugin before 3.4.2 does not have CSRF checks on some of its form actions such as deletion and duplication, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin perform such actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6063 | WP Fastest Cache &amp;lt; 1.2.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6063</link><description>The WP Fastest Cache WordPress plugin before 1.2.2 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5979 | eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt; 3.3.26 - Products Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5979</link><description>The eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress plugin before 3.3.26 does not have CSRF checks in some of its admin pages, which could allow attackers to make logged-in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks, such as delete all products</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49080 | Jupyter Server errors include tracebacks with path information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49080</link><description>The Jupyter Server provides the backend (i.e. the core services, APIs, and REST endpoints) for Jupyter web applications like Jupyter notebook, JupyterLab, and Voila. Unhandled errors in API requests coming from an authenticated user include traceback information, which can include path information. There is no known mechanism by which to trigger these errors without authentication, so the paths revealed are not considered particularly sensitive, given that the requesting user has arbitrary execution permissions already in the same environment. A fix has been introduced in commit `0056c3aa52` which no longer includes traceback information in JSON error responses. For compatibility, the traceback field is present, but always empty. This commit has been included in version 2.11.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47633 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in Traefik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47633</link><description>Traefik is an open source HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. The traefik docker container uses 100% CPU when it serves as its own backend, which is an automatically generated route resulting from the Docker integration in the default configuration. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.10.6 and 3.0.0-beta5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47106 | Incorrect processing of fragment in the URL leads to Authorization Bypass in Traefik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47106</link><description>Traefik is an open source HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. When a request is sent to Traefik with a URL fragment, Traefik automatically URL encodes and forwards the fragment to the backend server. This violates RFC 7230 because in the origin-form the URL should only contain the absolute path and the query. When this is combined with another frontend proxy like Nginx, it can be used to bypass frontend proxy URI-based access control restrictions. This vulnerability has been addressed in versions 2.10.6 and 3.0.0-beta5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47124 | Denial of service whith ACME HTTPChallenge in Traefik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47124</link><description>Traefik is an open source HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. When Traefik is configured to use the `HTTPChallenge` to generate and renew the Let's Encrypt TLS certificates, the delay authorized to solve the challenge (50 seconds) can be exploited by attackers to achieve a `slowloris attack`. This vulnerability has been patch in version 2.10.6 and 3.0.0-beta5. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should replace the `HTTPChallenge` with the `TLSChallenge` or the `DNSChallenge`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48910 | Microcks up to 1.17.1 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component /jobs and /artifact/download. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48910</link><description>Microcks up to 1.17.1 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component /jobs and /artifact/download. This vulnerability allows attackers to access network resources and sensitive information via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48967 | Ssolon &lt;= 2.6.0 and &lt;=2.5.12 is vulnerable to Deserialization of Untrusted Data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48967</link><description>Ssolon &lt;= 2.6.0 and &lt;=2.5.12 is vulnerable to Deserialization of Untrusted Data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48965 | An issue in the component /admin/api.plugs/script of ThinkAdmin v6.1.53 allows attackers to getshell via providing a crafted URL to download...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48965</link><description>An issue in the component /admin/api.plugs/script of ThinkAdmin v6.1.53 allows attackers to getshell via providing a crafted URL to download a malicious PHP file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48966 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /admin/api.upload/file of ThinkAdmin v6.1.53 allows attackers to execute arbitrary c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48966</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /admin/api.upload/file of ThinkAdmin v6.1.53 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted Zip file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48866 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the recipe preparation component within /api/objects/recipes and note component within /api/ob...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48866</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the recipe preparation component within /api/objects/recipes and note component within /api/objects/shopping_lists/ of Grocy &lt;= 4.0.3 allows attackers to obtain the victim's cookies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 15:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5768 | A vulnerability exists in the HCI IEC 60870-5-104 that affects the RTU500 series product versions listed below. 
Incomplete or wrong receive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5768</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the HCI IEC 60870-5-104 that affects the RTU500 series product versions listed below. 
Incomplete or wrong received APDU frame layout may 
cause blocking on link layer. Error reason was an endless blocking when reading incoming frames on link layer 
with wrong length information of APDU or delayed reception 
of data octets.


Only communication link of affected HCI IEC 60870-5-104 
is blocked. If attack sequence stops the communication to 
the previously attacked link gets normal again.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5768 | A vulnerability exists in the HCI IEC 60870-5-104 that affects the RTU500 series product versions listed below. 
Incomplete or wrong receive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5768</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the HCI IEC 60870-5-104 that affects the RTU500 series product versions listed below. 
Incomplete or wrong received APDU frame layout may 
cause blocking on link layer. Error reason was an endless blocking when reading incoming frames on link layer 
with wrong length information of APDU or delayed reception 
of data octets.


Only communication link of affected HCI IEC 60870-5-104 
is blocked. If attack sequence stops the communication to 
the previously attacked link gets normal again.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5767 | A vulnerability exists in the webserver that affects the 
RTU500 series product versions listed below. A malicious 
actor could perform cros...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5767</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the webserver that affects the 
RTU500 series product versions listed below. A malicious 
actor could perform cross-site scripting on the webserver 
due to an RDT language file being improperly sanitized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48815 | kkFileView v4.3.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48815</link><description>kkFileView v4.3.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41613 | EzViz Studio v2.2.0 is vulnerable to DLL hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41613</link><description>EzViz Studio v2.2.0 is vulnerable to DLL hijacking.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 13:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48863 | SEMCMS 3.9 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. Due to the lack of security checks on the input of the application, the attacker uses the existin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48863</link><description>SEMCMS 3.9 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. Due to the lack of security checks on the input of the application, the attacker uses the existing application to inject malicious SQL commands into the background database engine for execution, and sends some attack codes as commands or query statements to the interpreter. These malicious data can deceive the interpreter, so as to execute unplanned commands or unauthorized access to data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 13:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6460 | Information leak in nodejs-firestore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6460</link><description>A potential logging of the firestore key via logging within nodejs-firestore exists - Developers who were logging objects through this._settings would be logging the firestore key as well potentially exposing it to anyone with logs read access. We recommend upgrading to version 6.1.0 to avoid this issue</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 12:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48799 | TOTOLINK-X6000R Firmware-V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 is vulnerable to Command Execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48799</link><description>TOTOLINK-X6000R Firmware-V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 is vulnerable to Command Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 12:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48800 | In TOTOLINK X6000R_Firmware V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file sub_417338 function obtains fields from the front-end, connects them thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48800</link><description>In TOTOLINK X6000R_Firmware V9.4.0cu.852_B20230719, the shttpd file sub_417338 function obtains fields from the front-end, connects them through the snprintf function, and passes them to the CsteSystem function, resulting in a command execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 12:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32804 | Mali GPU Userspace Driver can make an Out-of-Bounds access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32804</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Arm Ltd Midgard GPU Userspace Driver, Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Userspace Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Userspace Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Userspace Driver allows a local non-privileged user to write a constant pattern to a limited amount of memory not allocated by the user space driver.This issue affects Midgard GPU Userspace Driver: from r0p0 through r32p0; Bifrost GPU Userspace Driver: from r0p0 through r44p0; Valhall GPU Userspace Driver: from r19p0 through r44p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Userspace Driver: from r41p0 through r44p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44302 | Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 and prior contain an improper authentication vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44302</link><description>Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 and prior contain an improper authentication vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain access of resources or functionality that could possibly lead to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44301 | Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 and prior contain a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. A network attacker with low privileges could potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44301</link><description>Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 and prior contain a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. A network attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44300 | Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0, contain a Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in PPOE. A local attacker with privileges could potentially exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44300</link><description>Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0, contain a Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in PPOE. A local attacker with privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44306 | Dell DM5500 contains a path traversal vulnerability in PPOE Component. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44306</link><description>Dell DM5500 contains a path traversal vulnerability in PPOE Component. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to overwrite the files stored on the server filesystem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6481 | Logback &amp;quot;receiver&amp;quot; DOS vulnerability CVE-2023-6378 incomplete fix</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6481</link><description>A serialization vulnerability in logback receiver component part of 
logback version 1.4.13, 1.3.13 and 1.2.12 allows an attacker to mount a Denial-Of-Service 
attack by sending poisoned data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44305 | Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0, contains a Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in PPOE. An unauthenticated remote attacker may exploit this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44305</link><description>Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0, contains a Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in PPOE. An unauthenticated remote attacker may exploit this vulnerability to crash the affected process or execute arbitrary code on the system by sending specially crafted input dat</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44291 | Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 contains an OS command injection vulnerability in PPOE component. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44291</link><description>Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 contains an OS command injection vulnerability in PPOE component. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to a system take over by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44304 | Dell DM5500 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability in PPOE Component. A remote attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44304</link><description>Dell DM5500 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability in PPOE Component. A remote attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to escape the restricted shell and gain root access to the appliance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5332 | Configuration in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5332</link><description>Patch in third party library Consul requires 'enable-script-checks' to be set to False. This was required to enable a patch by the vendor. Without this setting the patch could be bypassed. This only affects GitLab-EE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 06:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49287 | Buffer overflow vulnerabilities in tinydir</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49287</link><description>TinyDir is a lightweight C directory and file reader. Buffer overflows in the `tinydir_file_open()` function. This vulnerability has been patched in version 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49108 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in RakRak Document Plus Ver.3.2.0.0 to Ver.6.4.0.7 (excluding Ver.6.1.1.3a). If this vulnerability is ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49108</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in RakRak Document Plus Ver.3.2.0.0 to Ver.6.4.0.7 (excluding Ver.6.1.1.3a). If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary files on the server may be obtained or deleted by a user of the product with specific privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49093 | HtmlUnit vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via XSTL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49093</link><description>HtmlUnit is a GUI-less browser for Java programs. HtmlUnit is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via XSTL, when browsing the attacker’s webpage. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.9.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 04:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32841 | In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32841</link><description>In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving malformed RRC messages, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01128524; Issue ID: MOLY01128524 (MSV-846).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32842 | In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32842</link><description>In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving malformed RRC messages, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01130256; Issue ID: MOLY01130256 (MSV-848).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32843 | In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32843</link><description>In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving malformed RRC messages, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01130204; Issue ID: MOLY01130204 (MSV-849).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32844 | In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32844</link><description>In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving malformed RRC messages, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01128524; Issue ID: MOLY01130183 (MSV-850).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32845 | In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32845</link><description>In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving malformed RRC messages, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01128524; Issue ID: MOLY01139296 (MSV-860).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32846 | In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32846</link><description>In 5G Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service when receiving malformed RRC messages, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01128524; Issue ID: MOLY01138453 (MSV-861).</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32847 | In audio, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32847</link><description>In audio, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08241940; Issue ID: ALPS08241940.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32848 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32848</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08163896; Issue ID: ALPS08163896.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32849 | In cmdq, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32849</link><description>In cmdq, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08161758; Issue ID: ALPS08161758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32850 | In decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32850</link><description>In decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08016659; Issue ID: ALPS08016659.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32851 | In decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32851</link><description>In decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08016652; Issue ID: ALPS08016652.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32852 | In cameraisp, there is a possible information disclosure due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32852</link><description>In cameraisp, there is a possible information disclosure due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07670971; Issue ID: ALPS07670971.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32853 | In rpmb, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32853</link><description>In rpmb, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07648764; Issue ID: ALPS07648764.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32854 | In ril, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32854</link><description>In ril, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08240132; Issue ID: ALPS08240132.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32855 | In aee, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32855</link><description>In aee, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07909204; Issue ID: ALPS07909204.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32856 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32856</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07993705; Issue ID: ALPS07993705.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32857 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32857</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07993705; Issue ID: ALPS07993710.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32858 | In GZ, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing data erasing. This could lead to local information disclosure with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32858</link><description>In GZ, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing data erasing. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07806008; Issue ID: ALPS07806008.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32859 | In meta, there is a possible classic buffer overflow due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32859</link><description>In meta, there is a possible classic buffer overflow due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08000473; Issue ID: ALPS08000473.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32860 | In display, there is a possible classic buffer overflow due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32860</link><description>In display, there is a possible classic buffer overflow due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07929788; Issue ID: ALPS07929788.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32861 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32861</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08059081; Issue ID: ALPS08059081.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32862 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32862</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07388762; Issue ID: ALPS07388762.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32863 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32863</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07326314; Issue ID: ALPS07326314.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32864 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32864</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07292187; Issue ID: ALPS07292187.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32865 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32865</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07363456; Issue ID: ALPS07363456.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32866 | In mmp, there is a possible memory corruption due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32866</link><description>In mmp, there is a possible memory corruption due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07342152; Issue ID: ALPS07342152.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32867 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32867</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07560793; Issue ID: ALPS07560793.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32868 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32868</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07363632; Issue ID: ALPS07363632.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32869 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32869</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07363632; Issue ID: ALPS07363689.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32870 | In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32870</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07363740; Issue ID: ALPS07363740.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29258 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29258</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service through a specially crafted federated query on specific federation objects.  IBM X-Force ID:  252048.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:06:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38727 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38727</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted SQL statement.  IBM X-Force ID:  262257.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40687 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40687</link><description>IBM DB2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted RUNSTATS command on an 8TB table.  IBM X-Force ID:  264809.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:06:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48462 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48462</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48463 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48463</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48464 | In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48464</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42671 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42671</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42672 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42672</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42673 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42673</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42674 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42674</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42675 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42675</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42676 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42676</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42677 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42677</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42678 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42678</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42679 | In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42679</link><description>In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42680 | In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42680</link><description>In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42681 | In ion service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42681</link><description>In ion service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42682 | In gsp driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42682</link><description>In gsp driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42683 | In gsp driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42683</link><description>In gsp driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42684 | In gsp driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42684</link><description>In gsp driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42685 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42685</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42686 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42686</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42687 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42687</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42688 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42688</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42689 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42689</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42690 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42690</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42691 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42691</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42692 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42692</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42693 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42693</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42694 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42694</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42695 | In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42695</link><description>In wifi service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42696 | In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42696</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42697 | In omacp service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42697</link><description>In omacp service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42698 | In omacp service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42698</link><description>In omacp service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42699 | In omacp service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42699</link><description>In omacp service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42700 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42700</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42701 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42701</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42702 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42702</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42703 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42703</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42704 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42704</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42705 | In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42705</link><description>In imsservice, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42706 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42706</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42707 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42707</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42708 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42708</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42709 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42709</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42710 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42710</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42711 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42711</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42712 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42712</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42713 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42713</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42714 | In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42714</link><description>In firewall service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42715 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42715</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42716 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42716</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42717 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42717</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42718 | In dialer, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42718</link><description>In dialer, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42719 | In video service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42719</link><description>In video service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42720 | In video service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42720</link><description>In video service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42721 | In flv extractor, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42721</link><description>In flv extractor, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42722 | In camera service, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42722</link><description>In camera service, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42723 | In camera service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42723</link><description>In camera service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42724 | In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42724</link><description>In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42725 | In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42725</link><description>In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42726 | In TeleService, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42726</link><description>In TeleService, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42727 | In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42727</link><description>In gpu driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42728 | In phasecheckserver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42728</link><description>In phasecheckserver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42729 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42729</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42730 | In IMS service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42730</link><description>In IMS service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42731 | In Gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42731</link><description>In Gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42732 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42732</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42733 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42733</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42734 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42734</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42735 | In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42735</link><description>In telephony service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42736 | In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42736</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42737 | In telecom service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42737</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42738 | In telocom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42738</link><description>In telocom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42739 | In engineermode service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42739</link><description>In engineermode service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42740 | In telecom service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42740</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42741 | In telecom service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42741</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42742 | In sysui, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42742</link><description>In sysui, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42743 | In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42743</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42744 | In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42744</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42745 | In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42745</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42746 | In power manager, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional executio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42746</link><description>In power manager, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42747 | In camera service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42747</link><description>In camera service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42748 | In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42748</link><description>In telecom service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42749 | In enginnermode service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42749</link><description>In enginnermode service, there is a possible way to write permission usage records of an app due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42751 | In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42751</link><description>In gnss service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47701 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47701</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted query.  IBM X-Force ID:  266166.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38003 | IBM Db2 command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38003</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 could allow a user with DATAACCESS privileges to execute routines that they should not have access to.  IBM X-Force ID:  260214.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46167 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46167</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 11.5 federated server is vulnerable to a denial of service when a specially crafted cursor is used.  IBM X-Force ID:  269367.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>