<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-27709 | NanaZip .NET Single-File Manifest Parser Vulnerable to Out-of-Bounds Read via Unchecked RelativePathLength</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27709</link><description>NanaZip is an open source file archive. Starting in version 5.0.1252.0 and prior to versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0, NanaZip’s `.NET Single File Application` parser has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability in manifest parsing. A crafted bundle can provide a malformed `RelativePathLength` so the parser constructs a `std::string` from memory beyond `HeaderBuffer`, leading to crash and potential in-process memory disclosure. Versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27710 | NanaZip .NET Single-File Parser Integer Underflow Leads to Unbounded Allocation (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27710</link><description>NanaZip is an open source file archive. Starting in version 5.0.1252.0 and prior to versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in NanaZip’s `.NET Single File Application` parser. A crafted bundle can force an integer underflow in header-size calculation and trigger an unbounded memory allocation attempt during archive open. Versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27711 | NanaZip UFS Archive Parser Memory Corruption via Unvalidated Directory Record Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27711</link><description>NanaZip is an open source file archive. Starting in version 5.0.1252.0 and prior to versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0, a memory corruption vulnerability in NanaZip’s UFS parser allows a crafted `.ufs/.ufs2/.img` file to trigger out-of-bounds memory access during archive open/listing. The bug is reachable via normal user file-open flow and can cause process crash, hang, and potentially exploitable heap corruption. Versions 6.0.1638.0 and 6.5.1638.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27967 | Symlink Escape in Agent File Tools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27967</link><description>Zed, a code editor, has a symlink escape vulnerability in versions prior to 0.225.9 in Agent file tools (`read_file`, `edit_file`). It allows reading and writing files **outside the project directory** when a project contains symbolic links pointing to external paths. This bypasses the intended workspace boundary and privacy protections (`file_scan_exclusions`, `private_files`), potentially leaking sensitive user data to the LLM. Version 0.225.9 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27976 | Zed Extension Sandbox Escape via Tar Symlink Following</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27976</link><description>Zed, a code editor, has an extension installer allows tar/gzip downloads. Prior to version 0.224.4, the tar extractor (`async_tar::Archive::unpack`) creates symlinks from the archive without validation, and the path guard (`writeable_path_from_extension`) only performs lexical prefix checks without resolving symlinks. An attacker can ship a tar that first creates a symlink inside the extension workdir pointing outside (e.g., `escape -&gt; /`), then writes files through the symlink, causing writes to arbitrary host paths. This escapes the extension sandbox and enables code execution. Version 0.224.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27798 | ImageMagick: Heap Buffer Over-read in WaveletDenoise when processing small images</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27798</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability occurs when processing an image with small dimension using the `-wavelet-denoise` operator. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27799 | ImageMagick has a heap Buffer Over-read in its DJVU image format handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27799</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in the DJVU image format handler. The vulnerability occurs due to integer truncation when calculating the stride (row size) for pixel buffer allocation. The stride calculation overflows a 32-bit signed integer, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory reads. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27800 | Zed has Zip Slip Path Traversal in Extension Archive Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27800</link><description>Zed, a code editor, has a Zip Slip (Path Traversal) vulnerability exists in its extension archive extraction functionality prior to version 0.224.4. The `extract_zip()` function in `crates/util/src/archive.rs` fails to validate ZIP entry filenames for path traversal sequences (e.g., `../`). This allows a malicious extension to write files outside its designated sandbox directory by downloading and extracting a crafted ZIP archive. Version 0.224.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27630 | TinyWeb vulnerable to Remote Denial of Service via Thread/Connection Exhaustion (Slowloris)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27630</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. Versions prior to version 2.02 are vulnerable to a Denial of Service (DoS) attack known as Slowloris. The server spawns a new OS thread for every incoming connection without enforcing a maximum concurrency limit or an appropriate request timeout. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exhaust server concurrency limits and memory by opening numerous connections and sending data exceptionally slowly (e.g. 1 byte every few minutes). Anyone hosting services using TinyWeb is impacted. Version 2.02 fixes the issue. The patch introduces a `CMaxConnections` limit (set to 512) and a `CConnectionTimeoutSecs` idle timeout (set to 30 seconds). As a temporary workaround if upgrading is not immediately possible, consider placing the server behind a robust reverse proxy or Web Application Firewall (WAF) such as nginx, HAProxy, or Cloudflare, configured to buffer incomplete requests and aggressively enforce connection limits and timeouts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27633 | TinyWeb has Unbounded Content-Length Memory Exhaustion (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27633</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. Versions prior to version 2.02 have a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability via memory exhaustion. Unauthenticated remote attackers can send an HTTP POST request to the server with an exceptionally large `Content-Length` header (e.g., `2147483647`). The server continuously allocates memory for the request body (`EntityBody`) while streaming the payload without enforcing any maximum limit, leading to all available memory being consumed and causing the server to crash. Anyone hosting services using TinyWeb is impacted. Version 2.02 fixes the issue. The patch introduces a `CMaxEntityBodySize` limit (set to 10MB) for the maximum size of accepted payloads. As a temporary workaround if upgrading is not immediately possible, consider placing the server behind a Web Application Firewall (WAF) or reverse proxy (like nginx or Cloudflare) configured to explicitly limit the maximum allowed HTTP request body size (e.g., `client_max_body_size` in nginx).</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27635 | Manyfold vulnerable to OS command injection via ZIP filename in f3d render</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27635</link><description>Manyfold is an open source, self-hosted web application for managing a collection of 3d models, particularly focused on 3d printing. Prior to version 0.133.0, when model render generation is enabled, a logged-in user can achieve RCE by uploading a ZIP containing a file with a shell metacharacter in its name. The filename reaches a Ruby backtick call unsanitized. Version 0.133.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27933 | Manyfold vulnerable to session hijack via cookie leakage in proxy caches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27933</link><description>Manyfold is an open source, self-hosted web application for managing a collection of 3d models, particularly focused on 3d printing. Versions prior to 0.133.0 are vulnerable to session hijack via cookie leakage in proxy caches. Version 0.133.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27613 | CGI Parameter Injection (Bypass of STRICT_CGI_PARAMS and EscapeShellParam)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27613</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.01 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to bypass the web server's CGI parameter security controls. Depending on the server configuration and the specific CGI executable in use, the impact is either source code disclosure or remote code execution (RCE). Anyone hosting CGI scripts (particularly interpreted languages like PHP) using vulnerable versions of TinyWeb is impacted. The problem has been patched in version 2.01. If upgrading is not immediately possible, ensure `STRICT_CGI_PARAMS` is enabled (it is defined by default in `define.inc`) and/or do not use CGI executables that natively accept dangerous command-line flags (such as `php-cgi.exe`). If hosting PHP, consider placing the server behind a Web Application Firewall (WAF) that explicitly blocks URL query string parameters that begin with a hyphen (`-`) or contain encoded double quotes (`%22`).</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3209 | fosrl Pangolin Role verifyApiKeyRoleAccess access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3209</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in fosrl Pangolin up to 1.15.4-s.3. This affects the function verifyRoleAccess/verifyApiKeyRoleAccess of the component Role Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.15.4-s.4 mitigates this issue. The identifier of the patch is 5e37c4e85fae68e756be5019a28ca903b161fdd5. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 23:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27498 | n8n has Arbitrary Command Execution via File Write and Git Operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27498</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.2.0 and 1.123.8, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could chain the Read/Write Files from Disk node with git operations to achieve remote code execution. By writing to specific configuration files and then triggering a git operation, the attacker could execute arbitrary shell commands on the n8n host. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.2.0 and 1.123.8. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or disable the Read/Write Files from Disk node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.readWriteFile` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27578 | n8n Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Various Nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27578</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could inject arbitrary scripts into pages rendered by the n8n application using different techniques on various nodes (Form Trigger node, Chat Trigger node, Send &amp; Wait node, Webhook Node, and Chat Node). Scripts injected by a malicious workflow execute in the browser of any user who visits the affected page, enabling session hijacking and account takeover. The issues have been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1 and 1.123.21. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or disable the Webhook node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.webhook` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27497 | n8n has Potential Remote Code Execution via Merge Node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27497</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could leverage the Merge node's SQL query mode to execute arbitrary code and write arbitrary files on the n8n server. The issues have been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate all known vulnerabilities. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or disable the Merge node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.merge` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27577 | n8n: Expression Sandbox Escape Leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27577</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, additional exploits in the expression evaluation of n8n have been identified and patched following CVE-2025-68613. An authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could abuse crafted expressions in workflow parameters to trigger unintended system command execution on the host running n8n. The issues have been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate all known vulnerabilities. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or deploy n8n in a hardened environment with restricted operating system privileges and network access to reduce the impact of potential exploitation. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27493 | n8n has Unauthenticated Expression Evaluation via Form Node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27493</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, a second-order expression injection vulnerability existed in n8n's Form nodes that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to inject and evaluate arbitrary n8n expressions by submitting crafted form data. When chained with an expression sandbox escape, this could escalate to remote code execution on the n8n host. The vulnerability requires a specific workflow configuration to be exploitable. First, a form node with a field interpolating a value provided by an unauthenticated user, e.g. a form submitted value. Second, the field value must begin with an `=` character, which caused n8n to treat it as an expression and triggered a double-evaluation of the field content. There is no practical reason for a workflow designer to prefix a field with `=` intentionally — the character is not rendered in the output, so the result would not match the designer's expectations. If added accidentally, it would be noticeable and very unlikely to persist. An unauthenticated attacker would need to either know about this specific circumstance on a target instance or discover a matching form by chance. Even when the preconditions are met, the expression injection alone is limited to data accessible within the n8n expression context. Escalation to remote code execution requires chaining with a separate sandbox escape vulnerability. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Review usage of form nodes manually for above mentioned preconditions, disable the Form node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.form` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable, and/or disable the Form Trigger node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.formTrigger` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27494 | n8n has Arbitrary File Read via Python Code Node Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27494</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could use the Python Code node to escape the sandbox. The sandbox did not sufficiently restrict access to certain built-in Python objects, allowing an attacker to exfiltrate file contents or achieve RCE. On instances using internal Task Runners (default runner mode), this could result in full compromise of the n8n host. On instances using external Task Runners, the attacker might gain access to or impact other task executed on the Task Runner. Task Runners must be enabled using `N8N_RUNNERS_ENABLED=true`. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to this version or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only., and/or disable the Code node by adding `n8n-nodes-base.code` to the `NODES_EXCLUDE` environment variable. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27495 | n8n has a Sandbox Escape in its JavaScript Task Runner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27495</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22, an authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows could exploit a vulnerability in the JavaScript Task Runner sandbox to execute arbitrary code outside the sandbox boundary. On instances using internal Task Runners (default runner mode), this could result in full compromise of the n8n host. On instances using external Task Runners, the attacker might gain access to or impact other task executed on the Task Runner. Task Runners must be enabled using `N8N_RUNNERS_ENABLED=true`. The issue has been fixed in n8n versions 2.10.1, 2.9.3, and 1.123.22. Users should upgrade to one of these versions or later to remediate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations. Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only, and/or use external runner mode (`N8N_RUNNERS_MODE=external`) to limit the blast radius. These workarounds do not fully remediate the risk and should only be used as short-term mitigation measures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 22:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27148 | Storybook Dev Server Vulnerable to WebSocket Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27148</link><description>Storybook is a frontend workshop for building user interface components and pages in isolation. Prior to versions 7.6.23, 8.6.17, 9.1.19, and 10.2.10, the WebSocket functionality in Storybook's dev server, used to create and update stories, is vulnerable to WebSocket hijacking. This vulnerability only affects the Storybook dev server; production builds are not impacted. Exploitation requires a developer to visit a malicious website while their local Storybook dev server is running. Because the WebSocket connection does not validate the origin of incoming connections, a malicious site can silently send WebSocket messages to the local instance without any further user interaction. If the Storybook dev server is intentionally exposed publicly (e.g. for design reviews or stakeholder demos) the risk is higher, as no malicious site visit is required. Any unauthenticated attacker can send WebSocket messages to it directly. The vulnerability affects the WebSocket message handlers for creating and saving stories. Both are vulnerable to injection via unsanitized input in the componentFilePath field, which can be exploited to achieve persistent XSS or Remote Code Execution (RCE). Versions 7.6.23, 8.6.17, 9.1.19, and 10.2.10 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27575 | Vijkunja has Weak Password Policy Combined with Persistent Sessions After Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27575</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, the application allows users to set weak passwords (e.g., 1234, password) without enforcing minimum strength requirements. Additionally, active sessions remain valid after a user changes their password. An attacker who compromises an account (via brute-force or credential stuffing) can maintain persistent access even after the victim resets their password. Version 2.0.0 contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27616 | Vikunja Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Unsanitized SVG Attachment Upload Leading to Token Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27616</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, the application allows users to upload SVG files as task attachments. SVG is an XML-based format that supports JavaScript execution through elements such as</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27819 | Vikunja has Path Traversal in CLI Restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27819</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, the restoreConfig function in vikunja/pkg/modules/dump/restore.go of the go-vikunja/vikunja repository fails to sanitize file paths within the provided ZIP archive. A maliciously crafted ZIP can bypass the intended extraction directory to overwrite arbitrary files on the host system. Additionally, we’ve discovered that a malformed archive triggers a runtime panic, crashing the process immediately after the database has been wiped permanently. The application trusts the metadata in the ZIP archive. It uses the Name attribute of the zip.File struct directly in os.OpenFile calls without validation, allowing files to be written outside the intended directory. The restoration logic assumes a specific directory structure within the ZIP. When provided with a "minimalist" malicious ZIP, the application fails to validate the length of slices derived from the archive contents. Specifically, at line 154, the code attempts to access an index of len(ms)-2 on an insufficiently populated slice, triggering a panic. Version 2.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26985 | LORIS vulnerable to path traversal in electrophysiology_browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26985</link><description>LORIS (Longitudinal Online Research and Imaging System) is a self-hosted web application that provides data- and project-management for neuroimaging research. Starting in version 24.0.0 and prior to versions 26.0.5, 27.0.2, and 28.0.0, an authenticated user with the appropriate authorization can read configuration files on the server by exploiting a path traversal vulnerability. Some of these files contain hard-coded credentials. The vulnerability allows an attacker to read configuration files containing hard-coded credentials. The attacker could then authenticate to the database or other services if those credentials are reused. The attacker must be authenticated and have the required permissions. However, the vulnerability is easy to exploit and the application source code is public. This problem is fixed in LORIS v26.0.5 and v27.0.2 and above, and v28.0.0 and above. As a workaround, the electrophysiogy_browser in LORIS can be disabled by an administrator using the module manager.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27116 | Vikunja has Reflected HTML Injection via filter Parameter in Projects Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27116</link><description>Vikunja is an open-source self-hosted task management platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, a reflected HTML injection vulnerability exists in the Projects module where the `filter` URL parameter is rendered into the DOM without output encoding when the user clicks "Filter." While `&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2694 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.15.16 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Event/Organizer/Venue Update/Trash via REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2694</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to an improper capability check on the 'can_edit' and 'can_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.15.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update or trash events, organizers and venues via REST API.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26984 | LORIS media module vulnerable to remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26984</link><description>LORIS (Longitudinal Online Research and Imaging System) is a self-hosted web application that provides data- and project-management for neuroimaging research. Prior to versions 26.0.5, 27.0.2, and 28.0.0, an authenticated user with sufficient privileges can exploit a path traversal vulnerability to upload a malicious file to an arbitrary location on the server. Once uploaded, the file can be used to achieve remote code execution (RCE). An attacker must be authenticated and have the appropriate permissions to exploit this issue. If the server is configured as read-only, remote code execution (RCE) is not possible; however, the malicious file upload may still be achievable. This problem is fixed in LORIS v26.0.5 and above, v27.0.2 and above, and v28.0.0 and above. As a workaround, LORIS administrators can disable the media module if it is not being used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26986 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in rail_window_free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26986</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `rail_window_free` dereferences a freed `xfAppWindow` pointer during `HashTable_Free` cleanup because `xf_rail_window_common` calls `free(appWindow)` on title allocation failure without first removing the entry from the `railWindows` hash table, leaving a dangling pointer that is freed again on disconnect. Version 3.23.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27950 | FreeRDP heap-use-after-free in update_pointer_new(SDL): Fix Applied in the Wrong File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27950</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, the fix for the heap-use-after-free described in CVE-2026-24680 is incomplete. While the vulnerable execution flow referenced in the advisory exists in the SDL2 implementation, the fix appears to have been applied only to the SDL3 code path. In the SDL2 implementation, the pointer is not nulled after free. This creates a situation where the advisory suggests the vulnerability is fully resolved, while builds or environments still using SDL2 may retain the vulnerable logic. A complete fix is available in version 3.23.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27951 | FreeRDP has possible Integer overflow in Stream_EnsureCapacity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27951</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, the function `Stream_EnsureCapacity` can create an endless blocking loop. This may affect all client and server implementations using `FreeRDP`. For practical exploitation this will only work on 32bit systems where the available physical memory is `&gt;= SIZE_MAX`. Version 3.23.0 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26955 | FreeRDP has Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26955</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, a malicious RDP server can trigger a heap buffer overflow in FreeRDP clients using the GDI surface pipeline (e.g., `xfreerdp`) by sending an RDPGFX ClearCodec surface command with an out-of-bounds destination rectangle. The `gdi_SurfaceCommand_ClearCodec()` handler does not call `is_within_surface()` to validate the command rectangle against the destination surface dimensions, allowing attacker-controlled `cmd-&gt;left`/`cmd-&gt;top` (and subcodec rectangle offsets) to reach image copy routines that write into `surface-&gt;data` without bounds enforcement. The OOB write corrupts an adjacent `gdiGfxSurface` struct's `codecs*` pointer with attacker-controlled pixel data, and corruption of `codecs*` is sufficient to reach an indirect function pointer call (`NSC_CONTEXT.decode` at `nsc.c:500`) on a subsequent codec command — full instruction pointer (RIP) control demonstrated in exploitability harness. Users should upgrade to version 3.23.0 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26965 | FreeRDP has Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26965</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, in the RLE planar decode path, `planar_decompress_plane_rle()` writes into `pDstData` at `((nYDst+y) * nDstStep) + (4*nXDst) + nChannel` without verifying that `(nYDst+nSrcHeight)` fits in the destination height or that `(nXDst+nSrcWidth)` fits in the destination stride. When `TempFormat != DstFormat`, `pDstData` becomes `planar-&gt;pTempData` (sized for the desktop), while `nYDst` is only validated against the **surface** by `is_within_surface()`. A malicious RDP server can exploit this to perform a heap out-of-bounds write with attacker-controlled offset and pixel data on any connecting FreeRDP client. The OOB write reaches up to 132,096 bytes past the temp buffer end, and  on the brk heap (desktop ≤ 128×128), an adjacent `NSC_CONTEXT` struct's `decode` function pointer is overwritten with attacker-controlled pixel data — control-flow–relevant corruption (function pointer overwritten) demonstrated under deterministic heap layout (`nsc-&gt;decode = 0xFF414141FF414141`). Version 3.23.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3172 | pgvector buffer overflow in parallel HNSW index build</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3172</link><description>Buffer overflow in parallel HNSW index build in pgvector 0.6.0 through 0.8.1 allows a database user to leak sensitive data from other relations or crash the database server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0542 | Remote Code Execution in ServiceNow AI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0542</link><description>ServiceNow has addressed a remote code execution vulnerability that was identified in the ServiceNow AI platform.  This vulnerability could enable an unauthenticated user, in certain circumstances, to execute code within the ServiceNow Sandbox.   





ServiceNow addressed this vulnerability by deploying a security update to hosted instances. Relevant security updates also have been provided to ServiceNow self-hosted customers and partners. Further, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed patches and hot fixes. While we are not currently aware of exploitation against customer instances, we recommend customers promptly apply appropriate updates or upgrade if they have not already done so.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25954 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_rail_server_local_move_size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25954</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_rail_server_local_move_size` dereferences a freed `xfAppWindow` pointer because `xf_rail_get_window` returns an unprotected pointer from the `railWindows` hash table, and the main thread can concurrently delete the window (via a window delete order) while the RAIL channel thread is still using the pointer. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25955 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface (stale XImage)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25955</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface` reuses a cached `XImage` whose `data` pointer references a freed RDPGFX surface buffer, because `gdi_DeleteSurface` frees `surface-&gt;data` without invalidating the `appWindow-&gt;image` that aliases it. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25959 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_cliprdr_provide_data_</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25959</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_cliprdr_provide_data_` passes freed `pDstData` to `XChangeProperty` because the cliprdr channel thread calls `xf_cliprdr_server_format_data_response` which converts and uses the clipboard data without holding any lock, while the X11 event thread concurrently calls `xf_cliprdr_clear_cached_data` → `HashTable_Clear` which frees the same data via `xf_cached_data_free`, triggering a heap use after free. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25997 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_clipboard_format_equal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25997</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_clipboard_format_equal` reads freed `lastSentFormats` memory because `xf_clipboard_formats_free` (called from the cliprdr channel thread during auto-reconnect) frees the array while the X11 event thread concurrently iterates it in `xf_clipboard_changed`, triggering a heap use after free. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26271 | Buffer Overread in FreeRDP Icon Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26271</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, a buffer overread in `freerdp_image_copy_from_icon_data()` (libfreerdp/codec/color.c) can be triggered by crafted RDP Window Icon (TS_ICON_INFO) data. The bug is reachable over the network when a client processes icon data from an RDP server (or from a man-in-the-middle). Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27015 | FreeRDP: Smartcard NDR Alignment Padding Triggers Reachable WINPR_ASSERT Abort (Client DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27015</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, a missing bounds check in `smartcard_unpack_read_size_align()` (`libfreerdp/utils/smartcard_pack.c:1703`) allows a malicious RDP server to crash the FreeRDP client via a reachable `WINPR_ASSERT` → `abort()`. The crash occurs in upstream builds where `WITH_VERBOSE_WINPR_ASSERT=ON` (default in FreeRDP 3.22.0 / current WinPR CMake defaults). Smartcard redirection must be explicitly enabled by the user (e.g., `xfreerdp /smartcard`; `/smartcard-logon` implies `/smartcard`). Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25952 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_SetWindowMinMaxInfo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25952</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_SetWindowMinMaxInfo` dereferences a freed `xfAppWindow` pointer because `xf_rail_get_window` in `xf_rail_server_min_max_info` returns an unprotected pointer from the `railWindows` hash table, and the main thread can concurrently delete the window (via a window delete order) while the RAIL channel thread is still using the pointer. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25953 | FreeRDP has heap-use-after-free in xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface (freed appWindow)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25953</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_AppUpdateWindowFromSurface` reads from a freed `xfAppWindow` because the RDPGFX DVC thread obtains a bare pointer via `xf_rail_get_window` without any lifetime protection, while the main thread can concurrently delete the window through a fastpath window-delete order. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14511 | Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14511</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 12.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to cause denial of service by sending specially crafted files to the container registry event endpoint under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0752 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0752</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that under certain circumstances, could have allowed an unauthenticated user to inject arbitrary scripts into the Mermaid sandbox UI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1388 | Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1388</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 9.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to cause regular expression denial of service by sending specially crafted input to a merge request endpoint under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1662 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1662</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 14.4 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an unauthenticated user to cause Denial of Service by sending specially crafted requests to the Jira events endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1725 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1725</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting versions from 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have under certain conditions, allowed an unauthenticated user to cause denial of service by sending specially crafted requests to a CI jobs API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1747 | Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1747</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.11 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that, under certain conditions, could have allowed Developer-role users with insufficient privileges to make unauthorized modifications to protected Conan packages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22721 | VMware Aria Operations privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22721</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with privileges in vCenter to access Aria Operations may leverage this vulnerability to obtain administrative access in VMware Aria Operations. To remediate CVE-2026-22721, apply the patches listed in the 'Fixed Version' column of the 'Response Matrix' found in  VMSA-2026-0001 https://support.broadcom.com/web/ecx/support-content-notification/-/external/content/SecurityAdvisories/0/36947 .</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25942 | FreeRDP has global-buffer-overflow in xf_rail_server_execute_result</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25942</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.23.0, `xf_rail_server_execute_result` indexes the global `error_code_names[]` array (7 elements, indices 0–6) with an unchecked `execResult-&gt;execResult` value received from the server, allowing an out-of-bounds read when the server sends an `execResult` value of 7 or greater. Version 3.23.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2845 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2845</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.2 before 18.7.5, 18.8 before 18.8.5, and 18.9 before 18.9.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to cause denial of service by exploiting a Bitbucket Server import endpoint via repeatedly sending large responses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3200 | z-9527 admin user.js getUsers sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3200</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in z-9527 admin 1.0/2.0. The affected element is the function checkName/register/login/getUser/getUsers of the file /server/controller/user.js. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 20:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27691 | iccDEV has SIO in parse3DTable() at iccFromCube.cpp Line 218</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27691</link><description>iccDEV provides a set of libraries and tools for working with ICC color management profiles. In versions up to and including 2.3.1.4, signed integer overflow in iccFromCube.cpp during multiplication triggers undefined behavior, potentially causing crashes or incorrect ICC profile generation when processing crafted/large cube inputs. Commit 43ae18dd69fc70190d3632a18a3af2f3da1e052a fixes the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3187 | feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent API Endpoint upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3187</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent up to 1.3.2-beta. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/admin/sys-file/upload of the component API Endpoint. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.3-beta can resolve this issue. The name of the patch is aefaabfd7527188bfba3c8c9eee17c316d094802. Upgrading the affected component is recommended. The project was informed beforehand and acted very professional: "We have introduced a whitelist restriction on the /api/admin/sys-file/upload endpoint via the oss.allowedExts and oss.allowedMimeTypes configuration options, allowing the specification of permitted file extensions and MIME types for uploads."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3201 | Improperly Controlled Sequential Memory Allocation in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3201</link><description>USB HID protocol dissector memory exhaustion in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.3 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.13 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3202 | NULL Pointer Dereference in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3202</link><description>NTS-KE protocol dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.3 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3203 | Buffer Over-read in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3203</link><description>RF4CE Profile protocol dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 to 4.6.3 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.13 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3185 | feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent API Endpoint sys-message authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent up to 1.3.2-beta. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/admin/sys-message/ of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument messageId results in authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 1.3.3-beta is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as aefaabfd7527188bfba3c8c9eee17c316d094802. The affected component should be upgraded. The project was informed beforehand and acted very professional: "We have implemented message ownership verification, so that users can only query messages related to themselves."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3186 | feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent Password Reset password default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3186</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in feiyuchuixue sz-boot-parent up to 1.3.2-beta. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/admin/sys-user/reset/password/ of the component Password Reset Handler. This manipulation of the argument userId causes use of default password. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Upgrading to version 1.3.3-beta addresses this issue. Patch name: aefaabfd7527188bfba3c8c9eee17c316d094802. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component. The project was informed beforehand and acted very professional: "We have added authorization validation to the password reset interface; now only users with the corresponding permissions are allowed to perform password resets."</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28193 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.121962 apps were able to send requests to the app permissions endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28193</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.121962 apps were able to send requests to the app permissions endpoint</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28194 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 open redirect was possible in the React project creation flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28194</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 open redirect was possible in the React project creation flow</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28195 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 missing authorization allowed project developers to add parameters to build configurations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28195</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 missing authorization allowed project developers to add parameters to build configurations</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-28196 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 disabling versioned settings left a credentials config on disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-28196</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.11.3 disabling versioned settings left a credentials config on disk</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21725 | Authorization Bypass via TOCTOU in Grafana Datasource Deletion by Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21725</link><description>A time-of-create-to-time-of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability lets recently deleted-then-recreated data sources be re-deleted without permission to do so.

This requires several very stringent conditions to be met:

- The attacker must have admin access to the specific datasource prior to its first deletion.
- Upon deletion, all steps within the attack must happen within the next 30 seconds and on the same pod of Grafana.
- The attacker must delete the datasource, then someone must recreate it.
- The new datasource must not have the attacker as an admin.
- The new datasource must have the same UID as the prior datasource. These are randomised by default.
- The datasource can now be re-deleted by the attacker.
- Once 30 seconds are up, the attack is spent and cannot be repeated.
- No datasource with any other UID can be attacked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2624 | Authentication Bypass in ePati&amp;#x27;s Antikor NGFW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2624</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in ePati Cyber ​​Security Technologies Inc. Antikor Next Generation Firewall (NGFW) allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Antikor Next Generation Firewall (NGFW): from v.2.0.1298 before v.2.0.1301.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0704 | In affected version of Octopus Deploy it was possible to remove files and/or contents of files on the host using an API endpoint. The field ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0704</link><description>In affected version of Octopus Deploy it was possible to remove files and/or contents of files on the host using an API endpoint. The field lacked validation which could potentially result in ways to circumvent expected workflows.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3118 | Rhdh: graphql injection leading to platform-wide denial of service (dos) in rh developer hub orchestrator plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3118</link><description>A security flaw was identified in the Orchestrator Plugin of Red Hat Developer Hub (Backstage). The issue occurs due to insufficient input validation in GraphQL query handling. An authenticated user can inject specially crafted input into API requests, which disrupts backend query processing. This results in the entire Backstage application crashing and restarting, leading to a platform-wide Denial of Service (DoS). As a result, legitimate users temporarily lose access to the platform.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25701 | An Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in openSUSE sdbootutil allows local users to pre-create a directory to achieve various effects like...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25701</link><description>An Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in openSUSE sdbootutil allows local users to pre-create a directory to achieve various effects like:
  *  gain access to possible private information found in /var/lib/pcrlock.d
  *  manipulate the data backed up in /tmp/pcrlock.d.bak, therefore violating the integrity of the data should it be restored.
  *   overwrite protected system files with data from /var/lib/pcrlock.d by placing symlinks to existing files in the directory tree in /tmp/pcrlock.d.bak.


This issue affects sdbootutil: from ? before 5880246d3a02642dc68f5c8cb474bf63cdb56bca.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62878 | Local Path Provisioner vulnerable to Path Traversal via parameters.pathPattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62878</link><description>A malicious user can manipulate the parameters.pathPattern to create PersistentVolumes in arbitrary locations on the host node, potentially overwriting sensitive files or gaining access to unintended directories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67601 | Rancher CLI skips TLS verification on Rancher CLI login command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67601</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified within Rancher Manager, where using self-signed CA certificates and passing the -skip-verify flag to the Rancher CLI login command without also passing the –cacert flag results in the CLI attempting to fetch CA certificates stored in Rancher’s setting cacerts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26104 | Udisks: missing authorization check allows unprivileged users to back up luks headers via udisks d-bus api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26104</link><description>A flaw was found in the udisks storage management daemon that allows unprivileged users to back up LUKS encryption headers without authorization. The issue occurs because a privileged D-Bus method responsible for exporting encryption metadata does not perform a policy check. As a result, sensitive cryptographic metadata can be read and written to attacker-controlled locations. This weakens the confidentiality guarantees of encrypted storage volumes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67860 | NeuVector scanner insecurely handles passwords as command arguments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67860</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the NeuVector scanner where the scanner process accepts registry and controller credentials as command-line arguments, potentially exposing sensitive credentials to local users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26103 | Udisks: missing authorization check allows unprivileged users to restore luks headers via udisks d-bus api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26103</link><description>A flaw was found in the udisks storage management daemon that exposes a privileged D-Bus API for restoring LUKS encryption headers without proper authorization checks. The issue allows a local unprivileged user to instruct the root-owned udisks daemon to overwrite encryption metadata on block devices. This can permanently invalidate encryption keys and render encrypted volumes inaccessible. Successful exploitation results in a denial-of-service condition through irreversible data loss.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14742 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 10.2.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14742</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_search_recipes' and 'ajax_get_recipe' functions in all versions up to, and including, 10.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive recipe information including draft, pending, and private recipes that they shouldn't be able to access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2301 | Post Duplicator &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Meta Insertion via &amp;#x27;customMetaData&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2301</link><description>The Post Duplicator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary protected post meta insertion in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8. This is due to the `duplicate_post()` function in `includes/api.php` using `$wpdb-&gt;insert()` directly to the `wp_postmeta` table instead of WordPress's standard `add_post_meta()` function, which would call `is_protected_meta()` to prevent lower-privileged users from setting protected meta keys (those starting with `_`). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary protected post meta keys such as `_wp_page_template`, `_wp_attached_file`, and other sensitive meta keys on duplicated posts via the `customMetaData` JSON array parameter in the `/wp-json/post-duplicator/v1/duplicate-post` REST API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2367 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2367</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ays_block' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2410 | Disable Admin Notices – Hide Dashboard Notifications &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2410</link><description>The Disable Admin Notices – Hide Dashboard Notifications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2. This is due to missing nonce validation in the `showPageContent()` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary URLs to the blocked redirects list via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 10:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3171 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System queue.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3171</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /queue.php. This manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1916 | WPGSI: Spreadsheet Integration &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Creation and Deletion via Forged Base64 Token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1916</link><description>The WPGSI: Spreadsheet Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to missing capability checks and an insecure authentication mechanism on the `wpgsi_callBackFuncAccept` and `wpgsi_callBackFuncUpdate` REST API functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. Both REST endpoints use `permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true'`, allowing unauthenticated access. The plugin's custom token-based validation relies on a Base64-encoded JSON object containing the user ID and email address, but is not cryptographically signed. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to forge tokens using publicly enumerable information (admin user ID and email) to create, modify, and delete arbitrary WordPress posts and pages, granted they know the administrator's email address and an active integration ID with remote updates enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1929 | Advanced Woo Labels &amp;lt;= 2.37 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution via &amp;#x27;callback&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1929</link><description>The Advanced Woo Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.37. This is due to the use of `call_user_func_array()` with user-controlled callback and parameters in the `get_select_option_values()` AJAX handler without an allowlist of permitted callbacks or a capability check. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute arbitrary PHP functions and operating system commands on the server via the 'callback' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2416 | Geo Mashup &amp;lt;= 1.13.17 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;sort&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2416</link><description>The Geo Mashup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'sort' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.17. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2479 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Remote Library Image Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2479</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the use of `strpos()` for substring-based hostname validation instead of strict host comparison in the `ajax_upload_image()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application, which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3170 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System patient-search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3170</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /patient-search.php. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3169 | Tenda F453 httpd SafeEmailFilter fromSafeEmailFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3169</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. This impacts the function fromSafeEmailFilter of the file /goform/SafeEmailFilter of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument page leads to buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11563 | wcurl path traversal with percent-encoded slashes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11563</link><description>URLs containing percent-encoded slashes (`/` or `\`) can trick wcurl into
saving the output file outside of the current directory without the user
explicitly asking for it.

This flaw only affects the wcurl command line tool.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1614 | Rise Blocks – A Complete Gutenberg Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Site Identity Block Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1614</link><description>The Rise Blocks – A Complete Gutenberg Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘logoTag’ Site Identity block attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3167 | Tenda F453 httpd webtypelibrary formWebTypeLibrary buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3167</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. The impacted element is the function formWebTypeLibrary of the file /goform/webtypelibrary of the component httpd. Performing a manipulation of the argument webSiteId results in buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3168 | Tenda F453 httpd NatStaticSetting fromNatStaticSetting buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3168</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. This affects the function fromNatStaticSetting of the file /goform/NatStaticSetting of the component httpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument page can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3166 | Tenda F453 httpd RouteStatic fromRouteStatic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3166</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. The affected element is the function fromRouteStatic of the file /goform/RouteStatic of the component httpd. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25785 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) Sub-Manager Server Ver.9.4.7.3 and earlier, which may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25785</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) Sub-Manager Server Ver.9.4.7.3 and earlier, which may allow an attacker to tamper with arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3100 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was found in the FTP Backup on the ADM.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3100</link><description>The FTP Backup on the ADM will not properly strictly enforce TLS certificate verification while connecting to an FTP server using FTPES/FTPS. An improper validated TLS/SSL certificates allows a remote attacker can intercept network traffic to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack, which may intercept, modify, or obtain sensitive information such as authentication credentials and backup data.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.2.RE51.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3164 | itsourcecode News Portal Project contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3164</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3165 | Tenda F453 httpd AdvSetWrlsafeset fromSetWifiGusetBasic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3165</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda F453 1.0.0.3. Impacted is the function fromSetWifiGusetBasic of the file /goform/AdvSetWrlsafeset of the component httpd. This manipulation of the argument mit_ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3179 | A path traversal vulnerability was found in the FTP Backup on the ADM.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3179</link><description>The FTP Backup on the ADM does not properly sanitize filenames received from the FTP server when parsing directory listings. A malicious server or MITM attacker can craft filenames containing path traversal sequences, causing the client to write files outside the intended backup directory. A path traversal vulnerability may allow an attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the system and potentially achieve privilege escalation or remote code execution.
Affected products and versions include: from ADM 4.1.0 through ADM 4.3.3.ROF1 as well as from ADM 5.0.0 through ADM 5.1.2.RE51.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3153 | itsourcecode Document Management System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3153</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /register.php. Such manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3163 | SourceCodester Website Link Extractor URL file_get_contents server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3163</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Website Link Extractor 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function file_get_contents of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3151 | itsourcecode College Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3151</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login/login.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3152 | itsourcecode College Management System teacher-salary.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3152</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/teacher-salary.php. This manipulation of the argument teacher_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0976 | Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Configuration Manager, Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0976</link><description>Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager, Hitachi Configuration Manager.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.4-00; Hitachi Configuration Manager: from 8.6.1-00 before 11.0.5-00.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27624 | Coturn: IPv4-mapped IPv6 (::ffff:0:0/96) bypasses denied-peer-ip ACL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27624</link><description>Coturn is a free open source implementation of TURN and STUN Server. Coturn is commonly configured to block loopback and internal ranges using "denied-peer-ip" and/or default loopback restrictions. CVE-2020-26262 addressed bypasses involving "0.0.0.0", "[::1]" and "[::]", but IPv4-mapped IPv6 is not covered. When sending a "CreatePermission" or "ChannelBind" request with the "XOR-PEER-ADDRESS" value of "::ffff:127.0.0.1", a successful response is received, even though "127.0.0.0/8" is blocked via "denied-peer-ip". The root cause is that, prior to the updated fix implemented in version 4.9.0, three functions in "src/client/ns_turn_ioaddr.c" do not check "IN6_IS_ADDR_V4MAPPED". "ioa_addr_is_loopback()" checks "127.x.x.x" (AF_INET) and "::1" (AF_INET6), but not "::ffff:127.0.0.1." "ioa_addr_is_zero()" checks "0.0.0.0" and "::", but not "::ffff:0.0.0.0." "addr_less_eq()" used by "ioa_addr_in_range()" for "denied-peer-ip" matching: when the range is AF_INET and the peer is AF_INET6, the comparison returns 0 without extracting the embedded IPv4. Version 4.9.0 contains an updated fix to address the bypass of the fix for CVE-2020-26262.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27645 | changedetection.io Vulnerable to Reflected XSS in RSS Single Watch Error Response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27645</link><description>changedetection.io is a free open source web page change detection tool. In versions prior to 0.54.1, the RSS single-watch endpoint reflects the UUID path parameter directly in the HTTP response body without HTML escaping. Since Flask returns text/html by default for plain string responses, the browser parses and executes injected JavaScript. Version 0.54.1 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27696 | changedetection.io Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via Watch URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27696</link><description>changedetection.io is a free open source web page change detection tool. In versions prior to 0.54.1, changedetection.io is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) because the URL validation function `is_safe_valid_url()` does not validate the resolved IP address of watch URLs against private, loopback, or link-local address ranges. An authenticated user (or any user when no password is configured, which is the default) can add a watch for internal network URLs. The application fetches these URLs server-side, stores the response content, and makes it viewable through the web UI — enabling full data exfiltration from internal services. Version 0.54.1 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3148 | SourceCodester Simple and Nice Shopping Cart Script signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3148</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Simple and Nice Shopping Cart Script 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /signup.php. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3149 | itsourcecode College Management System asign-single-student-subjects.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3149</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/asign-single-student-subjects.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument course_code can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3150 | itsourcecode College Management System display-teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3150</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/display-teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument teacher_id leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27597 | @enclave-vm/core is vulnerable to Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27597</link><description>Enclave is a secure JavaScript sandbox designed for safe AI agent code execution. Prior to version 2.11.1, it is possible to escape the security boundraries set by `@enclave-vm/core`, which can be used to achieve remote code execution (RCE). The issue has been fixed in version 2.11.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27627 | Karakeep&amp;#x27;s Reddit plugin content bypasses DOMPurify sanitization, enabling stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27627</link><description>Karakeep is a elf-hostable bookmark-everything app. In version 0.30.0, when the Reddit metascraper plugin returns `readableContentHtml`, the HTML parsing subprocess uses it directly without running it through DOMPurify. Every other content source in the crawler goes through Readability + DOMPurify, but the Reddit path skips both. Since this content ends up in `dangerouslySetInnerHTML` in the reader view, any malicious HTML in the Reddit response gets executed in the user's browser. Version 0.31.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27636 | FreeScout: Missing .htaccess in Restricted File Extensions Allows Remote Code Execution on Apache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27636</link><description>FreeScout is a free help desk and shared inbox built with PHP's Laravel framework. Prior to version 1.8.206, FreeScout's file upload restriction list in `app/Misc/Helper.php` does not include `.htaccess` or `.user.ini` files. On Apache servers with `AllowOverride All` (a common configuration), an authenticated user can upload a `.htaccess` file to redefine how files are processed, enabling Remote Code Execution. This vulnerability can be exploited on its own or in combination with CVE-2026-27637. Version 1.8.206 fixes both vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27637 | FreeScout&amp;#x27;s Predictable Authentication Token Enables Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27637</link><description>FreeScout is a free help desk and shared inbox built with PHP's Laravel framework. Prior to version 1.8.206, FreeScout's `TokenAuth` middleware uses a predictable authentication token computed as `MD5(user_id + created_at + APP_KEY)`. This token is static (never expires/rotates), and if an attacker obtains the `APP_KEY` — a well-documented and common exposure vector in Laravel applications — they can compute a valid token for any user, including the administrator, achieving full account takeover without any password. This vulnerability can be exploited on its own or in combination with CVE-2026-27636. Version 1.8.206 fixes both vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27639 | Mercator vulnerable to stored XSS via unescaped Blade directives in display templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27639</link><description>Mercator is an open source web application designed to enable mapping of information systems. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Mercator prior to version 2026.02.22 due to the use of unescaped Blade directives (`{!! !!}`) in display templates. An authenticated user with the User role can inject arbitrary JavaScript payloads into fields such as "contact point" when creating or editing entities. The payload is then executed in the browser of any user who views the affected page, including administrators. Version 2026.02.22 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27640 | tfplan2md has Sensitive Value Exposure in Generated Reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27640</link><description>tfplan2md is software for converting Terraform plan JSON files into human-readable Markdown reports. Prior to version 1.26.1, a bug in tfplan2md affected several distinct rendering paths: AzApi resource body properties, AzureDevOps variable groups, Scriban template context variables, and hierarchical sensitivity detection. This caused reports to render values that should have been masked as "(sensitive)" instead. This issue is fixed in v1.26.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27641 | Flask-Reuploaded vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Server-Side Template Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27641</link><description>Flask-Reuploaded provides file uploads for Flask. A critical path traversal and extension bypass vulnerability in versions prior to 1.5.0 allows remote attackers to achieve arbitrary file write and remote code execution through Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI). Flask-Reuploaded has been patched in version 1.5.0. Some workarounds are available. Do not pass user input to the `name` parameter, use auto-generated filenames only, and implement strict input validation if `name` must be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27743 | SPIP referer_spam &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27743</link><description>The SPIP referer_spam plugin versions prior to 1.3.0 contain an unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the referer_spam_ajouter and referer_spam_supprimer action handlers. The handlers read the url parameter from a GET request and interpolate it directly into SQL LIKE clauses without input validation or parameterization. The endpoints do not enforce authorization checks and do not use SPIP action protections such as securiser_action(), allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27744 | SPIP tickets &amp;lt; 4.3.3 Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27744</link><description>The SPIP tickets plugin versions prior to 4.3.3 contain an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the forum preview handling for public ticket pages. The plugin appends untrusted request parameters into HTML that is later rendered by a template using unfiltered environment rendering (#ENV**), which disables SPIP output filtering. As a result, an unauthenticated attacker can inject crafted content that is evaluated through SPIP's template processing chain, leading to execution of code in the context of the web server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27745 | SPIP interface_traduction_objets &amp;lt; 2.2.2 Authenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27745</link><description>The SPIP interface_traduction_objets plugin versions prior to 4.3.3 contain an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the translation interface workflow. The plugin incorporates untrusted request data into a hidden form field that is rendered without SPIP output filtering. Because fields prefixed with an underscore bypass protection mechanisms and the hidden content is rendered with filtering disabled, an authenticated attacker with editor-level privileges can inject crafted content that is evaluated through SPIP's template processing chain, resulting in execution of code in the context of the web server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27746 | SPIP jeux &amp;lt; 4.1.1 Reflected XSS via index Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27746</link><description>The SPIP jeux plugin versions prior to 4.1.1 contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the pre_propre pipeline. The plugin incorporates untrusted request parameters into HTML output without proper output encoding, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary script content into pages that render a jeux block. When a victim is induced to visit a crafted URL, the injected content is reflected into the response and executed in the victim's browser context.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27747 | SPIP interface_traduction_objets &amp;lt; 2.2.2 Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27747</link><description>The SPIP interface_traduction_objets plugin versions prior to 4.3.3 contain an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in interface_traduction_objets_pipelines.php. When handling translation requests, the plugin reads the id_parent parameter from user-supplied input and concatenates it directly into a SQL WHERE clause in a call to sql_getfetsel() without input validation or parameterization. An authenticated attacker with editor-level privileges can inject crafted SQL expressions into the id_parent parameter to manipulate the backend query. Successful exploitation can result in disclosure or modification of database contents and may lead to denial of service depending on the database configuration and privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3147 | libvips csvload.c vips_foreign_load_csv_build heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libvips up to 8.18.0. This affects the function vips_foreign_load_csv_build of the file libvips/foreign/csvload.c. The manipulation results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is identified as b3ab458a25e0e261cbd1788474bbc763f7435780. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5781 | Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Configuration Manager, Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5781</link><description>Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager, Hitachi Configuration Manager, Hitachi Device Manager allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center API Configuration Manager: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.5-00; Hitachi Configuration Manager: from 8.5.1-00 before 11.0.5-00; Hitachi Device Manager: from 8.4.1-00 before 8.6.5-00.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25135 | OpenEMR&amp;#x27;s location resource for Group.$export operation returns entire patient/user population contact information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25135</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions prior to 8.0.0 have an information disclosure vulnerability that leaks the entire contact information for all users, organizations, and patients in the system to anyone who has the system/(Group,Patient,*).$export operation and system/Location.read capabilities.  This vulnerability will impact OpenEMR versions since 2023. This disclosure will only occur in extremely high trust environments as it requires using a confidential client with secure key exchange that requires an administrator to enable and grant permission before the app can even be used. This will typically only occur in server-server communication across trusted clients that already have established legal agreements. Version 8.0.0 contains a patch. As a workaround, disable clients that have the vulnerable scopes and only allow clients that do not have the system/Location.read scope until a fix has been deployed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27595 | Parse Dashboard has incomplete authentication on AI Agent endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27595</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the AI Agent API endpoint (POST `/apps/:appId/agent`) has multiple security vulnerabilities that, when chained, allow unauthenticated remote attackers to perform arbitrary read and write operations against any connected Parse Server database using the master key. The agent feature is opt-in; dashboards without an agent config are not affected. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 adds authentication, CSRF validation, and per-app authorization middleware to the agent endpoint. Read-only users are restricted to the `readOnlyMasterKey` with write permissions stripped server-side. A cache key collision between master key and read-only master key was also corrected. As a workaround, remove or comment out the agent configuration block from your Parse Dashboard configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27606 | Rollup 4 has Arbitrary File Write via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27606</link><description>Rollup is a module bundler for JavaScript. Versions prior to 2.80.0, 3.30.0, and 4.59.0 of the Rollup module bundler (specifically v4.x and present in current source) is vulnerable to an Arbitrary File Write via Path Traversal. Insecure file name sanitization in the core engine allows an attacker to control output filenames (e.g., via CLI named inputs, manual chunk aliases, or malicious plugins) and use traversal sequences (`../`) to overwrite files anywhere on the host filesystem that the build process has permissions for. This can lead to persistent Remote Code Execution (RCE) by overwriting critical system or user configuration files. Versions 2.80.0, 3.30.0, and 4.59.0 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27607 | RustFS&amp;#x27;s Missing Post Policy Validation leads to Arbitrary Object Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27607</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. In versions 1.0.0-alpha.56 through 1.0.0-alpha.82, RustFS does not validate policy conditions in presigned POST uploads (PostObject), allowing attackers to bypass content-length-range, starts-with, and Content-Type constraints. This enables unauthorized file uploads exceeding size limits, uploads to arbitrary object keys, and content-type spoofing, potentially leading to storage exhaustion, unauthorized data access, and security bypasses. Version 1.0.0-alpha.83 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27608 | Parse Dashboard Missing Authorization on Agent Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27608</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the AI Agent API endpoint (`POST /apps/:appId/agent`) does not enforce authorization. Authenticated users scoped to specific apps can access any other app's agent endpoint by changing the app ID in the URL. Read-only users are given the full master key instead of the read-only master key and can supply write permissions in the request body to perform write and delete operations. Only dashboards with `agent` configuration enabled are affected. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 adds per-app authorization checks and restricts read-only users to the `readOnlyMasterKey` with write permissions stripped server-side. As a workaround, remove the `agent` configuration block from your dashboard configuration. Dashboards without an `agent` config are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27609 | Parse Dashboard Missing CSRF Protection on Agent Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27609</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the AI Agent API endpoint (`POST /apps/:appId/agent`) lacks CSRF protection. An attacker can craft a malicious page that, when visited by an authenticated dashboard user, submits requests to the agent endpoint using the victim's session. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 adds CSRF middleware to the agent endpoint and embeds a CSRF token in the dashboard page. As a workaround, remove the `agent` configuration block from your dashboard configuration. Dashboards without an `agent` config are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27610 | Parse Dashboard Has a Cache Key Collision that Leaks Master Key to Read-Only Sessions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27610</link><description>Parse Dashboard is a standalone dashboard for managing Parse Server apps. In versions 7.3.0-alpha.42 through 9.0.0-alpha.7, the `ConfigKeyCache` uses the same cache key for both master key and read-only master key when resolving function-typed keys. Under specific timing conditions, a read-only user can receive the cached full master key, or a regular user can receive the cached read-only master key. The fix in version 9.0.0-alpha.8 uses distinct cache keys for master key and read-only master key. As a workaround, avoid using function-typed master keys, or remove the `agent` configuration block from your dashboard configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27611 | FileBrowser Quantum: Password Protection Not Enforced on Shared File Links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27611</link><description>FileBrowser Quantum is a free, self-hosted, web-based file manager. Prior to versions 1.1.3-stable and 1.2.6-beta, when users share password-protected files, the recipient can completely bypass the password and still download the file. This happens because the API returns a direct download link in the details of the share, which is accessible to anyone with JUST THE SHARE LINK, even without the password. Versions 1.1.3-stable and 1.2.6-beta fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27612 | Repostat Vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via repo prop in RepoCard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27612</link><description>Repostat is a React component to fetch and display GitHub repository info. Prior to version 1.0.1, the `RepoCard` component is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability occurs because the component uses React's `dangerouslySetInnerHTML` to render the repository name (`repo` prop) during the loading state without any sanitization. If a developer using this package passes unvalidated user input directly into the `repo` prop (for example, reading it from a URL query parameter), an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the user's browser. In version 1.0.1, the use of dangerouslySetInnerHTML has been removed, and the repo prop is now safely rendered using standard React JSX data binding, which automatically escapes HTML entities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27614 | Bugsink is vulnerable to Stored XSS via Pygments fallback in stacktrace rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27614</link><description>Bugsink is a self-hosted error tracking tool. In versions prior to 2.0.13, an unauthenticated attacker who can submit events to a Bugsink project can store arbitrary JavaScript in an event. The payload executes only if a user explicitly views the affected Stacktrace in the web UI. When Pygments returns more lines than it was given (a known upstream quirk that triggers with Ruby heredoc-style input), `_pygmentize_lines()` in `theme/templatetags/issues.py:75-77` falls back to returning the raw input lines. `mark_safe()` at line 111-113 is then applied unconditionally - including to those unsanitized raw lines. Since DSN endpoints are public by Sentry protocol, no account is needed to inject. The payload sits in the database until an admin looks at the event. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker to be able to submit events to the project (i.e. knows the DSN or can access a client that uses it), the Bugsink ingest endpoint is reachable to the attacker, and an administrator explicitly views the crafted event in the UI. Under those conditions, the attacker can execute JavaScript in the administrator’s browser and act with that user’s privileges within Bugsink. Version 2.0.13 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27615 | ADB-Explorer: UNC Path Support in ManualAdbPath Leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27615</link><description>ADB Explorer is a fluent UI for ADB on Windows. In versions prior to Beta 0.9.26022, ADB-Explorer allows the `ManualAdbPath` settings variable, which determines the path of the ADB binary to be executed, to be set to a Universal Naming Convention (UNC) path in the application's settings file. This allows an attacker to set the binary's path to point to a remote network resource, hosted on an attacker-controlled network share, thus granting the attacker full control over the binary being executed by the app. An attacker may leverage this vulnerability to execute code remotely on a victim's machine with the privileges of the user running the app. Exploitation is made possible by convincing a victim to run a shortcut of the app that points to a custom `App.txt` settings file, which sets `ManualAdbPath` (for example, when downloaded in an archive file). Version Beta 0.9.26022 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27621 | TypiCMS Core has Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27621</link><description>TypiCMS is a multilingual content management system based on the Laravel framework. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the file upload module of TypiCMS prior to version 16.1.7. The application allows users with file upload permissions to upload SVG files. While there is a MIME type validation, the content of the SVG file is not sanitized. An attacker can upload a specially crafted SVG file containing malicious JavaScript code. When another user (such as an administrator) views or accesses this file through the application, the script executes in their browser, leading to a compromise of that user's session. The issue is exacerbated by a bug in the SVG parsing logic, which can cause a 500 error if the uploaded SVG does not contain a `viewBox` attribute. However, this does not mitigate the XSS vulnerability, as an attacker can easily include a valid `viewBox` attribute in their malicious payload. Version 16.1.7 of TypiCMS Core fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27626 | OliveTin vulnerable to OS Command Injection via `password` argument type and webhook JSON extraction bypasses shell safety checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27626</link><description>OliveTin gives access to predefined shell commands from a web interface. In versions up to and including 3000.10.0, OliveTin's shell mode safety check (`checkShellArgumentSafety`) blocks several dangerous argument types but not `password`. A user supplying a `password`-typed argument can inject shell metacharacters that execute arbitrary OS commands. A second independent vector allows unauthenticated RCE via webhook-extracted JSON values that skip type safety checks entirely before reaching `sh -c`. When exploiting vector 1, any authenticated user (registration enabled by default, `authType: none` by default) can execute arbitrary OS commands on the OliveTin host with the permissions of the OliveTin process. When exploiting vector 2, an unauthenticated attacker can achieve the same if the instance receives webhooks from external sources, which is a primary OliveTin use case. When an attacker exploits both vectors, this results in unauthenticated RCE on any OliveTin instance using Shell mode with webhook-triggered actions. As of time of publication, a patched version is not available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27628 | pypdf has a possible infinite loop when loading circular /Prev entries in cross-reference streams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27628</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to 6.7.2, an attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to an infinite loop. This requires reading the file. This has been fixed in pypdf 6.7.2. As a workaround, one may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27629 | InvenTree Vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection (SSTI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27629</link><description>InvenTree is an Open Source Inventory Management System. Prior to version 1.2.3, insecure server-side templates can be hijacked to expose secure information to the client. When generating custom batch codes, the InvenTree server makes use of a customizable jinja2 template, which can be modified by a staff user to exfiltrate sensitive information or perform code execution on the server. This issue requires access by a user with granted staff permissions, followed by a request to generate a custom batch code via the API. Once the template has been modified in a malicious manner, the API call to generate a new batch code could be made by other users, and the template code will be executed with their user context. The code has been patched to ensure that all template generation is performed within a secure sandboxed context. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.3, and any versions from 1.3.0 onwards. Some workarounds are available. The batch code template is a configurable global setting which can be adjusted via any user with staff access. To prevent this setting from being edited, it can be overridden at a system level to a default value, preventing it from being edited. This requires system administrator access, and cannot be changed from the client side once the server is running. It is recommended that for InvenTree installations prior to 1.2.3 the `STOCK_BATCH_CODE_TEMPLATE` and `PART_NAME_FORMAT` global settings are overridden at the system level to prevent editing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27632 | Talishar Vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27632</link><description>Talishar is a fan-made Flesh and Blood project. Prior to commit 6be3871a14c192d1fb8146cdbc76f29f27c1cf48, the Talishar application lacks Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protections on critical state-changing endpoints, specifically within `SubmitChat.php` and other game interaction handlers. By failing to require unique, unpredictable session tokens, the application allows third-party malicious websites to forge requests on behalf of authenticated users, leading to unauthorized actions within active game sessions. The attacker would need to know both the proper gameName and playerID for the player. The player would also need to be browsing and interact with the infected website while playing a game. The vulnerability is fixed in commit 6be3871a14c192d1fb8146cdbc76f29f27c1cf48.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27822 | Rust has Critical Stored XSS in Preview Modal, leading to Administrative Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27822</link><description>RustFS is a distributed object storage system built in Rust. Prior to version 1.0.0-alpha.83, a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the RustFS Console allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the management console. By bypassing the PDF preview logic, an attacker can steal administrator credentials from `localStorage`, leading to full account takeover and system compromise. Version 1.0.0-alpha.83 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3145 | libvips matrixload.c vips_foreign_load_matrix_header memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3145</link><description>A flaw has been found in libvips up to 8.18.0. The affected element is the function vips_foreign_load_matrix_file_is_a/vips_foreign_load_matrix_header of the file libvips/foreign/matrixload.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to memory corruption. The attack needs to be launched locally. This patch is called d4ce337c76bff1b278d7085c3c4f4725e3aa6ece. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3146 | libvips matrixload.c vips_foreign_load_matrix_header null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3146</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in libvips up to 8.18.0. The impacted element is the function vips_foreign_load_matrix_header of the file libvips/foreign/matrixload.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be performed locally. The identifier of the patch is d4ce337c76bff1b278d7085c3c4f4725e3aa6ece. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:48:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69231 | OpenEMR has a Stored XSS in GAD-7 Form that Enables Session Hijacking and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69231</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the GAD-7 anxiety assessment form allows authenticated users with clinician privileges to inject malicious JavaScript that executes when other users view the form. This enables session hijacking, account takeover, and privilege escalation from clinician to administrator. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21443 | OpenEMR allows inconsistent escaping of translation function output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21443</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the `xl()` translation function returns unescaped strings. While wrapper functions exist for escaping in different contexts (`xlt()` for HTML, `xla()` for attributes, `xlj()` for JavaScript), there are places in the codebase where `xl()` output is used directly without escaping. If an attacker could insert malicious content into the translation database, these unescaped outputs could lead to XSS. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24847 | OpenEMR has Open Redirect in Eye Exam Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24847</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the Eye Exam form module allows any authenticated user to be redirected to an arbitrary external URL. This can be exploited for phishing attacks against healthcare providers using OpenEMR. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24849 | OpenEMR Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24849</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 7.0.4, the `disposeDocument()` method in `EtherFaxActions.php` allows authenticated users to read arbitrary files from the server filesystem. Any authenticated user (regardless of privilege level) can exploit this vulnerability to read sensitive files. Version 7.0.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24896 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control that allows unauthorized access to EDI Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24896</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, a Broken Access Control vulnerability exists in OpenEMR’s edih_main.php endpoint, which allows any authenticated user—including low-privilege roles like Receptionist—to access EDI log files by manipulating the log_select parameter in a GET request. The back-end fails to enforce role-based access control (RBAC), allowing sensitive system logs to be accessed outside the GUI-enforced permission boundaries. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25124 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control in Report/Clients/Message List CSV Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25124</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the OpenEMR application is vulnerable to an access control flaw that allows low-privileged users, such as receptionists, to export the entire message list containing sensitive patient and user data. The vulnerability lies in the message_list.php report export functionality, where there is no permission check before executing sensitive database queries. The only control in place is CSRF token verification, which does not prevent unauthorized data access if the token is acquired through other means. Version 8.0.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25127 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control on Care Coordination Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25127</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, the server does not properly validate user permission. Unauthorized users can view the information of authorized users. Version 8.0.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25131 | OpenEMR has Broken Access Control in Procedures Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25131</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 8.0.0, a Broken Access Control vulnerability exists in the OpenEMR order types management system, allowing low-privilege users (such as Receptionist) to add and modify procedure types without proper authorization. This vulnerability is present in the /openemr/interface/orders/types_edit.php endpoint. Version 8.0.0 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2914 | CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager Agent versions 25.10.0 and lower allow potential unauthorized privilege elevation leveraging CyberArk el...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2914</link><description>CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager Agent versions 25.10.0 and lower allow potential unauthorized privilege elevation leveraging CyberArk elevation dialogs</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67752 | OpenEMR Has Disabled SSL Certificate Verification in HTTP Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67752</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 7.0.4, OpenEMR's HTTP client wrapper (`oeHttp`/`oeHttpRequest`) disables SSL/TLS certificate verification by default (`verify: false`), making all external HTTPS connections vulnerable to man-in-the-middle (MITM) attacks. This affects communication with government healthcare APIs and user-configurable external services, potentially exposing Protected Health Information (PHI). Version 7.0.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68277 | OpenEMR allows links sent via Secure Messaging to be opened in OpenEMR and Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68277</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Prior to version 7.0.4, when a link is sent via Secure Messaging, clicking the link opens the website within the OpenEMR/Portal site. This behavior could be exploited for phishing. Version 7.0.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67491 | OpenEMR has Stored XSS in ub04 helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67491</link><description>OpenEMR is a free and open source electronic health records and medical practice management application. Versions 5.0.0.5 through 7.0.3.4 have a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the ub04 helper of the billing interface. The variable `$data` is passed in a click event handler enclosed in single quotes without proper sanitization. Thus, despite `json_encode` a malicious user can still inject a payload such as ` ac' &gt;&lt;img src="x" /&gt; ` to trigger the bug. This vulnerability allows low privileged users to embed malicious JS payloads on the server and perform stored XSS attack. This, in turn makes it possible for malicious users to steal the session cookies and perform unauthorized actions impersonating administrators. Version 7.0.4 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27598 | Dagu: Path traversal in DAG creation allows arbitrary YAML file write outside DAGs directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27598</link><description>Dagu is a workflow engine with a built-in Web user interface. In versions up to and including 1.16.7, the `CreateNewDAG` API endpoint (`POST /api/v1/dags`) does not validate the DAG name before passing it to the file store. An authenticated user with DAG write permissions can write arbitrary YAML files anywhere on the filesystem (limited by the process permissions). Since dagu executes DAG files as shell commands, writing a malicious DAG to the DAGs directory of another instance or overwriting config files can lead to remote code execution. Commit e2ed589105d79273e4e6ac8eb31525f765bb3ce4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3135 | itsourcecode News Portal Project add-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3135</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-category.php. This manipulation of the argument Category causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3137 | CodeAstro Food Ordering System food_ordering.exe stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3137</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Food Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file food_ordering.exe. Such manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3133 | itsourcecode Document Management System Login loging.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3133</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /loging.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3134 | itsourcecode News Portal Project edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3134</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /newsportal/admin/edit-category.php. The manipulation of the argument Category results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26351 | GetSimpleCMS-CE &amp;lt; 3.3.22 Stored XSS via components.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26351</link><description>GetSimpleCMS Community Edition (CE) version 3.3.16 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Theme to Components functionality within components.php. User-supplied input provided to the "slug" field of a component is stored without proper output encoding. While other fields are sanitized using safe_slash_html(), the slug parameter is written to XML and later rendered in the administrative interface without sanitation, resulting in persistent execution of arbitrary JavaScript. An authenticated administrator can inject malicious script content that executes whenever the affected Components page is viewed by any authenticated user, enabling session hijacking, unauthorized administrative actions, and persistent compromise of the CMS administrative interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27117 | bit7z has a path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27117</link><description>bit7z is a cross-platform C++ static library that allows the compression/extraction of archive files. Prior to version 4.0.11, a path traversal vulnerability ("Zip Slip") exists in bit7z's archive extraction functionality. The library does not adequately validate file paths contained in archive entries, allowing files to be written outside the intended extraction directory through three distinct mechanisms: relative path traversal, absolute path traversal, and symbolic link traversal. An attacker can exploit this by providing a malicious archive to any application that uses bit7z to extract untrusted archives. Successful exploitation results in arbitrary file write with the privileges of the process performing the extraction. This could lead to overwriting of application binaries, configuration files, or other sensitive data. The vulnerability does not directly enable reading of file contents; the confidentiality impact is limited to the calling application's own behavior after extraction. However, applications that subsequently serve or display extracted files may face secondary confidentiality risks from attacker-created symlinks. Fixes have been released in version 4.0.11. If upgrading is not immediately possible, users can mitigate the vulnerability by validating each entry's destination path before writing. Other mitigations include running extraction with least privilege and extracting untrusted archives in a sandboxed directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27593 | Statamic is vulnerable to account takeover via password reset link injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27593</link><description>Statmatic is a Laravel and Git powered content management system (CMS). Prior to versions 6.3.3 and 5.73.10, an attacker may leverage a vulnerability in the password reset feature to capture a user's token and reset the password on their behalf. The attacker must know the email address of a valid account on the site, and the actual user must blindly click the link in their email even though they didn't request the reset. This has been fixed in 6.3.3 and 5.73.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27204 | Wasmtime WASI implementations are vulnerable to guest-controlled resource exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27204</link><description>Wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. Prior to versions 24.0.6, 36.0.6, 4.0.04, 41.0.4, and 42.0.0, Wasmtime's implementation of WASI host interfaces are susceptible to guest-controlled resource exhaustion on the host. Wasmtime did not appropriately place limits on resource allocations requested by the guests. This serves as a Denial of Service vector. Wasmtime 24.0.6, 36.0.6, 40.0.4, 41.0.4, and 42.0.0 have all been released with the fix for this issue. These versions do not prevent this issue in their default configuration to avoid breaking preexisting behaviors. All versions of Wasmtime have appropriate knobs to prevent this behavior, and Wasmtime 42.0.0-and-later will have these knobs tuned by default to prevent this issue from happening. There are no known workarounds for this issue without upgrading. Embedders are recommended to upgrade and configure their embeddings as necessary to prevent possibly-malicious guests from triggering this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27572 | Wasmtime can panic when adding excessive fields to a `wasi:http/types.fields` instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27572</link><description>Wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. Prior to versions 24.0.6, 36.0.6, 4.0.04, 41.0.4, and 42.0.0, Wasmtime's implementation of the `wasi:http/types.fields` resource is susceptible to panics when too many fields are added to the set of headers. Wasmtime's implementation in the `wasmtime-wasi-http` crate is backed by a data structure which panics when it reaches excessive capacity and this condition was not handled gracefully in Wasmtime. Panicking in a WASI implementation is a Denial of Service vector for embedders and is treated as a security vulnerability in Wasmtime. Wasmtime 24.0.6, 36.0.6, 40.0.4, 41.0.4, and 42.0.0 patch this vulnerability and return a trap to the guest instead of panicking. There are no known workarounds at this time. Embedders are encouraged to update to a patched version of Wasmtime.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25891 | Fiber has an Arbitrary File Read in Static Middleware on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25891</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. A Path Traversal (CWE-22) vulnerability in Fiber allows a remote attacker to bypass the static middleware sanitizer and read arbitrary files on the server file system on Windows. This affects Fiber v3 through version 3.0.0. This has been patched in Fiber v3 version 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25899 | Fiber is Vulnerable to Denial of Service via Flash Cookie Unbounded Allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25899</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. In versions on the v3 branch prior to 3.1.0, the use of the `fiber_flash` cookie can force an unbounded allocation on any server. A crafted 10-character cookie value triggers an attempt to allocate up to 85GB of memory via unvalidated msgpack deserialization. No authentication is required. Every GoFiber v3 endpoint is affected regardless of whether the application uses flash messages. Version 3.1.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27195 | Wasmtime is vulnerable to panic when dropping a `[Typed]Func::call_async` future</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27195</link><description>Wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. Starting with Wasmtime 39.0.0, the `component-model-async` feature became the default, which brought with it a new implementation of `[Typed]Func::call_async` which made it capable of calling async-typed guest export functions.  However, that implementation had a bug leading to a panic under certain circumstances: First, the host embedding calls `[Typed]Func::call_async` on a function exported by a component, polling the returned `Future` once. Second, the component function yields control to the async runtime (e.g. Tokio), e.g. due to a call to host function registered using `LinkerInstance::func_wrap_async` which yields, or due an epoch interruption. Third, the host embedding drops the `Future` after polling it once.  This leaves the component instance in a non-reenterable state since the call never had a chance to complete. Fourth, the host embedding calls `[Typed]Func::call_async` again, polling the returned `Future`.  Since the component instance cannot be entered at this point, the call traps, but not before allocating a task and thread for the call. Fifth, the host embedding ignores the trap and drops the `Future`.  This panics due to the runtime attempting to dispose of the task created above, which panics since the thread has not yet exited. When a host embedder using the affected versions of Wasmtime calls `wasmtime::component::[Typed]Func::call_async` on a guest export and then drops the returned future without waiting for it to resolve, and then does so again with the same component instance, Wasmtime will panic. Embeddings that have the `component-model-async` compile-time feature disabled are unaffected. Wasmtime 40.0.4 and 41.0.4 have been patched to fix this issue. Versions 42.0.0 and later are not affected. If an embedding is not actually using any component-model-async features then disabling the `component-model-async` Cargo feature can work around this issue. This issue can also be worked around by either ensuring every `call_async` future is awaited until it completes or refraining from using the `Store` again after dropping a not-yet-resolved `call_async` future.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21410 | InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21410</link><description>InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS is susceptible to SQL Injection through its main web interface. Malicious users that use the vulnerable endpoint are potentially able to cause remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22553 | InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22553</link><description>All versions of InSAT MasterSCADA BUK-TS are susceptible to OS command injection through a field in its MMadmServ web interface. Malicious users that use the vulnerable endpoint are potentially able to cause remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25882 | Fiber has a Denial of Service Vulnerability via Route Parameter Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25882</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. A denial of service vulnerability exists in Fiber v2 and v3 that allows remote attackers to crash the application by sending requests to routes with more than 30 parameters. The vulnerability results from missing validation during route registration combined with an unbounded array write during request matching. Version 2.52.12 patches the issue in the v2 branch and 3.1.0 patches the issue in the v3 branch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46320 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in a FileMaker WebDirect custom homepage could lead to unauthorized access and remote code execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46320</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in a FileMaker WebDirect custom homepage could lead to unauthorized access and remote code execution. This vulnerability has been fully addressed in FileMaker Server 22.0.4 and FileMaker Server 21.1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24443 | EventSentry &amp;lt; 6.0.1.20 Web Reports Unverified Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24443</link><description>EventSentry versions prior to 6.0.1.20 contain an unverified password change vulnerability in the account management functionality of the Web Reports interface. The password change mechanism does not require validation of the current password before allowing a new password to be set. An attacker who gains temporary access to an authenticated user session can change the account password without knowledge of the original credentials. This enables persistent account takeover and, if administrative accounts are affected, may result in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10010 | Integrity Validation Bypass in CryptoPro Secure Disk for BitLocker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10010</link><description>The CPSD CryptoPro Secure Disk application boots a small Linux operating system to perform user authentication before using BitLocker to decrypt the Windows partition. The system is located on a separate unencrypted partition which can be reached by anyone with access to the hard disk.

Multiple checks are performed to validate the integrity of the Linux operating system and the CryptoPro Secure Disk application files. When files are changed an error is shown on system start. One of the checks is the Linux kernel's Integrity Measurement Architecture (IMA). It was identified that configuration files are not validated by the IMA and can then (if not checked by other measures) be changed. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the root user and enables an attacker to e.g., plant a backdoor and access data during execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27208 | api-gateway-deploy Affected by Exploitable Command Injection via Unprivileged Root Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27208</link><description>bleon-ethical/api-gateway-deploy provides API gateway deployment. Version 1.0.0 is vulnerable to an attack chain involving OS Command Injection and Privilege Escalation. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges within the container, potentially leading to a container escape and unauthorized infrastructure modifications. This is fixed in version 1.0.1 by implementing strict input sanitization and secure delimiters in entrypoint.sh, enforcing a non-root user (appuser) in the Dockerfile, and establishing mandatory security quality gates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27483 | MindsDB has Path Traversal in /api/files Leading to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27483</link><description>MindsDB is a platform for building artificial intelligence from enterprise data. Prior to version 25.9.1.1, there is a path traversal vulnerability in Mindsdb's /api/files interface, which an authenticated attacker can exploit to achieve remote command execution. The vulnerability exists in the "Upload File" module, which corresponds to the API endpoint /api/files. Since the multipart file upload does not perform security checks on the uploaded file path, an attacker can perform path traversal by using `../` sequences in the filename field. The file write operation occurs before calling clear_filename and save_file, meaning there is no filtering of filenames or file types, allowing arbitrary content to be written to any path on the server. Version 25.9.1.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14577 | PHP Function Injection in Slican NPC/IPL/IPM/IPU</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14577</link><description>Slican NCP/IPL/IPM/IPU devices are vulnerable to PHP Function Injection. An unauthenticated remote attacker is able to execute arbitrary PHP commands by sending specially crafted requests to /webcti/session_ajax.php endpoint.


This issue was fixed in version 1.24.0190 (Slican NCP) and 6.61.0010 (Slican IPL/IPM/IPU).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2459 | A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with Installer role to access and alter the contents of directories that the role...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2459</link><description>A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with Installer role to access and alter the contents of directories that the role is not authorized to do so.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2460 | A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with low-level privileges to access and alter the content of directories by using...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2460</link><description>A vulnerability exists in REB500 for an authenticated user with low-level privileges to access and alter the content of directories by using the DAC protocol that the user is not authorized to do so.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2634 | Spoofed web content presented under trusted domains using scripted navigation on Firefox iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2634</link><description>Malicious scripts could cause desynchronization between the address bar and web content before a response is received in Firefox iOS, allowing attacker-controlled pages to be presented under spoofed domains. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 147.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2757 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the WebRTC: Audio/Video component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2757</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the WebRTC: Audio/Video component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2758 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2758</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2759 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: ImageLib component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2759</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: ImageLib component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2760 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebRender component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2760</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebRender component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2761 | Sandbox escape in the Graphics: WebRender component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2761</link><description>Sandbox escape in the Graphics: WebRender component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2762 | Integer overflow in the JavaScript: Standard Library component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2762</link><description>Integer overflow in the JavaScript: Standard Library component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2763 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2763</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2764 | JIT miscompilation, use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2764</link><description>JIT miscompilation, use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2765 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2765</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2766 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2766</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2767 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2767</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2768 | Sandbox escape in the Storage: IndexedDB component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2768</link><description>Sandbox escape in the Storage: IndexedDB component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2769 | Use-after-free in the Storage: IndexedDB component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2769</link><description>Use-after-free in the Storage: IndexedDB component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2770 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Bindings (WebIDL) component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2770</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Bindings (WebIDL) component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2771 | Undefined behavior in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2771</link><description>Undefined behavior in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2772 | Use-after-free in the Audio/Video: Playback component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2772</link><description>Use-after-free in the Audio/Video: Playback component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2773 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Web Audio component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2773</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Web Audio component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2774 | Integer overflow in the Audio/Video component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2774</link><description>Integer overflow in the Audio/Video component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2775 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: HTML Parser component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2775</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: HTML Parser component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2776 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Telemetry component in External Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2776</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Telemetry component in External Software. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2777 | Privilege escalation in the Messaging System component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2777</link><description>Privilege escalation in the Messaging System component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2778 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2778</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2779 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Networking: JAR component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2779</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Networking: JAR component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2780 | Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2780</link><description>Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2781 | Integer overflow in the Libraries component in NSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2781</link><description>Integer overflow in the Libraries component in NSS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2782 | Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2782</link><description>Privilege escalation in the Netmonitor component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2783 | Information disclosure due to JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2783</link><description>Information disclosure due to JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2784 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2784</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2785 | Invalid pointer in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2785</link><description>Invalid pointer in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2786 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2786</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript Engine component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2787 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Window and Location component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2787</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Window and Location component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2788 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Audio/Video: GMP component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2788</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Audio/Video: GMP component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2789 | Use-after-free in the Graphics: ImageLib component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2789</link><description>Use-after-free in the Graphics: ImageLib component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2790 | Same-origin policy bypass in the Networking: JAR component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2790</link><description>Same-origin policy bypass in the Networking: JAR component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2791 | Mitigation bypass in the Networking: Cache component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2791</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the Networking: Cache component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2792 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox ESR 140.8, Thunderbird ESR 140.8, Firefox 148 and Thunderbird 148</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2792</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.7, Thunderbird ESR 140.7, Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2793 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox ESR 115.33, Firefox ESR 140.8, Thunderbird ESR 140.8, Firefox 148 and Thunderbird 148</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2793</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 115.32, Firefox ESR 140.7, Thunderbird ESR 140.7, Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.33, and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2794 | Information disclosure due to uninitialized memory in Firefox and Firefox Focus for Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2794</link><description>Information disclosure due to uninitialized memory in Firefox and Firefox Focus for Android. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2795 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2795</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2796 | JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2796</link><description>JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2797 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2797</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2798 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2798</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2799 | Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2799</link><description>Use-after-free in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2800 | Spoofing issue in the WebAuthn component in Firefox for Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2800</link><description>Spoofing issue in the WebAuthn component in Firefox for Android. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2801 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2801</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2802 | Race condition in the JavaScript: GC component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2802</link><description>Race condition in the JavaScript: GC component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2803 | Information disclosure, mitigation bypass in the Settings UI component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2803</link><description>Information disclosure, mitigation bypass in the Settings UI component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2804 | Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2804</link><description>Use-after-free in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2805 | Invalid pointer in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2805</link><description>Invalid pointer in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2806 | Uninitialized memory in the Graphics: Text component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2806</link><description>Uninitialized memory in the Graphics: Text component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2807 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox 148 and Thunderbird 148</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2807</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 147 and Thunderbird 147. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 148.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1772 | RTU500 web interface: An unprivileged user can read user management information. The information cannot be accessed via the RTU500 web user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1772</link><description>RTU500 web interface: An unprivileged user can read user management information. The information cannot be accessed via the RTU500 web user interface but requires further tools like browser development utilities to access them without required privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1773 | IEC 60870-5-104: Potential Denial of Service impact on reception of invalid U-format frame. Product is only affected if IEC 60870-5-104 bi-d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1773</link><description>IEC 60870-5-104: Potential Denial of Service impact on reception of invalid U-format frame. Product is only affected if IEC 60870-5-104 bi-directional functionality is configured. Enabling secure communication following IEC 62351-3 does not remediate the vulnerability but mitigates the risk of exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23969 | Apache Superset: Exposure of Sensitive Information via Incomplete ClickHouse Function Filtering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23969</link><description>Apache Superset utilizes a configurable dictionary, DISALLOWED_SQL_FUNCTIONS, to restrict the execution of potentially sensitive SQL functions within SQL Lab and charts. While this feature included restrictions for engines like PostgreSQL, a vulnerability was reported where the default list for the ClickHouse engine was incomplete.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.1.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.1.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23980 | Apache Superset: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a SQL Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23980</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Superset allows an authenticated user with read access to conduct error-based SQL injection via the sqlExpression or where parameters.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23982 | Apache Superset: Improper Authorization in Dataset Creation Allows Access Control Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23982</link><description>An Improper Authorization vulnerability exists in Apache Superset that allows a low-privileged user to bypass data access controls. When creating a dataset, Superset enforces permission checks to prevent users from querying unauthorized data. However, an authenticated attacker with permissions to write datasets and read charts can bypass these checks by overwriting the SQL query of an existing dataset.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23983 | Apache Superset: Sensitive Data Exposure via REST API (disabled by default)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23983</link><description>A Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability exists in Apache Superset allowing authenticated users to retrieve sensitive user information. The Tag endpoint (disabled by default) allows users to retrieve a list of objects associated with a specific tag.
When these associated objects include Users, the API response improperly serializes and returns sensitive fields, including password hashes (pbkdf2), email addresses, and login statistics. This vulnerability allows authenticated users with low privileges (e.g., Gamma role) to view sensitive authentication data 

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue or make sure TAGGING_SYSTEM is False (Apache Superset current default)</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23984 | Apache Superset: SQLLab Read-Only Bypass on PostgreSQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23984</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists in Apache Superset that allows an authenticated user with SQLLab access to bypass the read-only verification check when using a PostgreSQL database connection.
While the system effectively blocks standard Data Manipulation Language (DML) statements (e.g., INSERT, UPDATE, DELETE) on read-only connections, it fails to detect them in specially crafted SQL statements.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 6.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56373 | Apache Airflow: SSTI to Code Execution in Airflow through Shared DB Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56373</link><description>DAG Author (who already has quite a lot of permissions) could manipulate database of Airflow 2 in the way to execute arbitrary code in the web-server context, which they should normally not be able to do, leading to potentially remote code execution in the context of web-server (server-side) as a result of a user viewing historical task information.

The functionality responsible for that (log template history) has been disabled by default in 2.11.1 and users should upgrade to Airflow 3 if they want to continue to use log template history. They can also manually modify historical log file names if they want to see historical logs that were generated before the last log template change.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27555 | Apache Airflow: Connection Secrets not masked in UI when Connection are added via Airflow cli</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27555</link><description>Airflow versions before 2.11.1 have a vulnerability that allows authenticated users with audit log access to see sensitive values in audit logs which they should not see. When sensitive connection parameters were set via airflow CLI, values of those variables appeared in the audit log and were stored unencrypted in the Airflow database. While this risk is limited to users with audit log access, it is recommended to upgrade to Airflow 2.11.1 or a later version, which addresses this issue. Users who previously used the CLI to set connections should manually delete entries with those connection sensitive values from the log table. This is similar but not the same issue as CVE-2024-50378</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2664 | Out of bounds read vulnerability in grpcfuse kernel module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2664</link><description>An out of bounds read vulnerability in the grpcfuse kernel module present in the Linux VM in Docker Desktop for Windows, Linux and macOS up to version 4.61.0 could allow a local attacker to cause an unspecified impact by writing to /proc/docker entries. The issue has been fixed in Docker Desktop 4.62.0 .</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1524 | A local user can be impersonated when using federated authentication with Silent JIT Provisioning.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1524</link><description>When the "Silent Just-In-Time Provisioning" feature is enabled for a federated identity provider (IDP)  there is a risk that a local user store user's information may be replaced during the account provisioning process in cases where federated users share the same username as local users. 

 There will be no impact on your deployment if any of the preconditions mentioned below are not met. Only when all the preconditions mentioned below are fulfilled could a malicious actor associate a targeted local user account with a federated IDP user account that they control.

The Deployment should have: 
-An IDP configured for federated authentication with Silent JIT provisioning enabled.

The malicious actor should have:
-A fresh valid user account in the federated IDP that has not been used earlier.
-Knowledge of the username of a valid user in the local IDP. 
-An account at the federated IDP matching the targeted local username.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11165 | A sandbox escape vulnerability exists in dotCMS’s Velocity scripting engine (VTools) that allows authenticated users with scripting privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11165</link><description>A sandbox escape vulnerability exists in dotCMS’s Velocity scripting engine (VTools) that allows authenticated users with scripting privileges to bypass class and package restrictions enforced by SecureUberspectorImpl.

By dynamically modifying the Velocity engine’s runtime configuration and reinitializing its Uberspect, a malicious actor can remove the introspector.restrict.classes and introspector.restrict.packages protections.

Once these restrictions are cleared, the attacker can access arbitrary Java classes, including java.lang.Runtime, and execute arbitrary system commands under the privileges of the application process (e.g. dotCMS or Tomcat user).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40541 | SolarWinds Serv-U Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40541</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in Serv-U, which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to execute native code as a privileged account.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1229 | Incorrect calculation in CIRCL secp384r1 CombinedMult</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1229</link><description>The CombinedMult function in the CIRCL ecc/p384 package (secp384r1 curve) produces an incorrect value for specific inputs. The issue is fixed by using complete addition formulas.
ECDH and ECDSA signing relying on this curve are not affected.

The bug was fixed in  v1.6.3 https://github.com/cloudflare/circl/releases/tag/v1.6.3 .</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40538 | SolarWinds Serv-U Broken Access Control Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40538</link><description>A broken access control vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to create a system admin user and execute arbitrary code as a privileged account via domain admin or group admin privileges.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40539 | SolarWinds Serv-U Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40539</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to execute arbitrary native code as privileged account.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40540 | SolarWinds Serv-U Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40540</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when exploited, gives a malicious actor the ability to execute arbitrary native code as privileged account.

This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows deployments, the risk is scored as a medium because services frequently run under less-privileged service accounts by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15386 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt; 2.6.1 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15386</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery WordPress plugin before 2.6.1 is vulnerable to an Unauthenticated Stored-XSS attack due to flawed regex replacement rules that can be abused by posting a comment with a malicious link when lightbox for comments are enabled and then approved.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15589 | MuYuCMS Template Management Template.php delete_dir_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15589</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in MuYuCMS 2.7. Affected is the function delete_dir_file of the file application/admin/controller/Template.php of the component Template Management Page. This manipulation of the argument temn/tp causes path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24314 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in S/4HANA (Manage Payment Media)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24314</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP S/4HANA (Manage Payment Media) allows an authenticated attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted. This could cause low impact on confidentiality of the application while integrity and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3070 | SourceCodester Modern Image Gallery App upload.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3070</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Modern Image Gallery App 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file upload.php. The manipulation of the argument filename results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 05:48:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3069 | itsourcecode Document Management System edtlbls.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3069</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edtlbls.php. The manipulation of the argument field1 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27461 | Pimcore vulnerable to SQL injection via unsanitized filter value in Dependency Dao RLIKE clause</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27461</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. In versions up to and including 11.5.14.1 and 12.3.2, the filter query parameter in the dependency listing endpoints is JSON-decoded and the value field is concatenated directly into RLIKE clauses without sanitization or parameterized queries. Exploiting this issue requires admin authentication. An attacker with admin panel access can extract the full database including password hashes of other admin users. Version 12.3.3 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3066 | HummerRisk Cloud Compliance Scanning PlatformUtils.java fixedCommand command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3066</link><description>A flaw has been found in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. This vulnerability affects the function fixedCommand of the file hummer-common/hummer-common-core/src/main/java/com/hummer/common/core/utils/PlatformUtils.java of the component Cloud Compliance Scanning. Executing a manipulation can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3067 | HummerRisk Archive Extraction CommandUtils.java extractZip path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3067</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. This issue affects the function extractTarGZ/extractZip of the file hummer-common/hummer-common-core/src/main/java/com/hummer/common/core/utils/CommandUtils.java of the component Archive Extraction. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3068 | itsourcecode Document Management System deluser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3068</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Document Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /deluser.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument user2del can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11847 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the IP settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11847</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the IP settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11848 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Wake-on-LAN CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware version through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11848</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the Wake-on-LAN CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware version through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13942 | A command injection vulnerability in the UPnP function of the Zyxel EX3510-B0 firmware versions through 5.17(ABUP.15.1)C0 could allow a remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13942</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the UPnP function of the Zyxel EX3510-B0 firmware versions through 5.17(ABUP.15.1)C0 could allow a remote attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by sending specially crafted UPnP SOAP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13943 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the log file download function of the Zyxel EX3301-T0 firmware versions through 5.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13943</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the log file download function of the Zyxel EX3301-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVY.7)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1459 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the TR-369 certificate download CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1459</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the TR-369 certificate download CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.7)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25989 | ImageMagick has integer overflow or wraparound and incorrect conversion between numeric types in the internal SVG decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25989</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted SVG file can cause a denial of service. An off-by-one boundary check (`&gt;` instead of `&gt;=`) that allows bypass the guard and reach an undefined `(size_t)` cast. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26066 | ImageMagick has infinite loop when writing IPTCTEXT leads to denial of service via crafted profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26066</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted profile contain invalid IPTC data may cause an infinite loop when writing it with `IPTCTEXT`. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26198 | ormar is vulnerable to SQL Injection through aggregate functions min() and max()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26198</link><description>Ormar is a async mini ORM for Python. In versions 0.9.9 through 0.22.0, when performing aggregate queries, Ormar ORM constructs SQL expressions by passing user-supplied column names directly into `sqlalchemy.text()` without any validation or sanitization. The `min()` and `max()` methods in the `QuerySet` class accept arbitrary string input as the column parameter. While `sum()` and `avg()` are partially protected by an `is_numeric` type check that rejects non-existent fields, `min()` and `max()` skip this validation entirely. As a result, an attacker-controlled string is embedded as raw SQL inside the aggregate function call. Any unauthorized user can exploit this vulnerability to read the entire database contents, including tables unrelated to the queried model, by injecting a subquery as the column parameter. Version 0.23.0 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26283 | ImageMagick has possible infinite loop in JPEG encoder when using `jpeg:extent`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26283</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a `continue` statement in the JPEG extent binary search loop in the jpeg encoder causes an infinite loop when writing persistently fails. An attacker can trigger a 100% CPU consumption and process hang (Denial of Service) with a crafted image. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26284 | ImageMagick has heap overflow in pcd decoder that leads to out of bounds read.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26284</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, ImageMagick lacks proper boundary checking when processing Huffman-coded data from PCD (Photo CD) files. The decoder contains an function that has an incorrect initialization that could cause an out of bounds read. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26331 | yt-dlp: Arbitrary Command Injection when using the `--netrc-cmd` option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26331</link><description>yt-dlp is a command-line audio/video downloader. Starting in version 2023.06.21 and prior to version 2026.02.21, when yt-dlp's `--netrc-cmd` command-line option (or `netrc_cmd` Python API parameter) is used, an attacker could achieve arbitrary command injection on the user's system with a maliciously crafted URL. yt-dlp maintainers assume the impact of this vulnerability to be high for anyone who uses `--netrc-cmd` in their command/configuration or `netrc_cmd` in their Python scripts. Even though the maliciously crafted URL itself will look very suspicious to many users, it would be trivial for a maliciously crafted webpage with an inconspicuous URL to covertly exploit this vulnerability via HTTP redirect. Users without `--netrc-cmd` in their arguments or `netrc_cmd` in their scripts are unaffected. No evidence has been found of this exploit being used in the wild. yt-dlp version 2026.02.21 fixes this issue by validating all netrc "machine" values and raising an error upon unexpected input. As a workaround, users who are unable to upgrade should avoid using the `--netrc-cmd` command-line option (or `netrc_cmd` Python API parameter), or they should at least not pass a placeholder (`{}`) in their `--netrc-cmd` argument.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26981 | OpenEXR has heap-buffer-overflow via signed integer underflow in ImfContextInit.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26981</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In versions 3.3.0 through 3.3.6 and 3.4.0 through 3.4.4, a heap-buffer-overflow (OOB read) occurs in the `istream_nonparallel_read` function in `ImfContextInit.cpp` when parsing a malformed EXR file through a memory-mapped `IStream`. A signed integer subtraction produces a negative value that is implicitly converted to `size_t`, resulting in a massive length being passed to `memcpy`. Versions 3.3.7 and 3.4.5 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26983 | ImageMagick: Invalid MSL &amp;lt;map&amp;gt; can result in a use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26983</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, the MSL interpreter crashes when processing a invalid `&lt;map&gt;` element that causes it to use an image after it has been freed. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27126 | Craft CMS has Stored XSS in Table Field via &amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot; Column Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27126</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, a stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the `editableTable.twig` component when using the `html` column type. The application fails to sanitize the input, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript when another user views a page with the malicious table field. In order to exploit the vulnerability, an attacker must have an administrator account, and `allowAdminChanges` must be enabled in production, which is against Craft's security recommendations. Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27127 | Craft CMS has Cloud Metadata SSRF Protection Bypass via DNS Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27127</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, the SSRF validation in Craft CMS’s GraphQL Asset mutation performs DNS resolution separately from the HTTP request. This Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability enables DNS rebinding attacks, where an attacker’s DNS server returns different IP addresses for validation compared to the actual request. This is a bypass of the security fix for CVE-2025-68437 that allows access to all blocked IPs, not just IPv6 endpoints. Exploitation requires GraphQL schema permissions for editing assets in the `` volume and creating assets in the `` volume. These permissions may be granted to authenticated users with appropriate GraphQL schema access and/or Public Schema (if misconfigured with write permissions). Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27128 | Craft CMS&amp;#x27;s race condition in Token Service potentially allows for token usage greater than the token limit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27128</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, a Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition exists in Craft CMS’s token validation service for tokens that explicitly set a limited usage. The `getTokenRoute()` method reads a token’s usage count, checks if it’s within limits, then updates the database in separate non-atomic operations. By sending concurrent requests, an attacker can use a single-use impersonation token multiple times before the database update completes. To make this work, an attacker needs to obtain a valid user account impersonation URL with a non-expired token via some other means and exploit a race condition while bypassing any rate-limiting rules in place. For this to be a privilege escalation, the impersonation URL must include a token for a user account with more permissions than the current user. Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27129 | Cloud Metadata SSRF Protection Bypass via IPv6 Resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27129</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). In versions 4.5.0-RC1 through 4.16.18 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.22, the SSRF validation in Craft CMS’s GraphQL Asset mutation uses `gethostbyname()`, which only resolves IPv4 addresses. When a hostname has only AAAA (IPv6) records, the function returns the hostname string itself, causing the blocklist comparison to always fail and completely bypassing SSRF protection. This is a bypass of the security fix for CVE-2025-68437. Exploitation requires GraphQL schema permissions for editing assets in the `` volume and creating assets in the `` volume. These permissions may be granted to authenticated users with appropriate GraphQL schema access and/or Public Schema (if misconfigured with write permissions). Versions 4.16.19 and 5.8.23 patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3054 | Alinto SOGo cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3054</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Alinto SOGo 5.12.3/5.12.4. This impacts an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument hint leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3057 | a54552239 pearProjectApi Backend Task.php dateTotalForProject sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3057</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in a54552239 pearProjectApi up to 2.8.10. Affected is the function dateTotalForProject of the file application/common/Model/Task.php of the component Backend Interface. The manipulation of the argument projectCode results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3064 | HummerRisk Cloud Task Scheduler ResourceCreateService.java command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3064</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ResourceCreateService.java of the component Cloud Task Scheduler. Such manipulation of the argument regionId leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3065 | HummerRisk Cloud Task Dry-run CloudTaskService.java CommandUtils.commonExecCmdWithResult command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3065</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in HummerRisk up to 1.5.0. This affects the function CommandUtils.commonExecCmdWithResult of the file CloudTaskService.java of the component Cloud Task Dry-run. Performing a manipulation of the argument fileName results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3091 | An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Synology Presto Client before 2.1.3-0672 allows local users to read or write arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3091</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Synology Presto Client before 2.1.3-0672 allows local users to read or write arbitrary files during installation by placing a malicious DLL in advance in the same directory as the installer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11845 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the certificate downloader CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11845</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the certificate downloader CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11846 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the account settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11846</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in the account settings CGI program of the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware versions through 5.50(ABPM.9.6)C0 and the Zyxel WX3100-T0 firmware versions through 5.50(ABVL.4.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25897 | ImageMagick has heap overflow in sun decoder on 32-bit systems that can result in out of bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25897</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, an Integer Overflow vulnerability exists in the sun decoder. On 32-bit systems/builds, a carefully crafted image can lead to an out of bounds heap write. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25898 | Imagemagick Has Global Buffer Overflow (OOB Read) via Negative Pixel Index in UIL and XPM Writer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25898</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, the UIL and XPM image encoder do not validate the pixel index value returned by `GetPixelIndex()` before using it as an array subscript. In HDRI builds, `Quantum` is a floating-point type, so pixel index values can be negative. An attacker can craft an image with negative pixel index values to trigger a global buffer overflow read during conversion, leading to information disclosure or a process crash. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25965 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s policy bypass through path traversal allows reading restricted content despite secured policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25965</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, ImageMagick’s path security policy is enforced on the raw filename string before the filesystem resolves it. As a result, a policy rule such as /etc/* can be bypassed by a path traversal. The OS resolves the traversal and opens the sensitive file, but the policy matcher only sees the unnormalized path and therefore allows the read. This enables local file disclosure (LFI) even when policy-secure.xml is applied. Actions to prevent reading from files have been taken in versions .7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 But it make sure writing is also not possible the following should be added to one's policy. This will also be included in ImageMagick's more secure policies by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25966 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s Security Policy Bypass through config/policy-secure.xml via &amp;quot;fd handler&amp;quot; leads to stdin/stdout access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25966</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. The shipped "secure" security policy includes a rule intended to prevent reading/writing from standard streams. However, ImageMagick also supports fd: pseudo-filenames (e.g., fd:0, fd:1). Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, this path form is not blocked by the secure policy templates, and therefore bypasses the protection goal of "no stdin/stdout." Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch by including a change to the more secure policies by default. As a workaround, add the change to one's security policy manually.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25967 | ImageMagick has stack buffer overflow in FTXT reader via oversized integer field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25967</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, a stack-based buffer overflow exists in the ImageMagick FTXT image reader. A crafted FTXT file can cause out-of-bounds writes on the stack, leading to a crash. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25968 | ImageMagick has MSL attribute stack buffer overflow that leads to out of bounds write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25968</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a stack buffer overflow occurs when processing the an attribute in msl.c. A long value overflows a fixed-size stack buffer, leading to memory corruption. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25969 | ImageMagick has Memory Leak in coders/ashlar.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25969</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, a memory leak exists in `coders/ashlar.c`. The `WriteASHLARImage` allocates a structure.  However, when an exception is thrown, the allocated memory is not properly released, resulting in a potential memory leak. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25970 | ImageMagick SIXEL Decoder Has Signed Integer Overflow, Leading to Memory Corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25970</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a signed integer overflow vulnerability in ImageMagick's SIXEL decoder allows an attacker to trigger memory corruption and denial of service when processing a maliciously crafted SIXEL image file. The vulnerability occurs during buffer reallocation operations where pointer arithmetic using signed 32-bit integers overflows. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25971 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s MSL: Stack overflow in ProcessMSLScript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25971</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, Magick fails to check for circular references between two MSLs, leading to a stack overflow. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25982 | ImageMagick Has Heap Out-of-Bounds Read in DCM Decoder (ReadDCMImage)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25982</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the `coders/dcm.c` module. When processing DICOM files with a specific configuration, the decoder loop incorrectly reads bytes per iteration. This causes the function to read past the end of the allocated buffer, potentially leading to a Denial of Service (crash) or Information Disclosure (leaking heap memory into the image). Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25983 | ImageMagick has Use After Free in MSLStartElement in &amp;quot;coders/msl.c&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25983</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted MSL script triggers a heap-use-after-free. The operation element handler replaces and frees the image while the parser continues reading from it, leading to a UAF in ReadBlobString during further parsing. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25985 | Memory allocation with excessive without limits in the internal SVG decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25985</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a crafted SVG file containing an malicious element causes ImageMagick to attempt to allocate ~674 GB of memory, leading to an out-of-memory abort. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25986 | ImageMagick has a heap buffer overflow in YUV 4:2:2 decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25986</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer overflow write vulnerability exists in ReadYUVImage() (coders/yuv.c) when processing malicious YUV 4:2:2 (NoInterlace) images. The pixel-pair loop writes one pixel beyond the allocated row buffer. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25987 | ImageMagick has heap buffer over-read in MAP image decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25987</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in the MAP image decoder when processing crafted MAP files, potentially leading to crashes or unintended memory disclosure during image decoding. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25988 | ImageMagick&amp;#x27;s MSL image stack index not refreshed, leading to leaked images.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25988</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, sometimes msl.c fails to update the stack index, so an image is stored in the wrong slot and never freed on error, causing leaks. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3052 | DataLinkDC dinky Flink Proxy Controller FlinkProxyController.java proxyUba server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3052</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DataLinkDC dinky up to 1.2.5. The impacted element is the function proxyUba of the file dinky-admin/src/main/java/org/dinky/controller/FlinkProxyController.java of the component Flink Proxy Controller. Performing a manipulation results in server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3053 | DataLinkDC dinky OpenAPI Endpoint AppConfig.java addInterceptors missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3053</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in DataLinkDC dinky up to 1.2.5. This affects the function addInterceptors of the file dinky-admin/src/main/java/org/dinky/configure/AppConfig.java of the component OpenAPI Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25591 | New API has an SQL LIKE Wildcard Injection DoS via Token Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25591</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. Prior to version 0.10.8-alpha.10, a SQL LIKE wildcard injection vulnerability in the `/api/token/search` endpoint allows authenticated users to cause denial of service through resource exhaustion by crafting malicious search patterns. The token search endpoint accepts user-supplied `keyword` and `token` parameters that are directly concatenated into SQL LIKE clauses without escaping wildcard characters (`%`, `_`). This allows attackers to inject patterns that trigger expensive database queries. Version 0.10.8-alpha.10 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25637 | ImageMagick: Possible memory leak in ASHLAR encoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25637</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, a memory leak in the ASHLAR image writer allows an attacker to exhaust process memory by providing a crafted image that results in small objects that are allocated but never freed. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25638 | ImageMagick has memory leak in msl encoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25638</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, memory leak exists in `coders/msl.c`. In the `WriteMSLImage` function of the `msl.c` file, resources are allocated. But the function returns early without releasing these allocated resources. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25794 | ImageMagick has heap-buffer-overflow via signed integer overflow in `WriteUHDRImage` when writing UHDR images with large dimensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25794</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. `WriteUHDRImage` in `coders/uhdr.c` uses `int` arithmetic to compute the pixel buffer size. Prior to version 7.1.2-15, when image dimensions are large, the multiplication overflows 32-bit `int`, causing an undersized heap allocation followed by an out-of-bounds write. This can crash the process or potentially lead to an out of bounds heap write. Version 7.1.2-15 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25795 | ImageMagick has NULL pointer dereference in ReadSFWImage after DestroyImageInfo (sfw.c)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25795</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, in `ReadSFWImage()` (`coders/sfw.c`), when temporary file creation fails, `read_info` is destroyed before its `filename` member is accessed, causing a NULL pointer dereference and crash. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25796 | ImageMagick has memory leak of watermark Image object in ReadSTEGANOImage on multiple error/early-return paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25796</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, in `ReadSTEGANOImage()` (`coders/stegano.c`), the `watermark` Image object is not freed on three early-return paths, resulting in a definite memory leak (~13.5KB+ per invocation) that can be exploited for denial of service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25797 | ImageMagick vulnerable to Code injection via PostScript header in ps coders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25797</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, the ps coders, responsible for writing PostScript files, fails to sanitize the input before writing it into the PostScript header.  An attacker can provide a malicous file and inject arbitrary PostScript code. When the resulting file is processed by a printer or a viewer (like Ghostscript), the injected code is interpreted and executed. The html encoder does not properly escape strings that are written to in the html document. An attacker can provide a malicious file and injection arbitrary html code. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25798 | ImageMagick has NULL Pointer Dereference in ClonePixelCacheRepository via crafted image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25798</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a NULL pointer dereference in ClonePixelCacheRepository allows a remote attacker to crash any application linked against ImageMagick by supplying a crafted image file, resulting in denial of service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25799 | ImageMagick has Division-by-Zero in YUV sampling factor validation, which leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25799</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a logic error in YUV sampling factor validation allows an invalid sampling factor to bypass checks and trigger a division-by-zero during image loading, resulting in a reliable denial-of-service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25802 | New API has Potential XSS in its MarkdownRenderer component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25802</link><description>New API is a large language mode (LLM) gateway and artificial intelligence (AI) asset management system. Prior to version 0.10.8-alpha.9, a potential unsafe operation occurs in component `MarkdownRenderer.jsx`, allowing for Cross-Site Scripting(XSS) when the model outputs items containing `</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27729 | Astro has  memory exhaustion DoS due to missing request body size limit in Server Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27729</link><description>Astro is a web framework. In versions 9.0.0 through 9.5.3, Astro server actions have no default request body size limit, which can lead to memory exhaustion DoS. A single large POST to a valid action endpoint can crash the server process on memory-constrained deployments. On-demand rendered sites built with Astro can define server actions, which automatically parse incoming request bodies (JSON or FormData). The body is buffered entirely into memory with no size limit — a single oversized request is sufficient to exhaust the process heap and crash the server. Astro's Node adapter (`mode: 'standalone'`) creates an HTTP server with no body size protection. In containerized environments, the crashed process is automatically restarted, and repeated requests cause a persistent crash-restart loop. Action names are discoverable from HTML form attributes on any public page, so no authentication is required. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated denial of service against SSR standalone deployments using server actions. A single oversized request crashes the server process, and repeated requests cause a persistent crash-restart loop in containerized environments. Version 9.5.4 contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3050 | horilla-opensource horilla Leads global.js cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3050</link><description>A flaw has been found in horilla-opensource horilla up to 1.0.2. Impacted is an unknown function of the file static/assets/js/global.js of the component Leads Module. This manipulation of the argument Notes causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.0.3 is recommended to address this issue. Patch name: fc5c8e55988e89273012491b5f097b762b474546. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3051 | DataLinkDC dinky Project Name GitRepository.java getProjectDir path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3051</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DataLinkDC dinky up to 1.2.5. The affected element is the function getProjectDir of the file dinky-admin/src/main/java/org/dinky/utils/GitRepository.java of the component Project Name Handler. Such manipulation of the argument projectName leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69253 | free5GC vulnerable to improper error handling in NEF with information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69253</link><description>free5GC is an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions up to and including 1.4.1 of the User Data Repository are affected by Improper Error Handling with Information Exposure. The NEF component reliably leaks internal parsing error details (e.g., invalid character 'n' after top-level value) to remote clients, which can aid attackers in service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the Nnef_PfdManagement service may be vulnerable. free5gc/udr pull request 56 contains a patch. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9120 | RCE vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Carbonite Safe Server Backup.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9120</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in OpenText™ Carbonite Safe Server Backup allows Code Injection. 

The vulnerability could be exploited through an open port, potentially allowing unauthorized access.

This issue affects Carbonite Safe Server Backup: through 6.8.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21864 | Remote DoS from malformed RESTORE command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21864</link><description>Valkey-Bloom is a Rust based Valkey module which brings a Bloom Filter (Module) data type into the Valkey distributed key-value database. Prior to commit a68614b6e3845777d383b3a513cedcc08b3b7ccd, a specially crafted `RESTORE` command can cause Valkey to hit an assertion, causes the server to shutdown. Valkey modules are required to handle errors in RDB parsing by using `VALKEYMODULE_OPTIONS_HANDLE_IO_ERRORS` flag. If this flag is not set, errors encountered during parsing result in a system assertion which shuts down the system. Even though the Valkey-bloom module correctly handled the parsing, it did not originally set the flag. Commit a68614b6e3845777d383b3a513cedcc08b3b7ccd contains a patch. One may mitigate this defect by disabling the `RESTORE` command if it is unused by one's application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24481 | ImageMagick has Possible Heap Information Disclosure in PSD ZIP Decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24481</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap information disclosure vulnerability exists in ImageMagick's PSD (Adobe Photoshop) format handler. When processing a maliciously crafted PSD file containing ZIP-compressed layer data that decompresses to less than the expected size, uninitialized heap memory is leaked into the output image. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24484 | ImageMagick: Converting multi-layer nested MVG to SVG can cause DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24484</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, Magick fails to check for multi-layer nested mvg conversions to svg, leading to DoS. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24485 | ImageMagick: Infinite loop vulnerability when parsing a PCD file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24485</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, when a PCD file does not contain a valid Sync marker, the DecodeImage() function becomes trapped in an infinite loop while searching for the Sync marker, causing the program to become unresponsive and continuously consume CPU resources, ultimately leading to system resource exhaustion and denial of service. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25501 | free5GC SMF crash (nil pointer dereference) on PFCP SessionReportRequest when ReportType.DLDR is set but DownlinkDataReport IE is missing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25501</link><description>free5GC SMF provides Session Management Function for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, SMF panics due to nil pointer dereference and the SMF process terminates. This is triggered by a malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest on the SMF PFCP (UDP/8805) interface. No known upstream fix is available, but some workarounds are available. ACL/firewall the PFCP interface so only trusted UPF IPs can reach SMF (reduce spoofing/abuse surface); drop/inspect malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest messages at the network edge where feasible, and/or add recover() around PFCP handler dispatch to avoid whole-process termination (mitigation only).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25545 | Astro has Full-Read SSRF in error rendering via Host: header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25545</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 9.5.4, Server-Side Rendered pages that return an error with a prerendered custom error page (eg. `404.astro` or `500.astro`) are vulnerable to SSRF. If the `Host:` header is changed to an attacker's server, it will be fetched on `/500.html` and they can redirect this to any internal URL to read the response body through the first request. An attacker who can access the application without `Host:` header validation (eg. through finding the origin IP behind a proxy, or just by default) can fetch their own server to redirect to any internal IP. With this they can fetch cloud metadata IPs and interact with services in the internal network or localhost. For this to be vulnerable, a common feature needs to be used, with direct access to the server (no proxies). Version 9.5.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25576 | ImageMagick: Out of bounds read in multiple coders read raw pixel data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25576</link><description>ImageMagick is free and open-source software used for editing and manipulating digital images. Prior to versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40, a heap buffer over-read vulnerability exists in multiple raw image format handles. The vulnerability occurs when processing images with -extract dimensions larger than -size dimensions, causing out-of-bounds memory reads from a heap-allocated buffer. Versions 7.1.2-15 and 6.9.13-40 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26024 | free5GC SMF crash (nil pointer dereference) on PFCP SessionReportRequest when ReportType.USAR=1 and UsageReport omits mandatory URRID sub-IE ￼</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26024</link><description>free5GC SMF provides Session Management Function for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, SMF panics and terminates when processing a malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest on the PFCP (UDP/8805) interface. ￼No known upstream fix is available, but some workarounds are available. ACL/firewall the PFCP interface so only trusted UPF IPs can reach SMF (reduce spoofing/abuse surface); drop/inspect malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest messages at the network edge where feasible, and/or add recover() around PFCP handler dispatch to avoid whole-process termination (mitigation only).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26025 | free5GC SMF crash (nil pointer dereference) on PFCP SessionReportRequest when ReportType.USAR=1 and UsageReport omits mandatory URRID sub-IE ￼</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26025</link><description>free5GC SMF provides Session Management Function for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, SMF panics and terminates when processing a malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest on the PFCP (UDP/8805) interface. ￼No known upstream fix is available, but some workarounds are available. ACL/firewall the PFCP interface so only trusted UPF IPs can reach SMF (reduce spoofing/abuse surface); drop/inspect malformed PFCP SessionReportRequest messages at the network edge where feasible, and/or add recover() around PFCP handler dispatch to avoid whole-process termination (mitigation only).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27642 | free5GC has Improper Input Validation in UDM UEAU Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27642</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, remote attackers can inject control characters (e.g., %00) into the supi parameter, triggering internal URL parsing errors (net/url: invalid control character). This exposes system-level error details and can be used for service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM Nudm_UEAU service may be affected. free5gc/udm pull request 75 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27643 | free5GC has improper error handling in NEF with information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27643</link><description>free5GC UDR is the user data repository (UDR) for free5GC, an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, the NEF component reliably leaks internal parsing error details (e.g., invalid character 'n' after top-level value) to remote clients, which can aid attackers in service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC  using the Nnef_PfdManagement service may be affected. free5gc/udr pull request 56 contains a patch for the issue. There is no direct workaround at the application level. The recommendation is to apply the provided patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3046 | itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 check_profile_old.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3046</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode E-Logbook with Health Monitoring System for COVID-19 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /check_profile_old.php. The manipulation of the argument profile_id leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3049 | horilla-opensource horilla Query Parameter global_search.py get redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3049</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in horilla-opensource horilla up to 1.0.2. This issue affects the function get of the file horilla_generics/global_search.py of the component Query Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument prev_url results in open redirect. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.0.3 is capable of addressing this issue. The patch is identified as 730b5a44ff060916780c44a4bdbc8ced70a2cd27. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58041 | Smolder versions through 1.51 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58041</link><description>Smolder versions through 1.51 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions.

Smolder 1.51 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Smolder::DB::Developer uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69251 | free5GC has Improper Input Validation in UDM, Leading to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69251</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1,  remote attackers can inject control characters (e.g., %00) into the ueId parameter, triggering internal URL parsing errors (net/url: invalid control character). This exposes system implementation details and can aid in service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM Nudm_UECM service may be affected. free5gc/udm pull request 76 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69252 | free5GC has Null Pointer Dereference in UDM, Leading to Service Panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69252</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions up to and including 1.4.1 have a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability. Remote unauthenticated attackers can trigger a service panic (Denial of Service) by sending a crafted PUT request with an unexpected ueId, crashing the UDM service. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM component may be affected. free5gc/udm pull request 76 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69250 | free5GC has Improper Error Handling in UDM, Leading to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69250</link><description>free5gc UDM provides Unified Data Management (UDM) for free5GC, an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. In versions up to and including 1.4.1, the service reliably leaks detailed internal error messages (e.g., strconv.ParseInt parsing errors) to remote clients when processing invalid pduSessionId inputs. This exposes implementation details and can be used for service fingerprinting. All deployments of free5GC using the UDM Nudm_UECM DELETE service may be vulnerable. free5gc/udm pull request 76 contains a fix for the issue. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3044 | Tenda AC8 Httpd Service UploadCfg webCgiGetUploadFile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3044</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This affects the function webCgiGetUploadFile of the file /cgi-bin/UploadCfg of the component Httpd Service. The manipulation of the argument boundary leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3042 | itsourcecode Event Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3042</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3043 | itsourcecode Event Management System navbar.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3043</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/navbar.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument page can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21665 | The Print Service component of Fiserv Originate Loans Peripherals (formerly Velocity Services) in unsupported version 2021.2.4 (build 4.7.31...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21665</link><description>The Print Service component of Fiserv Originate Loans Peripherals (formerly Velocity Services) in unsupported version 2021.2.4 (build 4.7.3155.0011) uses deprecated .NET Remoting TCP channels that allow unsafe deserialization of untrusted data. When these services are exposed to an untrusted network in a client-managed deployment, an unauthenticated attacker can achieve remote code execution. Version 2021.2.4 is no longer supported by Fiserv. Customers should upgrade to a currently supported release (2025.1 or later) and ensure that .NET Remoting service ports are not exposed beyond trusted network boundaries.

This CVE documents behavior observed in a client-hosted deployment running an unsupported legacy version of Originate Loans Peripherals with .NET Remoting ports exposed to an untrusted network. This is not a default or supported configuration. Customers running legacy versions should upgrade to a currently supported release and ensure .NET Remoting ports are restricted to trusted network segments. The finding does not apply to Fiserv-hosted environments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3061 | Out of bounds read in Media in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3061</link><description>Out of bounds read in Media in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3062 | Out of bounds read and write in Tint in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3062</link><description>Out of bounds read and write in Tint in Google Chrome on Mac prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3063 | Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3063</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.116 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to inject scripts or HTML into a privileged page via DevTools. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27741 | Bludit &amp;lt;= 3.16.1 CSRF in Plugin and Theme Management Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27741</link><description>Bludit version 3.16.1 contains a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /admin/uninstall-plugin/ and /admin/install-theme/ endpoints. The application does not implement anti-CSRF tokens or other request origin validation mechanisms for these administrative actions. An attacker can induce an authenticated administrator to visit a malicious page that silently submits crafted requests, resulting in unauthorized plugin uninstallation or theme installation. This may lead to loss of functionality, execution of untrusted code via malicious themes, and compromise of system integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-27742 | Bludit &amp;lt;= 3.16.2 Stored XSS in Post Content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-27742</link><description>Bludit version 3.16.2 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the post content functionality. The application performs client-side sanitation of content input but does not enforce equivalent sanitation on the server side. An authenticated user can inject arbitrary JavaScript into the content field of a post, which is stored and later rendered to other users without proper output encoding. When viewed, the injected script executes in the context of the victim’s browser, allowing session hijacking, credential theft, content manipulation, or other actions within the user’s privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3040 | DrayTek Vigor 300B Web Management uploadlangs cgiGetFile os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3040</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in DrayTek Vigor 300B up to 1.5.1.6. This affects the function cgiGetFile of the file /cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi/uploadlangs of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument File leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor confirms that "300B is EoL, and this is an authenticated vulnerability. We don't plan to fix it." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3041 | xingfuggz BaykeShop Article Sidebar custom.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3041</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in xingfuggz BaykeShop up to 1.3.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file src/baykeshop/contrib/article/templates/baykeshop/sidebar/custom.html of the component Article Sidebar Module. Such manipulation of the argument sidebar.content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69232 | free5GC hasProtocol Compliance Violation in UPF Leading to SMF Service Disruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69232</link><description>free5GC is an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. free5GC go-upf versions up to and including 1.2.6, corresponding to free5gc smf up to and including 1.4.0, have an Improper Input Validation and Protocol Compliance vulnerability leading to Denial of Service. Remote attackers can disrupt core network functionality by sending a malformed PFCP Association Setup Request. The UPF incorrectly accepts it, entering an inconsistent state that causes subsequent legitimate requests to trigger SMF reconnection loops and service degradation. All deployments of free5GC using the UPF and SMF components may be affected. As of time of publication, a fix is in development but not yet available. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch, once released, is recommended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69247 | free5GC has Heap Buffer Overflow in UPF Leading to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69247</link><description>free5GC go-upf is the User Plane Function (UPF) implementation for 5G networks that is part of the free5GC project. Versions prior to 1.2.8 have a Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122) vulnerability leading to Denial of Service. Remote attackers can crash the UPF network element by sending a specially crafted PFCP Session Modification Request with an invalid SDF Filter length field. This causes a heap buffer overflow, resulting in complete service disruption for all connected UEs and potential cascading failures affecting the SMF. All deployments of free5GC using the UPF component may be affected. Version 1.2.8 of go-upf contains a fix.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69248 | free5GC has Array Index Out of Bounds in AMF Leading to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69248</link><description>free5GC is an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions up to and including 1.4.1 of free5GC's AMF service have a Buffer Overflow vulnerability leading to Denial of Service. Remote unauthenticated attackers can crash the AMF service by sending a specially crafted NAS Registration Request with a malformed 5GS Mobile Identity, causing complete denial of service for the 5G core network. All deployments of free5GC using the AMF component may be affected. Pull request 43 of the free5gc/nas repo contains a fix. No direct workaround is available at the application level. Applying the official patch is recommended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3028 | erzhongxmu JEEWMS JeecgListDemoController.java doAdd cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3028</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in erzhongxmu JEEWMS up to 3.7. This vulnerability affects the function doAdd of the file src/main/java/com/jeecg/demo/controller/JeecgListDemoController.java. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69208 | free5GC UDR&amp;#x27;s NEF incorrectly returns 500 for missing PFD data (UDR 404) in Nnef_PfdManagement GET request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69208</link><description>free5GC UDR is the user data repository (UDR) for free5GC, an an open-source project for 5th generation (5G) mobile core networks. Versions prior to 1.4.1 contain an Improper Error Handling vulnerability with Information Exposure. All deployments of free5GC using the Nnef_PfdManagement service may be affected. The NEF component reliably leaks internal parsing errors (e.g., invalid character 'n' after top-level value) to remote clients. This can aid attackers in fingerprinting server software and logic flows. Version 1.4.1 fixes the issue. There is no direct workaround at the application level. The recommended mitigation is to apply the provided patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25649 | Traccar Vulnerable to Authorization Code Theft via Open Redirect in OIDC Provider Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25649</link><description>Versions of the Traccar open-source GPS tracking system up to and including 6.11.1 contain an issue in which authenticated users can steal OAuth 2.0 authorization codes by exploiting an open redirect vulnerability in two OIDC-related endpoints. The `redirect_uri` parameter is not validated against a whitelist, allowing attackers to redirect authorization codes to attacker-controlled URLs, enabling account takeover on any OAuth-integrated application. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23521 | Traccar vulnerable to Path Traversal and External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23521</link><description>Versions of the Traccar open-source GPS tracking system up to and including 6.11.1 contain an issue in which authenticated users who can create or edit devices can set a device `uniqueId` to an absolute path. When uploading a device image, Traccar uses that `uniqueId` to build the filesystem path without enforcing that the resolved path stays under the media root. This allows writing files outside the media directory. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25648 | Traccar Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via Malicious SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25648</link><description>Versions of the Traccar open-source GPS tracking system starting with 6.11.1 contain an issue in which authenticated users can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of other users' browsers by uploading malicious SVG files as device images. The application accepts SVG file uploads without sanitization and serves them with the `image/svg+xml` Content-Type, allowing embedded JavaScript to execute when victims view the image. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3027 | erzhongxmu JEEWMS UEditor getContent.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3027</link><description>A vulnerability was found in erzhongxmu JEEWMS up to 3.7. This affects an unknown part of the file src/main/webapp/plug-in/ueditor/jsp/getContent.jsp of the component UEditor. The manipulation of the argument myEditor results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3075 | WordPress Simple Ajax Chat plugin &amp;lt;= 20251121 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3075</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Jeff Starr Simple Ajax Chat simple-ajax-chat allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Simple Ajax Chat: from n/a through &lt;= 20251121.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3025 | ShuoRen Smart Heating Integrated Management Platform ExampleNodeService.asmx unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3025</link><description>A flaw has been found in ShuoRen Smart Heating Integrated Management Platform 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /MP/Service/Webservice/ExampleNodeService.asmx. Executing a manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3026 | erzhongxmu JEEWMS UEditor getRemoteImage.jsp server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3026</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in erzhongxmu JEEWMS 3.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /plug-in/ueditor/jsp/getRemoteImage.jsp of the component UEditor. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 20:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22567 | ZIA Admin UI Input Validation Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22567</link><description>Improper validation of user-supplied input in the ZIA Admin UI could allow an authenticated administrator to initiate backend functions through specific input fields in limited scenarios.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22568 | Unauthorized information retrieval in ZIA Admin UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22568</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements in user-supplied input within the ZIA Admin UI could allow an authenticated administrator to access or retrieve unauthorized internal information in rare conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-3015 | UTT HiPER 810G formPolicyRouteConf strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-3015</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-171114. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPolicyRouteConf. Executing a manipulation of the argument GroupName can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69700 | Tenda FH1203 V2.0.1.6 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the modify_add_client_prio function, which is reachable via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69700</link><description>Tenda FH1203 V2.0.1.6 contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the modify_add_client_prio function, which is reachable via the formSetClientPrio CGI handler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21420 | Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions prior to 3.4.8, contains an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21420</link><description>Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions prior to 3.4.8, contains an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59873 | Session Token Exposure via URL Query Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59873</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in

Vulnerability in HCL Software ZIE for Web.

The application transmits sensitive session tokens and authentication identifiers within the URL query parameters . An attacker who gains access to any network log or operates a site linked from the application can hijack user sessions

This issue affects ZIE for Web: v16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40701 | Reflected Cross-Site scripting (XSS) in SOTE&amp;#x27;s SOTESHOP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40701</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in SOTESHOP, version 8.3.4. THis vulnerability allows an attacker execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser when a malicious URL with the 'id' parameter in '/adsTracker/checkAds' is sent to the victim. The vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user information such as session cookies, or to perform actions on their behalf.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40986 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in PideTuCita</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40986</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PideTuCita. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending him/her a malicious URL using the endpoint 'cookies/indes.php/'. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal confidential user data, such as session cookies or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2985 | Tiandy Video Surveillance System 视频监控平台 CLSBODownLoad.java downloadImage server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2985</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tiandy Video Surveillance System 视频监控平台 7.17.0. This impacts the function downloadImage of the file /com/tiandy/easy7/core/bo/CLSBODownLoad.java. Performing a manipulation of the argument urlPath results in server-side request forgery. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2984 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System drop_user.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2984</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/core/drop_user.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to denial of service. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41002 | SQL injection in Infoticketing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41002</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Infoticketing. This vulnerability allows
 an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete the
 database by sending a POST request using the 'code' parameter in '/components/cart/cartApplyDiscount.php'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2983 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Bulk Import import_users.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2983</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/core/import_users.php of the component Bulk Import. This manipulation of the argument File causes improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 10:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23552 | Apache Camel: Camel-Keycloak: Cross-Realm Token Acceptance Bypass in KeycloakSecurityPolicy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23552</link><description>Cross-Realm Token Acceptance Bypass in KeycloakSecurityPolicy Apache Camel Keycloak component. 

The Camel-Keycloak KeycloakSecurityPolicy does not validate the iss (issuer) claim of JWT tokens against the configured realm. A token issued by one Keycloak realm is silently accepted by a policy configured for a completely different realm, breaking tenant isolation.
This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.15.0 before 4.18.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25747 | Apache Camel: Deserialization of Untrusted Data in Camel LevelDB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25747</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel LevelDB component.

The Camel-LevelDB DefaultLevelDBSerializer class deserializes data read from the LevelDB aggregation repository using java.io.ObjectInputStream without applying any ObjectInputFilter or class-loading restrictions. An attacker who can write to the LevelDB database files used by a Camel application can inject a crafted serialized Java object that, when deserialized during normal aggregation repository operations, results in arbitrary code execution in the context of the application.
This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.10.0 before 4.10.8, from 4.14.0 before 4.14.5, from 4.15.0 before 4.18.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.0, which fixes the issue. For the 4.10.x LTS releases, users are recommended to upgrade to 4.10.9, while for 4.14.x LTS releases, users are recommended to upgrade to 4.14.5</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2981 | UTT HiPER 810G formTaskEdit_ap strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2981</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-1711. The affected element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formTaskEdit_ap. The manipulation of the argument txtMin2 results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2980 | UTT HiPER 810G setSysAdm strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2980</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT HiPER 810G up to 1.7.7-1711. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/setSysAdm. The manipulation of the argument passwd1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26365 | Akamai Ghost on Akamai CDN edge servers before 2026-02-06 mishandles processing of custom hop-by-hop HTTP headers, where an incoming request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26365</link><description>Akamai Ghost on Akamai CDN edge servers before 2026-02-06 mishandles processing of custom hop-by-hop HTTP headers, where an incoming request containing the header "Connection: Transfer-Encoding" could result in a forward request with invalid message framing, depending on the Akamai processing path. This could result in the origin server parsing the request body incorrectly, leading to HTTP request smuggling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2979 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py user_avatar_upload_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2979</link><description>A flaw has been found in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This issue affects the function user_avatar_upload_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_system/user/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Executing a manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2978 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py upload_file_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2978</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This vulnerability affects the function upload_file_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_system/params/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Performing a manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1367 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1367</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus versions 6522 and below are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection in the search report option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2977 | FastApiAdmin Scheduled Task API controller.py upload_controller unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2977</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. This affects the function upload_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_common/file/controller.py of the component Scheduled Task API. Such manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2976 | FastApiAdmin Download Endpoint controller.py download_controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2976</link><description>A weakness has been identified in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. Affected by this issue is the function download_controller of the file /backend/app/api/v1/module_common/file/controller.py of the component Download Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument file_path causes information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2975 | FastApiAdmin Custom Documentation Endpoint init_app.py reset_api_docs information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2975</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in FastApiAdmin up to 2.2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function reset_api_docs of the file /backend/app/plugin/init_app.py of the component Custom Documentation Endpoint. The manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2974 | AliasVault App Backup aliasvault.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2974</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in AliasVault App up to 0.25.3 on Android/iOS. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file shared_prefs/aliasvault.xml of the component Backup Handler. The manipulation of the argument accessToken/refreshToken/metadata/key_derivation_params/auth_methods leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. An attack has to be approached locally. The attack is considered to have high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. Upgrading to version 0.26.0 is able to resolve this issue. The identifier of the patch is 873ecc03f92238e162f98a068ad56069a922b4f6/0bd662320174d8265dfe3b05a04bc13efc960532. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The creator of the software explains: "Because of AliasVault's zero-knowledge encryption design, the tokens stored in aliasvault.xml are API session tokens that cannot decrypt the vault on their own: the master password is required for that. So while this isn't a direct vault compromise risk, there's no reason to include them in backups either."</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2972 | a466350665 Smart-SSO Role Edit UserController.java save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2972</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in a466350665 Smart-SSO up to 2.1.1. This affects the function Save of the file smart-sso-server/src/main/java/openjoe/smart/sso/server/controller/admin/UserController.java of the component Role Edit Page. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2971 | a466350665 Smart-SSO Login login.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in a466350665 Smart-SSO up to 2.1.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file smart-sso-server/src/main/resources/templates/login.html of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument redirectUri results in cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2969 | datapizza-labs datapizza-ai Jinja2 Template prompt.py ChatPromptTemplate special elements used in a template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2969</link><description>A flaw has been found in datapizza-labs datapizza-ai 0.0.2. Affected is the function ChatPromptTemplate of the file datapizza-ai-core/datapizza/modules/prompt/prompt.py of the component Jinja2 Template Handler. This manipulation of the argument Prompt causes improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2970 | datapizza-labs datapizza-ai cache.py RedisCache deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2970</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in datapizza-labs datapizza-ai 0.0.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RedisCache of the file datapizza-ai-cache/redis/datapizza/cache/redis/cache.py. Such manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack requires being on the local network. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2967 | Cesanta Mongoose TCP Sequence Number net_builtin.c getpeer verification of source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2967</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. This affects the function getpeer of the file /src/net_builtin.c of the component TCP Sequence Number Handler. The manipulation leads to improper verification of source of a communication channel. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2968 | Cesanta Mongoose Poly1305 Authentication Tag tls_chacha20.c mg_chacha20_poly1305_decrypt signature verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2968</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. This impacts the function mg_chacha20_poly1305_decrypt of the file /src/tls_chacha20.c of the component Poly1305 Authentication Tag Handler. The manipulation results in improper verification of cryptographic signature. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2998 | eAI Technologies｜ERP - DLL Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2998</link><description>ERP developed by eAI Technologies has a DLL Hijacking vulnerability, allowing authenticated local attackers to place a crafted DLL file in the same directory as the program, thereby executing arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2965 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM System Extension edit.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2965</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 1.2.9. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/SysModule/edit.html of the component System Extension Module. Performing a manipulation of the argument Title results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. This product is published under multiple names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2966 | Cesanta Mongoose DNS Transaction ID dns.c mg_sendnsreq random values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2966</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Cesanta Mongoose up to 7.20. The impacted element is the function mg_sendnsreq of the file /src/dns.c of the component DNS Transaction ID Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument random can lead to insufficiently random values. The attack can be launched remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2997 | WisdomGarden｜Tronclass - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2997</link><description>Tronclass developed by WisdomGarden has a Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability. After obtaining a course ID, authenticated remote attackers to modify a specific parameter to obtain a course invitation code, thereby joining any course.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24494 | SQL injection vulnerability in Order Up Online Ordering System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24494</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the /api/integrations/getintegrations endpoint of Order Up Online Ordering System 1.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to access sensitive backend database data via a crafted store_id parameter in a POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2964 | higuma web-audio-recorder-js Dynamic Config Handling WebAudioRecorder.js extend prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2964</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in higuma web-audio-recorder-js 0.1/0.1.1. Impacted is the function extend in the library lib/WebAudioRecorder.js of the component Dynamic Config Handling. Such manipulation leads to improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2962 | D-Link DWR-M960 Scheduled Reboot Configuration Endpoint formDateReboot sub_460F30 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2962</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This vulnerability affects the function sub_460F30 of the file /boafrm/formDateReboot of the component Scheduled Reboot Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2963 | Jinher OA C6 OfficeSupplyTypeRight.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2963</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Jinher OA C6 up to 20260210. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /C6/Jhsoft.Web.officesupply/OfficeSupplyTypeRight.aspx. This manipulation of the argument id/offsnum causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2960 | D-Link DWR-M960 formDhcpv6s sub_468D64 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2960</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. Affected by this issue is the function sub_468D64 of the file /boafrm/formDhcpv6s. Executing a manipulation of the argument submit-url can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2961 | D-Link DWR-M960 VPN Configuration Endpoint formVpnConfigSetup sub_4196C4 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2961</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M960 1.01.07. This affects the function sub_4196C4 of the file /boafrm/formVpnConfigSetup of the component VPN Configuration Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>