<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:29:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-30692 | A issue was discovered in ROS2 Galactic Geochelone versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows remote attackers to cause a denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30692</link><description>A issue was discovered in ROS2 Galactic Geochelone versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) in the ROS2 nodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30690 | An unauthorized node injection vulnerability has been identified in ROS2 Galactic Geochelone versions where ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30690</link><description>An unauthorized node injection vulnerability has been identified in ROS2 Galactic Geochelone versions where ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30688 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability has been discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30688</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability has been discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the file upload mechanism of the ROS2 system, including the server’s functionality for handling file uploads and the associated validation processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 05:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1664 | Responsive Gallery Grid &amp;lt; 2.3.11 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1664</link><description>The Responsive Gallery Grid WordPress plugin before 2.3.11 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 05:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30687 | An insecure deserialization vulnerability has been identified in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30687</link><description>An insecure deserialization vulnerability has been identified in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted input to the Data Serialization and Deserialization Components, Inter-Process Communication Mechanisms, and Network Communication Interfaces.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 05:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30684 | An insecure logging vulnerability has been identified within ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30684</link><description>An insecure logging vulnerability has been identified within ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to access sensitive information via inadequate security measures implemented within the logging mechanisms of ROS2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30686 | An issue was discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30686</link><description>An issue was discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via packages or nodes within the ROS2 system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30683 | A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in the C++ components of ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30683</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in the C++ components of ROS2 Iron Irwini versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via improper handling of arrays or strings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30681 | An OS command injection vulnerability has been discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini version ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30681</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini version ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via the command processing or system call components in ROS2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:10:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30680 | Shell injection vulnerability was discovered in ROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Iron Irwini in versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30680</link><description>Shell injection vulnerability was discovered in ROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Iron Irwini in versions ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information due to the way ROS2 handles shell command execution in components like command interpreters or interfaces that process external inputs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 04:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30679 | An issue was discovered in the default configurations of ROS2 Iron Irwini ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows unauthenticated att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30679</link><description>An issue was discovered in the default configurations of ROS2 Iron Irwini ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows unauthenticated attackers to authenticate using default credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 03:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30678 | An issue has been discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, where the system transmits messages in plaintext. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30678</link><description>An issue has been discovered in ROS2 Iron Irwini ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, where the system transmits messages in plaintext. This flaw exposes sensitive information, making it vulnerable to man-in-the-middle (MitM) attacks, and allowing attackers to intercept and access this data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 02:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30676 | A Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions where ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3. A malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30676</link><description>A Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in ROS2 Iron Irwini versions where ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3. A malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability remotely to crash the ROS2 nodes, thereby causing a denial of service. The flaw allows an attacker to cause unexpected behavior in the operation of ROS2 nodes, which leads to their failure and interrupts the regular operation of the system, thus making it unavailable for its intended users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 02:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25646 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Web Intelligence</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25646</link><description>Due to improper validation, SAP BusinessObject Business Intelligence Launch Pad allows an authenticated attacker to access operating system information using crafted document. On successful exploitation there could be a considerable impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27898 | Server-Side Request Forgery in SAP NetWeaver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27898</link><description>SAP NetWeaver application, due to insufficient input validation, allows an attacker to send a crafted request from a vulnerable web application targeting internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability. Thus, having a low impact on confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27899 | Security misconfiguration vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java User Management Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27899</link><description>Self-Registration and Modify your own profile in User Admin Application of NetWeaver AS Java does not enforce proper security requirements for the content of the newly defined security answer. This can be leveraged by an attacker to cause profound impact on confidentiality and low impact on both integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27901 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in SAP Asset Accounting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27901</link><description>SAP Asset Accounting could allow a high privileged attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by the users and pass it through to the file API's. Thus, causing a considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27983 | An attacker can make the Node.js HTTP/2 server completely unavailable by sending a small amount of HTTP/2 frames packets with a few HTTP/2 f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27983</link><description>An attacker can make the Node.js HTTP/2 server completely unavailable by sending a small amount of HTTP/2 frames packets with a few HTTP/2 frames inside. It is possible to leave some data in nghttp2 memory after reset when headers with HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frame are sent to the server and then a TCP connection is abruptly closed by the client triggering the Http2Session destructor while header frames are still being processed (and stored in memory) causing a race condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28167 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Group Reporting Data Collection (Enter Package Data)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28167</link><description>SAP Group Reporting Data Collection does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, specific data can be changed via the Enter Package Data app although the user does not have sufficient authorization causing high impact on Integrity of the appliction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2975 | A race condition was identified through which privilege escalation was possible in certain configurations.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2975</link><description>A race condition was identified through which privilege escalation was possible in certain configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30214 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30214</link><description>The application allows a high privilege attacker to append a malicious GET query parameter to Service invocations, which are reflected in the server response. Under certain circumstances, if the parameter contains a JavaScript, the script could be processed on client side.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30215 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30215</link><description>The Resource Settings page allows a high privilege attacker to load exploitable payload to be stored and reflected whenever a User visits the page. In a successful attack, some information could be obtained and/or modified. However, the attacker does not have control over what information is obtained, or the amount or kind of loss is limited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30216 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4 HANA (Cash Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30216</link><description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, attacker can add notes in the review request with 'completed' status affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30217 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4 HANA (Cash Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30217</link><description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can approve or reject a bank account application affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30218 | Denial of service (DOS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30218</link><description>The ABAP Application Server of SAP NetWeaver as well as ABAP Platform allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service. This leads to a considerable impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23584 | HCL BigFix Asset Discovery is affected by a security vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23584</link><description>The NMAP Importer service​ may expose data store credentials to authorized users of the Windows Registry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 23:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31047 | An issue in Academy Software Foundation openexr v.3.2.3 and before allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the conver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31047</link><description>An issue in Academy Software Foundation openexr v.3.2.3 and before allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the convert function of exrmultipart.cpp.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22949 | JFreeChart v1.5.4 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component /chart/annotations/CategoryLineAnnotation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22949</link><description>JFreeChart v1.5.4 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component /chart/annotations/CategoryLineAnnotation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23079 | JGraphT Core v1.5.2 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.jgrapht.alg.util.ToleranceDoubleComparator::compa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23079</link><description>JGraphT Core v1.5.2 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.jgrapht.alg.util.ToleranceDoubleComparator::compare(Double, Double).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23081 | ThreeTen Backport v1.6.8 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.threeten.bp.LocalDate::compareTo(ChronoLocal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23081</link><description>ThreeTen Backport v1.6.8 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.threeten.bp.LocalDate::compareTo(ChronoLocalDate).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23084 | Apfloat v1.10.1 was discovered to contain an ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException via the component org.apfloat.internal.DoubleCRTMath::add(double...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23084</link><description>Apfloat v1.10.1 was discovered to contain an ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException via the component org.apfloat.internal.DoubleCRTMath::add(double[], double[]).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0083 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0083</link><description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause a cross-site scripting error by network by running malicious scripts in users' browsers. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0082 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0082</link><description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause improper privilege management by sending open file requests to the application. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to local escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27632 | An issue in GNU Savane v.3.12 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the form_id in the form_header() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27632</link><description>An issue in GNU Savane v.3.12 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the form_id in the form_header() function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27631 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GNU Savane v.3.12 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via siteadmin/userg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27631</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GNU Savane v.3.12 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via siteadmin/usergroup.php</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 21:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3466 | SourceCodester Laundry Management System Pengeluaran.php laporan_filter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3466</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function laporan_filter of the file /application/controller/Pengeluaran.php. The manipulation of the argument dari/sampai leads to sql injection. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259747.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 21:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3465 | SourceCodester Laundry Management System Transaki.php laporan_filter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3465</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function laporan_filter of the file /application/controller/Transaki.php. The manipulation of the argument dari/sampai leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259746 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27630 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in GNU Savane v.3.12 and before allows a remote attacker to delete arbitrary files via crafted input...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27630</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in GNU Savane v.3.12 and before allows a remote attacker to delete arbitrary files via crafted input to the trackers_data_delete_file function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3464 | SourceCodester Laundry Management System Pelanggan.php laporan_filter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3464</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function laporan_filter of the file /application/controller/Pelanggan.php. The manipulation of the argument jeniskelamin leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259745 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23085 | Apfloat v1.10.1 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.apfloat.internal.DoubleScramble::scramble(double[], i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23085</link><description>Apfloat v1.10.1 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.apfloat.internal.DoubleScramble::scramble(double[], int, int[]).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23086 | Apfloat v1.10.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the component org.apfloat.internal.DoubleModMath::modPow(double.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23086</link><description>Apfloat v1.10.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the component org.apfloat.internal.DoubleModMath::modPow(double.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23078 | JGraphT Core v1.5.2 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.jgrapht.alg.util.ToleranceDoubleComparator::compa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23078</link><description>JGraphT Core v1.5.2 was discovered to contain a NullPointerException via the component org.jgrapht.alg.util.ToleranceDoubleComparator::compare(Double, Double).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3463 | SourceCodester Laundry Management System edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3463</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /karyawan/edit. The manipulation of the argument karyawan leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259744.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24279 | An issue in secdiskapp 1.5.1 (management program for NewQ Fingerprint Encryption Super Speed Flash Disk) allows attackers to gain escalated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24279</link><description>An issue in secdiskapp 1.5.1 (management program for NewQ Fingerprint Encryption Super Speed Flash Disk) allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via vsVerifyPassword and vsSetFingerPrintPower functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28224 | Ollama before 0.1.29 has a DNS rebinding vulnerability that can inadvertently allow remote access to the full API, thereby letting an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28224</link><description>Ollama before 0.1.29 has a DNS rebinding vulnerability that can inadvertently allow remote access to the full API, thereby letting an unauthorized user chat with a large language model, delete a model, or cause a denial of service (resource exhaustion).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28270 | An issue discovered in web-flash v3.0 allows attackers to reset passwords for arbitrary users via crafted POST request to /prod-api/user/res...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28270</link><description>An issue discovered in web-flash v3.0 allows attackers to reset passwords for arbitrary users via crafted POST request to /prod-api/user/resetPassword.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23082 | ThreeTen Backport v1.6.8 was discovered to contain an integer overflow via the component org.threeten.bp.format.DateTimeFormatter::parse(Cha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23082</link><description>ThreeTen Backport v1.6.8 was discovered to contain an integer overflow via the component org.threeten.bp.format.DateTimeFormatter::parse(CharSequence, ParsePosition).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3458 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway add_ikev2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3458</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add_ikev2.php. The manipulation of the argument TunnelId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259714 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3457 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway config_ISCGroupNoCache.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3457</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/config_ISCGroupNoCache.php. The manipulation of the argument GroupId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259713 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7164 | BackWPup &amp;lt; 4.0.4 - Unauthenticated Backup Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7164</link><description>The BackWPup WordPress plugin before 4.0.4 does not prevent visitors from leaking key information about ongoing backups, allowing unauthenticated attackers to download backups of a site's database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3456 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway config_Anticrack.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3456</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/config_Anticrack.php. The manipulation of the argument GroupId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259712.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 16:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31447 | Shopware has Improper Session Handling in store-api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31447</link><description>Shopware 6 is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. Starting in version 6.3.5.0 and prior to versions 6.6.1.0 and 6.5.8.8, when a authenticated request is made to `POST /store-api/account/logout`, the cart will be cleared, but the User won't be logged out. This affects only the direct store-api usage, as the PHP Storefront listens additionally on `CustomerLogoutEvent` and invalidates the session additionally. The problem has been fixed in Shopware 6.6.1.0 and 6.5.8.8. Those who are unable to update can install the latest version of the Shopware Security Plugin as a workaround.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31442 | Redon-Hub has incorrect permissions on all admin related commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31442</link><description>Redon Hub is a Roblox Product Delivery Bot, also known as a Hub. In all hubs before version 1.0.2, all commands are capable of being ran by all users, including admin commands. This allows users to receive products for free and delete/create/update products/tags/etc. The only non-affected command is `/products admin clear` as this was already programmed for bot owners only. All users should upgrade to version 1.0.2 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3445 | SourceCodester Laundry Management System laporan_filter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3445</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /karyawan/laporan_filter. The manipulation of the argument data_karyawan leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259702 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3455 | Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway add_postlogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3455</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_postlogin.php. The manipulation of the argument SingleLoginId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259711.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31224 | GPT Academic: Pickle deserializing cookies may pose RCE risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31224</link><description>GPT Academic provides interactive interfaces for large language models. A vulnerability was found in gpt_academic versions 3.64 through 3.73. The server deserializes untrustworthy data from the client, which may risk remote code execution. Any device that exposes the GPT Academic service to the Internet is vulnerable. Version 3.74 contains a patch for the issue. There are no known workarounds aside from upgrading to a patched version.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31221 | Clients removed during unpairing process may regain access if Sunshine was not restarted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31221</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Starting in version 0.10.0 and prior to version 0.23.0, after unpairing all devices in the web UI interface and then pairing only one device, all of the previously devices will be temporarily paired. Version 0.23.0 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, restarting Sunshine after unpairing all devices prevents the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3443 | SourceCodester Prison Management System apply_leave.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3443</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Employee/apply_leave.php. The manipulation of the argument txtstart_date/txtend_date leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259696.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3444 | Wangshen SecGate 3600 ?g=net_pro_keyword_import_save unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3444</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Wangshen SecGate 3600 up to 20240408. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /?g=net_pro_keyword_import_save. The manipulation of the argument reqfile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259701 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3442 | SourceCodester Prison Management System delete_leave.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3442</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Employee/delete_leave.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259695.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31205 | Saleor CSRF bypass in refreshToken mutation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31205</link><description>Saleor is an e-commerce platform. Starting in version 3.10.0 and prior to versions 3.14.64, 3.15.39, 3.16.39, 3.17.35, 3.18.31, and 3.19.19, an attacker may bypass cross-set request forgery (CSRF) validation when calling refresh token mutation with empty string. When a user provides an empty string in `refreshToken` mutation, while the token persists in `JWT_REFRESH_TOKEN_COOKIE_NAME` cookie, application omits validation against CSRF token and returns valid access token. Versions 3.14.64, 3.15.39, 3.16.39, 3.17.35, 3.18.31, and 3.19.19 contain a patch for the issue. As a workaround, one may replace `saleor.graphql.account.mutations.authentication.refresh_token.py.get_refresh_token`. This will fix the issue, but be aware, that it returns `JWT_MISSING_TOKEN` instead of `JWT_INVALID_TOKEN`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30269 | DataEase has database configuration information exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30269</link><description>DataEase, an open source data visualization and analysis tool, has a database configuration information exposure vulnerability prior to version 2.5.0. Visiting the `/de2api/engine/getEngine;.js` path via a browser reveals that the platform's database configuration is returned. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.5.0. No known workarounds are available aside from upgrading.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3440 | SourceCodester Prison Management System edit_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3440</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Admin/edit_profile.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259693 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3441 | SourceCodester Prison Management System edit-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3441</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Employee/edit-profile.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259694 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28732 | An issue was discovered in OFPMatch in parser.py in Faucet SDN Ryu version 4.34, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28732</link><description>An issue was discovered in OFPMatch in parser.py in Faucet SDN Ryu version 4.34, allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) (infinite loop).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2511 | Unbounded memory growth with session handling in TLSv1.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2511</link><description>Issue summary: Some non-default TLS server configurations can cause unbounded
memory growth when processing TLSv1.3 sessions

Impact summary: An attacker may exploit certain server configurations to trigger
unbounded memory growth that would lead to a Denial of Service

This problem can occur in TLSv1.3 if the non-default SSL_OP_NO_TICKET option is
being used (but not if early_data support is also configured and the default
anti-replay protection is in use). In this case, under certain conditions, the
session cache can get into an incorrect state and it will fail to flush properly
as it fills. The session cache will continue to grow in an unbounded manner. A
malicious client could deliberately create the scenario for this failure to
force a Denial of Service. It may also happen by accident in normal operation.

This issue only affects TLS servers supporting TLSv1.3. It does not affect TLS
clients.

The FIPS modules in 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue. OpenSSL
1.0.2 is also not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10006 | GamerZ WP-PostRatings wp-postratings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10006</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GamerZ WP-PostRatings up to 1.64. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file wp-postratings.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.65 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 6182a5682b12369ced0becd3b505439ce2eb8132. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-259629 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125111 | namithjawahar Wp-Insert cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125111</link><description>A vulnerability was found in namithjawahar Wp-Insert up to 2.0.8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.9 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is a07b7b08084b9b85859f3968ce7fde0fd1fcbba3. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259628.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28066 | In Unify CP IP Phone firmware 1.10.4.3, Weak Credentials are used (a hardcoded root password).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28066</link><description>In Unify CP IP Phone firmware 1.10.4.3, Weak Credentials are used (a hardcoded root password).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2834 | OpenText ArcSight Management Center and ArcSight Platform Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2834</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in OpenText ArcSight Management Center and ArcSight Platform. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31806 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability in the RebootSystem function which c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31806</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability in the RebootSystem function which can reboot the system without authorization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31807 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the hostTime parameter in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31807</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the hostTime parameter in the NTPSyncWithHost function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31808 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the webWlanIdx parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31808</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the webWlanIdx parameter in the setWebWlanIdx function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31809 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the FileName parameter in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31809</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the FileName parameter in the setUpgradeFW function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31811 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the langType parameter in th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31811</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the langType parameter in the setLanguageCfg function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31812 | In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211, an attacker can obtain sensitive information without authorization through the function getWiFiExt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31812</link><description>In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211, an attacker can obtain sensitive information without authorization through the function getWiFiExtenderConfig.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31813 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 does not contain an authentication mechanism by default.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31813</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 does not contain an authentication mechanism by default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31814 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 allows attackers to bypass login through the Form_Login function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31814</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 allows attackers to bypass login through the Form_Login function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31805 | TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 allows attackers to start the Telnet service without authorization via the telnet_enabled parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31805</link><description>TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 allows attackers to start the Telnet service without authorization via the telnet_enabled parameter in the setTelnetCfg function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31815 | In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7314_B20191204, an attacker can obtain the configuration file without authorization through /cgi-bin/ExportSetting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31815</link><description>In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7314_B20191204, an attacker can obtain the configuration file without authorization through /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31816 | In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211, an attacker can obtain sensitive information without authorization through the function getEasyWiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31816</link><description>In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211, an attacker can obtain sensitive information without authorization through the function getEasyWizardCfg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31817 | In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211, an attacker can obtain sensitive information without authorization through the function getSysStat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31817</link><description>In TOTOLINK EX200 V4.0.3c.7646_B20201211, an attacker can obtain sensitive information without authorization through the function getSysStatusCfg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43216 | AbrhilSoft Employee's Portal before v5.6.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability in the login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43216</link><description>AbrhilSoft Employee's Portal before v5.6.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability in the login page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26574 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Wondershare Filmora v.13.0.51 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26574</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Wondershare Filmora v.13.0.51 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the WSNativePushService.exe</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3439 | SourceCodester Prison Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3439</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Account/login.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259692.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 11:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3438 | SourceCodester Prison Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3438</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/login.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259691.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 11:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26811 | ksmbd: validate payload size in ipc response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26811</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: validate payload size in ipc response

If installing malicious ksmbd-tools, ksmbd.mountd can return invalid ipc
response to ksmbd kernel server. ksmbd should validate payload size of
ipc response from ksmbd.mountd to avoid memory overrun or
slab-out-of-bounds. This patch validate 3 ipc response that has payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 10:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52364 | Vulnerability of input parameters being not strictly verified in the RSMC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52364</link><description>Vulnerability of input parameters being not strictly verified in the RSMC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52385 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the RSMC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52385</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the RSMC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52386 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the RSMC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52386</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the RSMC module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27895 | Vulnerability of permission control in the window module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27895</link><description>Vulnerability of permission control in the window module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27896 | Input verification vulnerability in the log module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can affect integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27896</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the log module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can affect integrity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27897 | Input verification vulnerability in the call module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27897</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the call module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52550 | Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52550</link><description>Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52551 | Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52551</link><description>Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52552 | Input verification vulnerability in the power module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52552</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the power module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52553 | Race condition vulnerability in the Wi-Fi module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52553</link><description>Race condition vulnerability in the Wi-Fi module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52554 | Permission control vulnerability in the Bluetooth module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52554</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the Bluetooth module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31375 | WordPress WP2LEADS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31375</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saleswonder.Biz Team WP2LEADS.This issue affects WP2LEADS: from n/a through 3.2.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52359 | Vulnerability of permission verification in some APIs in the ActivityTaskManagerService module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52359</link><description>Vulnerability of permission verification in some APIs in the ActivityTaskManagerService module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52543 | Permission verification vulnerability in the system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52543</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52544 | Vulnerability of file path verification being bypassed in the email module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52544</link><description>Vulnerability of file path verification being bypassed in the email module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52545 | Vulnerability of undefined permissions in the Calendar app.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52545</link><description>Vulnerability of undefined permissions in the Calendar app.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52546 | Vulnerability of package name verification being bypassed in the Calendar app.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52546</link><description>Vulnerability of package name verification being bypassed in the Calendar app.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52549 | Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52549</link><description>Vulnerability of data verification errors in the kernel module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31357 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31357</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BdThemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52539 | Permission verification vulnerability in the Settings module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52539</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the Settings module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52540 | Vulnerability of improper authentication in the Iaware module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52540</link><description>Vulnerability of improper authentication in the Iaware module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52541 | Authentication vulnerability in the API for app pre-loading.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52541</link><description>Authentication vulnerability in the API for app pre-loading.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52542 | Permission verification vulnerability in the system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52542</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the system module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52388 | Permission control vulnerability in the clock module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52388</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the clock module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52537 | Vulnerability of package name verification being bypassed in the HwIms module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52537</link><description>Vulnerability of package name verification being bypassed in the HwIms module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52538 | Vulnerability of package name verification being bypassed in the HwIms module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52538</link><description>Vulnerability of package name verification being bypassed in the HwIms module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23189 | Embedded content references at tasks could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23189</link><description>Embedded content references at tasks could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account, access to another account within the same context or an successful social engineering attack to make users import external content. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-generated content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23190 | Upsell shop information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23190</link><description>Upsell shop information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23191 | Upsell advertisement information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23191</link><description>Upsell advertisement information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23192 | RSS feeds that contain malicious data- attributes could be abused to inject script code to a users browser session when reading compromised ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23192</link><description>RSS feeds that contain malicious data- attributes could be abused to inject script code to a users browser session when reading compromised RSS feeds or successfully luring users to compromised accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Potentially malicious attributes now get removed from external RSS content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30675 | Unauthorized node injection vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability could allow a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30675</link><description>Unauthorized node injection vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability could allow a malicious user to escalate privileges by injecting malicious ROS2 nodes into the system remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30674 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3, allows remote attackers to gain contr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30674</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3, allows remote attackers to gain control of multiple ROS2 nodes. Unauthorized information access to these nodes could result in compromised system integrity, the execution of arbitrary commands, and disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30672 | Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30672</link><description>Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), and obtain sensitive information via the file upload component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30667 | Insecure deserialization vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30667</link><description>Insecure deserialization vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or obtain sensitive information via crafted input to the data handling components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30666 | A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in the C++ components of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30666</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in the C++ components of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via improper handling of arrays or strings within these components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30665 | An OS command injection vulnerability has been discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30665</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability primarily affects the command processing or system call components in ROS, making them susceptible to manipulation by malicious entities. Through this, unauthorized commands can be executed, leading to remote code execution (RCE), data theft, and malicious activities. The affected components include External Command Execution Modules, System Call Handlers, and Interface Scripts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30663 | An issue was discovered in the default configurations of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSIO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30663</link><description>An issue was discovered in the default configurations of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to gain access using default credentials, posing a serious threat to the integrity and security of the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30662 | An issue was discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, where the system transmit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30662</link><description>An issue was discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, where the system transmits messages in plaintext. This flaw exposes sensitive information, making it vulnerable to man-in-the-middle (MitM) attacks, and allowing attackers to easily intercept and access this data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30661 | An unauthorized access vulnerability has been discovered in ROS Melodic Morenia versions where ROS_VERSION is 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30661</link><description>An unauthorized access vulnerability has been discovered in ROS Melodic Morenia versions where ROS_VERSION is 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3. This vulnerability could potentially allow a malicious user to gain unauthorized information access to multiple ROS nodes remotely. Unauthorized information access to these nodes could result in compromised system integrity, the execution of arbitrary commands, and disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30659 | Shell Injection vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia versions ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30659</link><description>Shell Injection vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia versions ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27488 | Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in ZLMediaKit versions 1.0 through 8.0, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27488</link><description>Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in ZLMediaKit versions 1.0 through 8.0, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information. The application system enables the http API interface by default and uses the secret parameter method to authenticate the http restful api interface, but the secret is hardcoded by default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31022 | An issue was discovered in CandyCMS version 1.0.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the install.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31022</link><description>An issue was discovered in CandyCMS version 1.0.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the install.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1292 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt; 2.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1292</link><description>The WPB Show Core WordPress plugin before 2.7 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1588 | SendPress Newsletters &amp;lt;= 1.23.11.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1588</link><description>The SendPress Newsletters WordPress plugin through 1.23.11.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1589 | SendPress Newsletters &amp;lt;= 1.23.11.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Form Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1589</link><description>The SendPress Newsletters WordPress plugin through 1.23.11.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1752 | Font Farsi &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1752</link><description>The Font Farsi WordPress plugin through 1.6.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1956 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt; 2.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1956</link><description>The wpb-show-core WordPress plugin before 2.7 does not sanitise and escape the parameters before outputting it back in the response of an unauthenticated request, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1958 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt; 2.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1958</link><description>The WPB Show Core WordPress plugin before 2.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or unauthenticated users</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52341 | In Plaintext COUNTER CHECK message accepted before AS security activation, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52341</link><description>In Plaintext COUNTER CHECK message accepted before AS security activation, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52342 | In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52342</link><description>In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52343 | In SecurityCommand message after as security has been actived., there is a possible improper input validation. This could lead to remote inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52343</link><description>In SecurityCommand message after as security has been actived., there is a possible improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52344 | In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52344</link><description>In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52345 | In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52345</link><description>In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52346 | In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52346</link><description>In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52347 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52347</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52348 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52348</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52349 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52349</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52350 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52350</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52351 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52351</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52352 | In Network Adapter Service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52352</link><description>In Network Adapter Service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52533 | In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52533</link><description>In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52534 | In ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52534</link><description>In ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52535 | In vsp driver, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52535</link><description>In vsp driver, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52536 | In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52536</link><description>In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23658 | In camera driver, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23658</link><description>In camera driver, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28744 | The password is empty in the initial configuration of ACERA 9010-08 firmware v02.04 and earlier, and ACERA 9010-24 firmware v02.04 and earli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28744</link><description>The password is empty in the initial configuration of ACERA 9010-08 firmware v02.04 and earlier, and ACERA 9010-24 firmware v02.04 and earlier. An unauthenticated attacker may log in to the product with no password, and obtain and/or alter information such as network configuration and user information. The products are affected only when running in non MS mode with the initial configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36829 | The Mojolicious module before 8.65 for Perl is vulnerable to secure_compare timing attacks that allow an attacker to guess the length of a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36829</link><description>The Mojolicious module before 8.65 for Perl is vulnerable to secure_compare timing attacks that allow an attacker to guess the length of a secret string. Only versions after 1.74 are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47208 | The Mojolicious module before 9.11 for Perl has a bug in format detection that can potentially be exploited for denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47208</link><description>The Mojolicious module before 9.11 for Perl has a bug in format detection that can potentially be exploited for denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3437 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Avatar add-admin.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3437</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/add-admin.php of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259631.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3434 | CP Plus Wi-Fi Camera User Management improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3434</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CP Plus Wi-Fi Camera up to 20240401. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component User Management. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259615. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3436 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Avatar edit-photo.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3436</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Admin/edit-photo.php of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259630 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3433 | PuneethReddyHC Event Management register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3433</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PuneethReddyHC Event Management 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /backend/register.php. The manipulation of the argument event_id/full_name/email/mobile/college/branch leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-259614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3432 | PuneethReddyHC Event Management register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3432</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PuneethReddyHC Event Management 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /backend/register.php. The manipulation of the argument event_id/full_name/email/mobile/college/branch leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259613 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3430 | QKSMS Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3430</link><description>A vulnerability was found in QKSMS up to 3.9.4 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259611. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3431 | EyouCMS Backend deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3431</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EyouCMS 1.6.5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=Field&amp;a=channel_edit of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument channel_id leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259612. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:07:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31948 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an attacker using a malformed Prefix SID attribute in a BGP UPDATE packet can cause the bgpd daemon to crash...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31948</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an attacker using a malformed Prefix SID attribute in a BGP UPDATE packet can cause the bgpd daemon to crash.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31949 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an infinite loop can occur when receiving a MP/GR capability as a dynamic capability because malformed data ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31949</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an infinite loop can occur when receiving a MP/GR capability as a dynamic capability because malformed data results in a pointer not advancing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31950 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ri for OSPF LSA packets during an attempt t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31950</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ri for OSPF LSA packets during an attempt to read Segment Routing subTLVs (their size is not validated).</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31951 | In the Opaque LSA Extended Link parser in FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ext_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31951</link><description>In the Opaque LSA Extended Link parser in FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ext_link for OSPF LSA packets during an attempt to read Segment Routing Adjacency SID subTLVs (lengths are not validated).</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31291 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.6 - IDOR on Friend Request vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31291</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31296 | WordPress BookingPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.81 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31296</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Repute Infosystems BookingPress.This issue affects BookingPress: from n/a through 1.0.81.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31233 | WordPress Rehub theme &amp;lt;= 19.6.1 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Sizam Rehub.This issue affects Rehub: from n/a through 19.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31234 | WordPress REHub Framework plugin &amp;lt; 19.6.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Sizam REHub Framework.This issue affects REHub Framework: from n/a before 19.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31241 | WordPress LearnPress Export Import plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress Export Import.This issue affects LearnPress Export Import: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22155 | WordPress WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22155</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic WooCommerce.This issue affects WooCommerce: from n/a through 8.5.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31236 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.93 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.3.93.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31260 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge.This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31255 | WordPress ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31255</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ELEXtensions ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31256 | WordPress WebinarPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.33.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31256</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebinarPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WebinarPress: from n/a through 1.33.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31257 | WordPress Formsite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31257</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Formsite Formsite | Embed online forms to collect orders, registrations, leads, and surveys allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Formsite | Embed online forms to collect orders, registrations, leads, and surveys: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31258 | WordPress Form to Chat App plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31258</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Micro.Company Form to Chat App allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Form to Chat App: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31306 | WordPress Essential Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Blocks for Gutenberg allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Essential Blocks for Gutenberg: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31344 | WordPress Easy Login Styler  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31344</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Phpbits Creative Studio Easy Login Styler – White Label Admin Login Page for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Login Styler – White Label Admin Login Page for WordPress: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31346 | WordPress Gradient Text Widget for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31346</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blocksmarket Gradient Text Widget for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gradient Text Widget for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31348 | WordPress Super Testimonials plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31348</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themepoints Testimonials allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Testimonials: from n/a through 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31280 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31280</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin.This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 4.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31286 | WordPress WP Photo Album Plus plugin &amp;lt; 8.6.03.005 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31286</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in J.N. Breetvelt a.K.A. OpaJaap WP Photo Album Plus.This issue affects WP Photo Album Plus: from n/a before 8.6.03.005.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31292 | WordPress Import XML and RSS Feeds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31292</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Moove Agency Import XML and RSS Feeds.This issue affects Import XML and RSS Feeds: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31349 | WordPress MailMunch – Grow your Email List plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MailMunch MailMunch – Grow your Email List allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MailMunch – Grow your Email List: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3428 | SourceCodester Online Courseware edit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3428</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259600.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31277 | WordPress Product Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.32 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31277</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PickPlugins Product Designer.This issue affects Product Designer: from n/a through 1.0.32.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31345 | WordPress Auto Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31345</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Sukhchain Singh Auto Poster.This issue affects Auto Poster: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31288 | WordPress RapidLoad plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31288</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in RapidLoad RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize.This issue affects RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize: from n/a through 2.2.11.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31308 | WordPress WP Import Export Lite &amp;amp; WP Import Export plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.26 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31308</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in VJInfotech WP Import Export Lite.This issue affects WP Import Export Lite: from n/a through 3.9.26.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3427 | SourceCodester Online Courseware addq.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3427</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file addq.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259599.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3426 | SourceCodester Online Courseware editt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3426</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file editt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 16:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3425 | SourceCodester Online Courseware activateall.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3425</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/activateall.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259597 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 16:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3424 | SourceCodester Online Courseware listscore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3424</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/listscore.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259596.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3423 | SourceCodester Online Courseware activateteach.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3423</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/activateteach.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259595.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3422 | SourceCodester Online Courseware activatestud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3422</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/activatestud.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 13:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3421 | SourceCodester Online Courseware deactivatestud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3421</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/deactivatestud.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259593 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3420 | SourceCodester Online Courseware saveedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3420</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/saveedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259592.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3419 | SourceCodester Online Courseware edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3419</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259591.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3418 | SourceCodester Online Courseware deactivateteach.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3418</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/deactivateteach.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259590 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52716 | Vulnerability of starting activities in the background in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52716</link><description>Vulnerability of starting activities in the background in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52717 | Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52717</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4438 | kyivstarteam react-native-sms-user-consent SmsUserConsentModule.kt registerReceiver improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4438</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in kyivstarteam react-native-sms-user-consent up to 1.1.4 on Android. Affected by this issue is the function registerReceiver of the file android/src/main/java/ua/kyivstar/reactnativesmsuserconsent/SmsUserConsentModule.kt. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Attacking locally is a requirement. Upgrading to version 1.1.5 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 5423dcb0cd3e4d573b5520a71fa08aa279e4c3c7. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259508.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52715 | The SystemUI module has a vulnerability in permission management.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52715</link><description>The SystemUI module has a vulnerability in permission management.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52382 | Vulnerability of improper control over foreground service notifications in the notification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52382</link><description>Vulnerability of improper control over foreground service notifications in the notification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52714 | Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the hwnff module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52714</link><description>Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the hwnff module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52713 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52713</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30418 | Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the app management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30418</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the app management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30416 | Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the underlying driver module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30416</link><description>Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the underlying driver module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30417 | Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth-based sharing module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30417</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth-based sharing module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30413 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30413</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30414 | Command injection vulnerability in the AccountManager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30414</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in the AccountManager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30415 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30415</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3417 | SourceCodester Online Courseware saveeditt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3417</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/saveeditt.php. The manipulation of the argument contact leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259589 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3416 | SourceCodester Online Courseware editt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3416</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/editt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259588.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 03:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6877 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Store...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6877</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Content-Type field of error messages when retrieving an invalid RSS feed. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>