<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-14021 | LlamaIndex &amp;lt;= 0.11.6 BGEM3Index Unsafe Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-14021</link><description>LlamaIndex (run-llama/llama_index) versions up to and including 0.11.6 contain an unsafe deserialization vulnerability in BGEM3Index.load_from_disk() in llama_index/indices/managed/bge_m3/base.py. The function uses pickle.load() to deserialize multi_embed_store.pkl from a user-supplied persist_dir without validation. An attacker who can provide a crafted persist directory containing a malicious pickle file can trigger arbitrary code execution when the victim loads the index from disk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58339 | LlamaIndex &amp;lt;= 0.12.2 VannaQueryEngine SQL Execution Allows Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58339</link><description>LlamaIndex (run-llama/llama_index) versions up to and including 0.12.2 contain an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the VannaPack VannaQueryEngine implementation. The custom_query() logic generates SQL statements from a user-supplied prompt and executes them via vn.run_sql() without enforcing query execution limits In downstream deployments where untrusted users can supply prompts, an attacker can trigger expensive or unbounded SQL operations that exhaust CPU or memory resources, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. The vulnerable execution path occurs in llama_index/packs/vanna/base.py within custom_query().</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58340 | LangChain &amp;lt;= 0.3.1 MRKLOutputParser ReDoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58340</link><description>LangChain versions up to and including 0.3.1 contain a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) vulnerability in the MRKLOutputParser.parse() method (libs/langchain/langchain/agents/mrkl/output_parser.py). The parser applies a backtracking-prone regular expression when extracting tool actions from model output. An attacker who can supply or influence the parsed text (for example via prompt injection in downstream applications that pass LLM output directly into MRKLOutputParser.parse()) can trigger excessive CPU consumption by providing a crafted payload, causing significant parsing delays and a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15514 | Ollama Multi-Modal Model Image Processing NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15514</link><description>Ollama 0.11.5-rc0 through current version 0.13.5 contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability in the multi-modal model image processing functionality. When processing base64-encoded image data via the /api/chat endpoint, the application fails to validate that the decoded data represents valid media before passing it to the mtmd_helper_bitmap_init_from_buf function. This function can return NULL for malformed input, but the code does not check this return value before dereferencing the pointer in subsequent operations. A remote attacker can exploit this by sending specially crafted base64 image data that decodes to invalid media, causing a segmentation fault and crashing the runner process. This results in a denial of service condition where the model becomes unavailable to all users until the service is restarted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22212 | TinyOS &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in mcp2200gpio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22212</link><description>TinyOS versions up to and including 2.1.2 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the mcp2200gpio utility. The vulnerability is caused by unsafe use of strcpy() and strcat() functions when constructing device paths during automatic device discovery. A local attacker can exploit this by creating specially crafted filenames under /dev/usb/, leading to stack memory corruption and application crashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22213 | RIOT OS &amp;lt;= 2026.01-devel-317 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in tapslip6 Utility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22213</link><description>RIOT OS versions up to and including 2026.01-devel-317 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the tapslip6 utility. The vulnerability is caused by unsafe string concatenation in the devopen() function, which constructs a device path using unbounded user-controlled input. The utility uses strcpy() and strcat() to concatenate the fixed prefix '/dev/' with a user-supplied device name provided via the -s command-line option without bounds checking. This allows an attacker to supply an excessively long device name and overflow a fixed-size stack buffer, leading to process crashes and memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22214 | RIOT OS &amp;lt;= 2026.01-devel-317 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in ethos Serial Frame Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22214</link><description>RIOT OS versions up to and including 2026.01-devel-317 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the ethos utility due to missing bounds checking when processing incoming serial frame data. The vulnerability occurs in the _handle_char() function, where incoming frame bytes are appended to a fixed-size stack buffer without verifying that the current write index remains within bounds. An attacker capable of sending crafted serial or TCP-framed input can cause the current write index to exceed the buffer size, resulting in a write past the end of the stack buffer. This condition leads to memory corruption and application crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22695 | LIBPNG has a heap buffer over-read in png_image_read_direct_scaled (regression from CVE-2025-65018 fix)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22695</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From 1.6.51 to 1.6.53, there is a heap buffer over-read in the libpng simplified API function png_image_finish_read when processing interlaced 16-bit PNGs with 8-bit output format and non-minimal row stride. This is a regression introduced by the fix for CVE-2025-65018. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.54.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22801 | LIBPNG has an integer truncation causing heap buffer over-read in png_image_write_*</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22801</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. From 1.6.26 to 1.6.53, there is an integer truncation in the libpng simplified write API functions png_write_image_16bit and png_write_image_8bit causes heap buffer over-read when the caller provides a negative row stride (for bottom-up image layouts) or a stride exceeding 65535 bytes. The bug was introduced in libpng 1.6.26 (October 2016) by casts added to silence compiler warnings on 16-bit systems. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.54.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22812 | OpenCode&amp;#x27;s Unauthenticated HTTP Server Allows Arbitrary Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22812</link><description>OpenCode is an open source AI coding agent. Prior to 1.0.216, OpenCode automatically starts an unauthenticated HTTP server that allows any local process (or any website via permissive CORS) to execute arbitrary shell commands with the user's privileges. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.216.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22813 | Malicious website can execute commands on the local system through XSS in the OpenCode web UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22813</link><description>OpenCode is an open source AI coding agent. The markdown renderer used for LLM responses will insert arbitrary HTML into the DOM. There is no sanitization with DOMPurify or even a CSP on the web interface to prevent JavaScript execution via HTML injection. This means controlling the LLM response for a chat session gets JavaScript execution on the http://localhost:4096 origin. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22805 | Metabase channel test endpoint can reach internal local addresses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22805</link><description>Metabase is an open-source data analytics platform. Prior to 55.13, 56.3, and 57.1, self-hosted Metabase instances that allow users to create subscriptions could be potentially impacted if their Metabase is colocated with other unsecured resources. This vulnerability is fixed in 55.13, 56.3, and 57.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22800 | PILOS affected by a CSRF via GET request allows unintentional termination of all active video conferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22800</link><description>PILOS (Platform for Interactive Live-Online Seminars) is a frontend for BigBlueButton. Prior to 4.10.0, Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in an administrative API endpoint responsible for terminating all active video conferences on a single server. The affected endpoint performs a destructive action but is exposed via an HTTP GET request. Although proper authorization checks are enforced and the endpoint cannot be triggered cross-site, the use of GET allows the action to be implicitly invoked through same-site content (e.g. embedded resources rendered within the application). As a result, an authenticated administrator who views crafted content within the application may unknowingly trigger the endpoint, causing all active video conferences on the server to be terminated without explicit intent or confirmation. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.10.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22804 | Termix has a Stored XSS in File Manager leading to Local File Inclusion (LFI) in Electron and Session Hijacking in Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22804</link><description>Termix is a web-based server management platform with SSH terminal, tunneling, and file editing capabilities. From 1.7.0 to 1.9.0, Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Termix File Manager component. The application fails to sanitize SVG file content before rendering it. This allows an attacker who has compromised a managed SSH server to plant a malicious file, which, when previewed by the Termix user, executes arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the application. The vulnerability is located in src/ui/desktop/apps/file-manager/components/FileViewer.tsx. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22798 | hermes&amp;#x27;s raw options logging may disclose secrets passed in via subcommand options argument</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22798</link><description>hermes is an implementation of the HERMES workflow to automatize software publication with rich metadata. From 0.8.1 to before 0.9.1, hermes subcommands take arbitrary options under the -O argument. These have been logged in raw form. If users provide sensitive data such as API tokens (e.g., via hermes deposit -O invenio_rdm.auth_token SECRET), these are written to the log file in plain text, making them available to whoever can access the log file. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22799 | emlog Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22799</link><description>Emlog is an open source website building system. emlog v2.6.1 and earlier exposes a REST API endpoint (/index.php?rest-api=upload) for media file uploads. The endpoint fails to implement proper validation of file types, extensions, and content, allowing authenticated attackers (with a valid API key or admin session cookie) to upload arbitrary files (including malicious PHP scripts) to the server. An attacker can obtain the API key either by gaining administrator access to enable the REST API setting, or via information disclosure vulnerabilities in the application. Once uploaded, the malicious PHP file can be executed to gain remote code execution (RCE) on the target server, leading to full server compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22794 | Account Takeover Vulnerability in Appsmith</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22794</link><description>Appsmith is a platform to build admin panels, internal tools, and dashboards. Prior to 1.93, the server uses the Origin value from the request headers as the email link baseUrl without validation. If an attacker controls the Origin, password reset / email verification links in emails can be generated pointing to the attacker’s domain, causing authentication tokens to be exposed and potentially leading to account takeover. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.93.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22789 | WebErpMesv2 has a File Upload Validation Bypass Leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22789</link><description>WebErpMesv2 is a Resource Management and Manufacturing execution system Web for industry. Prior to 1.19, WebErpMesv2 contains a file upload validation bypass vulnerability in multiple controllers that allows authenticated users to upload arbitrary files, including PHP scripts, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE). This vulnerability is identical in nature to CVE-2025-52130 but exists in different code locations that were not addressed by the original fix. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29329 | Buffer Overflow in the ippprint (Internet Printing Protocol) service in Sagemcom F@st 3686 MAGYAR_4.121.0 allows remote attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29329</link><description>Buffer Overflow in the ippprint (Internet Printing Protocol) service in Sagemcom F@st 3686 MAGYAR_4.121.0 allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22788 | WebErpMesv2 allows unauthenticated API Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22788</link><description>WebErpMesv2 is a Resource Management and Manufacturing execution system Web for industry. Prior to 1.19, the WebErpMesV2 application exposes multiple sensitive API endpoints without authentication middleware. An unauthenticated remote attacker can read business-critical data including companies, quotes, orders, tasks, and whiteboards. Limited write access allows creation of company records and full manipulation of collaboration whiteboards. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12420 | Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation in ServiceNow AI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12420</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the ServiceNow AI Platform that could enable an unauthenticated user to impersonate another user and perform the operations that the impersonated user is entitled to perform.

ServiceNow has addressed this vulnerability by deploying a relevant security update to  hosted instances in October 2025. Security updates have also been provided to ServiceNow self-hosted customers, partners, and hosted customers with unique configurations. Additionally, the vulnerability is addressed in the listed Store App versions. We recommend that customers promptly apply an appropriate security update or upgrade if they have not already done so.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67146 | Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in AbhishekMali21 GYM-MANAGEMENT-SYSTEM 1.0 via the 'name' parameter in (1) member_search.php, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67146</link><description>Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in AbhishekMali21 GYM-MANAGEMENT-SYSTEM 1.0 via the 'name' parameter in (1) member_search.php, (2) trainer_search.php, and (3) gym_search.php, and via the 'id' parameter in (4) payment_search.php. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit these issues to inject malicious SQL commands, leading to unauthorized data extraction, authentication bypass, or modification of database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22786 | The arbitrary file upload vulnerability caused by path traversal is on github.com/flipped-aurora/gin-vue-admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22786</link><description>Gin-vue-admin is a backstage management system based on vue and gin. Gin-vue-admin &lt;= v2.8.7 has a path traversal vulnerability in the breakpoint resume upload functionality. Attacker can upload any files on any directory. In the breakpoint_continue.go file, the MakeFile function accepts a fileName parameter through the /fileUploadAndDownload/breakpointContinueFinish API endpoint and directly concatenates it with the base directory path (./fileDir/) using os.OpenFile() without any validation for directory traversal sequences (e.g., ../). An attacker with file upload privileges could exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67147 | Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in amansuryawanshi Gym-Management-System-PHP 1.0 via the 'name', 'email', and 'comment' paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67147</link><description>Multiple SQL Injection vulnerabilities exist in amansuryawanshi Gym-Management-System-PHP 1.0 via the 'name', 'email', and 'comment' parameters in (1) submit_contact.php, the 'username' and 'pass_key' parameters in (2) secure_login.php, and the 'login_id', 'pwfield', and 'login_key' parameters in (3) change_s_pwd.php. An unauthenticated or authenticated attacker can exploit these issues to bypass authentication, execute arbitrary SQL commands, modify database records, delete data, or escalate privileges to administrator level.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22772 | Fulcio vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via MetaIssuer Regex Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22772</link><description>Fulcio is a certificate authority for issuing code signing certificates for an OpenID Connect (OIDC) identity. Prior to 1.8.5, Fulcio's metaRegex() function uses unanchored regex, allowing attackers to bypass MetaIssuer URL validation and trigger SSRF to arbitrary internal services. Since the SSRF only can trigger GET requests, the request cannot mutate state. The response from the GET request is not returned to the caller so data exfiltration is not possible. A malicious actor could attempt to probe an internal network through Blind SSRF. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-41074 | A CSRF issue in index.php in QloApps hotel eCommerce 1.5.1 allows an attacker to change the admin's email address via a crafted HTML documen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41074</link><description>A CSRF issue in index.php in QloApps hotel eCommerce 1.5.1 allows an attacker to change the admin's email address via a crafted HTML document.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36331 | Incorrect access control in the /member/orderList API of xmall v1.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily access other users' order details via ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36331</link><description>Incorrect access control in the /member/orderList API of xmall v1.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily access other users' order details via manipulation of the query parameter userId.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51567 | A SQL Injection was found in the /exam/user/profile.php page of kashipara Online Exam System V1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51567</link><description>A SQL Injection was found in the /exam/user/profile.php page of kashipara Online Exam System V1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL command to get unauthorized database access via the rname, rcollage, rnumber, rgender and rpassword parameters in a POST HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66802 | Sourcecodester Covid-19 Contact Tracing System 1.0 is vulnerable to RCE (Remote Code Execution). The application receives a reverse shell (p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66802</link><description>Sourcecodester Covid-19 Contact Tracing System 1.0 is vulnerable to RCE (Remote Code Execution). The application receives a reverse shell (php) into imagem of the user enabling RCE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22200 | osTicket &amp;lt;= 1.18.2 PDF Export Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22200</link><description>Enhancesoft osTicket versions up to and including 1.18.2 contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability in the ticket PDF export functionality. A remote attacker can submit a ticket containing crafted rich-text HTML that includes PHP filter expressions which are insufficiently sanitized before being processed by the mPDF PDF generator during export. When the attacker exports the ticket to PDF, the generated PDF can embed the contents of attacker-selected files from the server filesystem as bitmap images, allowing disclosure of sensitive local files in the context of the osTicket application user. This issue is exploitable in default configurations where guests may create tickets and access ticket status, or where self-registration is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22784 | Lychee cross-album password propagation on Album unlocking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22784</link><description>Lychee is a free, open-source photo-management tool. Prior to 7.1.0, an authorization vulnerability exists in Lychee's album password unlock functionality that allows users to gain possibly unauthorized access to other users' password-protected albums. When a user unlocks a password-protected public album, the system automatically unlocks ALL other public albums that share the same password, resulting in a complete authorization bypass. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22785 | orval MCP client is vulnerable to a code injection attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22785</link><description>orval generates type-safe JS clients (TypeScript) from any valid OpenAPI v3 or Swagger v2 specification. Prior to 7.18.0, the MCP server generation logic relies on string manipulation that incorporates the summary field from the OpenAPI specification without proper validation or escaping. This allows an attacker to "break out" of the string literal and inject arbitrary code. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.18.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22776 | cpp-httplib vulnerable to a denial of service (DOS) using a zip bomb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22776</link><description>cpp-httplib is a C++11 single-file header-only cross platform HTTP/HTTPS library. Prior to version 0.30.1, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in cpp-httplib due to the unsafe handling of compressed HTTP request bodies (Content-Encoding: gzip, br, etc.). The library validates the payload_max_length against the compressed data size received from the network, but does not limit the size of the decompressed data stored in memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22781 | TinyWeb CGI Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22781</link><description>TinyWeb is a web server (HTTP, HTTPS) written in Delphi for Win32. TinyWeb HTTP Server before version 1.98 is vulnerable to OS command injection via CGI ISINDEX-style query parameters. The query parameters are passed as command-line arguments to the CGI executable via Windows CreateProcess(). An unauthenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the server by injecting Windows shell metacharacters into HTTP requests. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.98.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22783 | Iris Allows Arbitrary File Deletion via Mass Assignment in Datastore File Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22783</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform that helps incident responders share technical details during investigations. Prior to 2.4.24, the DFIR-IRIS datastore file management system has a vulnerability where mass assignment of the file_local_name field combined with path trust in the delete operation enables authenticated users to delete arbitrary filesystem paths. The vulnerability manifests through a three-step attack chain: authenticated users upload a file to the datastore, update the file's file_local_name field to point to an arbitrary filesystem path through mass assignment, then trigger the delete operation which removes the target file without path validation. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22252 | LibreChat MCP Stdio Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22252</link><description>LibreChat is a ChatGPT clone with additional features. Prior to v0.8.2-rc2, LibreChat's MCP stdio transport accepts arbitrary commands without validation, allowing any authenticated user to execute shell commands as root inside the container through a single API request. This vulnerability is fixed in v0.8.2-rc2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22771 | Envoy Extension Policy lua scripts injection causes arbitrary command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22771</link><description>Envoy Gateway is an open source project for managing Envoy Proxy as a standalone or Kubernetes-based application gateway. Prior to 1.5.7 and 1.6.2, EnvoyExtensionPolicy Lua scripts executed by Envoy proxy can be used to leak the proxy's credentials. These credentials can then be used to communicate with the control plane and gain access to all secrets that are used by Envoy proxy, e.g. TLS private keys and credentials used for downstream and upstream communication. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.7 and 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22251 | wlc may leak API keys due to an insecure API key configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22251</link><description>wlc is a Weblate command-line client using Weblate's REST API. Prior to 1.17.0, wlc supported providing unscoped API keys in the setting. This practice was discouraged for years, but the code was never removed. This might cause the API key to be leaked to different servers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22033 | Label Studio vulnerable to full account takeover by chaining Stored XSS + IDOR in User Profile via custom_hotkeys field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22033</link><description>Label Studio is a multi-type data labeling and annotation tool. In 1.22.0 and earlier, a persistent stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the custom_hotkeys functionality of the application. An authenticated attacker (or one who can trick a user/administrator into updating their custom_hotkeys) can inject JavaScript code that executes in other users’ browsers when those users load any page using the templates/base.html template. Because the application exposes an API token endpoint (/api/current-user/token) to the browser and lacks robust CSRF protection on some API endpoints, the injected script may fetch the victim’s API token or call token reset endpoints — enabling full account takeover and unauthorized API access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22250 | wlc can skip SSL verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22250</link><description>wlc is a Weblate command-line client using Weblate's REST API. Prior to 1.17.0, the SSL verification would be skipped for some crafted URLs. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.17.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68471 | Avahi has a reachable assertion in lookup_start</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68471</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In 0.9-rc2 and earlier, avahi-daemon can be crashed by sending 2 unsolicited announcements with CNAME resource records 2 seconds apart.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68276 | Avahi has a reachable assertion in avahi_wide_area_scan_cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68276</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In 0.9-rc2 and earlier, an unprivileged local users can crash avahi-daemon (with wide-area disabled) by creating record browsers with the AVAHI_LOOKUP_USE_WIDE_AREA flag set via D-Bus. This can be done by either calling
the RecordBrowserNew method directly or creating hostname/address/service resolvers/browsers that create those browsers internally themselves.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68468 | Avahi has a reachable assertion in lookup_multicast_callback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68468</link><description>Avahi is a system which facilitates service discovery on a local network via the mDNS/DNS-SD protocol suite. In 0.9-rc2 and earlier, avahi-daemon can be crashed by sending unsolicited announcements containing CNAME resource records pointing it to resource records with short TTLs. As soon as they expire avahi-daemon crashes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68657 | espressif/usb_host_hid Double-Free Race Condition in USB Host HID Device Close Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68657</link><description>Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host HID (Human Interface Device) Driver allows access to HID devices. Prior to 1.1.0, calls to hid_host_device_close() can free the same usb_transfer_t twice. The USB event callback and user code share the hid_iface_t state without locking, so both can tear down a READY interface simultaneously, corrupting heap metadata inside the ESP USB host stack. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68656 | Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host HID (Human Interface Device) Driver Descriptor Use-After-Free Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68656</link><description>Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host HID (Human Interface Device) Driver allows access to HID devices. Prior to 1.1.0, usb_class_request_get_descriptor() frees and reallocates hid_device-&gt;ctrl_xfer when an oversized descriptor is requested but continues to use the stale local pointer, leading to an immediate use-after-free when processing attacker-controlled Report Descriptor lengths. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22050 | ONTAP versions 9.16.1 prior to 9.16.1P9 and 9.17.1 prior to 9.17.1P2 with snapshot locking enabled are susceptible to a vulnerability which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22050</link><description>ONTAP versions 9.16.1 prior to 9.16.1P9 and 9.17.1 prior to 9.17.1P2 with snapshot locking enabled are susceptible to a vulnerability which could allow a privileged remote attacker to set the snapshot expiry time to none.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63314 | A static password reset token in the password reset function of DDSN Interactive Acora CMS v10.7.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily reset the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63314</link><description>A static password reset token in the password reset function of DDSN Interactive Acora CMS v10.7.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily reset the user password and execute a full account takeover via a replay attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68622 | Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host UVC Class Driver has a stack buffer overflow in UVC descriptor printing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68622</link><description>Espressif ESP-IDF USB Host UVC Class Driver allows video streaming from USB cameras. Prior to 2.4.0, a vulnerability in the esp-usb UVC host implementation allows a malicious USB Video Class (UVC) device to trigger a stack buffer overflow during configuration-descriptor parsing. When UVC configuration-descriptor printing is enabled, the host prints detailed descriptor information provided by the connected USB device. A specially crafted UVC descriptor may advertise an excessively large length. Because this value is not validated before being copied into a fixed-size stack buffer, an attacker can overflow the buffer and corrupt memory. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68472 | MindsDB has improper sanitation of filepath that leads to information disclosure and DOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68472</link><description>MindsDB is a platform for building artificial intelligence from enterprise data. Prior to version 25.11.1, an unauthenticated path traversal in the file upload API lets any caller read arbitrary files from the server filesystem and move them into MindsDB’s storage, exposing sensitive data. The PUT handler in file.py directly joins user-controlled data into a filesystem path when the request body is JSON and source_type is not "url". Only multipart uploads and URL-sourced uploads receive sanitization; JSON uploads lack any call to clear_filename or equivalent checks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66689 | A path traversal vulnerability exists in Zen MCP Server before 9.8.2 that allows authenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66689</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in Zen MCP Server before 9.8.2 that allows authenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the system. The vulnerability is caused by flawed logic in the is_dangerous_path() validation function that uses exact string matching against a blacklist of system directories. Attackers can bypass these restrictions by accessing subdirectories of blacklisted paths.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46068 | An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46068</link><description>An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update mechanism</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46070 | An issue in Automai BotManager v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the BotManager.exe component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46070</link><description>An issue in Automai BotManager v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the BotManager.exe component</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46066 | An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46066</link><description>An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46067 | An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via a crafted js file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46067</link><description>An issue in Automai Director v.25.2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via a crafted js file</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66939 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in 66biolinks by AltumCode v.61.0.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted favicon fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66939</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in 66biolinks by AltumCode v.61.0.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted favicon file</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71063 | Errands before 46.2.10 does not verify TLS certificates for CalDAV servers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71063</link><description>Errands before 46.2.10 does not verify TLS certificates for CalDAV servers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67813 | Quest KACE Desktop Authority through 11.3.1 has Insecure Permissions on the Named Pipes used for inter-process communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67813</link><description>Quest KACE Desktop Authority through 11.3.1 has Insecure Permissions on the Named Pipes used for inter-process communication</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41077 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Viafirma products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41077</link><description>IDOR vulnerability has been found in Viafirma Inbox v4.5.13 that allows any authenticated user without privileges in the application to list all users, access and modify their data. This allows the user's email addresses to be modified and, subsequently, using the password recovery functionality to access the application by impersonating any user, including those with administrative permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41078 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Viafirma products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41078</link><description>Weaknesses in the authorization mechanisms of Viafirma Documents v3.7.129 allow an authenticated user without privileges to list and access other user data, use user creation, modification, and deletion features, and escalate privileges by impersonating other users of the application in the generation and signing of documents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65552 | D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.1 is vulnerable to RF replay attacks on the 433 MHz sensor communication channel. The system does...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65552</link><description>D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.1 is vulnerable to RF replay attacks on the 433 MHz sensor communication channel. The system does not implement rolling codes, message authentication, or anti-replay protection, allowing an attacker within RF range to record valid alarm/control frames and replay them to trigger false alarms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65553 | D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.17 is susceptible to RF jamming on the 433 MHz alarm sensor channel. An attacker within RF range ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65553</link><description>D3D Wi-Fi Home Security System ZX-G12 v2.1.17 is susceptible to RF jamming on the 433 MHz alarm sensor channel. An attacker within RF range can transmit continuous interference to block sensor transmissions, resulting in missed alarms and loss of security monitoring. The device lacks jamming detection or mitigations, creating a denial-of-service condition that may lead to undetected intrusions or failure to trigger safety alerts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41005 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41005</link><description>Imaster's MEMS Events CRM contains an SQL injection vulnerability in‘keyword’ parameter in ‘/memsdemo/exchange_offers.php’.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41006 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41006</link><description>Imaster's MEMS Events CRM contains an SQL injection vulnerability in ‘phone’ parameter in ‘/memsdemo/login.php’.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41004 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41004</link><description>Imaster's Patient Records Management System is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the endpoint ‘/projects/hospital/admin/complaints.php’ through the ‘id’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41003 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Imaster products Open configuration options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41003</link><description>Imaster's Patient Record Management System contains a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the endpoint ‘/projects/hospital/admin/edit_patient.php’. By injecting a malicious script into the ‘firstname’ parameter, the JavaScript code is stored and executed every time a user accesses the patient list, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40975 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40975</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's HRMGo, consisting of a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/hrmgo/ticket/changereply’, using the ‘description’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40976 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40976</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's TicketGo, consisting of a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/ticketgo-saas/home’, using the ‘description’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40977 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40977</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's eCommerceGo SaaS, consisting of a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/store-ticket’, using the ‘subject’ and ‘description’ parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40978 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WorkDo products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40978</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WorkDo's eCommerceGo SaaS, consisting of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request to ‘/ticket/x/conversion’, using the ‘reply_description’ parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14279 | DNS Rebinding Vulnerability in mlflow/mlflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14279</link><description>MLFlow versions up to and including 3.4.0 are vulnerable to DNS rebinding attacks due to a lack of Origin header validation in the MLFlow REST server. This vulnerability allows malicious websites to bypass Same-Origin Policy protections and execute unauthorized calls against REST endpoints. An attacker can query, update, and delete experiments via the affected endpoints, leading to potential data exfiltration, destruction, or manipulation. The issue is resolved in version 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 08:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0855 | Merit LILIN｜IP Camera - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0855</link><description>Certain IP Camera models developed by Merit LILIN has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14579 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt; 6.7.0.89 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14579</link><description>The Quiz Maker WordPress plugin before 6.7.0.89 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0854 | Merit LILIN｜NVR - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0854</link><description>Certain DVR/NVR models developed by Merit LILIN has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69274 | Spectrum broken authorization scheme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69274</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.10 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69275 | Spectrum outdated java library in class-path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69275</link><description>Dependency on Vulnerable Third-Party Component vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.9 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69276 | Spectrum insecure deserialiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69276</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Object Injection.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.13 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69270 | Spectrum session token in URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69270</link><description>Information Exposure Through Query Strings in GET Request vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.8 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69271 | Spectrum basic authentication in use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69271</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Sniffing Attacks.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.13 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69272 | Spectrum password returned in clear</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69272</link><description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Sniffing Attacks.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 21.2.1 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69273 | Spectrum broken authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69273</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.10 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:06:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69267 | Spectrum directory path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69267</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (Path Traversal) vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Path Traversal.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.8 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69268 | Spectrum reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69268</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 24.3.8 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69269 | Spectrum command injection in NCM service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69269</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Broadcom DX NetOps Spectrum on Windows, Linux allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects DX NetOps Spectrum: 23.3.6 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0853 | A-Plus Video Technologies｜NVR - Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0853</link><description>Certain NVR models developed by A-Plus Video Technologies has a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access the debug page and obtain device status information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52694 | Execution of arbitrary SQL commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52694</link><description>Successful exploitation of the SQL injection vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands on the vulnerable service when it is exposed to the Internet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0852 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0852</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateUser.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0851 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminAddUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0851</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddUser.php. The manipulation of the argument txtusername leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 23:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0850 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System delete_activity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0850</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_activity.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument activity_id can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 23:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68493 | Apache Struts, Apache Struts: XXE vulnerability in outdated XWork component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68493</link><description>Missing XML Validation vulnerability in Apache Struts, Apache Struts.

This issue affects Apache Struts: from 2.0.0 before 2.2.1; Apache Struts: from 2.2.1 through 6.1.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15506 | AcademySoftwareFoundation OpenColorIO FileRules.cpp ConvertToRegularExpression out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15506</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AcademySoftwareFoundation OpenColorIO up to 2.5.0. This issue affects the function ConvertToRegularExpression of the file src/OpenColorIO/FileRules.cpp. Performing a manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named ebdbb75123c9d5f4643e041314e2bc988a13f20d. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The fix was added to the 2.5.1 milestone.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0843 | jiujiujia/victor123/wxw850227 jjjfood/jjjshop_food index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0843</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in jiujiujia/victor123/wxw850227 jjjfood and jjjshop_food up to 20260103. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php/api/product.category/index. Such manipulation of the argument latitude leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is distributed under multiple different names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0842 | Flycatcher Toys smART Sketcher Bluetooth Low Energy missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0842</link><description>A flaw has been found in Flycatcher Toys smART Sketcher up to 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Bluetooth Low Energy Interface. This manipulation causes missing authentication. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0841 | UTT 进取 520W formPictureUrl strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0841</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this issue is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formPictureUrl. The manipulation of the argument importpictureurl results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 07:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0840 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigNoticeConfig strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0840</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigNoticeConfig. The manipulation of the argument timestart leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0839 | UTT 进取 520W APSecurity strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0839</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. Affected is the function strcpy of the file /goform/APSecurity. Executing a manipulation of the argument wepkey1 can lead to buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0838 | UTT 进取 520W ConfigWirelessBase strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0838</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This impacts the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigWirelessBase. Performing a manipulation of the argument ssid results in buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0837 | UTT 进取 520W formFireWall strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0837</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. This affects the function strcpy of the file /goform/formFireWall. Such manipulation of the argument GroupName leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 05:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0836 | UTT 进取 520W formConfigFastDirectionW strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0836</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 进取 520W 1.7.7-180627. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/formConfigFastDirectionW. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15505 | Luxul XWR-600 Web Administration cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15505</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Luxul XWR-600 up to 4.0.1. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Web Administration Interface. The manipulation of the argument Guest Network/Wireless Profile SSID results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond with a technical statement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0824 | questdb ui Web Console cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0824</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in questdb ui up to 1.11.9. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Web Console. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. Upgrading to version 1.1.10 is recommended to address this issue. The patch is identified as b42fd9f18476d844ae181a10a249e003dafb823d. You should upgrade the affected component. The vendor confirmed early that the fix "is going to be released as a part of QuestDB 9.3.0" as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12379 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.17.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Modern Heading Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12379</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a combination of the 'tag' and ‘title_tag’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13393 | Featured Image from URL (FIFU) &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;fifu_input_url&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13393</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.1. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs before passing them to the getimagesize() function in the Elementor widget integration. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services via the fifu_input_url parameter in the FIFU Elementor widget granted they have permissions to use Elementor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0822 | quickjs-ng quickjs quickjs.c js_typed_array_sort heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0822</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in quickjs-ng quickjs up to 0.11.0. This issue affects the function js_typed_array_sort of the file quickjs.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is 53eefbcd695165a3bd8c584813b472cb4a69fbf5. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0821 | quickjs-ng quickjs quickjs.c js_typed_array_constructor heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0821</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in quickjs-ng quickjs up to 0.11.0. This vulnerability affects the function js_typed_array_constructor of the file quickjs.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called c5d80831e51e48a83eab16ea867be87f091783c5. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14555 | Countdown Timer - Widget Countdown &amp;lt;= 2.7.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14555</link><description>The Countdown Timer – Widget Countdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpdevart_countdown' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15504 | lief-project LIEF ELF Binary Parser.tcc parse_binary null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15504</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in lief-project LIEF up to 0.17.1. Affected by this issue is the function Parser::parse_binary of the file src/ELF/Parser.tcc of the component ELF Binary Parser. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. Upgrading to version 0.17.2 can resolve this issue. The patch is identified as 81bd5d7ea0c390563f1c4c017c9019d154802978. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14506 | ConvertForce Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 0.0.7 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting via entrance_animation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14506</link><description>The ConvertForce Popup Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Gutenberg block's `entrance_animation` attribute in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.7. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52435 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: Invalid error handling in pause encryption procedure in NimBLE controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52435</link><description>J2EE Misconfiguration: Data Transmission Without Encryption vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Improper handling of Pause Encryption procedure on Link Layer results in a previously encrypted connection being left in un-encrypted state allowing an eavesdropper to observe the remainder of the exchange.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through &lt;= 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53470 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in NimBLE HCI H4 driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53470</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in Apache  NimBLE HCI H4 driver. Specially crafted HCI event could lead to invalid memory read in H4 driver.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.8. 

This issue requires a broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53477 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: NULL Pointer Dereference in NimBLE host HCI layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53477</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Apache Nimble.

Missing validation of HCI connection complete or HCI command TX buffer could lead to NULL pointer dereference.
This issue requires disabled asserts and broken or bogus Bluetooth controller and thus severity is considered low.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62235 | Apache Mynewt NimBLE: Incorrect handling of SMP Security Request could lead to undesirable pairing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62235</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Apache NimBLE.

Receiving specially crafted Security Request could lead to removal of original bond and re-bond with impostor.
This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0831 | Templately &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary JSON File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0831</link><description>The Templately plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Write in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8. This is due to inadequate input validation in the `save_template_to_file()` function where user-controlled parameters like `session_id`, `content_id`, and `ai_page_ids` are used to construct file paths without proper sanitization. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to write arbitrary `.ai.json` files to locations within the uploads directory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15503 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System common.jsp unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15503</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /fort/trust/version/common/common.jsp. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14976 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt;= 4.4.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14976</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form Builder, Custom Login Form, User Profile, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'process_row_actions' function with the 'delete' action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary post via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15502 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System session SessionController os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15502</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Management System up to 3.0.8. The affected element is the function SessionController of the file /isomp-protocol/protocol/session. Such manipulation of the argument Hostname leads to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 08:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14948 | miniOrange OTP Verification and SMS Notification for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.3.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Notification Settings Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14948</link><description>The miniOrange OTP Verification and SMS Notification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the `enable_wc_sms_notification` AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable or disable SMS notification settings for WooCommerce orders.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 07:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14943 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 8.7.2 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14943</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.2. This is due to a misconfigured authorization check on the 'getShipItemFullText' function which only verifies that a user has the 'read' capability (Subscriber-level) and a valid nonce, but fails to verify whether the user has permission to access the specific post being requested. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract data from password-protected, private, or draft posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22773 | vLLM is vulnerable to DoS in Idefics3 vision models via image payload with ambiguous dimensions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22773</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). In versions from 0.6.4 to before 0.12.0, users can crash the vLLM engine serving multimodal models that use the Idefics3 vision model implementation by sending a specially crafted 1x1 pixel image. This causes a tensor dimension mismatch that results in an unhandled runtime error, leading to complete server termination. This issue has been patched in version 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22777 | ComfyUI-Manager is Vulnerable to CRLF Injection in Configuration Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22777</link><description>ComfyUI-Manager is an extension designed to enhance the usability of ComfyUI. Prior to versions 3.39.2 and 4.0.5, an attacker can inject special characters into HTTP query parameters to add arbitrary configuration values to the config.ini file. This can lead to security setting tampering or modification of application behavior. This issue has been patched in versions 3.39.2 and 4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22704 | haxcms-php 11.0.6 Stored XSS Leading to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22704</link><description>HAX CMS helps manage microsite universe with PHP or NodeJs backends. In versions 11.0.6 to before 25.0.0, HAX CMS is vulnerable to stored XSS, which could lead to account takeover. This issue has been patched in version 25.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22702 | virtualenv Has TOCTOU Vulnerabilities in Directory Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22702</link><description>virtualenv is a tool for creating isolated virtual python environments. Prior to version 20.36.1, TOCTOU (Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use) vulnerabilities in virtualenv allow local attackers to perform symlink-based attacks on directory creation operations. An attacker with local access can exploit a race condition between directory existence checks and creation to redirect virtualenv's app_data and lock file operations to attacker-controlled locations. This issue has been patched in version 20.36.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22703 | Cosign verification accepts any valid Rekor entry under certain conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22703</link><description>Cosign provides code signing and transparency for containers and binaries. Prior to versions 2.6.2 and 3.0.4, Cosign bundle can be crafted to successfully verify an artifact even if the embedded Rekor entry does not reference the artifact's digest, signature or public key. When verifying a Rekor entry, Cosign verifies the Rekor entry signature, and also compares the artifact's digest, the user's public key from either a Fulcio certificate or provided by the user, and the artifact signature to the Rekor entry contents. Without these comparisons, Cosign would accept any response from Rekor as valid. A malicious actor that has compromised a user's identity or signing key could construct a valid Cosign bundle by including any arbitrary Rekor entry, thus preventing the user from being able to audit the signing event. This issue has been patched in versions 2.6.2 and 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22705 | RustCrypto: Signatures has timing side-channel in ML-DSA decomposition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22705</link><description>RustCrypto: Signatures offers support for digital signatures, which provide authentication of data using public-key cryptography. Prior to version 0.1.0-rc.2, a timing side-channel was discovered in the Decompose algorithm which is used during ML-DSA signing to generate hints for the signature. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.0-rc.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22701 | filelock Time-of-Check-Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) Symlink Vulnerability in SoftFileLock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22701</link><description>filelock is a platform-independent file lock for Python. Prior to version 3.20.3, a TOCTOU race condition vulnerability exists in the SoftFileLock implementation of the filelock package. An attacker with local filesystem access and permission to create symlinks can exploit a race condition between the permission validation and file creation to cause lock operations to fail or behave unexpectedly. The vulnerability occurs in the _acquire() method between raise_on_not_writable_file() (permission check) and os.open() (file creation). During this race window, an attacker can create a symlink at the lock file path, potentially causing the lock to operate on an unintended target file or leading to denial of service. This issue has been patched in version 3.20.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22693 | Null Pointer Dereference in SubtableUnicodesCache::create leading to DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22693</link><description>HarfBuzz is a text shaping engine. Prior to version 12.3.0, a null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the SubtableUnicodesCache::create function located in src/hb-ot-cmap-table.hh. The function fails to check if hb_malloc returns NULL before using placement new to construct an object at the returned pointer address. When hb_malloc fails to allocate memory (which can occur in low-memory conditions or when using custom allocators that simulate allocation failures), it returns NULL. The code then attempts to call the constructor on this null pointer using placement new syntax, resulting in undefined behavior and a Segmentation Fault. This issue has been patched in version 12.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22685 | DevToys Path Traversal (“Zip Slip”) Vulnerability in DevToys Extension Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22685</link><description>DevToys is a desktop app for developers. In versions from 2.0.0.0 to before 2.0.9.0, a path traversal vulnerability exists in the DevToys extension installation mechanism. When processing extension packages (NUPKG archives), DevToys does not sufficiently validate file paths contained within the archive. A malicious extension package could include crafted file entries such as ../../…/target-file, causing the extraction process to write files outside the intended extensions directory. This flaw enables an attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the user’s system with the privileges of the DevToys process. Depending on the environment, this may lead to code execution, configuration tampering, or corruption of application or system files. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22689 | Mailpit is vulnerable to Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking (CSWSH) allowing unauthenticated access to emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22689</link><description>Mailpit is an email testing tool and API for developers. Prior to version 1.28.2, the Mailpit WebSocket server is configured to accept connections from any origin. This lack of Origin header validation introduces a Cross-Site WebSocket Hijacking (CSWSH) vulnerability. An attacker can host a malicious website that, when visited by a developer running Mailpit locally, establishes a WebSocket connection to the victim's Mailpit instance (default ws://localhost:8025). This allows the attacker to intercept sensitive data such as email contents, headers, and server statistics in real-time. This issue has been patched in version 1.28.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22611 | AWS SDK for .NET V4 adopted defense in depth enhancement for region parameter value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22611</link><description>AWS SDK for .NET works with Amazon Web Services to help build scalable solutions with Amazon S3, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon Glacier, and more. From versions 4.0.0 to before 4.0.3.3, Customer applications could be configured to improperly route AWS API calls to non-existent or non-AWS hosts. This notification is related to the use of specific values for the region input field when calling AWS services. An actor with access to the environment in which the SDK is used could set the region input field to an invalid value. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22698 | RustCrypto SM2-PKE has 32-bit Biased Nonce Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22698</link><description>RustCrypto: Elliptic Curves is general purpose Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) support, including types and traits for representing various elliptic curve forms, scalars, points, and public/secret keys composed thereof. In versions 0.14.0-pre.0 and 0.14.0-rc.0, a  critical vulnerability exists in the SM2 Public Key Encryption (PKE) implementation where the ephemeral nonce k is generated with severely reduced entropy. A unit mismatch error causes the nonce generation function to request only 32 bits of randomness instead of the expected 256 bits. This reduces the security of the encryption from a 128-bit level to a trivial 16-bit level, allowing a practical attack to recover the nonce k and decrypt any ciphertext given only the public key and ciphertext. This issue has been patched via commit e4f7778.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22699 | RustCrypto SM2-PKE has Unchecked AffinePoint Decoding (unwrap) in decrypt()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22699</link><description>RustCrypto: Elliptic Curves is general purpose Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) support, including types and traits for representing various elliptic curve forms, scalars, points, and public/secret keys composed thereof. In versions 0.14.0-pre.0 and 0.14.0-rc.0, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the SM2 PKE decryption path where an invalid elliptic-curve point (C1) is decoded and the resulting value is unwrapped without checking. Specifically, AffinePoint::from_encoded_point(&amp;amp;encoded_c1) may return a None/CtOption::None when the supplied coordinates are syntactically valid but do not lie on the SM2 curve. The calling code previously used .unwrap(), causing a panic when presented with such input. This issue has been patched via commit 085b7be.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22700 | RustCrypto Has Insufficient Length Validation in decrypt() in SM2-PKE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22700</link><description>RustCrypto: Elliptic Curves is general purpose Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) support, including types and traits for representing various elliptic curve forms, scalars, points, and public/secret keys composed thereof. In versions 0.14.0-pre.0 and 0.14.0-rc.0, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the SM2 public-key encryption (PKE) implementation: the decrypt() path performs unchecked slice::split_at operations on input buffers derived from untrusted ciphertext. An attacker can submit short/undersized ciphertext or carefully-crafted DER-encoded structures to trigger bounds-check panics (Rust unwinding) which crash the calling thread or process. This issue has been patched via commit e60e991.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22690 | pypdf has possible long runtimes for missing /Root object with large /Size values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22690</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to version 6.6.0, pypdf has possible long runtimes for missing /Root object with large /Size values. An attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to possibly long runtimes for actually invalid files. This can be achieved by omitting the /Root entry in the trailer, while using a rather large /Size value. Only the non-strict reading mode is affected. This issue has been patched in version 6.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22691 | pypdf has possible long runtimes for malformed startxref</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22691</link><description>pypdf is a free and open-source pure-python PDF library. Prior to version 6.6.0, pypdf has possible long runtimes for malformed startxref. An attacker who uses this vulnerability can craft a PDF which leads to possibly long runtimes for invalid startxref entries. When rebuilding the cross-reference table, PDF files with lots of whitespace characters become problematic. Only the non-strict reading mode is affected. Only the non-strict reading mode is affected. This issue has been patched in version 6.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22687 | WeKnora vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22687</link><description>WeKnora is an LLM-powered framework designed for deep document understanding and semantic retrieval. Prior to version 0.2.5, after WeKnora enables the Agent service, it allows users to call the database query tool. Due to insufficient backend validation, an attacker can use prompt‑based bypass techniques to evade query restrictions and obtain sensitive information from the target server and database. This issue has been patched in version 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22688 | WeKnora has Command Injection in MCP stdio test</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22688</link><description>WeKnora is an LLM-powered framework designed for deep document understanding and semantic retrieval. Prior to version 0.2.5, there is a command injection vulnerability that allows authenticated users to inject stdio_config.command/args into MCP stdio settings, causing the server to execute subprocesses using these injected values. This issue has been patched in version 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13457 | WooCommerce Square &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure in get_token_by_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13457</link><description>The WooCommerce Square plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.1 via the get_token_by_id  function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to expose arbitrary Square "ccof" (credit card on file) values and leverage this value to potentially make fraudulent charges on the target site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61674 | October CMS Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Editor and Branding Styles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61674</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform. Prior to versions 3.7.13 and 4.0.12, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in October CMS backend configuration forms. A user with the Global Editor Settings permission could inject malicious HTML/JS into the stylesheet input at Markup Styles. A specially crafted input could break out of the intended</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61676 | October CMS Vulnerable to Stored XSS via Branding Styles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61676</link><description>October is a Content Management System (CMS) and web platform. Prior to versions 3.7.13 and 4.0.12, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities was identified in October CMS backend configuration forms. A user with the Customize Backend Styles permission could inject malicious HTML/JS into the stylesheet input at Styles from Branding &amp; Appearance settings. A specially crafted input could break out of the intended</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65090 | XWiki Full Calendar Macro vulnerable to data leak through Calendar.JSONService</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65090</link><description>XWiki Full Calendar Macro displays objects from the wiki on the calendar. Prior to version 2.4.6, users with the rights to view the Calendar.JSONService page (including guest users) can exploit the data leak vulnerability by accessing database info, with the exception of passwords. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65091 | XWiki Full Calendar Macro vulnerable to SQL injection through Calendar.JSONService</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65091</link><description>XWiki Full Calendar Macro displays objects from the wiki on the calendar. Prior to version 2.4.5, users with the right to view the Calendar.JSONService page (including guest users) can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability by accessing database info or starting a DoS attack. This issue has been patched in version 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22589 | Spree API has Unauthenticated IDOR - Guest Address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22589</link><description>Spree is an open source e-commerce solution built with Ruby on Rails. Prior to versions 4.10.2, 5.0.7, 5.1.9, and 5.2.5, an Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability was identified that allows an unauthenticated attacker to access guest address information without supplying valid credentials or session cookies. This issue has been patched in versions 4.10.2, 5.0.7, 5.1.9, and 5.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22610 | Angular has XSS Vulnerability via Unsanitized SVG Script Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22610</link><description>Angular is a development platform for building mobile and desktop web applications using TypeScript/JavaScript and other languages. Prior to versions 19.2.18, 20.3.16, 21.0.7, and 21.1.0-rc.0, a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in the Angular Template Compiler. The vulnerability exists because Angular’s internal sanitization schema fails to recognize the href and xlink:href attributes of SVG</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59057 | React Router has XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59057</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/react versions 1.15.0 through 2.17.0. and react-router versions 7.0.0 through 7.8.2, a XSS vulnerability exists in in React Router's meta()/ APIs in Framework Mode when generating script:ld+json tags which could allow arbitrary JavaScript execution during SSR if untrusted content is used to generate the tag. There is no impact if the application is being used in Declarative Mode () or Data Mode (createBrowserRouter/). This issue has been patched in @remix-run/react version 2.17.1 and react-router version 7.9.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61686 | React Router has Path Traversal in File Session Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61686</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @react-router/node versions 7.0.0 through 7.9.3, @remix-run/deno prior to version 2.17.2, and @remix-run/node prior to version 2.17.2, if createFileSessionStorage() is being used from @react-router/node (or @remix-run/node/@remix-run/deno in Remix v2) with an unsigned cookie, it is possible for an attacker to cause the session to try to read/write from a location outside the specified session file directory. The success of the attack would depend on the permissions of the web server process to access those files. Read files cannot be returned directly to the attacker. Session file reads would only succeed if the file matched the expected session file format. If the file matched the session file format, the data would be populated into the server side session but not directly returned to the attacker unless the application logic returned specific session information. This issue has been patched in @react-router/node version 7.9.4, @remix-run/deno version 2.17.2, and @remix-run/node version 2.17.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68470 | React Router has unexpected external redirect via untrusted paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68470</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In versions 6.0.0 through 6.30.1 and 7.0.0 through 7.9.5, an attacker-supplied path can be crafted so that when a React Router application navigates to it via navigate(), , or redirect(), the app performs a navigation/redirect to an external URL. This is only an issue if you are passing untrusted content into navigation paths in your application code. This issue has been patched in versions 6.30.2 and 7.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21884 | React Router SSR XSS in ScrollRestoration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21884</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/react version prior to 2.17.3. and react-router 7.0.0 through 7.11.0, a XSS vulnerability exists in in React Router's  API in Framework Mode when using the getKey/storageKey props during Server-Side Rendering which could allow arbitrary JavaScript execution during SSR if untrusted content is used to generate the keys. There is no impact if server-side rendering in Framework Mode is disabled, or if Declarative Mode () or Data Mode (createBrowserRouter/) is being used. This issue has been patched in @remix-run/react version 2.17.3 and react-router version 7.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22029 | React Router vulnerable to XSS via Open Redirects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22029</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/router version prior to 1.23.2. and react-router 7.0.0 through 7.11.0, React Router (and Remix v1/v2) SPA open navigation redirects originating from loaders or actions in Framework Mode, Data Mode, or the unstable RSC modes can result in unsafe URLs causing unintended javascript execution on the client. This is only an issue if you are creating redirect paths from untrusted content or via an open redirect. There is no impact if Declarative Mode () is being used. This issue has been patched in @remix-run/router version 1.23.2 and react-router version 7.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22030 | React Router has CSRF issue in Action/Server Action Request Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22030</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In @remix-run/server-runtime version prior to 2.17.3. and react-router 7.0.0 through 7.11.0, React Router (or Remix v2) is vulnerable to CSRF attacks on document POST requests to UI routes when using server-side route action handlers in Framework Mode, or when using React Server Actions in the new unstable RSC modes. There is no impact if Declarative Mode () or Data Mode (createBrowserRouter/) is being used. This issue has been patched in @remix-run/server-runtime version 2.17.3 and react-router version 7.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22594 | Ghost has Staff 2FA bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22594</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.105.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost's 2FA mechanism allows staff users to skip email 2FA. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22595 | Ghost has Staff Token permission bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22595</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.121.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost's handling of Staff Token authentication allowed certain endpoints to be accessed that were only intended to be accessible via Staff Session authentication. External systems that have been authenticated via Staff Tokens for Admin/Owner-role users would have had access to these endpoints. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22596 | Ghost has SQL Injection in Members Activity Feed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22596</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.90.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost's /ghost/api/admin/members/events endpoint allows users with authentication credentials for the Admin API to execute arbitrary SQL. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22597 | Ghost has SSRF via External Media Inliner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22597</link><description>Ghost is a Node.js content management system. In versions 5.38.0 through 5.130.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.10.3, a vulnerability in Ghost’s media inliner mechanism allows staff users in possession of a valid authentication token for the Ghost Admin API to exfiltrate data from internal systems via SSRF. This issue has been patched in versions 5.130.6 and 6.11.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22600 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read via ImageMagick SVG Coder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22600</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. A Local File Read (LFR) vulnerability exists in the work package PDF export functionality of OpenProject prior to version 16.6.4. By uploading a specially crafted SVG file (disguised as a PNG) as a work package attachment, an attacker can exploit the backend image processing engine (ImageMagick). When the work package is exported to PDF, the backend attempts to resize the image, triggering the ImageMagick text: coder. This allows an attacker to read arbitrary local files that the application user has permissions to access (e.g., /etc/passwd, all project configuration files, private project data, etc.). The attack requires permissions to upload attachments to a container that can be exported to PDF, such as a work package. The issue has been patched in version 16.6.4. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22601 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to Code Execution in E-Mail function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22601</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. For OpenProject version 16.6.1 and below, a registered administrator can execute arbitrary command by configuring sendmail binary path and sending a test email. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22602 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to User Enumeration via User ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22602</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to version 16.6.2, a low‑privileged logged-in user can view the full names of other users. Since user IDs are assigned sequentially and predictably (e.g., 1 to 1000), an attacker can extract a complete list of all users’ full names by iterating through these URLs. The same behavior can also be reproduced via the OpenProject API, allowing automated retrieval of full names through the API as well. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22603 | OpenProject has no protection against brute-force attacks in the Change Password function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22603</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to version 16.6.2, OpenProject’s unauthenticated password-change endpoint (/account/change_password) was not protected by the same brute-force safeguards that apply to the normal login form. In affected versions, an attacker who can guess or enumerate user IDs can send unlimited password-change requests for a given account without triggering lockout or other rate-limiting controls. This allows automated password-guessing (e.g., with wordlists of common passwords) against valid accounts. Successful guessing results in full account compromise for the targeted user and, depending on that user’s role, can lead to further privilege escalation inside the application. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22604 | OpenProject is vulnerable to user enumeration via the change password function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22604</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. For OpenProject versions from 11.2.1 to before 16.6.2, when sending a POST request to the /account/change_password endpoint with an arbitrary User ID as the password_change_user_id parameter, the resulting error page would show the username for the requested user. Since this endpoint is intended to be called without being authenticated, this allows to enumerate the user names of all accounts registered in an OpenProject instance. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22605 | OpenProject is Vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in Meetings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22605</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. OpenProject versions prior to version 16.6.3, allowed users with the View Meetings permission on any project, to access meeting details of meetings that belonged to projects, the user does not have access to. This issue has been patched in version 16.6.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22606 | Fickling has a bypass via runpy.run_path() and runpy.run_module()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22606</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Fickling versions up to and including 0.1.6 do not treat Python’s runpy module as unsafe. Because of this, a malicious pickle that uses runpy.run_path() or runpy.run_module() is classified as SUSPICIOUS instead of OVERTLY_MALICIOUS. If a user relies on Fickling’s output to decide whether a pickle is safe to deserialize, this misclassification can lead them to execute attacker-controlled code on their system. This affects any workflow or product that uses Fickling as a security gate for pickle deserialization. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22607 | Fickling Blocklist Bypass: cProfile.run()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22607</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Fickling versions up to and including 0.1.6 do not treat Python's cProfile module as unsafe. Because of this, a malicious pickle that uses cProfile.run() is classified as SUSPICIOUS instead of OVERTLY_MALICIOUS. If a user relies on Fickling's output to decide whether a pickle is safe to deserialize, this misclassification can lead them to execute attacker-controlled code on their system. This affects any workflow or product that uses Fickling as a security gate for pickle deserialization. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22608 | Fickling vulnerable to use of ctypes and pydoc gadget chain to bypass detection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22608</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Prior to version 0.1.7, both ctypes and pydoc modules aren't explicitly blocked. Even other existing pickle scanning tools (like picklescan) do not block pydoc.locate. Chaining these two together can achieve RCE while the scanner still reports the file as LIKELY_SAFE. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22609 | Fickling has Static Analysis Bypass via Incomplete Dangerous Module Blocklist</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22609</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Prior to version 0.1.7, the unsafe_imports() method in Fickling's static analyzer fails to flag several high-risk Python modules that can be used for arbitrary code execution. Malicious pickles importing these modules will not be detected as unsafe, allowing attackers to bypass Fickling's primary static safety checks. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22612 | Fickling vulnerable to detection bypass due to &amp;quot;builtins&amp;quot; blindness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22612</link><description>Fickling is a Python pickling decompiler and static analyzer. Prior to version 0.1.7, Fickling is vulnerable to detection bypass due to "builtins" blindness. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21897 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-Bounds Write in Crypto_Config_Add_Gvcid_Managed_Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21897</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the Crypto_Config_Add_Gvcid_Managed_Parameters function only checks whether gvcid_counter &gt; GVCID_MAN_PARAM_SIZE. As a result, it allows up to the 251st entry, which causes a write past the end of the array, overwriting gvcid_counter located immediately after gvcid_managed_parameters_array[250]. This leads to an out-of-bounds write, and the overwritten gvcid_counter may become an arbitrary value, potentially affecting the parameter lookup/registration logic that relies on it. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21898 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-bounds Read in Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21898</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the Crypto_AOS_ProcessSecurity function reads memory without valid bounds checking when parsing AOS frame hashes. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21899 | CryptoLib has an out-of-bounds read and crash vulnerability when decoding an empty Base64url string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21899</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, in base64urlDecode, padding-stripping dereferences input[inputLen - 1] before checking that inputLen &gt; 0 or that input != NULL. For inputLen == 0, this becomes an OOB read at input[-1], potentially crashing the process. If input == NULL and inputLen == 0, it dereferences NULL - 1. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21900 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-Bounds Read in KMC Encrypt Metadata Parsing via Flawed strtok Pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21900</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, an out-of-bounds heap read vulnerability in cryptography_encrypt() occurs when parsing JSON metadata from KMC server responses. The flawed strtok iteration pattern uses ptr + strlen(ptr) + 1 which reads one byte past allocated buffer boundaries when processing short or malformed metadata strings. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22023 | CryptoLib Has Out-of-Bounds Read in KMC AEAD Encrypt Metadata Parsing via Flawed strtok Pattern</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22023</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, there is an out-of-bounds heap read vulnerability in cryptography_aead_encrypt(). This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22024 | CryptoLib Memory Leak in KMC Encrypt Function Leads to Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22024</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the cryptography_encrypt() function allocates multiple buffers for HTTP requests and JSON parsing that are never freed on any code path. Each call leaks approximately 400 bytes of memory. Sustained traffic can gradually exhaust available memory. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22025 | CryptoLib Memory Leak on HTTP Error Response in KMC Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22025</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, when the KMC server returns a non-200 HTTP status code, cryptography_encrypt() and cryptography_decrypt() return immediately without freeing previously allocated buffers. Each failed request leaks approximately 467 bytes. Repeated failures (from a malicious server or network issues) can gradually exhaust memory. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22026 | CryptoLib Unbounded Memory Allocation in KMC HTTP Response Handler Allows Resource Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22026</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the libcurl write_callback function in the KMC crypto service client allows unbounded memory growth by reallocating response buffers without any size limit or overflow check. A malicious KMC server can return arbitrarily large HTTP responses, forcing the client to allocate excessive memory until the process is terminated by the OS. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22027 | CryptoLib Vulnerable to Heap Buffer Overflow in MariaDB SA Hexstring Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22027</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, the convert_hexstring_to_byte_array() function in the MariaDB SA interface writes decoded bytes into a caller-provided buffer without any capacity check. When importing SA fields from the database (e.g., IV, ARSN, ABM), a malformed or oversized hex string in the database can overflow the destination buffer, corrupting adjacent heap memory. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22697 | CryptoLib Has Heap Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in KMC Base64 Decode Handling (KMC JSON base64ciphertext/base64cleartext)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22697</link><description>CryptoLib provides a software-only solution using the CCSDS Space Data Link Security Protocol - Extended Procedures (SDLS-EP) to secure communications between a spacecraft running the core Flight System (cFS) and a ground station. Prior to version 1.4.3, CryptoLib’s KMC crypto service integration is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow when decoding Base64-encoded ciphertext/cleartext fields returned by the KMC service. The decode destination buffer is sized using an expected output length (len_data_out), but the Base64 decoder writes output based on the actual Base64 input length and does not enforce any destination size limit. An oversized Base64 string in the KMC JSON response can cause out-of-bounds writes on the heap, resulting in process crash and potentially code execution under certain conditions. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>