<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:38:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-24961 | Insecure path traversal in filesystem and filesystem-nio2 storage backends in org.gaul S3Proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24961</link><description>org.gaul S3Proxy implements the S3 API and proxies requests. Users of the filesystem and filesystem-nio2 storage backends could unintentionally expose local files to users. This issue has been addressed in version 2.6.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34896 | An issue in Nedis SmartLife Video Doorbell (WIFICDP10GY), Nedis SmartLife IOS v1.4.0 causes users who are disconnected from a previous peer-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34896</link><description>An issue in Nedis SmartLife Video Doorbell (WIFICDP10GY), Nedis SmartLife IOS v1.4.0 causes users who are disconnected from a previous peer-to-peer connection with the device to still have access to live video feed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34897 | Nedis SmartLife android app v1.4.0 was discovered to contain an API key disclosure vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34897</link><description>Nedis SmartLife android app v1.4.0 was discovered to contain an API key disclosure vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44449 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Quorum onQ OS v.6.0.0.5.2064 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the msg para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44449</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Quorum onQ OS v.6.0.0.5.2064 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the msg parameter in the Login page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57451 | ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has a directory traversal vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController#getFileList, which allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57451</link><description>ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has a directory traversal vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController#getFileList, which allows attackers to view any directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56946 | Denial of service in DNS-over-QUIC in Technitium DNS Server &lt;= v13.2.2 allows remote attackers to permanently stop the server from accepting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56946</link><description>Denial of service in DNS-over-QUIC in Technitium DNS Server &lt;= v13.2.2 allows remote attackers to permanently stop the server from accepting new DNS-over-QUIC connections by triggering unhandled exceptions in listener threads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57097 | ClassCMS 4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in class/admin/channel.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57097</link><description>ClassCMS 4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in class/admin/channel.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57450 | ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 is vulnerable to File Upload via the Create template function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57450</link><description>ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 is vulnerable to File Upload via the Create template function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57452 | ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController, which allows attackers to delete ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57452</link><description>ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController, which allows attackers to delete any file and folder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57498 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in sayski ForestBlog 20241223 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the article editing fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57498</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in sayski ForestBlog 20241223 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the article editing function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57098 | Moss v0.1.3 version has an SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to inject carefully designed payloads into the order parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57098</link><description>Moss v0.1.3 version has an SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to inject carefully designed payloads into the order parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57099 | ClassCMS v4.8 has a code execution vulnerability. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by constructing a payload in the classview parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57099</link><description>ClassCMS v4.8 has a code execution vulnerability. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by constructing a payload in the classview parameter of the model management feature, allowing them to execute arbitrary code and potentially take control of the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22978 | eladmin &lt;=2.7 is vulnerable to CSV Injection in the exception log download module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22978</link><description>eladmin &lt;=2.7 is vulnerable to CSV Injection in the exception log download module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11132 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11132</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11133 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Event Ticket Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11133</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_pdf_download_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download event tickets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11134 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Bookings Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11134</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eventer_export_bookings_csv' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above, to download bookings, which contains customers' personal data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12511 | SMB/FTP Address Book Scan Pass-back attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12511</link><description>With address book access, SMB/FTP settings could be modified, redirecting scans and possibly capturing credentials. This requires enabled scan functions and printer access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12859 | BoomBox Theme Extensions &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12859</link><description>The BoomBox Theme Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 via the 'boombox_listing' shortcode 'type' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56921 | An issue was discovered in Open5gs v2.7.2. InitialUEMessage, Registration request sent at a specific time can crash AMF due to incorrect err...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56921</link><description>An issue was discovered in Open5gs v2.7.2. InitialUEMessage, Registration request sent at a specific time can crash AMF due to incorrect error handling of gmm_state_exception() function upon receipt of the Nausf_UEAuthentication_Authenticate response.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25065 | SSRF vulnerability in the RSS feed parser in Zimbra Collaboration 9.0.0 before Patch 43, 10.0.x before 10.0.12, and 10.1.x before 10.1.4 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25065</link><description>SSRF vulnerability in the RSS feed parser in Zimbra Collaboration 9.0.0 before Patch 43, 10.0.x before 10.0.12, and 10.1.x before 10.1.4 allows unauthorized redirection to internal network endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25181 | A SQL injection vulnerability in timeoutWarning.asp in Advantive VeraCore through 2025.1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25181</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in timeoutWarning.asp in Advantive VeraCore through 2025.1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the PmSess1 parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25064 | SQL injection vulnerability in the ZimbraSyncService SOAP endpoint in Zimbra Collaboration 10.0.x before 10.0.12 and 10.1.x before 10.1.4.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25064</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the ZimbraSyncService SOAP endpoint in Zimbra Collaboration 10.0.x before 10.0.12 and 10.1.x before 10.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57669 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Zrlog backup-sql-file.jar v.3.0.31 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57669</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Zrlog backup-sql-file.jar v.3.0.31 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the BackupController.java file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57968 | Advantive VeraCore before 2024.4.2.1 allows remote authenticated users to upload files to unintended folders (e.g., ones that are accessible...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57968</link><description>Advantive VeraCore before 2024.4.2.1 allows remote authenticated users to upload files to unintended folders (e.g., ones that are accessible during web browsing by other users). upload.aspx can be used for this.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57237 | Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57237</link><description>Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerability arises because the cmd parameter does not properly sanitize input and the response is served with a Content-Type of text/html. This behavior allows the browser to execute injected JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57238 | Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerability allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57238</link><description>Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerability allows an attacker to manipulate SQL queries by injecting malicious SQL code into the order_by parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12510 | LDAP Authentication Sever Pass-back attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12510</link><description>If LDAP settings are accessed, authentication could be redirected to another server, potentially exposing credentials. This requires admin access and an active LDAP setup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50656 | itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Full Name field in registration.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50656</link><description>itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Full Name field in registration.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57004 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Roundcube Webmail 1.6.9 allows remote authenticated users to upload a malicious file as an email...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57004</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Roundcube Webmail 1.6.9 allows remote authenticated users to upload a malicious file as an email attachment, leading to the triggering of the XSS by visiting the SENT session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24898 | rust openssl ssl::select_next_proto use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24898</link><description>rust-openssl is a set of OpenSSL bindings for the Rust programming language. In affected versions `ssl::select_next_proto` can return a slice pointing into the `server` argument's buffer but with a lifetime bound to the `client` argument. In situations where the `sever` buffer's lifetime is shorter than the `client` buffer's, this can cause a use after free. This could cause the server to crash or to return arbitrary memory contents to the client. The crate`openssl` version 0.10.70 fixes the signature of `ssl::select_next_proto` to properly constrain the output buffer's lifetime to that of both input buffers. Users are advised to upgrade. In standard usage of `ssl::select_next_proto` in the callback passed to `SslContextBuilder::set_alpn_select_callback`, code is only affected if the `server` buffer is constructed *within* the callback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53943 | An issue was discovered in NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to XSS via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53943</link><description>An issue was discovered in NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to XSS via the 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz name parameters, allowing an attacker to execute JavaScript within the context of the current user by injecting JavaScript into the SSID field. If an administrator logs into the device, the injected script runs in their browser, executing the malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57967 | PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 has potentially elevated privileges in LDAP m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57967</link><description>PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 has potentially elevated privileges in LDAP mapping.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36437 | The com.enflick.android.TextNow (aka TextNow: Call + Text Unlimited) application 24.17.0.2 for Android enables any installed application (wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36437</link><description>The com.enflick.android.TextNow (aka TextNow: Call + Text Unlimited) application 24.17.0.2 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone calls without user interaction by sending a crafted intent via the com.enflick.android.TextNow.activities.DialerActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53942 | An issue was discovered on NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to command in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53942</link><description>An issue was discovered on NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to command injection via the 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz name parameters, allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands on the device (with root-level permissions) via crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57175 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the PHPGURUKUL Online Birth Certificate System v1.0 via the profile name...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57175</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the PHPGURUKUL Online Birth Certificate System v1.0 via the profile name to /user/certificate-form.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56161 | Improper signature verification in AMD CPU ROM microcode patch loader may allow an attacker with local administrator privilege to load malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56161</link><description>Improper signature verification in AMD CPU ROM microcode patch loader may allow an attacker with local administrator privilege to load malicious CPU microcode resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity of a confidential guest running under AMD SEV-SNP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54840 | PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 does not properly address environment issues ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54840</link><description>PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 does not properly address environment issues that can contribute to Host header injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38404 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38404</link><description>Transient DOS when registration accept OTA is received with incorrect ciphering key data IE in modem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38411 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38411</link><description>Memory corruption while registering a buffer from user-space to kernel-space using IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38412 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38412</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from user-space to kernel-space to handle session errors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38413 | Improper Input Validation in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38413</link><description>Memory corruption while processing frame packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38414 | Buffer Over-read in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38414</link><description>Information disclosure while processing information on firmware image during core initialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38416 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38416</link><description>Information disclosure during audio playback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38417 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive Multimedia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38417</link><description>Information disclosure while processing IO control commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38418 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38418</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing the memory map info in IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38420 | Improper Input Validation in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38420</link><description>Memory corruption while configuring a Hypervisor based input virtual device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45560 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45560</link><description>Memory corruption while taking a snapshot with hardware encoder due to unvalidated userspace buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45561 | Use After Free in Windows WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45561</link><description>Memory corruption while handling  IOCTL call from user-space to set latency level.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45569 | Improper Validation of Array Index in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45569</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing the ML IE due to invalid frame content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45571 | Use After Free in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45571</link><description>Memory corruption may occour occur when stopping the WLAN interface after processing a WMI command from the interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45573 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45573</link><description>Memory corruption may occour while generating test pattern due to negative indexing of display ID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45582 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45582</link><description>Memory corruption while validating number of devices in Camera kernel .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45584 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Automotive Android OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45584</link><description>Memory corruption can occur when a compat IOCTL call is followed by a normal IOCTL call from userspace.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49832 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49832</link><description>Memory corruption in Camera due to unusually high number of nodes passed to AXI port.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49833 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49833</link><description>Memory corruption can occur in the camera when an invalid CID is used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49834 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49834</link><description>Memory corruption while power-up or power-down sequence of the camera sensor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49837 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Automotive OS Platform QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49837</link><description>Memory corruption while reading CPU state data during guest VM suspend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49838 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49838</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing the OCI IE with invalid length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49839 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Cmn</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49839</link><description>Memory corruption during management frame processing due to mismatch in T2LM info element.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49840 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49840</link><description>Memory corruption while Invoking IOCTL calls from user-space to validate FIPS encryption or decryption functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49843 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Graphics_Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49843</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL from user space to handle GPU AHB bus error.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55456 | lunasvg v3.0.1 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component gray_find_cell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55456</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.1 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component gray_find_cell</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43333 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.2.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43333</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in NotFound Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro: from n/a through 7.6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50500 | WordPress Phlox Core Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 2.17.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50500</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in By Averta Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme: from n/a through 2.17.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22260 | WordPress Meta Tag Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22260</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pixelite Meta Tag Manager. This issue affects Meta Tag Manager: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22292 | WordPress Powerful Auto Chat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22292</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Felipe Peixoto Powerful Auto Chat allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Powerful Auto Chat: from n/a through 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22677 | WordPress Uix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22677</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UIUX Lab Uix Shortcodes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Uix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22679 | WordPress Job Board Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.60 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Job Board Manager allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Job Board Manager: from n/a through 2.1.60.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22681 | WordPress Content Cloner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22681</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xfinity Soft Content Cloner allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Content Cloner: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22682 | WordPress Hesabfa Accounting Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22682</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hesabfa Hesabfa Accounting allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Hesabfa Accounting: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22683 | WordPress NotificationX plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22683</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper NotificationX allows Stored XSS. This issue affects NotificationX: from n/a through 2.9.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22684 | WordPress WP BASE Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22684</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hakan Ozevin WP BASE Booking allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP BASE Booking: from n/a through 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22685 | WordPress Tags to Keywords plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22685</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CheGevara Tags to Keywords allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tags to Keywords: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22686 | WordPress CF7 Google Sheets Connector plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.17 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22686</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GSheetConnector CF7 Google Sheets Connector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CF7 Google Sheets Connector: from n/a through 5.0.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22688 | WordPress Unlimited Page Sidebars plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22688</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ederson Peka Unlimited Page Sidebars allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Unlimited Page Sidebars: from n/a through 0.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22690 | WordPress DigiTimber cPanel Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22690</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DigiTimber DigiTimber cPanel Integration allows Stored XSS. This issue affects DigiTimber cPanel Integration: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22691 | WordPress WP Travel plugin &amp;lt;= 10.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22691</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WP Travel WP Travel allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Travel: from n/a through 10.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22693 | WordPress Contest Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 25.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Contest Gallery Contest Gallery allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Contest Gallery: from n/a through 25.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22694 | WordPress Hide Shipping Method For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22694</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theDotstore Hide Shipping Method For WooCommerce. This issue affects Hide Shipping Method For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22695 | WordPress Nirweb support plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22695</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in NirWp Team Nirweb support. This issue affects Nirweb support: from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22701 | WordPress Traveler Layout Essential For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22701</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in NotFound Traveler Layout Essential For Elementor. This issue affects Traveler Layout Essential For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22703 | WordPress Forge – Front-End Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22703</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in manuelvicedo Forge – Front-End Page Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Forge – Front-End Page Builder: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22704 | WordPress Signature plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery ( CSRF ) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22704</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Abinav Thakuri WordPress Signature allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WordPress Signature: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22775 | WordPress Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp;amp; Crawler Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22775</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in idIA Tech Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp; Crawler allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp; Crawler: from n/a through 5.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23491 | WordPress VSTEMPLATE Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23491</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vikashsrivastava1111989 VSTEMPLATE Creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects VSTEMPLATE Creator: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23527 | WordPress WC Wallet plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23527</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hemnath Mouli WC Wallet allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WC Wallet: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23561 | WordPress MLL Audio Player MP3 Ajax plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound MLL Audio Player MP3 Ajax allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MLL Audio Player MP3 Ajax: from n/a through 0.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23581 | WordPress Demo User DZS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23581</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Digital Zoom Studio Demo User DZS allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Demo User DZS: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23582 | WordPress Bulk Categories Assign plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23582</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Haider Ali Bulk Categories Assign allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bulk Categories Assign: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23588 | WordPress WOW Best CSS Compiler plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23588</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WOW WordPress WOW Best CSS Compiler allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WOW Best CSS Compiler: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23590 | WordPress Dezdy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Burtay Arat Dezdy allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Dezdy: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23591 | WordPress blu Logistics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23591</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blu Logistics Pte. Ltd. blu Logistics allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects blu Logistics: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23593 | WordPress EmailPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound EmailPress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects EmailPress: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23594 | WordPress Google Map With Fancybox plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23594</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uzzal mondal Google Map With Fancybox allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Google Map With Fancybox: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23599 | WordPress eMarksheet plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound eMarksheet allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects eMarksheet: from n/a through 5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23614 | WordPress WordPress Additional Logins plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23614</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nik Sudan WordPress Additional Logins allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress Additional Logins: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23685 | WordPress RomanCart On WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23685</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound RomanCart allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects RomanCart: from n/a through 0.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23747 | WordPress Awesome Timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23747</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nitesh Singh Awesome Timeline allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Awesome Timeline: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23755 | WordPress PAFacile plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23755</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound PAFacile allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects PAFacile: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23799 | WordPress .TUBE Video Curator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23799</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in .TUBE gTLD .TUBE Video Curator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects .TUBE Video Curator: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23819 | WordPress WP Cloud plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23819</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound WP Cloud allows Absolute Path Traversal. This issue affects WP Cloud: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23920 | WordPress ApplicantPro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23920</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ApplicantPro ApplicantPro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ApplicantPro: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23923 | WordPress Lockets Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.999 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23923</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Lockets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Lockets: from n/a through 0.999.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23984 | WordPress Dynamic URL SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23984</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainvireinfo Dynamic URL SEO allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Dynamic URL SEO: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24536 | WordPress ThriveDesk plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThriveDesk ThriveDesk allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ThriveDesk: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24541 | WordPress DK White Label plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24541</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Emili Castells DK White Label allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects DK White Label: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24544 | WordPress Bitcoin and Altcoin Wallets plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24544</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alexandros Georgiou Bitcoin and Altcoin Wallets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bitcoin and Altcoin Wallets: from n/a through 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24545 | WordPress BSK Forms Validation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24545</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BannerSky.com BSK Forms Validation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BSK Forms Validation: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24556 | WordPress MooWoodle plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24556</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in DualCube MooWoodle allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects MooWoodle: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24557 | WordPress PlainInventory plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in plainware.com PlainInventory allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects PlainInventory: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24559 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.15.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.15.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24569 | WordPress PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24569</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in RedefiningTheWeb PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder allows Path Traversal. This issue affects PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24574 | WordPress PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader: from n/a through 2.6.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24576 | WordPress Landing Page Cat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24576</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fatcat Apps Landing Page Cat allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Landing Page Cat: from n/a through 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24605 | WordPress WOLF plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.5 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24605</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in realmag777 WOLF allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WOLF: from n/a through 1.0.8.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24620 | WordPress AIO Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24620</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound AIO Shortcodes allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AIO Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24629 | WordPress Import Excel to Gravity Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.18 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24629</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPGear Import Excel to Gravity Forms allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Import Excel to Gravity Forms: from n/a through 1.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24630 | WordPress Sikshya LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.21 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MantraBrain Sikshya LMS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Sikshya LMS: from n/a through 0.0.21.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24631 | WordPress BP Email Assign Templates Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PhiloPress BP Email Assign Templates allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BP Email Assign Templates: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24639 | WordPress Korea for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.11 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24639</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in GREYS Korea for WooCommerce allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Korea for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24642 | WordPress Setup Default Featured Image plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24642</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theme funda Setup Default Featured Image allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Setup Default Featured Image: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24643 | WordPress WPGuppy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24643</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Amento Tech Pvt ltd WPGuppy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WPGuppy: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24646 | WordPress XML for Avito Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Maxim Glazunov XML for Avito allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects XML for Avito: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24656 | WordPress Realtyna Provisioning Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Realtyna Realtyna Provisioning allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Realtyna Provisioning: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24660 | WordPress Simple Membership Custom Messages Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24660</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wp.insider Simple Membership Custom Messages allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Simple Membership Custom Messages: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24661 | WordPress Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24661</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MagePeople Team Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce allows Object Injection. This issue affects Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24676 | WordPress Custom WP Store Locator plugin  &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24676</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metatagg Inc Custom WP Store Locator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom WP Store Locator: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24684 | WordPress Media Downloader Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.7.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24684</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ederson Peka Media Downloader allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Media Downloader: from n/a through 0.4.7.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24697 | WordPress Image Gallery – Responsive Photo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24697</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Realwebcare Image Gallery – Responsive Photo Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Image Gallery – Responsive Photo Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24707 | WordPress Photo Gallery – GT3 Image Gallery &amp;amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.7.24 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24707</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GT3 Photo Gallery Photo Gallery - GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Photo Gallery - GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery: from n/a through 2.7.7.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24781 | WordPress WPJobBoard plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24781</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WPJobBoard allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WPJobBoard: from n/a through 5.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57522 | SourceCodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Users.php. An attacker can inject a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57522</link><description>SourceCodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Users.php. An attacker can inject a malicious script into the username or name field during user creation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6790 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver can cause the whole system to become unresponsive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6790</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a non-privileged user process to make valid GPU memory processing operations, including via WebGL or WebGPU, to cause the whole system to become unresponsive.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: r44p1, from r46p0 through r49p0, from r50p0 through r51p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: r44p1, from r46p0 through r49p0, from r50p0 through r51p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: r44p1, from r46p0 through r49p0, from r50p0 through r51p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0015 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0015</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to make improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r48p0 through r49p1, from r50p0 through r52p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r48p0 through r49p1, from r50p0 through r52p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10395 | net: lib: http_server: Buffer Under-read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10395</link><description>No proper validation of the length of user input in http_server_get_content_type_from_extension.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 07:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13347 | Essential WP Real Estate &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13347</link><description>The Essential WP Real Estate WordPress plugin through 1.1.3 does not escape generated URLs before outputting them in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25066 | nDPI through 4.12 has a potential stack-based buffer overflow in ndpi_address_cache_restore in lib/ndpi_cache.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25066</link><description>nDPI through 4.12 has a potential stack-based buffer overflow in ndpi_address_cache_restore in lib/ndpi_cache.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57966 | libarchiveplugin.cpp in KDE ark before 24.12.0 can extract to an absolute path from an archive.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57966</link><description>libarchiveplugin.cpp in KDE ark before 24.12.0 can extract to an absolute path from an archive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25062 | An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It doesn't sufficiently isolate long text content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25062</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It doesn't sufficiently isolate long text content when the CKEditor 5 rich text editor is used. This allows a potential attacker to craft specialized HTML and JavaScript that may be executed when an administrator attempts to edit a piece of content. This vulnerability is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have the ability to create long text content (such as through the node or comment forms) and an administrator must edit (not view) the content that contains the malicious content. This problem only exists when using the CKEditor 5 module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25063 | An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It does not sufficiently validate uploaded SVG im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25063</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It does not sufficiently validate uploaded SVG images to ensure they do not contain potentially dangerous SVG tags. SVG images can contain clickable links and executable scripting, and using a crafted SVG, it is possible to execute scripting in the browser when an SVG image is viewed. This issue is mitigated by the attacker needing to be able to upload SVG images, and that Backdrop embeds all uploaded SVG images within &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; tags, which prevents scripting from executing. The SVG must be viewed directly by its URL in order to run any embedded scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20141 | In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20141</link><description>In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291402; Issue ID: MSV-2073.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20142 | In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20142</link><description>In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291406; Issue ID: MSV-2070.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20147 | In Bluetooth FW, there is a possible reachable assertion due to improper exception handling. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20147</link><description>In Bluetooth FW, there is a possible reachable assertion due to improper exception handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00389046 (Note: For MT79XX chipsets) / ALPS09136501 (Note: For MT2737, MT3603, MT6XXX, and MT8XXX chipsets); Issue ID: MSV-1797.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20631 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20631</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00397141; Issue ID: MSV-2187.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20632 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20632</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00397139; Issue ID: MSV-2188.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20633 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20633</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00400889; Issue ID: MSV-2491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20634 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution, if a UE has conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20634</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01289384; Issue ID: MSV-2436.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20635 | In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20635</link><description>In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09403752; Issue ID: MSV-2434.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20636 | In secmem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20636</link><description>In secmem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09403554; Issue ID: MSV-2431.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20637 | In network HW, there is a possible system hang due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20637</link><description>In network HW, there is a possible system hang due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00399035; Issue ID: MSV-2380.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20638 | In DA, there is a possible read of uninitialized heap data due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20638</link><description>In DA, there is a possible read of uninitialized heap data due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291449; Issue ID: MSV-2066.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20639 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20639</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2060.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20640 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20640</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2059.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20641 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20641</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2058.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20642 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20642</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2057.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20643 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20643</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker has physical access to the device, if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2056.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0974 | MaxD Lightning Module deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0974</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MaxD Lightning Module 4.43 on OpenCart. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument li_op/md leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0973 | CmsEasy index.php backAll_action path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0973</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CmsEasy 7.7.7.9. This vulnerability affects the function backAll_action in the library lib/admin/database_admin.php of the file /index.php?case=database&amp;amp;act=backAll&amp;amp;admin_dir=admin&amp;amp;site=default. The manipulation of the argument select[] leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0972 | Zenvia Movidesk New Ticket cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0972</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Zenvia Movidesk up to 25.01.22. This affects an unknown part of the component New Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument subject leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 25.01.22.245a473c54 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0971 | Zenvia Movidesk Profile Editing EditProfile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Zenvia Movidesk up to 25.01.22. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Account/EditProfile of the component Profile Editing. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 25.01.22.245a473c54 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0970 | Zenvia Movidesk Login redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0970</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Zenvia Movidesk up to 25.01.22. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Account/Login. The manipulation of the argument ReturnUrl leads to open redirect. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 25.01.22.245a473c54 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0967 | code-projects Chat System add_chatroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chat System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/add_chatroom.php. The manipulation of the argument chatname/chatpass leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 15:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0131 | NVIDIA GPU kernel driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a potential user-mode attacker could read  a buffer with an in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0131</link><description>NVIDIA GPU kernel driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a potential user-mode attacker could read  a buffer with an incorrect length. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 01:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0961 | code-projects Job Recruitment load_job-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0961</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /_parse/load_job-details.php. The manipulation of the argument business_stream_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 22:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0950 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System staffview.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0950</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file staffview.php. The manipulation of the argument staffid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 20:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0949 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System partview.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0949</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file partview.php. The manipulation of the argument typeid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 19:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0948 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System incview.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0948</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file incview.php. The manipulation of the argument incid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0947 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System expview.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0947</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file expview.php. The manipulation of the argument expid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 17:03:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0946 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System templatedelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0946</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file templatedelete.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 16:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0945 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System typedelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0945</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file typedelete.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 15:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0944 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System customerview.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0944</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file customerview.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 12:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13612 | Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13612</link><description>The Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'better_messages_live_chat_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 12:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13775 | WooCommerce Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 17.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion and Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13775</link><description>The WooCommerce Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and loss of data due to missing capability checks on the 'ajax_delete_message', 'ajax_get_customers_partial_list', and 'ajax_get_admins_list' functions in all versions up to, and including, 17.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts, and read names, emails, and capabilities of all users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 12:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0943 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System deldoc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0943</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file deldoc.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 10:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12825 | Custom Related Posts &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Private Post Search and Relation Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12825</link><description>The Custom Related Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access &amp; modification of data due to a missing capability check on three AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to search posts and link/unlink relations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13371 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13371</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary emails sending due to a missing capability check on the sendEmailToJobSeeker() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send arbitrary emails with arbitrary content from the sites mail server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13372 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Resume Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13372</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.6 via the getresumefiledownloadbyid() and getallresumefiles() functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download users resumes without the appropriate authorization to do so.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13425 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Employer+) Arbitrary Company Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13425</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.6 via the enforcedelete() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Employer-level access and above, to delete other users companies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13428 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Company Logo Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13428</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.6 via the deleteCompanyLogo() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary company logos.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13429 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Employer+) Arbitrary Job Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13429</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.6 via the 'jobenforcedelete' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with employer-level access and above, to delete arbitrary</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 07:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23091 | An Improper Certificate Validation on UniFi OS devices, with Identity Enterprise configured, could allow a malicious actor to execute a man-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23091</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation on UniFi OS devices, with Identity Enterprise configured, could allow a malicious actor to execute a man-in-the-middle (MitM) attack during application update.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11829 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11829</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Table Widget's searchable_label parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13341 | MultiLoca - WooCommerce Multi Locations Inventory Management &amp;lt;= 4.1.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13341</link><description>The MultiLoca - WooCommerce Multi Locations Inventory Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'data-id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.11 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0939 | MagicForm - WordPress Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0939</link><description>The MagicForm plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the plugin's AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to invoke those actions in order to delete or view logs, modify forms or modify plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12768 | Responsive iframe &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12768</link><description>The Responsive iframe WordPress plugin through 1.2.0 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13096 | WP Finance &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13096</link><description>The WP Finance WordPress plugin through 1.3.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13097 | WP Finance &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13097</link><description>The WP Finance WordPress plugin through 1.3.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13098 | WP Email Newsletter &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13098</link><description>The WordPress Email Newsletter WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13099 | Widget4call &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13099</link><description>The Widget4Call WordPress plugin through 1.0.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12041 | Directorist – AI-Powered WordPress Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings &amp;lt;= 8.0.12 - Unauthenticated User Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12041</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered WordPress Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 8.0.12 via the /wp-json/directorist/v1/users/ endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including including usernames, email addresses, names, and more information about users.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 05:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0365 | Jupiterx Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0365</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.7 via the inline SVG feature. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 05:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0366 | Jupiter X Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SVG Upload to Local File Inclusion (Remote Code Execution)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0366</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.7 via the get_svg() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution. In this specific case,  an attacker can create a form that allows SVG uploads, upload an SVG file with malicious content and then include the SVG file in a post to achieve remote code execution. This means it is relatively easy to gain remote code execution as a contributor-level user and above by default.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 05:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53295 | Dell PowerProtect DD versions prior to 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.20 contain an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53295</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD versions prior to 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.20 contain an improper access control vulnerability. A local malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 04:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51534 | Dell PowerProtect DD versions prior to DDOS 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.20 contain a path traversal vulnerability. A local low privileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51534</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD versions prior to DDOS 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.20 contain a path traversal vulnerability. A local low privileged could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized overwrite of OS files stored on the server filesystem. Exploitation could lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 04:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53296 | Dell PowerProtect DD versions prior to 7.10.1.50 and 7.13.1.20 contain a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the RestAPI. A high pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53296</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD versions prior to 7.10.1.50 and 7.13.1.20 contain a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the RestAPI. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 04:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11780 | Site Search 360 &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11780</link><description>The Site Search 360 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ss360-resultblock' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12171 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12171</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_agent_add_user' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new administrative user accounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12184 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Form Submission Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12184</link><description>The WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the accua_forms_download_submitted_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download other user submitted forms.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12620 | AnimateGL Animations for WordPress – Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg Blocks Animations &amp;lt;= 1.4.23 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12620</link><description>The AnimateGL Animations for WordPress – Elementor &amp; Gutenberg Blocks Animations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'agl_json' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.23. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13343 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt;= 31.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13343</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the ajax_assign_new_roles() function in all versions up to, and including, 31.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13547 | aThemes Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13547</link><description>The aThemes Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13651 | RapidLoad – Optimize Web Vitals Automatically &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Setting Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13651</link><description>The RapidLoad – Optimize Web Vitals Automatically plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_deactivate() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset some of the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 03:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>