<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-38200 | Microsoft Office Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38200</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38218 | Microsoft Edge (HTML-based) Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38218</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38219 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38219</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41481 | Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Mermaid component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41481</link><description>Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Mermaid component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41482 | Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the MathJax component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41482</link><description>Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the MathJax component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43167 | Unbound: null pointer dereference in unbound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43167</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the ub_ctx_set_fwd function in Unbound. This issue could allow an attacker who can invoke specific sequences of API calls to cause a segmentation fault. When certain API functions such as ub_ctx_set_fwd and ub_ctx_resolvconf are called in a particular order, the program attempts to read from a NULL pointer, leading to a crash. This issue can result in a denial of service by causing the application to terminate unexpectedly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43168 | Unbound: heap-buffer-overflow in unbound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43168</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow flaw was found in the cfg_mark_ports function within Unbound's config_file.c, which can lead to memory corruption. This issue could allow an attacker with local access to provide specially crafted input, potentially causing the application to crash or allowing arbitrary code execution. This could result in a denial of service or unauthorized actions on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40473 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "manage_houses.php" in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40473</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "manage_houses.php" in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "House_no" and "Description" parameter fields.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40474 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "edit-cate.php" in SourceCodester House Rental Management System v1.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40474</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "edit-cate.php" in SourceCodester House Rental Management System v1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7272 | FFmpeg swresample.c fill_audiodata heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7272</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FFmpeg up to 5.1.5. This affects the function fill_audiodata of the file /libswresample/swresample.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This issue was fixed in version 6.0 by 9903ba28c28ab18dc7b7b6fb8571cc8b5caae1a6 but a backport for 5.1 was forgotten. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 5.1.6 and 6.0 9903ba28c28ab18dc7b7b6fb8571cc8b5caae1a6 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40475 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /rental/payment_report.php, /rental/ba...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40475</link><description>SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /rental/payment_report.php, /rental/balance_report.php, /rental/invoices.php, /rental/tenants.php, and /rental/users.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40476 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0. This could lead to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40476</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0. This could lead to an attacker tricking the administrator into adding/modifying/deleting valid tenant data via a crafted HTML page, as demonstrated by a Delete Tenant action at the /rental/ajax.php?action=delete_tenant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40481 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/admin/view-enquiry.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40481</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/admin/view-enquiry.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the Contact Us page "message" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40477 | A SQL injection vulnerability in "/oahms/admin/forgot-password.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40477</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in "/oahms/admin/forgot-password.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "email" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42001 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Forced Browsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42001</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability affecting Vonets





 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and wifi bridge repeaters, software versions 
3.3.23.6.9 and prior enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to 
bypass authentication via a specially crafted direct request when 
another user has an active session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37023 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37023</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities affecting Vonets 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software 
versions 3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enable an authenticated remote attacker 
to execute arbitrary OS commands via various endpoint parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39791 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39791</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities affecting Vonets



 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and wifi bridge repeaters, software versions 
3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enable an unauthenticated remote attacker to 
execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39815 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Improper Check or Handling of Exceptional Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39815</link><description>Improper check or handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability 
affecting Vonets

 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enable an unauthenticated 
remote attacker to cause a denial of service. A specially-crafted 
HTTP request to pre-authentication resources can crash the service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29082 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29082</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability affecting Vonets

 industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 3.3.23.6.9 
and prior, enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to bypass 
authentication and factory reset the device via unprotected goform 
endpoints.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40482 | An Unrestricted file upload vulnerability was found in "/Membership/edit_member.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40482</link><description>An Unrestricted file upload vulnerability was found in "/Membership/edit_member.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40484 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/oahms/search.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40484</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/oahms/search.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchdata" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40486 | A SQL injection vulnerability in "/index.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40486</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in "/index.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands and bypass Login via the email or password Login parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41936 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41936</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability affecting Vonets industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 3.3.23.6.9 
and prior, enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to read arbitrary 
files and bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40488 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in the Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0. This could lead to an attacker tri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40488</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in the Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0. This could lead to an attacker tricking the administrator into deleting valid member data via a crafted HTML page, as demonstrated by a Delete Member action at the /delete_members.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40487 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/view_type.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40487</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/view_type.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via membershipType parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40261 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR17, 4.0.0 SR07, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR04, and 4.3.0 SR03 fails to validate file at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40261</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR17, 4.0.0 SR07, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR04, and 4.3.0 SR03 fails to validate file attributes during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28865 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR15, 4.0.0 SR05, 4.1.0 SR03, and 4.2.0 SR02 fails to validate the directory conte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28865</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR15, 4.0.0 SR05, 4.1.0 SR03, and 4.2.0 SR02 fails to validate the directory contents of certain directories (e.g., ensuring the expected hash sum) during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33206 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR16, 4.0.0 SR06, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR03, and 4.3.0 SR01 fails to validate symlink...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33206</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR16, 4.0.0 SR06, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR03, and 4.3.0 SR01 fails to validate symlinks during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37382 | An issue discovered in import host feature in Ab Initio Metadata Hub and Authorization Gateway before 4.3.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37382</link><description>An issue discovered in import host feature in Ab Initio Metadata Hub and Authorization Gateway before 4.3.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted modification of server configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41161 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41161</link><description>Use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability affecting Vonets industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 
3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to 
bypass authentication using hard-coded administrator credentials. These 
accounts cannot be disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24062 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR12, 4.0.0 SR04, 4.1.0 SR02, and 4.2.0 SR01 fails to validate the directory struc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24062</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR12, 4.0.0 SR04, 4.1.0 SR02, and 4.2.0 SR01 fails to validate the directory structure of the root file system during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24063 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR10 fails to validate /etc/mtab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24063</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR10 fails to validate /etc/mtab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24064 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR4 fails to validate /etc/initab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24064</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR4 fails to validate /etc/initab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39287 | Dorsett Controls InfoScan Exposure of Sensitive Information To An Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39287</link><description>Dorsett Controls Central Server update server has potential information 
leaks with an unprotected file that contains passwords and API keys.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42408 | Dorsett Controls InfoScan Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42408</link><description>The InfoScan client download page can be intercepted with a proxy, to 
expose filenames located on the system, which could lead to additional 
information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0104 | NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in the LDAP AAA component, where a user can cause imprope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0104</link><description>NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in the LDAP AAA component, where a user can cause improper access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42493 | Dorsett Controls InfoScan Exposure of Sensitive Information To An Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42493</link><description>Dorsett Controls InfoScan is vulnerable due to a leak of possible 
sensitive information through the response headers and the rendered 
JavaScript prior to user login.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0101 | NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in ipfilter, where improper ipfilter definitions could en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0101</link><description>NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in ipfilter, where improper ipfilter definitions could enable an attacker to cause a failure by attacking the switch. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0107 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0107</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42366 | VR Overlay RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42366</link><description>VRCX is an assistant/companion application for VRChat. In versions prior to 2024.03.23, a CefSharp browser with over-permission and cross-site scripting via overlay notification can be combined to result in remote command execution. These vulnerabilities are patched in VRCX 2023.12.24. In addition to the patch, VRCX maintainers worked with the VRC team and blocked the older version of VRCX on the VRC's API side. Users who use the older version of VRCX must update their installation to continue using VRCX.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7394 | Stored XSS in getAttributeSetName()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7394</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9 through 9.3.2 and below 8.5.18 are vulnerable to Stored XSS in getAttributeSetName().  A rogue administrator could inject malicious code. The Concrete CMS team gave this a CVSS v3.1 rank of 2 with vector  AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator  and a CVSS v4.0 rank of 1.8 with vector  CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/4.0#CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N . Thanks, m3dium for reporting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42365 | Asterisk allows `Write=originate` as sufficient permissions for code execution / `System()` dialplan</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42365</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange (PBX) and telephony toolkit. Prior to asterisk versions 18.24.2, 20.9.2, and 21.4.2 and certified-asterisk versions 18.9-cert11 and 20.7-cert2, an AMI user with `write=originate` may change all configuration files in the `/etc/asterisk/` directory. This occurs because they are able to curl remote files and write them to disk, but are also able to append to existing files using the `FILE` function inside the `SET` application. This issue may result in privilege escalation, remote code execution and/or blind server-side request forgery with arbitrary protocol. Asterisk versions 18.24.2, 20.9.2, and 21.4.2 and certified-asterisk versions 18.9-cert11 and 20.7-cert2 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0108 | NVIDIA Jetson Linux contains a vulnerability in NvGPU where error handling paths in GPU MMU mapping code fail to clean up a failed mapping a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0108</link><description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux contains a vulnerability in NvGPU where error handling paths in GPU MMU mapping code fail to clean up a failed mapping attempt. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, code execution, and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0102 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm, where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds read issue by decei...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0102</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm, where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds read issue by deceiving a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41238 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /smsa/student_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41238</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /smsa/student_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "username" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7477 | Avaya Aura System Manager SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7477</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was found which could allow a command line interface (CLI) user with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary queries against the Avaya Aura System Manager database. 

Affected versions include 10.1.x.x and 10.2.x.x. Versions prior to 10.1 are end of manufacturer support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7480 | Improper access control in Avaya Aura System Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7480</link><description>An Improper access control vulnerability was found in Avaya Aura System Manager which could allow a command-line interface (CLI) user with administrative privileges to read arbitrary files on the system. Affected versions include 10.1.x.x and 10.2.x.x. Versions prior to 10.1 are end of manufacturer support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42357 | Shopware vulnerable to blind SQL-injection in DAL aggregations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42357</link><description>Shopware is an open commerce platform. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, the Shopware application API contains a search functionality which enables users to search through information stored within their Shopware instance. The searches performed by this function can be aggregated using the parameters in the `aggregations` object. The `name` field in this `aggregations` object is vulnerable SQL-injection and can be exploited using SQL parameters. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, 6.3, and 6.4, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7490 | Remote Code Execution in Advanced Software Framework DHCP server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7490</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Microchip Techology Advanced Software Framework example DHCP server can cause remote code execution through a buffer overflow.
 This vulnerability is associated with program files tinydhcpserver.C and program routines lwip_dhcp_find_option.

This issue affects Advanced Software Framework: through 3.52.0.2574.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42355 | Shopware vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection in Twig using deprecation silence tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42355</link><description>Shopware, an open ecommerce platform, has a new Twig Tag `sw_silent_feature_call` which silences deprecation messages while triggered in this tag. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, it accepts as parameter a string the feature flag name to silence, but this parameter is not escaped properly and allows execution of code. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.2, 6.3,  and 6.4, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42356 | Shopware vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection in Twig using Context functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42356</link><description>Shopware is an open commerce platform. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, the `context` variable is injected into almost any Twig Template and allows to access to current language, currency information. The context object allows also to switch for a short time the scope of the Context as a helper with a callable function. The function can be called also from Twig and as the second parameter allows any callable, it's possible to call from Twig any statically callable PHP function/method. It's not possible as customer to provide any Twig code, the attacker would require access to Administration to exploit it using Mail templates or using App Scripts. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, 6.3 and 6.4 corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42354 | Shopware vulnerable to Improper Access Control with ManyToMany associations in store-api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42354</link><description>Shopware is an open commerce platform. The store-API works with regular entities and not expose all fields for the public API; fields need to be marked as ApiAware in the EntityDefinition. So only ApiAware fields of the EntityDefinition will be encoded to the final JSON. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, the processing of the Criteria did not considered ManyToMany associations and so they were not considered properly and the protections didn't get used. This issue cannot be reproduced with the default entities by Shopware, but can be triggered with extensions. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.2, 6.3,  and 6.4, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41942 | JupyterHub has a privilege escalation vulnerability with the `admin:users` scope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41942</link><description>JupyterHub is software that allows one to create a multi-user server for Jupyter notebooks. Prior to versions 4.1.6 and 5.1.0, if a user is granted the `admin:users` scope, they may escalate their own privileges by making themselves a full admin user. The impact is relatively small in that `admin:users` is already an extremely privileged scope only granted to trusted users.
In effect, `admin:users` is equivalent to `admin=True`, which is not intended. Note that the change here only prevents escalation to the built-in JupyterHub admin role that has unrestricted permissions. It does not prevent users with e.g. `groups` permissions from granting themselves or other users permissions via group membership, which is intentional. Versions 4.1.6 and 5.1.0 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7348 | PostgreSQL relation replacement during pg_dump executes arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7348</link><description>Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition in pg_dump in PostgreSQL allows an object creator to execute arbitrary SQL functions as the user running pg_dump, which is often a superuser. The attack involves replacing another relation type with a view or foreign table. The attack requires waiting for pg_dump to start, but winning the race condition is trivial if the attacker retains an open transaction. Versions before PostgreSQL 16.4, 15.8, 14.13, 13.16, and 12.20 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3659 | Command injection in KAON AR2140 routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3659</link><description>Firmware in KAON AR2140 routers prior to version 4.2.16 is vulnerable to a shell command injection via sending a crafted request to one of the endpoints.
In order to exploit this vulnerability, one has to have access to the administrative portal of the router.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2800 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2800</link><description>ReDoS flaw in RefMatcher when matching branch names using wildcards in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions from 11.3 prior to 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2 allows denial of service via Regex backtracking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3035 | Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3035</link><description>A permission check vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.12 prior to 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2  allowed for LFS tokens to read and write to the user owned repositories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3114 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3114</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.10 prior to 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2, with the processing logic for parsing invalid commits can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3958 | Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3958</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. An issue was found that allows someone  to abuse a discrepancy between the Web application display and the git command line interface to social engineer victims into cloning non-trusted code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4207 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4207</link><description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 prior 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. When viewing an XML file in a repository in raw mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5423 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5423</link><description>Multiple Denial of Service (DoS) conditions has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.0 prior to 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2 which allowed an attacker to cause resource exhaustion via banzai pipeline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7554 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7554</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.9 before 17.0.6, all versions starting from 17.1 before 17.1.4, all versions starting from 17.2 before 17.2.2. Under certain conditions, access tokens may have been logged when an API request was made in a specific manner.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7610 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7610</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting with 15.9 before 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. It is possible for an attacker to cause catastrophic backtracking while parsing results from Elasticsearch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4210 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4210</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting with 12.6 before 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. It is possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using crafted adoc files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4784 | Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4784</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE starting from version 16.7 before 17.0.6, version 17.1 before 17.1.4 and 17.2 before 17.2.2 that allowed bypassing the password re-entry requirement to approve a policy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6329 | Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6329</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.16 prior to 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2, which causes the web interface to fail to render the diff correctly when the path is encoded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42037 | Vulnerability of uncaught exceptions in the Graphics module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42037</link><description>Vulnerability of uncaught exceptions in the Graphics module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42038 | Vulnerability of PIN enhancement failures in the screen lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42038</link><description>Vulnerability of PIN enhancement failures in the screen lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42033 | Access control vulnerability in the security verification module
mpact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42033</link><description>Access control vulnerability in the security verification module
mpact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42034 | LaunchAnywhere vulnerability in the account module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42034</link><description>LaunchAnywhere vulnerability in the account module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42035 | Permission control vulnerability in the App Multiplier module
Impact:Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect functionality ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42035</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the App Multiplier module
Impact:Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect functionality and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42036 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the Notepad module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42036</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the Notepad module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42032 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the Contacts module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42032</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the Contacts module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42031 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the Settings module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42031</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the Settings module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42251 | mm: page_ref: remove folio_try_get_rcu()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42251</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: page_ref: remove folio_try_get_rcu()

The below bug was reported on a non-SMP kernel:

[  275.267158][ T4335] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  275.267949][ T4335] kernel BUG at include/linux/page_ref.h:275!
[  275.268526][ T4335] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] KASAN PTI
[  275.269001][ T4335] CPU: 0 PID: 4335 Comm: trinity-c3 Not tainted 6.7.0-rc4-00061-gefa7df3e3bb5 #1
[  275.269787][ T4335] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.2-debian-1.16.2-1 04/01/2014
[  275.270679][ T4335] RIP: 0010:try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[  275.272813][ T4335] RSP: 0018:ffffc90005dcf650 EFLAGS: 00010202
[  275.273346][ T4335] RAX: 0000000000000246 RBX: ffffea00066e0000 RCX: 0000000000000000
[  275.274032][ T4335] RDX: fffff94000cdc007 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffffea00066e0034
[  275.274719][ T4335] RBP: ffffea00066e0000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: fffff94000cdc006
[  275.275404][ T4335] R10: ffffea00066e0037 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: 0000000000000136
[  275.276106][ T4335] R13: ffffea00066e0034 R14: dffffc0000000000 R15: ffffea00066e0008
[  275.276790][ T4335] FS:  00007fa2f9b61740(0000) GS:ffffffff89d0d000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  275.277570][ T4335] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  275.278143][ T4335] CR2: 00007fa2f6c00000 CR3: 0000000134b04000 CR4: 00000000000406f0
[  275.278833][ T4335] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
[  275.279521][ T4335] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
[  275.280201][ T4335] Call Trace:
[  275.280499][ T4335]  
[ 275.280751][ T4335] ? die (arch/x86/kernel/dumpstack.c:421 arch/x86/kernel/dumpstack.c:434 arch/x86/kernel/dumpstack.c:447)
[ 275.281087][ T4335] ? do_trap (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:112 arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:153)
[ 275.281463][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.281884][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.282300][ T4335] ? do_error_trap (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:174)
[ 275.282711][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.283129][ T4335] ? handle_invalid_op (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:212)
[ 275.283561][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.283990][ T4335] ? exc_invalid_op (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:264)
[ 275.284415][ T4335] ? asm_exc_invalid_op (arch/x86/include/asm/idtentry.h:568)
[ 275.284859][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.285278][ T4335] try_grab_folio (mm/gup.c:148)
[ 275.285684][ T4335] __get_user_pages (mm/gup.c:1297 (discriminator 1))
[ 275.286111][ T4335] ? __pfx___get_user_pages (mm/gup.c:1188)
[ 275.286579][ T4335] ? __pfx_validate_chain (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:3825)
[ 275.287034][ T4335] ? mark_lock (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:4656 (discriminator 1))
[ 275.287416][ T4335] __gup_longterm_locked (mm/gup.c:1509 mm/gup.c:2209)
[ 275.288192][ T4335] ? __pfx___gup_longterm_locked (mm/gup.c:2204)
[ 275.288697][ T4335] ? __pfx_lock_acquire (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5722)
[ 275.289135][ T4335] ? __pfx___might_resched (kernel/sched/core.c:10106)
[ 275.289595][ T4335] pin_user_pages_remote (mm/gup.c:3350)
[ 275.290041][ T4335] ? __pfx_pin_user_pages_remote (mm/gup.c:3350)
[ 275.290545][ T4335] ? find_held_lock (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5244 (discriminator 1))
[ 275.290961][ T4335] ? mm_access (kernel/fork.c:1573)
[ 275.291353][ T4335] process_vm_rw_single_vec+0x142/0x360
[ 275.291900][ T4335] ? __pfx_process_vm_rw_single_vec+0x10/0x10
[ 275.292471][ T4335] ? mm_access (kernel/fork.c:1573)
[ 275.292859][ T4335] process_vm_rw_core+0x272/0x4e0
[ 275.293384][ T4335] ? hlock_class (a
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42252 | closures: Change BUG_ON() to WARN_ON()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42252</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

closures: Change BUG_ON() to WARN_ON()

If a BUG_ON() can be hit in the wild, it shouldn't be a BUG_ON()

For reference, this has popped up once in the CI, and we'll need more
info to debug it:

03240 ------------[ cut here ]------------
03240 kernel BUG at lib/closure.c:21!
03240 kernel BUG at lib/closure.c:21!
03240 Internal error: Oops - BUG: 00000000f2000800 [#1] SMP
03240 Modules linked in:
03240 CPU: 15 PID: 40534 Comm: kworker/u80:1 Not tainted 6.10.0-rc4-ktest-ga56da69799bd #25570
03240 Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
03240 Workqueue: btree_update btree_interior_update_work
03240 pstate: 00001005 (nzcv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT +SSBS BTYPE=--)
03240 pc : closure_put+0x224/0x2a0
03240 lr : closure_put+0x24/0x2a0
03240 sp : ffff0000d12071c0
03240 x29: ffff0000d12071c0 x28: dfff800000000000 x27: ffff0000d1207360
03240 x26: 0000000000000040 x25: 0000000000000040 x24: 0000000000000040
03240 x23: ffff0000c1f20180 x22: 0000000000000000 x21: ffff0000c1f20168
03240 x20: 0000000040000000 x19: ffff0000c1f20140 x18: 0000000000000001
03240 x17: 0000000000003aa0 x16: 0000000000003ad0 x15: 1fffe0001c326974
03240 x14: 0000000000000a1e x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 1fffe000183e402d
03240 x11: ffff6000183e402d x10: dfff800000000000 x9 : ffff6000183e402e
03240 x8 : 0000000000000001 x7 : 00009fffe7c1bfd3 x6 : ffff0000c1f2016b
03240 x5 : ffff0000c1f20168 x4 : ffff6000183e402e x3 : ffff800081391954
03240 x2 : 0000000000000001 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : 00000000a8000000
03240 Call trace:
03240  closure_put+0x224/0x2a0
03240  bch2_check_for_deadlock+0x910/0x1028
03240  bch2_six_check_for_deadlock+0x1c/0x30
03240  six_lock_slowpath.isra.0+0x29c/0xed0
03240  six_lock_ip_waiter+0xa8/0xf8
03240  __bch2_btree_node_lock_write+0x14c/0x298
03240  bch2_trans_lock_write+0x6d4/0xb10
03240  __bch2_trans_commit+0x135c/0x5520
03240  btree_interior_update_work+0x1248/0x1c10
03240  process_scheduled_works+0x53c/0xd90
03240  worker_thread+0x370/0x8c8
03240  kthread+0x258/0x2e8
03240  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
03240 Code: aa1303e0 d63f0020 a94363f7 17ffff8c (d4210000)
03240 ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
03240 Kernel panic - not syncing: Oops - BUG: Fatal exception
03240 SMP: stopping secondary CPUs
03241 SMP: failed to stop secondary CPUs 13,15
03241 Kernel Offset: disabled
03241 CPU features: 0x00,00000003,80000008,4240500b
03241 Memory Limit: none
03241 ---[ end Kernel panic - not syncing: Oops - BUG: Fatal exception ]---
03246 ========= FAILED TIMEOUT copygc_torture_no_checksum in 7200s</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42253 | gpio: pca953x: fix pca953x_irq_bus_sync_unlock race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42253</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpio: pca953x: fix pca953x_irq_bus_sync_unlock race

Ensure that `i2c_lock' is held when setting interrupt latch and mask in
pca953x_irq_bus_sync_unlock() in order to avoid races.

The other (non-probe) call site pca953x_gpio_set_multiple() ensures the
lock is held before calling pca953x_write_regs().

The problem occurred when a request raced against irq_bus_sync_unlock()
approximately once per thousand reboots on an i.MX8MP based system.

 * Normal case

   0-0022: write register AI|3a {03,02,00,00,01} Input latch P0
   0-0022: write register AI|49 {fc,fd,ff,ff,fe} Interrupt mask P0
   0-0022: write register AI|08 {ff,00,00,00,00} Output P3
   0-0022: write register AI|12 {fc,00,00,00,00} Config P3

 * Race case

   0-0022: write register AI|08 {ff,00,00,00,00} Output P3
   0-0022: write register AI|08 {03,02,00,00,01} *** Wrong register ***
   0-0022: write register AI|12 {fc,00,00,00,00} Config P3
   0-0022: write register AI|49 {fc,fd,ff,ff,fe} Interrupt mask P0</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42254 | io_uring: fix error pbuf checking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42254</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: fix error pbuf checking

Syz reports a problem, which boils down to NULL vs IS_ERR inconsistent
error handling in io_alloc_pbuf_ring().

KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000000-0x0000000000000007]
RIP: 0010:__io_remove_buffers+0xac/0x700 io_uring/kbuf.c:341
Call Trace:
 
 io_put_bl io_uring/kbuf.c:378 [inline]
 io_destroy_buffers+0x14e/0x490 io_uring/kbuf.c:392
 io_ring_ctx_free+0xa00/0x1070 io_uring/io_uring.c:2613
 io_ring_exit_work+0x80f/0x8a0 io_uring/io_uring.c:2844
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3231 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xa2c/0x1830 kernel/workqueue.c:3312
 worker_thread+0x86d/0xd40 kernel/workqueue.c:3390
 kthread+0x2f0/0x390 kernel/kthread.c:389
 ret_from_fork+0x4b/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:244</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42255 | tpm: Use auth only after NULL check in tpm_buf_check_hmac_response()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42255</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tpm: Use auth only after NULL check in tpm_buf_check_hmac_response()

Dereference auth after NULL check in tpm_buf_check_hmac_response().
Otherwise, unless tpm2_sessions_init() was called, a call can cause NULL
dereference, when TCG_TPM2_HMAC is enabled.

[jarkko: adjusted the commit message.]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42256 | cifs: Fix server re-repick on subrequest retry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42256</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cifs: Fix server re-repick on subrequest retry

When a subrequest is marked for needing retry, netfs will call
cifs_prepare_write() which will make cifs repick the server for the op
before renegotiating credits; it then calls cifs_issue_write() which
invokes smb2_async_writev() - which re-repicks the server.

If a different server is then selected, this causes the increment of
server-&gt;in_flight to happen against one record and the decrement to happen
against another, leading to misaccounting.

Fix this by just removing the repick code in smb2_async_writev().  As this
is only called from netfslib-driven code, cifs_prepare_write() should
always have been called first, and so server should never be NULL and the
preparatory step is repeated in the event that we do a retry.

The problem manifests as a warning looking something like:

 WARNING: CPU: 4 PID: 72896 at fs/smb/client/smb2ops.c:97 smb2_add_credits+0x3f0/0x9e0 [cifs]
 ...
 RIP: 0010:smb2_add_credits+0x3f0/0x9e0 [cifs]
 ...
  smb2_writev_callback+0x334/0x560 [cifs]
  cifs_demultiplex_thread+0x77a/0x11b0 [cifs]
  kthread+0x187/0x1d0
  ret_from_fork+0x34/0x60
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30

Which may be triggered by a number of different xfstests running against an
Azure server in multichannel mode.  generic/249 seems the most repeatable,
but generic/215, generic/249 and generic/308 may also show it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42257 | ext4: use memtostr_pad() for s_volume_name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42257</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: use memtostr_pad() for s_volume_name

As with the other strings in struct ext4_super_block, s_volume_name is
not NUL terminated. The other strings were marked in commit 072ebb3bffe6
("ext4: add nonstring annotations to ext4.h"). Using strscpy() isn't
the right replacement for strncpy(); it should use memtostr_pad()
instead.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42030 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the content sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42030</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the content sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7265 | Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7265</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22069 | Permission and Access Control Vulnerability in ZXV10 XT802/ET301</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22069</link><description>There is a permission and access control vulnerability of ZTE's ZXV10 XT802/ET301 product.Attackers with common permissions can log in the terminal web and change the password of the administrator illegally by intercepting requests to change the passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6481 | Search Filter Pro &amp;lt; 2.5.18 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6481</link><description>The Search &amp; Filter Pro WordPress plugin before 2.5.18 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 06:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6884 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP &amp;lt; 3.2.39 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6884</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP  WordPress plugin before 3.2.39 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 06:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5226 | Fuse Social Floating Sidebar &amp;lt;= 5.4.10 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5226</link><description>The Fuse Social Floating Sidebar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the file upload functionality in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.10 due to insufficient validation of SVG files. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6824 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.38 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Content Deletion and Arbitrary Title Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6824</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'check_temp_validity' and 'update_template_title' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.38. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary content and update post and page titles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7150 | Slider by 10Web – Responsive Image Slider &amp;lt;= 1.2.57 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7150</link><description>The Slider by 10Web – Responsive Image Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.57 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7548 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.9.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via order Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7548</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.9.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5668 | Lightbox &amp;amp; Modal Popup WordPress Plugin – FooBox &amp;lt;= 2.7.28 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Data Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5668</link><description>The Lightbox &amp; Modal Popup WordPress Plugin – FooBox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML data attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6869 | Falang multilanguage for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.3.52 - Missing Authorization to Translation Update and Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6869</link><description>The Falang multilanguage for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.52. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update and delete translations and expose the administrator email address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6987 | Orchid Store &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 -  Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6987</link><description>The Orchid Store theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'orchid_store_activate_plugin' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate the Addonify Floating Cart For WooCommerce plugin if it is installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6254 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6254</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on form submissions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to submit forms intended for public use as another user via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. On sites where unfiltered_html is enabled, this can lead to the admin unknowingly adding a Stored Cross-Site Scripting payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6552 | Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6552</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to the plugin utilizing Symfony and leaving display_errors on within test files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7350 | Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Online Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress 1.1.6  - 1.1.7 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7350</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Online Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions 1.1.6 to 1.1.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to logging them in when completing a booking. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as registered users, including administrators, if they have access to that user's email.  This is only exploitable when the 'Auto login user after successful booking' setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7492 | MainWP Child Reports &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7492</link><description>The MainWP Child Reports plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the network_options_action() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options that can be leveraged for privilege escalation via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This is only exploitable on multisite instances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21302 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21302</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38202 | Windows Update Stack Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38202</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7486 | MultiPurpose &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7486</link><description>The MultiPurpose theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 via deserialization of untrusted input through the 'wpeden_post_meta' post meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7560 | News Flash &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7560</link><description>The News Flash theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the newsflash_post_meta meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7561 | The Next &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7561</link><description>The The Next theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the wpeden_post_meta post meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6892 | Journyx Reflected Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6892</link><description>Attackers can craft a malicious link that once clicked will execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the Journyx web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6893 | Journyx Unauthenticated XML External Entities Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6893</link><description>The "soap_cgi.pyc" API handler allows the XML body of SOAP requests to contain references to external entities. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to read local files, perform server-side request forgery, and overwhelm the web server resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6891 | Journyx Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6891</link><description>Attackers with a valid username and password can exploit a python code injection vulnerability during the natural login flow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6707 | Open WebUI Arbitrary File Upload + Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6707</link><description>Attacker controlled files can be uploaded to arbitrary locations on the web server's filesystem by abusing a path traversal vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6890 | Journyx Unauthenticated Password Reset Bruteforce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6890</link><description>Password reset tokens are generated using an insecure source of randomness. Attackers who know the username of the Journyx installation user can bruteforce the password reset and change the administrator password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6706 | Open WebUI Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6706</link><description>Attackers can craft a malicious prompt that coerces the language model into executing arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the web page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41912 | A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices. The firmware flaw does not properly i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41912</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices. The firmware flaw does not properly implement access controls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 20:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41239 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/smsa/add_class_submit.php" in Kashipara Responsive School Management System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41239</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/smsa/add_class_submit.php" in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "class_name" parameter field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41237 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /smsa/teacher_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41237</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /smsa/teacher_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "username" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41241 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in " /smsa/admin_login.php" in Kashipara Responsive School Management System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41241</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in " /smsa/admin_login.php" in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "error" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41240 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in " /smsa/teacher_login.php" in Kashipara Responsive School Management Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41240</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in " /smsa/teacher_login.php" in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "error" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41242 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /smsa/student_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41242</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /smsa/student_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "error" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41243 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_marks.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41243</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_marks.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view MARKS details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7585 | Tenda i22 apPortalAuth formApPortalWebAuth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7585</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i22 1.0.0.3(4687) and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formApPortalWebAuth of the file /goform/apPortalAuth. The manipulation of the argument webUserName/webUserPassword leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20451 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business SPA300 Series IP Phones and Cisco Small Business SPA5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20451</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business SPA300 Series IP Phones and Cisco Small Business SPA500 Series IP Phones could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly.

These vulnerabilities exist because HTTP packets are not properly checked for errors. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP packet to the remote interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition on the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7143 | Pulpcore: rbac permissions incorrectly assigned in tasks that create objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7143</link><description>A flaw was found in the Pulp package. When a role-based access control (RBAC) object in Pulp is set to assign permissions on its creation, it uses the `AutoAddObjPermsMixin` (typically the add_roles_for_object_creator method). This method finds the object creator by checking the current authenticated user. For objects that are created within a task, this current user is set by the first user with any permissions on the task object. This means the oldest user with model/domain-level task permissions will always be set as the current user of a task, even if they didn't dispatch the task. Therefore, all objects created in tasks will have their permissions assigned to this oldest user, and the creating user will receive nothing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20450 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business SPA300 Series IP Phones and Cisco Small Business SPA5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20450</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business SPA300 Series IP Phones and Cisco Small Business SPA500 Series IP Phones could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges.

These vulnerabilities exist because incoming HTTP packets are not properly checked for errors, which could result in a buffer overflow. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overflow an internal buffer and execute arbitrary commands at the root privilege level.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:54:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20454 | Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business SPA300 Series IP Phones and Cisco Small Business SPA5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20454</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business SPA300 Series IP Phones and Cisco Small Business SPA500 Series IP Phones could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges.

These vulnerabilities exist because incoming HTTP packets are not properly checked for errors, which could result in a buffer overflow. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overflow an internal buffer and execute arbitrary commands at the root privilege level.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20479 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack ag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20479</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have Admin privileges on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20443 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack ag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41244 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_class.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41244</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_class.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view CLASS details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7061 | Okta Verify for Windows is vulnerable to privilege escalation through DLL hijacking. The vulnerability is fixed in Okta Verify for Windows v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7061</link><description>Okta Verify for Windows is vulnerable to privilege escalation through DLL hijacking. The vulnerability is fixed in Okta Verify for Windows version 5.0.2. To remediate this vulnerability, upgrade to 5.0.2 or greater.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7584 | Tenda i22 apPortalPhoneAuth formApPortalPhoneAuth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7584</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda i22 1.0.0.3(4687). Affected is the function formApPortalPhoneAuth of the file /goform/apPortalPhoneAuth. The manipulation of the argument data leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41245 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_teachers.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41245</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_teachers.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view TEACHER details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41250 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_students.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41250</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_students.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view STUDENT details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41246 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/admin_dashboard.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41246</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/admin_dashboard.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view administrator dashboard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41249 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_subject.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41249</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/view_subject.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view SUBJECT details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41251 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/admin_teacher_register_approval.php and /smsa/admin_teacher_register_approval_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41251</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/admin_teacher_register_approval.php and /smsa/admin_teacher_register_approval_submit.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view and approve Teacher registration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41252 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/admin_student_register_approval.php and /smsa/admin_student_register_approval_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41252</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/admin_student_register_approval.php and /smsa/admin_student_register_approval_submit.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view and approve student registration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7583 | Tenda i22 apPortalOneKeyAuth formApPortalOneKeyAuth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7583</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda i22 1.0.0.3(4687). This issue affects the function formApPortalOneKeyAuth of the file /goform/apPortalOneKeyAuth. The manipulation of the argument data leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41248 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/add_subject.php and /smsa/add_subject_submit.php in Kashipara Responsive School...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41248</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/add_subject.php and /smsa/add_subject_submit.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to add a new subject entry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41247 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/add_class.php and /smsa/add_class_submit.php in Kashipara Responsive School Man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41247</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /smsa/add_class.php and /smsa/add_class_submit.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v3.2.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to add a new class entry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41308 | An issue in the Ping feature of IT Solutions Enjay CRM OS v1.0 allows attackers to escape the restricted terminal environment and gain root-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41308</link><description>An issue in the Ping feature of IT Solutions Enjay CRM OS v1.0 allows attackers to escape the restricted terminal environment and gain root-level privileges on the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41309 | An issue in the Hardware info module of IT Solutions Enjay CRM OS v1.0 allows attackers to escape the restricted terminal environment and ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41309</link><description>An issue in the Hardware info module of IT Solutions Enjay CRM OS v1.0 allows attackers to escape the restricted terminal environment and gain root-level privileges on the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7582 | Tenda i22 apPortalAccessCodeAuth formApPortalAccessCodeAuth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7582</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda i22 1.0.0.3(4687). This vulnerability affects the function formApPortalAccessCodeAuth of the file /goform/apPortalAccessCodeAuth. The manipulation of the argument accessCode/data/acceInfo leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34480 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0 allows admin/category/view_category.php id SQL Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34480</link><description>SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0 allows admin/category/view_category.php id SQL Injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34479 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0 allows classes/Master.php id SQL Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34479</link><description>SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0 allows classes/Master.php id SQL Injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41432 | An IP Spoofing vulnerability has been discovered in Likeshop up to 2.5.7.20210811. This issue allows an attacker to replace their real IP ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41432</link><description>An IP Spoofing vulnerability has been discovered in Likeshop up to 2.5.7.20210811. This issue allows an attacker to replace their real IP address with any arbitrary IP address, specifically by adding a forged 'X-Forwarded' or 'Client-IP' header to requests. Exploiting IP spoofing, attackers can bypass account lockout mechanisms during attempts to log into admin accounts, spoof IP addresses in requests sent to the server, and impersonate IP addresses that have logged into user accounts, etc.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42232 | libceph: fix race between delayed_work() and ceph_monc_stop()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42232</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

libceph: fix race between delayed_work() and ceph_monc_stop()

The way the delayed work is handled in ceph_monc_stop() is prone to
races with mon_fault() and possibly also finish_hunting().  Both of
these can requeue the delayed work which wouldn't be canceled by any of
the following code in case that happens after cancel_delayed_work_sync()
runs -- __close_session() doesn't mess with the delayed work in order
to avoid interfering with the hunting interval logic.  This part was
missed in commit b5d91704f53e ("libceph: behave in mon_fault() if
cur_mon &lt; 0") and use-after-free can still ensue on monc and objects
that hang off of it, with monc-&gt;auth and monc-&gt;monmap being
particularly susceptible to quickly being reused.

To fix this:

- clear monc-&gt;cur_mon and monc-&gt;hunting as part of closing the session
  in ceph_monc_stop()
- bail from delayed_work() if monc-&gt;cur_mon is cleared, similar to how
  it's done in mon_fault() and finish_hunting() (based on monc-&gt;hunting)
- call cancel_delayed_work_sync() after the session is closed</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42233 | filemap: replace pte_offset_map() with pte_offset_map_nolock()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42233</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

filemap: replace pte_offset_map() with pte_offset_map_nolock()

The vmf-&gt;ptl in filemap_fault_recheck_pte_none() is still set from
handle_pte_fault().  But at the same time, we did a pte_unmap(vmf-&gt;pte). 
After a pte_unmap(vmf-&gt;pte) unmap and rcu_read_unlock(), the page table
may be racily changed and vmf-&gt;ptl maybe fails to protect the actual page
table.  Fix this by replacing pte_offset_map() with
pte_offset_map_nolock().

As David said, the PTL pointer might be stale so if we continue to use
it infilemap_fault_recheck_pte_none(), it might trigger UAF.  Also, if
the PTL fails, the issue fixed by commit 58f327f2ce80 ("filemap: avoid
unnecessary major faults in filemap_fault()") might reappear.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42234 | mm: fix crashes from deferred split racing folio migration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42234</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: fix crashes from deferred split racing folio migration

Even on 6.10-rc6, I've been seeing elusive "Bad page state"s (often on
flags when freeing, yet the flags shown are not bad: PG_locked had been
set and cleared??), and VM_BUG_ON_PAGE(page_ref_count(page) == 0)s from
deferred_split_scan()'s folio_put(), and a variety of other BUG and WARN
symptoms implying double free by deferred split and large folio migration.

6.7 commit 9bcef5973e31 ("mm: memcg: fix split queue list crash when large
folio migration") was right to fix the memcg-dependent locking broken in
85ce2c517ade ("memcontrol: only transfer the memcg data for migration"),
but missed a subtlety of deferred_split_scan(): it moves folios to its own
local list to work on them without split_queue_lock, during which time
folio-&gt;_deferred_list is not empty, but even the "right" lock does nothing
to secure the folio and the list it is on.

Fortunately, deferred_split_scan() is careful to use folio_try_get(): so
folio_migrate_mapping() can avoid the race by folio_undo_large_rmappable()
while the old folio's reference count is temporarily frozen to 0 - adding
such a freeze in the !mapping case too (originally, folio lock and
unmapping and no swap cache left an anon folio unreachable, so no freezing
was needed there: but the deferred split queue offers a way to reach it).</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42235 | s390/mm: Add NULL pointer check to crst_table_free() base_crst_free()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42235</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/mm: Add NULL pointer check to crst_table_free() base_crst_free()

crst_table_free() used to work with NULL pointers before the conversion
to ptdescs.  Since crst_table_free() can be called with a NULL pointer
(error handling in crst_table_upgrade() add an explicit check.

Also add the same check to base_crst_free() for consistency reasons.

In real life this should not happen, since order two GFP_KERNEL
allocations will not fail, unless FAIL_PAGE_ALLOC is enabled and used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42236 | usb: gadget: configfs: Prevent OOB read/write in usb_string_copy()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42236</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: gadget: configfs: Prevent OOB read/write in usb_string_copy()

Userspace provided string 's' could trivially have the length zero. Left
unchecked this will firstly result in an OOB read in the form
`if (str[0 - 1] == '\n') followed closely by an OOB write in the form
`str[0 - 1] = '\0'`.

There is already a validating check to catch strings that are too long.
Let's supply an additional check for invalid strings that are too short.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42237 | firmware: cs_dsp: Validate payload length before processing block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42237</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: cs_dsp: Validate payload length before processing block

Move the payload length check in cs_dsp_load() and cs_dsp_coeff_load()
to be done before the block is processed.

The check that the length of a block payload does not exceed the number
of remaining bytes in the firwmware file buffer was being done near the
end of the loop iteration. However, some code before that check used the
length field without validating it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42238 | firmware: cs_dsp: Return error if block header overflows file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42238</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: cs_dsp: Return error if block header overflows file

Return an error from cs_dsp_power_up() if a block header is longer
than the amount of data left in the file.

The previous code in cs_dsp_load() and cs_dsp_load_coeff() would loop
while there was enough data left in the file for a valid region. This
protected against overrunning the end of the file data, but it didn't
abort the file processing with an error.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42239 | bpf: Fail bpf_timer_cancel when callback is being cancelled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42239</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fail bpf_timer_cancel when callback is being cancelled

Given a schedule:

timer1 cb			timer2 cb

bpf_timer_cancel(timer2);	bpf_timer_cancel(timer1);

Both bpf_timer_cancel calls would wait for the other callback to finish
executing, introducing a lockup.

Add an atomic_t count named 'cancelling' in bpf_hrtimer. This keeps
track of all in-flight cancellation requests for a given BPF timer.
Whenever cancelling a BPF timer, we must check if we have outstanding
cancellation requests, and if so, we must fail the operation with an
error (-EDEADLK) since cancellation is synchronous and waits for the
callback to finish executing. This implies that we can enter a deadlock
situation involving two or more timer callbacks executing in parallel
and attempting to cancel one another.

Note that we avoid incrementing the cancelling counter for the target
timer (the one being cancelled) if bpf_timer_cancel is not invoked from
a callback, to avoid spurious errors. The whole point of detecting
cur-&gt;cancelling and returning -EDEADLK is to not enter a busy wait loop
(which may or may not lead to a lockup). This does not apply in case the
caller is in a non-callback context, the other side can continue to
cancel as it sees fit without running into errors.

Background on prior attempts:

Earlier versions of this patch used a bool 'cancelling' bit and used the
following pattern under timer-&gt;lock to publish cancellation status.

lock(t-&gt;lock);
t-&gt;cancelling = true;
mb();
if (cur-&gt;cancelling)
	return -EDEADLK;
unlock(t-&gt;lock);
hrtimer_cancel(t-&gt;timer);
t-&gt;cancelling = false;

The store outside the critical section could overwrite a parallel
requests t-&gt;cancelling assignment to true, to ensure the parallely
executing callback observes its cancellation status.

It would be necessary to clear this cancelling bit once hrtimer_cancel
is done, but lack of serialization introduced races. Another option was
explored where bpf_timer_start would clear the bit when (re)starting the
timer under timer-&gt;lock. This would ensure serialized access to the
cancelling bit, but may allow it to be cleared before in-flight
hrtimer_cancel has finished executing, such that lockups can occur
again.

Thus, we choose an atomic counter to keep track of all outstanding
cancellation requests and use it to prevent lockups in case callbacks
attempt to cancel each other while executing in parallel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42240 | x86/bhi: Avoid warning in #DB handler due to BHI mitigation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42240</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/bhi: Avoid warning in #DB handler due to BHI mitigation

When BHI mitigation is enabled, if SYSENTER is invoked with the TF flag set
then entry_SYSENTER_compat() uses CLEAR_BRANCH_HISTORY and calls the
clear_bhb_loop() before the TF flag is cleared. This causes the #DB handler
(exc_debug_kernel()) to issue a warning because single-step is used outside the
entry_SYSENTER_compat() function.

To address this issue, entry_SYSENTER_compat() should use CLEAR_BRANCH_HISTORY
after making sure the TF flag is cleared.

The problem can be reproduced with the following sequence:

  $ cat sysenter_step.c
  int main()
  { asm("pushf; pop %ax; bts $8,%ax; push %ax; popf; sysenter"); }

  $ gcc -o sysenter_step sysenter_step.c

  $ ./sysenter_step
  Segmentation fault (core dumped)

The program is expected to crash, and the #DB handler will issue a warning.

Kernel log:

  WARNING: CPU: 27 PID: 7000 at arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:1009 exc_debug_kernel+0xd2/0x160
  ...
  RIP: 0010:exc_debug_kernel+0xd2/0x160
  ...
  Call Trace:
  &lt;#DB&gt;
   ? show_regs+0x68/0x80
   ? __warn+0x8c/0x140
   ? exc_debug_kernel+0xd2/0x160
   ? report_bug+0x175/0x1a0
   ? handle_bug+0x44/0x90
   ? exc_invalid_op+0x1c/0x70
   ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1f/0x30
   ? exc_debug_kernel+0xd2/0x160
   exc_debug+0x43/0x50
   asm_exc_debug+0x1e/0x40
  RIP: 0010:clear_bhb_loop+0x0/0xb0
  ...
  
  
   ? entry_SYSENTER_compat_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x8d
  

  [ bp: Massage commit message. ]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42241 | mm/shmem: disable PMD-sized page cache if needed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42241</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/shmem: disable PMD-sized page cache if needed

For shmem files, it's possible that PMD-sized page cache can't be
supported by xarray.  For example, 512MB page cache on ARM64 when the base
page size is 64KB can't be supported by xarray.  It leads to errors as the
following messages indicate when this sort of xarray entry is split.

WARNING: CPU: 34 PID: 7578 at lib/xarray.c:1025 xas_split_alloc+0xf8/0x128
Modules linked in: binfmt_misc nft_fib_inet nft_fib_ipv4 nft_fib_ipv6   \
nft_fib nft_reject_inet nf_reject_ipv4 nf_reject_ipv6 nft_reject        \
nft_ct nft_chain_nat nf_nat nf_conntrack nf_defrag_ipv6 nf_defrag_ipv4  \
ip_set rfkill nf_tables nfnetlink vfat fat virtio_balloon drm fuse xfs  \
libcrc32c crct10dif_ce ghash_ce sha2_ce sha256_arm64 sha1_ce virtio_net \
net_failover virtio_console virtio_blk failover dimlib virtio_mmio
CPU: 34 PID: 7578 Comm: test Kdump: loaded Tainted: G W 6.10.0-rc5-gavin+ #9
Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS edk2-20240524-1.el9 05/24/2024
pstate: 83400005 (Nzcv daif +PAN -UAO +TCO +DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : xas_split_alloc+0xf8/0x128
lr : split_huge_page_to_list_to_order+0x1c4/0x720
sp : ffff8000882af5f0
x29: ffff8000882af5f0 x28: ffff8000882af650 x27: ffff8000882af768
x26: 0000000000000cc0 x25: 000000000000000d x24: ffff00010625b858
x23: ffff8000882af650 x22: ffffffdfc0900000 x21: 0000000000000000
x20: 0000000000000000 x19: ffffffdfc0900000 x18: 0000000000000000
x17: 0000000000000000 x16: 0000018000000000 x15: 52f8004000000000
x14: 0000e00000000000 x13: 0000000000002000 x12: 0000000000000020
x11: 52f8000000000000 x10: 52f8e1c0ffff6000 x9 : ffffbeb9619a681c
x8 : 0000000000000003 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : ffff00010b02ddb0
x5 : ffffbeb96395e378 x4 : 0000000000000000 x3 : 0000000000000cc0
x2 : 000000000000000d x1 : 000000000000000c x0 : 0000000000000000
Call trace:
 xas_split_alloc+0xf8/0x128
 split_huge_page_to_list_to_order+0x1c4/0x720
 truncate_inode_partial_folio+0xdc/0x160
 shmem_undo_range+0x2bc/0x6a8
 shmem_fallocate+0x134/0x430
 vfs_fallocate+0x124/0x2e8
 ksys_fallocate+0x4c/0xa0
 __arm64_sys_fallocate+0x24/0x38
 invoke_syscall.constprop.0+0x7c/0xd8
 do_el0_svc+0xb4/0xd0
 el0_svc+0x44/0x1d8
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x134/0x150
 el0t_64_sync+0x17c/0x180

Fix it by disabling PMD-sized page cache when HPAGE_PMD_ORDER is larger
than MAX_PAGECACHE_ORDER.  As Matthew Wilcox pointed, the page cache in a
shmem file isn't represented by a multi-index entry and doesn't have this
limitation when the xarry entry is split until commit 6b24ca4a1a8d ("mm:
Use multi-index entries in the page cache").</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42242 | mmc: sdhci: Fix max_seg_size for 64KiB PAGE_SIZE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42242</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mmc: sdhci: Fix max_seg_size for 64KiB PAGE_SIZE

blk_queue_max_segment_size() ensured:

	if (max_size &lt; PAGE_SIZE)
		max_size = PAGE_SIZE;

whereas:

blk_validate_limits() makes it an error:

	if (WARN_ON_ONCE(lim-&gt;max_segment_size &lt; PAGE_SIZE))
		return -EINVAL;

The change from one to the other, exposed sdhci which was setting maximum
segment size too low in some circumstances.

Fix the maximum segment size when it is too low.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42243 | mm/filemap: make MAX_PAGECACHE_ORDER acceptable to xarray</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42243</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/filemap: make MAX_PAGECACHE_ORDER acceptable to xarray

Patch series "mm/filemap: Limit page cache size to that supported by
xarray", v2.

Currently, xarray can't support arbitrary page cache size.  More details
can be found from the WARN_ON() statement in xas_split_alloc().  In our
test whose code is attached below, we hit the WARN_ON() on ARM64 system
where the base page size is 64KB and huge page size is 512MB.  The issue
was reported long time ago and some discussions on it can be found here
[1].

[1] https://www.spinics.net/lists/linux-xfs/msg75404.html

In order to fix the issue, we need to adjust MAX_PAGECACHE_ORDER to one
supported by xarray and avoid PMD-sized page cache if needed.  The code
changes are suggested by David Hildenbrand.

PATCH[1] adjusts MAX_PAGECACHE_ORDER to that supported by xarray
PATCH[2-3] avoids PMD-sized page cache in the synchronous readahead path
PATCH[4] avoids PMD-sized page cache for shmem files if needed

Test program
============
# cat test.c
#define _GNU_SOURCE
#include 
#include 
#include 
#include 
#include 
#include 
#include syscall.h&gt;
#include mman.h&gt;

#define TEST_XFS_FILENAME	"/tmp/data"
#define TEST_SHMEM_FILENAME	"/dev/shm/data"
#define TEST_MEM_SIZE		0x20000000

int main(int argc, char **argv)
{
	const char *filename;
	int fd = 0;
	void *buf = (void *)-1, *p;
	int pgsize = getpagesize();
	int ret;

	if (pgsize != 0x10000) {
		fprintf(stderr, "64KB base page size is required\n");
		return -EPERM;
	}

	system("echo force &gt; /sys/kernel/mm/transparent_hugepage/shmem_enabled");
	system("rm -fr /tmp/data");
	system("rm -fr /dev/shm/data");
	system("echo 1 &gt; /proc/sys/vm/drop_caches");

	/* Open xfs or shmem file */
	filename = TEST_XFS_FILENAME;
	if (argc &gt; 1 &amp;&amp; !strcmp(argv[1], "shmem"))
		filename = TEST_SHMEM_FILENAME;

	fd = open(filename, O_CREAT | O_RDWR | O_TRUNC);
	if (fd &lt; 0) {
		fprintf(stderr, "Unable to open &lt;%s&gt;\n", filename);
		return -EIO;
	}

	/* Extend file size */
	ret = ftruncate(fd, TEST_MEM_SIZE);
	if (ret) {
		fprintf(stderr, "Error %d to ftruncate()\n", ret);
		goto cleanup;
	}

	/* Create VMA */
	buf = mmap(NULL, TEST_MEM_SIZE,
		   PROT_READ | PROT_WRITE, MAP_SHARED, fd, 0);
	if (buf == (void *)-1) {
		fprintf(stderr, "Unable to mmap &lt;%s&gt;\n", filename);
		goto cleanup;
	}

	fprintf(stdout, "mapped buffer at 0x%p\n", buf);
	ret = madvise(buf, TEST_MEM_SIZE, MADV_HUGEPAGE);
        if (ret) {
		fprintf(stderr, "Unable to madvise(MADV_HUGEPAGE)\n");
		goto cleanup;
	}

	/* Populate VMA */
	ret = madvise(buf, TEST_MEM_SIZE, MADV_POPULATE_WRITE);
	if (ret) {
		fprintf(stderr, "Error %d to madvise(MADV_POPULATE_WRITE)\n", ret);
		goto cleanup;
	}

	/* Punch the file to enforce xarray split */
	ret = fallocate(fd, FALLOC_FL_KEEP_SIZE | FALLOC_FL_PUNCH_HOLE,
        		TEST_MEM_SIZE - pgsize, pgsize);
	if (ret)
		fprintf(stderr, "Error %d to fallocate()\n", ret);

cleanup:
	if (buf != (void *)-1)
		munmap(buf, TEST_MEM_SIZE);
	if (fd &gt; 0)
		close(fd);

	return 0;
}

# gcc test.c -o test
# cat /proc/1/smaps | grep KernelPageSize | head -n 1
KernelPageSize:       64 kB
# ./test shmem
   :
------------[ cut here ]------------
WARNING: CPU: 17 PID: 5253 at lib/xarray.c:1025 xas_split_alloc+0xf8/0x128
Modules linked in: nft_fib_inet nft_fib_ipv4 nft_fib_ipv6 nft_fib  \
nft_reject_inet nf_reject_ipv4 nf_reject_ipv6 nft_reject nft_ct    \
nft_chain_nat nf_nat nf_conntrack nf_defrag_ipv6 nf_defrag_ipv4    \
ip_set nf_tables rfkill nfnetlink vfat fat virtio_balloon          \
drm fuse xfs libcrc32c crct10dif_ce ghash_ce sha2_ce sha256_arm64  \
virtio_net sha1_ce net_failover failover virtio_console virtio_blk \
dimlib virtio_mmio
CPU: 17 PID: 5253 Comm: test Kdump: loaded Tainted: G W 6.10.0-rc5-gavin+ #12
Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS edk2-20240524-1.el9 05/24/2024
pstate: 83400005 (Nzcv daif +PAN -UAO +TC
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42244 | USB: serial: mos7840: fix crash on resume</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42244</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

USB: serial: mos7840: fix crash on resume

Since commit c49cfa917025 ("USB: serial: use generic method if no
alternative is provided in usb serial layer"), USB serial core calls the
generic resume implementation when the driver has not provided one.

This can trigger a crash on resume with mos7840 since support for
multiple read URBs was added back in 2011. Specifically, both port read
URBs are now submitted on resume for open ports, but the context pointer
of the second URB is left set to the core rather than mos7840 port
structure.

Fix this by implementing dedicated suspend and resume functions for
mos7840.

Tested with Delock 87414 USB 2.0 to 4x serial adapter.

[ johan: analyse crash and rewrite commit message; set busy flag on
         resume; drop bulk-in check; drop unnecessary usb_kill_urb() ]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42245 | Revert &amp;quot;sched/fair: Make sure to try to detach at least one movable task&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42245</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "sched/fair: Make sure to try to detach at least one movable task"

This reverts commit b0defa7ae03ecf91b8bfd10ede430cff12fcbd06.

b0defa7ae03ec changed the load balancing logic to ignore env.max_loop if
all tasks examined to that point were pinned. The goal of the patch was
to make it more likely to be able to detach a task buried in a long list
of pinned tasks. However, this has the unfortunate side effect of
creating an O(n) iteration in detach_tasks(), as we now must fully
iterate every task on a cpu if all or most are pinned. Since this load
balance code is done with rq lock held, and often in softirq context, it
is very easy to trigger hard lockups. We observed such hard lockups with
a user who affined O(10k) threads to a single cpu.

When I discussed this with Vincent he initially suggested that we keep
the limit on the number of tasks to detach, but increase the number of
tasks we can search. However, after some back and forth on the mailing
list, he recommended we instead revert the original patch, as it seems
likely no one was actually getting hit by the original issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42246 | net, sunrpc: Remap EPERM in case of connection failure in xs_tcp_setup_socket</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42246</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net, sunrpc: Remap EPERM in case of connection failure in xs_tcp_setup_socket

When using a BPF program on kernel_connect(), the call can return -EPERM. This
causes xs_tcp_setup_socket() to loop forever, filling up the syslog and causing
the kernel to potentially freeze up.

Neil suggested:

  This will propagate -EPERM up into other layers which might not be ready
  to handle it. It might be safer to map EPERM to an error we would be more
  likely to expect from the network system - such as ECONNREFUSED or ENETDOWN.

ECONNREFUSED as error seems reasonable. For programs setting a different error
can be out of reach (see handling in 4fbac77d2d09) in particular on kernels
which do not have f10d05966196 ("bpf: Make BPF_PROG_RUN_ARRAY return -err
instead of allow boolean"), thus given that it is better to simply remap for
consistent behavior. UDP does handle EPERM in xs_udp_send_request().</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42247 | wireguard: allowedips: avoid unaligned 64-bit memory accesses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42247</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wireguard: allowedips: avoid unaligned 64-bit memory accesses

On the parisc platform, the kernel issues kernel warnings because
swap_endian() tries to load a 128-bit IPv6 address from an unaligned
memory location:

 Kernel: unaligned access to 0x55f4688c in wg_allowedips_insert_v6+0x2c/0x80 [wireguard] (iir 0xf3010df)
 Kernel: unaligned access to 0x55f46884 in wg_allowedips_insert_v6+0x38/0x80 [wireguard] (iir 0xf2010dc)

Avoid such unaligned memory accesses by instead using the
get_unaligned_be64() helper macro.

[Jason: replace src[8] in original patch with src+8]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42248 | tty: serial: ma35d1: Add a NULL check for of_node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42248</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tty: serial: ma35d1: Add a NULL check for of_node

The pdev-&gt;dev.of_node can be NULL if the "serial" node is absent.
Add a NULL check to return an error in such cases.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42249 | spi: don&amp;#x27;t unoptimize message in spi_async()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42249</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: don't unoptimize message in spi_async()

Calling spi_maybe_unoptimize_message() in spi_async() is wrong because
the message is likely to be in the queue and not transferred yet. This
can corrupt the message while it is being used by the controller driver.

spi_maybe_unoptimize_message() is already called in the correct place
in spi_finalize_current_message() to balance the call to
spi_maybe_optimize_message() in spi_async().</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42250 | cachefiles: add missing lock protection when polling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42250</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cachefiles: add missing lock protection when polling

Add missing lock protection in poll routine when iterating xarray,
otherwise:

Even with RCU read lock held, only the slot of the radix tree is
ensured to be pinned there, while the data structure (e.g. struct
cachefiles_req) stored in the slot has no such guarantee.  The poll
routine will iterate the radix tree and dereference cachefiles_req
accordingly.  Thus RCU read lock is not adequate in this case and
spinlock is needed here.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7581 | Tenda A301 WifiBasicSet formWifiBasicSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7581</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda A301 15.13.08.12. This affects the function formWifiBasicSet of the file /goform/WifiBasicSet. The manipulation of the argument security leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7580 | Alien Technology ALR-F800 system.html os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Alien Technology ALR-F800 up to 19.10.24.00. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/system.html. The manipulation of the argument uploadedFile with the input ;whoami leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41989 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. The floatformat template filter is subject to significant memory c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41989</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. The floatformat template filter is subject to significant memory consumption when given a string representation of a number in scientific notation with a large exponent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41990 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. The urlize() and urlizetrunc() template filters are subject to a p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41990</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. The urlize() and urlizetrunc() template filters are subject to a potential denial-of-service attack via very large inputs with a specific sequence of characters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41991 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. The urlize and urlizetrunc template filters, and the AdminURLField...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41991</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. The urlize and urlizetrunc template filters, and the AdminURLFieldWidget widget, are subject to a potential denial-of-service attack via certain inputs with a very large number of Unicode characters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42005 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. QuerySet.values() and values_list() methods on models with a JSONF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42005</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.0 before 5.0.8 and 4.2 before 4.2.15. QuerySet.values() and values_list() methods on models with a JSONField are subject to SQL injection in column aliases via a crafted JSON object key as a passed *arg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43199 | Nagios NDOUtils before 2.1.4 allows privilege escalation from nagios to root because certain executable files are owned by the nagios user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43199</link><description>Nagios NDOUtils before 2.1.4 allows privilege escalation from nagios to root because certain executable files are owned by the nagios user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7579 | Alien Technology ALR-F800 File Name upgrade.cgi popen os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Alien Technology ALR-F800 up to 19.10.24.00. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function popen of the file /var/www/cgi-bin/upgrade.cgi of the component File Name Handler. The manipulation of the argument uploadedFile leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43044 | Jenkins 2.470 and earlier, LTS 2.452.3 and earlier allows agent processes to read arbitrary files from the Jenkins controller file system by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43044</link><description>Jenkins 2.470 and earlier, LTS 2.452.3 and earlier allows agent processes to read arbitrary files from the Jenkins controller file system by using the `ClassLoaderProxy#fetchJar` method in the Remoting library.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43045 | Jenkins 2.470 and earlier, LTS 2.452.3 and earlier does not perform a permission check in an HTTP endpoint, allowing attackers with Overall/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43045</link><description>Jenkins 2.470 and earlier, LTS 2.452.3 and earlier does not perform a permission check in an HTTP endpoint, allowing attackers with Overall/Read permission to access other users' "My Views".</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7578 | Alien Technology ALR-F800 cmd.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7578</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Alien Technology ALR-F800 up to 19.10.24.00. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /var/www/cmd.php. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7355 | Organization chart &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title_input and node_description Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7355</link><description>The Organization chart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title_input’ and 'node_description' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. By default, this can only be exploited by administrators, but the ability to use and configure charts can be extended to subscribers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7353 | Accept Stripe Payments &amp;lt;= 2.0.86 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via accept_stripe_payment_ng Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7353</link><description>The Accept Stripe Payments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's accept_stripe_payment_ng shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.86 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6522 | Modern Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 7.12.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6522</link><description>The Modern Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 7.12.1 via the 'mec_fes_form' AJAX function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7267 | Internal infrastructure data leak in EZD RP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7267</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Naukowa i Akademicka Sieć Komputerowa - Państwowy Instytut Badawczy EZD RP allows logged-in user to retrieve information about IP infrastructure and credentials. This issue affects EZD RP all versions before 19.6</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7265 | Privilege Escalation in EZD RP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7265</link><description>Incorrect User Management vulnerability in Naukowa i Akademicka Sieć Komputerowa - Państwowy Instytut Badawczy EZD RP allows logged-in user to change the password of any user, including root user, which could lead to privilege escalation. This issue affects EZD RP: from 15 before 15.84, from 16 before 16.15, from 17 before 17.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7266 | Users listing in EZD RP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7266</link><description>Incorrect User Management vulnerability in Naukowa i Akademicka Sieć Komputerowa - Państwowy Instytut Badawczy EZD RP allows logged-in user to list all users in the system, including those from other organizations. This issue affects EZD RP: from 15 before 15.84, from 16 before 16.15, from 17 before 17.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7553 | Accessing Untrusted Directory May Allow Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7553</link><description>Incorrect validation of files loaded from a local untrusted directory may allow local privilege escalation if the underlying operating systems is Windows. This may result in the application executing arbitrary behaviour determined by the contents of untrusted files. This issue affects MongoDB Server v5.0 versions prior to 5.0.27, MongoDB Server v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.16, MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.12, MongoDB Server v7.3 versions prior 7.3.3, MongoDB C Driver versions prior to 1.26.2 and MongoDB PHP Driver versions prior to 1.18.1.

Required Configuration:

Only environments with Windows as the underlying operating system is affected by this issue</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5290 | An issue was discovered in Ubuntu wpa_supplicant that resulted in loading of arbitrary shared objects, which allows a local unprivileged att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5290</link><description>An issue was discovered in Ubuntu wpa_supplicant that resulted in loading of arbitrary shared objects, which allows a local unprivileged attacker to escalate privileges to the user that wpa_supplicant runs as (usually root).




Membership in the netdev group or access to the dbus interface of wpa_supplicant allow an unprivileged user to specify an arbitrary path to a module to be loaded by the wpa_supplicant process; other escalation paths might exist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42062 | Apache CloudStack: User Key Exposure to Domain Admins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42062</link><description>CloudStack account-users by default use username and password based authentication for API and UI access. Account-users can generate and register randomised API and secret keys and use them for the purpose of API-based automation and integrations. Due to an access permission validation issue that affects Apache CloudStack versions 4.10.0 up to 4.19.1.0, domain admin accounts were found to be able to query all registered account-users API and secret keys in an environment, including that of a root admin. An attacker who has domain admin access can exploit this to gain root admin and other-account privileges and perform malicious operations that can result in compromise of resources integrity and confidentiality, data loss, denial of service and availability of CloudStack managed infrastructure.

Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache CloudStack 4.18.2.3 or 4.19.1.1, or later, which addresses this issue. Additionally, all account-user API and secret keys should be regenerated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42222 | Apache CloudStack: Unauthorised Network List Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42222</link><description>In Apache CloudStack 4.19.1.0, a regression in the network listing API allows unauthorised list access of network details for domain admin and normal user accounts. This vulnerability compromises tenant isolation, potentially leading to unauthorised access to network details, configurations and data.

Affected users are advised to upgrade to version 4.19.1.1 to address this issue. Users on older versions of CloudStack considering to upgrade, can skip 4.19.1.0 and upgrade directly to 4.19.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3973 | House Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3973</link><description>The House Manager  WordPress plugin through 1.0.8.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 06:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6494 | WordPress File Upload &amp;lt; 4.24.8 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6494</link><description>The WordPress File Upload WordPress plugin before 4.24.8 does not properly sanitize and escape certain parameters, which could allow unauthenticated users to execute stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 06:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34788 | An improper authentication vulnerability in web component of EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows a remote malicious user to access potentially sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34788</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability in web component of EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows a remote malicious user to access potentially sensitive information</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36130 | An insufficient authorization vulnerability in web component of EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows an unauthorized attacker within the network to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36130</link><description>An insufficient authorization vulnerability in web component of EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows an unauthorized attacker within the network to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the appliance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36131 | An insecure deserialization vulnerability in web component of EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36131</link><description>An insecure deserialization vulnerability in web component of EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the appliance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36132 | Insufficient verification of authentication controls in EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to bypass authentication and access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36132</link><description>Insufficient verification of authentication controls in EPMM prior to 12.1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to bypass authentication and access sensitive resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37403 | Ivanti Docs@Work for Android, before 2.26.0 is affected by the 'Dirty Stream' vulnerability. The application fails to properly sanitize file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37403</link><description>Ivanti Docs@Work for Android, before 2.26.0 is affected by the 'Dirty Stream' vulnerability. The application fails to properly sanitize file names, resulting in a path traversal-affiliated vulnerability. This potentially enables other malicious apps on the device to read sensitive information stored in the app root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34613 | Improper access control in Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information of Galaxy wat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34613</link><description>Improper access control in Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information of Galaxy watch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34614 | Out-of-bound write in libsmat.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34614</link><description>Out-of-bound write in libsmat.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34615 | Out-of-bound write in libsmat.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34615</link><description>Out-of-bound write in libsmat.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34616 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in KnoxDualDARPolicy prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34616</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in KnoxDualDARPolicy prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34617 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in Telephony prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure default Messag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34617</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in Telephony prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to configure default Message application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34618 | Improper access control in System property prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access cell related information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34618</link><description>Improper access control in System property prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access cell related information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34619 | Improper input validation in librtp.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34619</link><description>Improper input validation in librtp.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34620 | Improper privilege management in SumeNNService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34620</link><description>Improper privilege management in SumeNNService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to start privileged service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34621 | Out-of-bounds read in applying binary with data in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34621</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying binary with data in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34622 | Out-of-bounds write in appending paragraph in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34622</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in appending paragraph in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with Samsung Notes privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34623 | Out-of-bounds write in applying connected information in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34623</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in applying connected information in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code with Samsung Notes privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34624 | Out-of-bounds read in applying paragraphs in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34624</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying paragraphs in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34625 | Out-of-bounds read in applying connection point in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34625</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying connection point in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34626 | Out-of-bounds read in applying own binary in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34626</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying own binary in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34627 | Out-of-bounds read in parsing implemention in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34627</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in parsing implemention in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34628 | Out-of-bounds read in applying binary with path in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34628</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying binary with path in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34629 | Out-of-bounds read in applying binary with text common object in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34629</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying binary with text common object in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34630 | Out-of-bounds read in applying own binary with textbox in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially rea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34630</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying own binary with textbox in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34631 | Out-of-bounds read in applying new binary in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34631</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in applying new binary in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attackers to potentially read memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34632 | Out-of-bounds read in uuid parsing in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34632</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in uuid parsing in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34633 | Out-of-bounds read in parsing object header in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34633</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in parsing object header in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34634 | Out-of-bounds read in parsing connected object list in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34634</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in parsing connected object list in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34635 | Out-of-bounds read in parsing textbox object in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34635</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in parsing textbox object in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.21.62 allows local attacker to access unauthorized memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34636 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.94.2 allows local attackers to get sensitive inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34636</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.94.2 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34604 | Improper access control in LedCoverService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34604</link><description>Improper access control in LedCoverService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34605 | Improper access control in SamsungHealthService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34605</link><description>Improper access control in SamsungHealthService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34606 | Improper access control in SmartThingsService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34606</link><description>Improper access control in SmartThingsService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34607 | Improper access control in SamsungNotesService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34607</link><description>Improper access control in SamsungNotesService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34608 | Improper access control in PaymentManagerService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34608</link><description>Improper access control in PaymentManagerService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34609 | Improper access control in VoiceNoteService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34609</link><description>Improper access control in VoiceNoteService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to bypass restrictions on starting services from the background.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34610 | Improper access control in ExtControlDeviceService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34610</link><description>Improper access control in ExtControlDeviceService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access protected data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34611 | Improper access control in KnoxService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34611</link><description>Improper access control in KnoxService prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34612 | Out-of-bound write in libcodec2secmp4vdec.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34612</link><description>Out-of-bound write in libcodec2secmp4vdec.so prior to SMR Aug-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38166 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38166</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38206 | Microsoft Copilot Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38206</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41270 | An issue discovered in the RunHTTPServer function in Gorush v1.18.4 allows attackers to intercept and manipulate data due to use of deprecat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41270</link><description>An issue discovered in the RunHTTPServer function in Gorush v1.18.4 allows attackers to intercept and manipulate data due to use of deprecated TLS version.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42219 | 1Password 8 before 8.10.36 for macOS allows local attackers to exfiltrate vault items because XPC inter-process communication validation is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42219</link><description>1Password 8 before 8.10.36 for macOS allows local attackers to exfiltrate vault items because XPC inter-process communication validation is insufficient.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42218 | 1Password 8 before 8.10.36 for macOS allows local attackers to exfiltrate vault items by bypassing macOS-specific security mechanisms.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42218</link><description>1Password 8 before 8.10.36 for macOS allows local attackers to exfiltrate vault items by bypassing macOS-specific security mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7532 | Out of bounds memory access in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruptio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7532</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7533 | Use after free in Sharing in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7533</link><description>Use after free in Sharing in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7534 | Heap buffer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7534</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7535 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7535</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7536 | Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7536</link><description>Use after free in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7550 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7550</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.99 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42400 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerabilities in the Soft AP Daemon Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42400</link><description>Multiple unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the Soft AP daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected Access Point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42399 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerabilities in the Soft AP Daemon Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42399</link><description>Multiple unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the Soft AP daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected Access Point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42398 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerabilities in the Soft AP Daemon Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42398</link><description>Multiple unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the Soft AP daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected Access Point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42393 | Unauthenticated Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Command Execution (RCE) in the Soft AP Daemon Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42393</link><description>There are vulnerabilities in the Soft AP Daemon Service which could allow a threat actor to execute an unauthenticated RCE attack. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42394 | Unauthenticated Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Command Execution (RCE) in the Soft AP Daemon Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42394</link><description>There are vulnerabilities in the Soft AP Daemon Service which could allow a threat actor to execute an unauthenticated RCE attack. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:07:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42395 | Unauthenticated Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Command Execution (RCE) in the AP Certificate Management Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42395</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the AP Certificate Management Service which could allow a threat actor to execute an unauthenticated RCE attack. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system leading to complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:07:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42396 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerabilities in the AP Certificate Management Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42396</link><description>Multiple unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the AP Certificate Management daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected Access Point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:07:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28740 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Koha ILS 23.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the additonal-content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28740</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Koha ILS 23.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the additonal-contents.pl component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42397 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerabilities in the AP Certificate Management Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42397</link><description>Multiple unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the AP Certificate Management daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected Access Point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28739 | An issue in Koha ILS 23.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the format parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28739</link><description>An issue in Koha ILS 23.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the format parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41677 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to improper HTML escaping in qwik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41677</link><description>Qwik is a performance focused javascript framework. A potential mutation XSS vulnerability exists in Qwik for versions up to but not including 1.6.0. Qwik improperly escapes HTML on server-side rendering. It converts strings according to the rules found in the `render-ssr.ts` file. It sometimes causes the situation that the final DOM tree rendered on browsers is different from what Qwik expects on server-side rendering. This may be leveraged to perform XSS attacks, and a type of the XSS is known as mXSS (mutation XSS). This has been resolved in qwik version 1.6.0 and @builder.io/qwik version 1.7.3. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42347 | URL preview setting for a room is controllable by the homeserver in matrix-react-sdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42347</link><description>matrix-react-sdk  is a react-based SDK for inserting a Matrix chat/voip client into a web page. A malicious homeserver could manipulate a user's account data to cause the client to enable URL previews in end-to-end encrypted rooms, in which case any URLs in encrypted messages would be sent to the server. This was patched in matrix-react-sdk 3.105.0. Deployments that trust their homeservers, as well as closed federations of trusted servers, are not affected. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39227 | GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39227</link><description>GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16, XE300 v4.3.16, E750 v4.3.12, AP1300/S1300 v4.3.13, and XE3000/X3000 v4.4 were discovered to contain a shell injection vulnerability via the interface check_ovpn_client_config.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42358 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (&amp;#x27;Infinite Loop&amp;#x27;) in pdfio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42358</link><description>PDFio is a simple C library for reading and writing PDF files. There is a denial of service (DOS) vulnerability in the TTF parser. Maliciously crafted TTF files can cause the program to utilize 100% of the Memory and enter an infinite loop. This can also lead to a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability. An infinite loop occurs in the read_camp function by nGroups value. The ttf.h library is vulnerable. A value called nGroups is extracted from the file, and by changing that value, you can cause the program to utilize 100% of the Memory and enter an infinite loop. If the value of nGroups in the file is small, an infinite loop will not occur. This library, whether used as a standalone binary or as part of another application, is vulnerable to DOS attacks when parsing certain types of files. Automated systems, including web servers that use this code to convert PDF submissions into plaintext, can be DOSed if an attacker uploads a malicious TTF file. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.3.1. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39229 | An issue in GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39229</link><description>An issue in GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16, XE300 v4.3.16, E750 v4.3.12, AP1300/S1300 v4.3.13, XE3000/X3000 v4, and B2200/MV1000/MV1000W/USB150/N300/SF1200 v3.216 allows attackers to intercept communications via a man-in-the-middle attack when DDNS clients are reporting data to the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7502 | Delta Electronics DIAScreen Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7502</link><description>A crafted DPA file could force Delta Electronics DIAScreen to overflow a stack-based buffer, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43111 | Long pressing on a download link could potentially allow Javascript commands to be executed within the browser This vulnerability affects Fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43111</link><description>Long pressing on a download link could potentially allow Javascript commands to be executed within the browser This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43112 | Long pressing on a download link could potentially provide a means for cross-site scripting This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 129...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43112</link><description>Long pressing on a download link could potentially provide a means for cross-site scripting This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43113 | The contextual menu for links could provide an opportunity for cross-site scripting attacks This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 129...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43113</link><description>The contextual menu for links could provide an opportunity for cross-site scripting attacks This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7564 | Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7564</link><description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the get_response_json_result endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24680.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39225 | GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39225</link><description>GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16, XE300 v4.3.16, E750 v4.3.12, AP1300/S1300 v4.3.13, and XE3000/X3000 v4.4 were discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28806 | Signature validation error in DLL allows disabling anti-tampering protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28806</link><description>An Improper Validation of signature in Zscaler Client Connector on Windows allows an authenticated user to disable anti-tampering. This issue affects Client Connector on Windows &lt;4.2.0.190.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6988 | Use after free in Downloads in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6988</link><description>Use after free in Downloads in Google Chrome on iOS prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6989 | Use after free in Loader in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6989</link><description>Use after free in Loader in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6991 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6991</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6994 | Heap buffer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6994</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6995 | Inappropriate implementation in Fullscreen in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6995</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Fullscreen in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6996 | Race in Frames in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6996</link><description>Race in Frames in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6997 | Use after free in Tabs in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6997</link><description>Use after free in Tabs in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6998 | Use after free in User Education in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6998</link><description>Use after free in User Education in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6999 | Inappropriate implementation in FedCM in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6999</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in FedCM in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7000 | Use after free in CSS in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7000</link><description>Use after free in CSS in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7001 | Inappropriate implementation in HTML in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7001</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in HTML in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7003 | Inappropriate implementation in FedCM in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7003</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in FedCM in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7004 | Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Safe Browsing in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7004</link><description>Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Safe Browsing in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to bypass discretionary access control via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7005 | Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Safe Browsing in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7005</link><description>Insufficient validation of untrusted input in Safe Browsing in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.72 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to bypass discretionary access control via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23483 | Local Privilege Escalation via lack of input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23483</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Zscaler Client Connector on MacOS allows OS Command Injection. This issue affects Zscaler Client Connector on MacOS &lt;4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39226 | GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39226</link><description>GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16, XE300 v4.3.16, E750 v4.3.12, AP1300/S1300 v4.3.13, and XE3000/X3000 v4.4 were discovered to contain insecure permissions in the endpoint /cgi-bin/glc. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or possibly a directory traversal via crafted JSON data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23460 | Incorrect signature validation of package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23460</link><description>The Zscaler Updater process does not validate the digital signature of the installer before execution, allowing arbitrary code to be locally executed. This affects Zscaler Client Connector on MacOS &lt;4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23458 | Local Privilege Escalation on Zscaler Client Connector on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23458</link><description>While copying individual autoupdater log files, reparse point check was missing which could result into crafted attacks, potentially leading to a local privilege escalation. This issue affects Zscaler Client Connector on Windows &lt;4.2.0.190.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23464 | Zscaler bypass with administrative privileges on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23464</link><description>In certain cases, Zscaler Internet Access (ZIA) can be disabled by PowerShell commands with admin rights. This affects Zscaler Client Connector on Windows &lt;4.2.1</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6720 | Light Poll &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Poll Answers Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6720</link><description>The Light Poll WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23456 | Signature validation issue leads to Anti-Tampering bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23456</link><description>Anti-tampering can be disabled under certain conditions without signature validation. This affects Zscaler Client Connector &lt;4.2.0.190 with anti-tampering enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39228 | GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39228</link><description>GL-iNet products AR750/AR750S/AR300M/AR300M16/MT300N-V2/B1300/MT1300/SFT1200/X750 v4.3.11, MT3000/MT2500/AXT1800/AX1800/A1300/X300B v4.5.16, XE300 v4.3.16, E750 v4.3.12, AP1300/S1300 v4.3.13, XE3000/X3000 v4, and B2200/MV1000/MV1000W/USB150/N300/SF1200 v3.216 were discovered to contain a shell injection vulnerability via the interface check_config.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39751 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39751</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  297429</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41616 | D-Link DIR-300 REVA FIRMWARE v1.06B05_WW contains hardcoded credentials in the Telnet service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41616</link><description>D-Link DIR-300 REVA FIRMWARE v1.06B05_WW contains hardcoded credentials in the Telnet service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41333 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Phpgurukul Tourism Management System v2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41333</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Phpgurukul Tourism Management System v2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the uname parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36424 | K7RKScan.sys in K7 Ultimate Security before 17.0.2019 allows local users to cause a denial of service (BSOD) because of a NULL pointer deref...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36424</link><description>K7RKScan.sys in K7 Ultimate Security before 17.0.2019 allows local users to cause a denial of service (BSOD) because of a NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7552 | DataGear Data Schema Page ConversionSqlParamValueMapper.java evaluateVariableExpression expression language injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7552</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DataGear up to 5.0.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function evaluateVariableExpression of the file ConversionSqlParamValueMapper.java of the component Data Schema Page. The manipulation leads to improper neutralization of special elements used in an expression language statement. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273697 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41910 | A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices.  The firmware contained multiple XXS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41910</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices.  The firmware contained multiple XXS vulnerabilities in the version of JavaScript used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41911 | A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices. The flaw does not properly neutralize...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41911</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices. The flaw does not properly neutralize input during a web page generation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40819 | ID4Portais in version &lt; V.2022.837.002a returns message parameter unsanitized in the response, resulting in a HTML Injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40819</link><description>ID4Portais in version &lt; V.2022.837.002a returns message parameter unsanitized in the response, resulting in a HTML Injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41913 | Clariti Manager – Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41913</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the firmware builds up to 10.10.2.2 in Poly Clariti Manager devices.  The firmware flaw does not properly sanitize User input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30170 | PrivX before 34.0 allows data exfiltration and denial of service via the REST API. This is fixed in minor versions 33.1, 32.3, 31.3, and lat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30170</link><description>PrivX before 34.0 allows data exfiltration and denial of service via the REST API. This is fixed in minor versions 33.1, 32.3, 31.3, and later, and in major version 34.0 and later,</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41226 | A CSV injection vulnerability in Automation Anywhere Automation 360 version 21094 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41226</link><description>A CSV injection vulnerability in Automation Anywhere Automation 360 version 21094 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33897 | A compromised HMS Networks Cosy+ device could be used to request a Certificate Signing Request from Talk2m for another device, resulting in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33897</link><description>A compromised HMS Networks Cosy+ device could be used to request a Certificate Signing Request from Talk2m for another device, resulting in an availability issue. The issue was patched on the Talk2m production server on April 18, 2024.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40101 | A Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in '/search' in microweber 2.0.15 and earlier allowing unauthenticated remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40101</link><description>A Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in '/search' in microweber 2.0.15 and earlier allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the 'keywords' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33989 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe School Event Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33989</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted javascript payload to an authenticated user and partially take over their browser session via the 'eventdate' and 'events' parameters in 'port/event_print.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33990 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe School Event Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33990</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted javascript payload to an authenticated user and partially take over their browser session via the 'id' and 'view' parameters in '/user/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33991 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe School Event Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33991</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the 'view' parameter in '/eventwinner/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33992 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe School Event Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33992</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the 'view' parameter in '/student/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33993 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe School Event Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33993</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain their session details via the 'view' parameter in /candidate/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33994 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe School Event Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33994</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain their session details via the 'view' parameter in '/event/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6357 | Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6357</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference vulnerability identified in OpenText ArcSight Intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6358 | Incorrect Authorization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6358</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability identified in OpenText ArcSight Intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6359 | Privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6359</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability identified in OpenText ArcSight Intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33982 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33982</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the 'StudentID' parameter in '/AttendanceMonitoring/student/controller.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33983 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33983</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the  'Attendance', 'attenddate' and 'YearLevel' parameters in '/AttendanceMonitoring/report/attendance_print.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33984 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33984</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the  'Attendance', 'attenddate' and 'YearLevel' parameters in '/AttendanceMonitoring/report/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33985 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33985</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the  'View' parameter in '/course/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33986 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33986</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the  'View' parameter in '/department/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33987 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33987</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the  'Attendance', 'attenddate', 'YearLevel', 'eventdate', 'events', 'Users' and 'YearLevel' parameters in '/report/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33988 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33988</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in School Attendance Monitoring System and School Event Management System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the  'Attendance', 'attenddate' and 'YearLevel' parameters in '/report/attendance_print.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43114 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 possible privilege escalation due to incorrect directory permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43114</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.1 possible privilege escalation due to incorrect directory permissions</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7518 | Select options could obscure the fullscreen notification dialog. This could be used by a malicious site to perform a spoofing attack. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7518</link><description>Select options could obscure the fullscreen notification dialog. This could be used by a malicious site to perform a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7519 | Insufficient checks when processing graphics shared memory could have led to memory corruption. This could be leveraged by an attacker to pe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7519</link><description>Insufficient checks when processing graphics shared memory could have led to memory corruption. This could be leveraged by an attacker to perform a sandbox escape. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7520 | A type confusion bug in WebAssembly could be leveraged by an attacker to potentially achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Fire...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7520</link><description>A type confusion bug in WebAssembly could be leveraged by an attacker to potentially achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7521 | Incomplete WebAssembly exception handing could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7521</link><description>Incomplete WebAssembly exception handing could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7522 | Editor code failed to check an attribute value. This could have led to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Fire...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7522</link><description>Editor code failed to check an attribute value. This could have led to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7523 | A select option could partially obscure security prompts. This could be used by a malicious site to trick a user into granting permissions. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7523</link><description>A select option could partially obscure security prompts. This could be used by a malicious site to trick a user into granting permissions. 
*This issue only affects Android versions of Firefox.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7524 | Firefox adds web-compatibility shims in place of some tracking scripts blocked by Enhanced Tracking Protection.  On a site protected by Cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7524</link><description>Firefox adds web-compatibility shims in place of some tracking scripts blocked by Enhanced Tracking Protection.  On a site protected by Content Security Policy in "strict-dynamic" mode, an attacker able to inject an HTML element could have used a DOM Clobbering attack on some of the shims and achieved XSS, bypassing the CSP strict-dynamic protection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7525 | It was possible for a web extension with minimal permissions to create a `StreamFilter` which could be used to read and modify the response ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7525</link><description>It was possible for a web extension with minimal permissions to create a `StreamFilter` which could be used to read and modify the response body of requests on any site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7526 | ANGLE failed to initialize parameters which lead to reading from uninitialized memory. This could be leveraged to leak sensitive data from m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7526</link><description>ANGLE failed to initialize parameters which lead to reading from uninitialized memory. This could be leveraged to leak sensitive data from memory. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7527 | Unexpected marking work at the start of sweeping could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt;...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7527</link><description>Unexpected marking work at the start of sweeping could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7528 | Incorrect garbage collection interaction in IndexedDB could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129 and Firef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7528</link><description>Incorrect garbage collection interaction in IndexedDB could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7529 | The date picker could partially obscure security prompts. This could be used by a malicious site to trick a user into granting permissions. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7529</link><description>The date picker could partially obscure security prompts. This could be used by a malicious site to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7530 | Incorrect garbage collection interaction could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7530</link><description>Incorrect garbage collection interaction could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7531 | Calling `PK11_Encrypt()` in NSS using CKM_CHACHA20 and the same buffer for input and output can result in plaintext on an Intel Sandy Bridge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7531</link><description>Calling `PK11_Encrypt()` in NSS using CKM_CHACHA20 and the same buffer for input and output can result in plaintext on an Intel Sandy Bridge processor. In Firefox this only affects the QUIC header protection feature when the connection is using the ChaCha20-Poly1305 cipher suite. The most likely outcome is connection failure, but if the connection persists despite the high packet loss it could be possible for a network observer to identify packets as coming from the same source despite a network path change. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 129, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7551 | juzaweb CMS Theme Editor default path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7551</link><description>A vulnerability was found in juzaweb CMS up to 3.4.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-cp/theme/editor/default of the component Theme Editor. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273696. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33974 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33974</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following 'Users in '/report/printlogs.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33969 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33969</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'id' in '/AttendanceMonitoring/department/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33970 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33970</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'studid' in '/candidate/controller.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33971 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33971</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following   'username' in '/login.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33972 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33972</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following    'events' in '/report/event_print.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33973 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33973</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following    'Attendance' and 'YearLevel' in '/report/attendance_print.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33967 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33967</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'view' in 'Attendance' and 'YearLevel' in '/AttendanceMonitoring/report/attendance_print.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33968 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33968</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'Attendance' and 'YearLevel' in '/AttendanceMonitoring/report/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33960 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33960</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following 'end' in '/admin/mod_reports/printreport.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33961 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33961</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following 'code' in '/admin/mod_reservation/controller.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33962 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33962</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following 'code' in '/admin/mod_reservation/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33963 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33963</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following 'id' in '/admin/mod_room/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33964 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33964</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'id' in '/admin/mod_users/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33965 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33965</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'view' in '/tubigangarden/admin/mod_accomodation/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33966 | SQL injection in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33966</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following  'xtsearch' in '/admin/mod_reports/index.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33959 | SQL injection in Janobe PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33959</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in it through the following 'categ' in '/admin/mod_reports/printreport.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33980 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33980</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the 'start' parameter in '/admin/mod_reports/printreport.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33981 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33981</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the 'start' parameter in '/admin/mod_reports/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33957 | SQL injection in Janobe E-Negosyo System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33957</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in E-Negosyo System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in 'id' in '/admin/orders/controller.php' parameter</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33958 | SQL injection in Janobe E-Negosyo System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33958</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in E-Negosyo System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in 'phonenumber' in '/passwordrecover.php' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33978 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe E-Negosyo System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33978</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in E-Negosyo System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain their session cookie details via 'category' parameter in '/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33979 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33979</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PayPal, Credit Card and Debit Card Payment affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain details of their session cookie via the 'q', 'arrival', 'departure' and 'accomodation' parameters in '/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7317 | Folders – Unlimited Folders to Organize Media Library Folder, Pages, Posts, File Manager &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7317</link><description>The Folders – Unlimited Folders to Organize Media Library Folder, Pages, Posts, File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33977 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe E-Negosyo System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33977</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in E-Negosyo System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could create a specially crafted URL and send it to a victim to obtain their session cookie details via 'view' parameter in /admin/orders/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33975 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe E-Negosyo System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33975</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in E-Negosyo System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted JavaScript payload to an authenticated user and partially take over their browser session via 'view' parameter in '/admin/products/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33976 | Cross-site Scripting in Janobe E-Negosyo System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33976</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in E-Negosyo System affecting version 1.0. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted JavaScript payload to an authenticated user and partially take over their browser session via 'id' parameter in '/admin/user/index.php'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7246 | HPACK table poisoning in gRPC C++, Python &amp;amp; Ruby</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7246</link><description>It's possible for a gRPC client communicating with a HTTP/2 proxy to poison the HPACK table between the proxy and the backend such that other clients see failed requests. It's also possible to use this vulnerability to leak other clients HTTP header keys, but not values.

This occurs because the error status for a misencoded header is not cleared between header reads, resulting in subsequent (incrementally indexed) added headers in the first request being poisoned until cleared from the HPACK table.

Please update to a fixed version of gRPC as soon as possible. This bug has been fixed in 1.58.3, 1.59.5, 1.60.2, 1.61.3, 1.62.3, 1.63.2, 1.64.3, 1.65.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:21:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41995 | Initialization of a resource with an insecure default vulnerability exists in JavaTM Platform Ver.12.89 and earlier. If this vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41995</link><description>Initialization of a resource with an insecure default vulnerability exists in JavaTM Platform Ver.12.89 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, the product may be affected by some known TLS1.0 and TLS1.1 vulnerabilities. As for the specific products/models/versions of MFPs and printers that contain JavaTM Platform, see the information provided by the vendor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6201 | HaloITSM - Emailing Template Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6201</link><description>HaloITSM versions up to 2.146.1 are affected by a Template Injection vulnerability within the engine used to generate emails. This can lead to the leakage of potentially sensitive information. HaloITSM versions past 2.146.1 (and patches starting from 2.143.61 ) fix the mentioned vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6202 | HaloITSM - SAML XML Signature Wrapping (XSW)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6202</link><description>HaloITSM versions up to 2.146.1 are affected by a SAML XML Signature Wrapping (XSW) vulnerability. When having a SAML integration configured, anonymous actors could impersonate arbitrary HaloITSM users by just knowing their email address. HaloITSM versions past 2.146.1 (and patches starting from 2.143.61 ) fix the mentioned vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6203 | HaloITSM - Password Reset Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6203</link><description>HaloITSM versions up to 2.146.1 are affected by a Password Reset Poisoning vulnerability. Poisoned password reset links can be sent to existing HaloITSM users (given their email address is known). When these poisoned links get accessed (e.g. manually by the victim or automatically by an email client software), the password reset token is leaked to the malicious actor, allowing them to set a new password for the victim's account.This potentially leads to account takeover attacks.HaloITSM versions past 2.146.1 (and patches starting from 2.143.61 ) fix the mentioned vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6651 | WordPress File Upload &amp;lt; 4.24.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6651</link><description>The WordPress File Upload WordPress plugin before 4.24.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6766 | Shortcodes Ultimate Pro &amp;lt; 7.2.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6766</link><description>The shortcodes-ultimate-pro WordPress plugin before 7.2.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7055 | FFmpeg pnmdec.c pnm_decode_frame heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7055</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg up to 7.0.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function pnm_decode_frame in the library /libavcodec/pnmdec.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 7.0.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273651.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7082 | easy-table-of-contents &amp;lt; 2.0.68 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7082</link><description>The Easy Table of Contents WordPress plugin before 2.0.68 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Editor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7084 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt; 4.12.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7084</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite WordPress plugin before 4.12.1 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Admin+ to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6200 | HaloITSM - Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Tickets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6200</link><description>HaloITSM versions up to 2.146.1 are affected by a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The injected JavaScript code can execute arbitrary action on behalf of the user accessing a ticket. HaloITSM versions past 2.146.1 (and patches starting from 2.143.61 ) fix the mentioned vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5708 | WPBakery &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5708</link><description>The WPBakery Visual Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, and with post permissions granted by an Administrator, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5709 | WPBakery &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5709</link><description>The WPBakery Visual Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 7.7 via the 'layout_name' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, and with post permissions granted by an Administrator, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39817 | Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Office 10.0.0 to 10.8.6, which may allow a user who can login to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39817</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into sent data issue exists in Cybozu Office 10.0.0 to 10.8.6, which may allow a user who can login to the product to view data that the user does not have access by conducting 'search' under certain conditions in Custom App.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7506 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System setlogo.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7506</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /setlogo.php. The manipulation of the argument bgimg leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273649 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28962 | Dell Command | Update, Dell Update, and Alienware Update UWP, versions prior to 5.4, contain an Exposed Dangerous Method or Function vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28962</link><description>Dell Command | Update, Dell Update, and Alienware Update UWP, versions prior to 5.4, contain an Exposed Dangerous Method or Function vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7505 | itsourcecode Bike Delivery System contact_us_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7505</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Bike Delivery System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file contact_us_action.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273648.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7009 | Calibre SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7009</link><description>Unsanitized user-input in Calibre &lt;= 7.15.0 allow users with permissions to perform full-text searches to achieve SQL injection on the SQLite database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6781 | Calibre Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6781</link><description>Path traversal in Calibre &lt;= 7.14.0 allow unauthenticated attackers to achieve arbitrary file read.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6782 | Calibre Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6782</link><description>Improper access control in Calibre 6.9.0 ~ 7.14.0 allow unauthenticated attackers to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7008 | Calibre Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7008</link><description>Unsanitized user-input in Calibre &lt;= 7.15.0 allow attackers to perform reflected cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7500 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System admin_class.php save_settings unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7500</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function save_settings of the file admin/admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273626 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6886 | Inproper Sanitation of field leading to stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6886</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gitea Gitea Open Source Git Server allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gitea Open Source Git Server: 1.22.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7499 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System flights.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7499</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file flights.php. The manipulation of the argument departure_airport_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273625 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7498 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System Admin Login Page login.php login2 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7498</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function login/login2 of the file /admin/login.php of the component Admin Login Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273624.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5828 | EL Injection Vulnerability in Hitachi Tuning Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5828</link><description>Expression Language Injection vulnerability in Hitachi Tuning Manager on Windows, Linux, Solaris allows Code Injection.This issue affects Hitachi Tuning Manager: before 8.8.7-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5963 | An unquoted executable path exists in Hitachi Device Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5963</link><description>Unquoted Executable Path vulnerability in Hitachi Device Manager on Windows (Device Manager Server component).This issue affects Hitachi Device Manager: before 8.8.7-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7497 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7497</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273623.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5000 | Horizontal scrolling announcements &amp;lt;= 2.4 -  Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5000</link><description>The Horizontal scrolling announcements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's 'hsas-shortcode' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6315 | Blox Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.65 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6315</link><description>The Blox Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'handleUploadFile' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.65. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7484 | CRM Perks Forms &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7484</link><description>The CRM Perks Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'handle_uploaded_files' function in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7485 | Traffic Manager &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7485</link><description>The Traffic Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in the 'UserWebStat' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7496 | itsourcecode Airline Reservation System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7496</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Airline Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273622 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7495 | itsourcecode Laravel Accounting System HomeController.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7495</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Laravel Accounting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file app/Http/Controllers/HomeController.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273621 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 01:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>